<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-06-15T22:15:10.582Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-06-15T22:15:10.582Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IMF Data Shows Decline in US Dollar Dominance]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7415e0e954</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/imf-data-shows-decline-in-us-dollar-dominance/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T22:10:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recent data from the International Monetary Fund (IMF) points to an ongoing decline in the U.S. dollar’s share of allocated foreign reserves held by central banks and governments. Economists explained that reserve managers are attracted to nontraditional reserve currencies “because they provide diversification and relatively attractive yields, and because they have become increasingly easy to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Market Experts Say Dogecoin ETF Is Coming As Meme Coins Gain Ground]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7415e1b0a1</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-market-experts-say-dogecoin-etf-is-coming-as-meme-coins-gain-ground/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T22:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two prominent crypto market experts have shed light on the future of meme coins in this market cycle, predicting the potential launch of a Dogecoin Exchange-Traded Fund (ETF) soon. 
 
Crypto Heavyweights Affirm Dogecoin ETF Is Coming
 
Co-founder of BitMEX, Arthur Hayes and Chief Executive Officer (CEO) and co-founder of Real Vision, Raoul Pal have appeared in a recent YouTube podcast on Coin Bureau, sharing insights on the potential for a Dogecoin ETF as meme coins continue to gain traction in the market. 
 
 
When questioned about what meme coins he was keeping an eye on in his portfolio, Hayes asserted that Dogecoin could potentially get an ETF by the end of the cycle. He based his predictions on the substantial growth rate of the doggy-themed meme coin over the years, highlighting Doge…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Market Experts Say Dogecoin ETF Is Coming As Meme Coins Gain Ground]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19591548/Crypto-Market-Experts-Say-Dogecoin-ETF-Is-Coming-As-Meme-Coins-Gain-Ground</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19591548/Crypto-Market-Experts-Say-Dogecoin-ETF-Is-Coming-As-Meme-Coins-Gain-Ground"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T22:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two prominent crypto market experts have shed light on the future of meme coins in this market cycle, predicting the potential launch of a Dogecoin Exchange-Traded Fund (ETF) soon. Crypto Heavyweights Affirm Dogecoin ETF Is Coming Co-founder of BitMEX, Arthur Hayes and Chief Executive Officer...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$526,714,000,000 Bank Reveals Data Breach As Hacker Claims Personal Information of 65,000 Account Holders For Sale: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19591535/526714000000-Bank-Reveals-Data-Breach-As-Hacker-Claims-Personal-Information-of-65000-Account-Holders-For-Sale-Report</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19591535/526714000000-Bank-Reveals-Data-Breach-As-Hacker-Claims-Personal-Information-of-65000-Account-Holders-For-Sale-Report"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T21:46:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the largest banks in the US says it has suffered a security breach as a notorious hacker claims sensitive data on thousands of account holders is now for sale. North Carolina-based lender Truist Bank just confirmed its systems were breached in October, reports tech news site Bleeping...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Bitcoin Reserves down by 15% since February – All the details]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19591492/Coinbase-Bitcoin-Reserves-down-by-15-since-February-All-the-details</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19591492/Coinbase-Bitcoin-Reserves-down-by-15-since-February-All-the-details"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T21:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Due to the surge in demand for spot BTC ETFs, the coins held on Coinbase have declined since February.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When my altcoin goes from $200 to $208 overnight  #shorts]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19591496/When-my-altcoin-goes-from-200-to-208-overnight-shorts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19591496/When-my-altcoin-goes-from-200-to-208-overnight-shorts"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T21:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When my altcoin goes from $200 to $208 overnightIntroducing the ALTCOINBUZZ ALPHA x DECUBATE Special Offer! Decubate Bronze+ Tier Members can now claim a full refund on your 1st month of Altcoin Buzz Alpha Membership!Eligibility✅ Submit your Bronze+ Member email ID to #Alpha channel in Discord...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LEAKED: Biden Admin to Attend Bitcoin Roundtable With Key Congressional Officials in DC]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7415ee95f8</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/markets/leaked-biden-admin-to-attend-bitcoin-roundtable-with-key-congressional-officials-in-dc"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T20:58:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Congressman Ro Khanna, representing California's 17th congressional district, is set to host a Bitcoin and blockchain roundtable in Washington D.C. in early July, according to a private email sent by Khanna's Office, seen by Bitcoin Magazine. 
Khanna's Office described the upcoming meeting as "the most significant meeting between policymakers and innovation leaders in blockchain to date."
The roundtable is expected to feature officials from the Biden Administration, House, and Senate, alongside American businessman Mark Cuban, according to the email. The primary objective of this meeting is to strategize on how to keep "Bitcoin and blockchain innovation in the United States."
This initiative is seen as a response to former President Donald Trump's recent endorsements of the Bitcoin in…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nik Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LEAKED: Biden Admin to Attend Bitcoin Roundtable With Key Congressional Officials in DC]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19591476/LEAKED-Biden-Admin-to-Attend-Bitcoin-Roundtable-With-Key-Congressional-Officials-in-DC</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19591476/LEAKED-Biden-Admin-to-Attend-Bitcoin-Roundtable-With-Key-Congressional-Officials-in-DC"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T20:52:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The proposed meeting, led by U.S. Congressman Ro Khanna, is set to discuss how to keep Bitcoin and blockchain innovation inside the U.S.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance co-founder beseeches Elon Musk to address cryptocurrency scams on X]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19591469/Binance-co-founder-beseeches-Elon-Musk-to-address-cryptocurrency-scams-on-X</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19591469/Binance-co-founder-beseeches-Elon-Musk-to-address-cryptocurrency-scams-on-X"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T20:46:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to Yi He, “a significant amount of money” was lost when X.com users were tricked by an impersonation scam.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nigerian Regulator Warns Against Investing in Meme Coin Linked to Davido]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7415e8e4fd</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/nigerian-regulator-warns-against-investing-in-meme-coin-linked-to-davido/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T20:30:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Nigerian securities regulator warned residents against investing in a meme coin linked to singer and celebrity Davido. The regulator described the meme coin as a highly risky investment, saying investors who invest in it do so at their own risk. The Commission will continue to monitor the ecosystem and will exercise its authority if […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Musk promises ban on Apple, Greenpeace calls for Bitcoin’s PoS, and other news: Hodler’s Digest, June 9-15]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19591464/Musk-promises-ban-on-Apple-Greenpeace-calls-for-Bitcoins-PoS-and-other-news-Hodlers-Digest-June-9-15</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19591464/Musk-promises-ban-on-Apple-Greenpeace-calls-for-Bitcoins-PoS-and-other-news-Hodlers-Digest-June-9-15"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk threatens to ban Apple devices if they integrate with ChatGPT, Greenpeace calls for a shift in Bitcoin’s consensus mechanism, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gemini Agrees To $50 Million Settlement With New York AG]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7415eab393</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/gemini-to-50-million-settlement-with-new-york-ag/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T20:07:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The New York State Attorney General’s Office has secured a settlement of approximately $50 million with the crypto exchange Gemini Trust Company, LLC (Gemini). This marks the latest development in a high-stakes lawsuit involving the New York AG, Gemini, its former business partner Genesis Global Capital, and several other defendants. 
 
 
Gemini Banned From Running Crypto Lending Program
 
In a press release on Friday, New York Attorney General Letitia James announced the successful recovery of $50 million from Gemini targeted at compensating victims who lost money to the exchange’s popular earn program. 
 
James stated that over 230,000 investors, including 29,000 New Yorkers were deceived into investing in Gemini’s Earn, an investment initiative run collaboratively with defunct crypto le…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Semilore Faleti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) Holders Sell, Stalling Price Recovery]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19591475/Ethereum-ETH-Holders-Sell-Stalling-Price-Recovery</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19591475/Ethereum-ETH-Holders-Sell-Stalling-Price-Recovery"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T20:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum’s (ETH) price has disappointed investors, falling from nearly $4,000 to below $3,500. This has led to many holders moving their ETH to the exchanges to minimize their losses. Ethereum Investors Lose Confidence Ethereum’s price drop is causing ETH holders to become increasingly...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SHIB Burns Soar 658% as Shiba Inu Eyes Massive Rebound]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19591432/SHIB-Burns-Soar-658-as-Shiba-Inu-Eyes-Massive-Rebound</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19591432/SHIB-Burns-Soar-658-as-Shiba-Inu-Eyes-Massive-Rebound"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu burns have seen major rise, while SHIB price is on verge of breakout]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Rejects Ripple’s Argument]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19591398/SEC-Rejects-Ripples-Argument</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19591398/SEC-Rejects-Ripples-Argument"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T19:20:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC refutes Ripple's comparison to Terraform Labs in court, insisting on a $2 billion fine due to significant differences between the cases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hoskinson Announces Cardano Game-Changer, Days After Blasting Anti-ADA Media Coverage]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19591396/Hoskinson-Announces-Cardano-Game-Changer-Days-After-Blasting-Anti-ADA-Media-Coverage</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19591396/Hoskinson-Announces-Cardano-Game-Changer-Days-After-Blasting-Anti-ADA-Media-Coverage"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T19:19:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a post on X, the Cardano founder noted that the upcoming upgrade would be the most significant milestone in the history of Cardano.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Over 300 Million Users Depend on Tether’s USDT, Says Paolo Ardoino]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19591418/Over-300-Million-Users-Depend-on-Tethers-USDT-Says-Paolo-Ardoino</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19591418/Over-300-Million-Users-Depend-on-Tethers-USDT-Says-Paolo-Ardoino"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T19:18:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tether CEO Paolo Ardoino recently emphasized USDT’s significant role in driving demand for the US dollar in emerging markets. Ardoino’s comments were in response to an article suggesting that dollar-backed stablecoins contribute to the demand for US public debt. Over 300 Million People Use USDT...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy Plans $700 Million Bitcoin Purchase]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19591390/MicroStrategy-Plans-700-Million-Bitcoin-Purchase</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19591390/MicroStrategy-Plans-700-Million-Bitcoin-Purchase"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T19:16:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy is set to invest $700 million in Bitcoin, a move that could significantly boost the cryptocurrency's price amidst current market volatility.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CBDC Interest Climbs Steadily Over Five Years, Google Trends Data Shows]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7415d7c4a1</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/cbdc-interest-climbs-steadily-over-five-years-google-trends-data-shows/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T19:09:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Trends data reveals a consistent increase in search interest for “CBDC,” which stands for central bank digital currency, over the past five years. The term has maintained a score above 20 since August 2022, on a scale of 1 to 100, where 100 signifies peak interest. CBDCs See Consistent Search Growth, Top Regions Include […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance, BNB, and CZ – Should you be worried about this report’s findings?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19591370/Binance-BNB-and-CZ-Should-you-be-worried-about-this-reports-findings</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19591370/Binance-BNB-and-CZ-Should-you-be-worried-about-this-reports-findings"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T19:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recent Forbes report could ring alarm bells for BNB in the long run.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hedge Fund Founder Predicts the Fate of Altcoins]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19591358/Hedge-Fund-Founder-Predicts-the-Fate-of-Altcoins</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19591358/Hedge-Fund-Founder-Predicts-the-Fate-of-Altcoins"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T18:47:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quinn Thompson, founder of cryptocurrency hedge fund Lekker Capital, evaluated altcoins in his statement. Continue Reading: Hedge Fund Founder Predicts the Fate of Altcoins]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2 cryptocurrencies to reach $5 billion market cap in the second half of the year]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19591319/2-cryptocurrencies-to-reach-5-billion-market-cap-in-the-second-half-of-the-year</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19591319/2-cryptocurrencies-to-reach-5-billion-market-cap-in-the-second-half-of-the-year"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T18:22:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The expanding role of decentralized finance (DeFi), enhancements in blockchain scalability, and the increasing use of smart contracts are expected … Continue reading]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Slips Below 1-Day SMA: Is BTC Heading For Fresh Lows?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7415ddfaa4</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/is-bitcoin-heading-for-fresh-lows/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T18:03:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC), the leading cryptocurrency by market capitalization, is facing renewed bearish pressure as its price falls below the 1-day Simple Moving Average (SMA). This technical indicator, widely used by traders to gauge market trends, signals a potential continuation of the downward trajectory for BTC. 
 
As Bitcoin targets new lows, the breach of the 1-day SMA underscores increasing bearish sentiment and heightened volatility in the market. Investors and analysts are closely monitoring this development, as it may indicate further declines and set the stage for Bitcoin to test lower support levels.
 
With a market capitalization of more than $1.3 trillion and a trading volume of more than $25 billion as of the time of writing, the price of Bitcoin is currently down by 1.49%, trading a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Godspower Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Slips Below 1-Day SMA: Is BTC Heading For Fresh Lows?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19591292/Bitcoin-Slips-Below-1-Day-SMA-Is-BTC-Heading-For-Fresh-Lows</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19591292/Bitcoin-Slips-Below-1-Day-SMA-Is-BTC-Heading-For-Fresh-Lows"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T18:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC), the leading cryptocurrency by market capitalization, is facing renewed bearish pressure as its price falls below the 1-day Simple Moving Average (SMA). This technical indicator, widely used by traders to gauge market trends, signals a potential continuation of the downward...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LATAM Crypto Roundup: Itaú Unibanco Launches Cryptocurrency Trading, Bitcoin Pharaoh Remains in Prison, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19591342/LATAM-Crypto-Roundup-Itau-Unibanco-Launches-Cryptocurrency-Trading-Bitcoin-Pharaoh-Remains-in-Prison-and-More</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19591342/LATAM-Crypto-Roundup-Itau-Unibanco-Launches-Cryptocurrency-Trading-Bitcoin-Pharaoh-Remains-in-Prison-and-More"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BeInCrypto comprehensive Latam Crypto Roundup brings Latin America’s most important news and trends. With reporters in Brazil, Mexico, Argentina, and more, we cover the latest updates and insights from the region’s crypto scene. This week’s roundup includes stories about Brazil’s Bitcoin...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Net-worth update: Here’s how much CZ owns of Binance coin (BNB)]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19591269/Net-worth-update-Heres-how-much-CZ-owns-of-Binance-coin-BNB</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19591269/Net-worth-update-Heres-how-much-CZ-owns-of-Binance-coin-BNB"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T17:47:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to an exclusive Forbes report on June 14, Binance founder Changpeng Zhao (CZ) owns a staggering 64% of the … Continue reading]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bloomberg Analyst Now Expects Spot Ethereum ETFs to Launch on July 2]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7415d8f76f</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bloomberg-analyst-now-expects-spot-ethereum-etfs-to-launch-on-july-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T17:34:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bloomberg’s senior ETF analyst has updated his spot ethereum exchange-traded fund (ETF) prediction. “We are moving up our over/under date for the launch of spot ether ETF to July 2nd,” he said. This revision follows light comments from the SEC Staff on issuers’ S-1 filings. The analyst believes there is a decent chance the SEC […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash Community Unites for "Jessica" Upgrade Event]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19591252/Bitcoin-Cash-Community-Unites-for-Jessica-Upgrade-Event</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19591252/Bitcoin-Cash-Community-Unites-for-Jessica-Upgrade-Event"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T17:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bitcoin Cash community recently gathered in Ljubljana, Slovenia for the highly anticipated BCH Bliss conference, held on May 14-15. The event served as a celebration of a significant network upgrade called "Jessica," which introduces an innovative adaptive block size limit for the Bitcoin...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New York Recovers $50 Million From Gemini — Bans the Exchange From Crypto Lending in the State]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7415c0581b</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/new-york-recovers-50-million-from-gemini-bans-the-exchange-from-crypto-lending-in-the-state/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T16:24:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New York Attorney General Letitia James has secured a $50 million settlement from cryptocurrency exchange Gemini for Earn program investors. This settlement ensures that all defrauded investors will fully recover the assets they invested but were unable to withdraw when the program collapsed. Additionally, Gemini is now banned from operating any crypto lending program in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Notcoin’ Airdrop Claim Ending as Telegram Crypto Gaming Hype Builds]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235594</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235594/notcoin-airdrop-claim-ending-telegram-crypto-gaming-hype"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T15:34:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s one day left for Notcoin players to claim their NOT tokens as Hamster Kombat and other Telegram games gain serious traction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFT Market Sees Gains for Second Consecutive Week, Sales Up 10.95%]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7415c885e0</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/nft-market-sees-gains-for-second-consecutive-week-sales-up-10-95/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T15:13:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Non-fungible token (NFT) sales increased by 10.95% this week compared to the previous week, marking the second consecutive week of gains. Despite a 76.7% drop in the number of buyers, blockchain-issued digital collectibles achieved $141.73 million in sales. NFT Market Trends: Bitcoin and Ethereum Lead Sales Volume In the previous week, NFT sales had risen […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Surge Incoming? MicroStrategy Prepares To Buy $700 Million Worth Of BTC]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7415c90a66</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-surge-incoming-microstrategy-prepares-to-buy-700-million-worth-of-btc/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T15:08:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy, a leading American business intelligence and analytics company, has unveiled plans to buy Bitcoin once again. The AI-powered firm upsized its initial $500 million offerings on convertible notes to $700 million, intending to use the proceeds to acquire an equivalent amount of Bitcoin. This massive Bitcoin purchase could see the price of the cryptocurrency rising, triggered by the boost in demand amidst price volatility. 
 
 
MicroStrategy Set To Increase Bitcoin Holdings 
 
In a recent press release, MicroStrategy announced the sales of its new $700 million convertible notes offerings, which it plans to use to buy more Bitcoin and expand its already substantial holdings. The company disclosed the pricing of the $700 million debt notes, featuring a 2.25% interest rate and a ma…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rapper Lil Pump Gets Dual Solana-Themed Tattoos]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7415cab128</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/rapper-lil-pump-gets-dual-solana-themed-tattoos/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T14:53:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gazzy Garcia, also known as Lil Pump, his professional rapper name, surprised his over 15 million followers on Instagram and X by posting pictures showing two new Solana-themed tattoos. The first featured the stylized name of the Solana blockchain on his forehead, while the second depicted the logo of one of the most popular Solana […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Despite Crypto Market Downturn, TON Achieves All-Time High]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7415b0ca20</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/despite-crypto-market-downturn-ton-achieves-all-time-high/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T13:54:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While bitcoin and the broader cryptocurrency market experienced declines over the past three days, The Open Network’s toncoin (TON) hit an all-time high on Saturday morning, reaching $8.25 per unit. TON has climbed into the top ten rankings with a current market valuation close to $20 billion. TON Defies Crypto Market Slump, Reaches New Peak […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Friendly Evolve Bank Under Scrutiny: Cease and Desist Order Issued]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7415bc2926</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/crypto-friendly-evolve-bank-under-scrutiny-cease-and-desist-order-issued/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T13:23:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Federal Reserve and Arkansas State Bank Department have mandated sweeping reforms at Evolve Bank & Trust following significant compliance breaches. The order highlights issues in anti-money laundering efforts and consumer protection, especially in its dealings with fintech companies and prominent crypto players like FTX. Compliance Concerns Trigger Regulatory Action Against Evolve Bank Evolve Bank […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Would You Pay $40K in Solana for a Date With a Playboy Playmate?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235264</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235264/would-you-pay-40k-solana-date-playboy-playmate"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T13:01:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Only1 is a crypto-fueled OnlyFans alternative on Solana—and already, people are shelling out big bucks to get closer to creators.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erika Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Innovative Block Size Upgrade Takes Spotlight at Bitcoin Cash Bliss Conference]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7415baa96d</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/innovative-block-size-upgrade-takes-spotlight-at-bitcoin-cash-bliss-conference/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T12:21:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following the BCH Bliss conference, a focal event for Bitcoin Cash enthusiasts held May 14-15 in Ljubljana, Slovenia, Jonathan Silverblood introduced a Bitcoin Cash Podcast on X, featuring a collection of tracks from the event. This gathering also celebrated the “Jessica” upgrade, which launched the network’s innovative adaptive block size limit. BCH Bliss 2024: A […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Team Member Shares Update On SHIB Eternity Game, TREAT Token]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7415bb0f4d</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-shares-update-on-eternity-game/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T12:18:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recent update has revealed that the Shiba Inu team has been hard at work behind the scenes getting everything in place for the blockchain launch of SHIB Eternity, despite the recent downturn in the price of SHIB. According to a social media post by Lucie, a prominent member of Shiba Inu’s development team, the long-awaited blockchain version of the SHIB Eternity game is set to launch very soon. Another exciting update is the upcoming launch of TREAT tokens, which will play a big role in SHIB Eternity. Lucie is the marketing lead for Shiba Inu’s development team. 
 
 
What We Know So Far About SHIB Eternity
 
SHIB Eternity is a free-to-play collectible card game for mobile devices where users can play against other players using “unique Shiboshis.” The game has an in-game currency called …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nicehash Partners With Marathon to Launch Custom Firmware for ASIC Bitcoin Miners]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7415a6f961</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/nicehash-partners-with-marathon-to-launch-custom-firmware-for-asic-bitcoin-miners/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T11:41:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bitcoin hashing power marketplace, Nicehash, has launched custom software for ASIC miners optimized for its mining platform. The firmware is designed to help miners drive greater efficiency from ASIC devices and increase revenue. Nicehash CEO said the collaboration with Marathon will strengthen its market position and enable miners globally to attain unparalleled efficiency and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week In Coins: Bitcoin Slumps, TON Surges as Gaming Tokens Burn]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235568</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235568/this-week-in-coins-bitcoin-ton-gaming-tokens"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T11:31:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto saw few winners this week, with the exception of Toncoin and some Bitcoin-bullish stocks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Electrocoin Launches Its New Cryptocurrency Exchange Platform, Electrocoin Trade]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7415a2dc20</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/electrocoin-launches-its-new-cryptocurrency-exchange-platform-electrocoin-trade/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T11:03:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. One of the biggest cryptocurrency exchange services in Croatia, Electrocoin, has recently launched their new cryptocurrency exchange platform called Electrocoin Trade, providing services for natural and legal clients in the EU. The platform includes two core services – cryptocurrency exchange and trading service without prior registration to the platform, and cryptocurrency exchange and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Spot ETFs To Make Trading Debut In July – Here’s The Date]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7415a9a991</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-spot-etfs-to-make-trading-debut-in-july/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T09:58:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following the approval of the Ethereum spot ETFs (exchange-traded funds), potential issuers have had to wait for the trading debuts of their products. This has led to much commentary and speculation on the possible date for the final approvals of the Ether ETFs.
 
Bloomberg analyst Eric Balchunas is the latest personality to predict when the Ethereum spot ETFs could begin trading in the United States. 
 
Why Ethereum Spot ETFs May Start Trading By July 2
 
In a recent post on the X platform, Balchunas put forward July 2, 2024, as the new projected date for when the spot Ethereum exchange-traded funds could begin trading. This update is based on the Securities and Exchange Commission’s (SEC) response to issuers on Friday, June 14.
 
 
According to the ETF expert, the SEC made “pretty light”…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Opeyemi Sule</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Gang Arrested for Exploiting Digital Yuan]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741594081e</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/chinese-gang-arrested-for-exploiting-digital-yuan/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T09:35:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Zhejiang province, China, a criminal gang exploited digital yuan accounts to illegally cash out over 200,000 yuan ($27,566) within four days. The digital yuan, or e-CNY, is the People’s Bank of China’s (PBOC) central bank digital currency (CBDC), which has experienced substantial growth in usage. Adoption has reached 260 million wallets across 25 cities, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram Game 'Hamster Kombat' Claims Explosive Growth, Topping 150 Million Players]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235547</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235547/telegram-game-hamster-kombat-150-million-players"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T21:39:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That’s a 50% surge from just a week ago for the red-hot Telegram game ahead of the TON token. Toncoin hit an all-time high too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop Shares Edge Down Ahead of Critical Shareholder Meeting]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235538</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235538/gamestop-shares-edge-down-ahead-of-critical-shareholder-meeting"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T21:10:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price of GameStop shares were little changed Friday as Roaring Kitty's social media accounts were silent ahead of Monday's meeting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Will Hit $200,000 in 2025, MicroStrategy Will Outperform: Bernstein]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235527</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235527/bitcoin-price-200000-in-2025-microstrategy-outperform-bernstein"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T20:50:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The global investment firm Bernstein estimated Bitcoin will hit $200,000 by 2025, revising its price target from $150,000 in March.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pope Francis Calls for Global Ban on AI Weapons]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235521</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235521/pope-francis-g7-ai-weapon-ban"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T20:37:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“No machine should ever choose to take the life of a human being,” the Pontiff said at the G7 Summit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gemini to Pay Another $50 Million in Latest Settlement Over Earn Program]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235505</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235505/gemini-50-million-earn-settlement-new-york"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T19:27:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New York Attorney General Letitia James says the recovered funds “will make defrauded investors whole.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Kawailani Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Layer-2 Network Stacks Halted for 9 Hours—What Happened?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235507</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235507/bitcoin-layer-2-network-stacks-halted-9-hours"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T19:05:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stacks stopped producing blocks for about nine hours early Friday, causing a price plunge in the Bitcoin layer-2's token as well. Here's why.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[94% of Central Banks Considering Wholesale CBDCs, Says BIS]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235501</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235501/94-of-central-banks-considering-wholesale-cbdcs-says-bis"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T18:45:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to the report, central banks are more likely to issue wholesale CBDC than retail CBDC in the next six years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 138 - MORE CELEB COINS!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/KzCZzgqx/fomo-hour-138-more-celeb-coins</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/KzCZzgqx/fomo-hour-138-more-celeb-coins"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T18:05:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Altcoins bleed out heavy, BTC dominance rises towards 60%. Miners continue to be large BTC sellers, whales accumulate. ETF inflows slow, hedge fund allocations point to basis trades. ETH ETFs approvals see little movement, coming 'in the summer’. Stocks continue to hit ATHs as CPI & PPI both come in soft. TON performs best in L1s, active wallets eclipse ETH. Andrew Tate joins celebrity memecoin meta, DADDY hits $350m. SOL DEX volumes eclipse ETH in memecoin frenzy. Curve founder defaults on CRV debt as DeFi coins tumble. Terraform Labs & Do Kwon to pay $4.5bn fine to SEC. BAMK hits $350m in Runes as it issues BTC stablecoin. Gaming tokens face huge sell-off, PRIME changes tokenomics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Calculated Betrayal’: Snowden Slams OpenAI Over NSA Ties]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235490</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235490/calculated-betrayal-snowden-slams-openai-nsa-ties"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T17:38:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI's recent appointment of a former NSA director has sparked immediate backlash from whistleblower Edward Snowden and others.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Plunges as Over $150 Million in Longs Get Rekt]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235488</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235488/bitcoin-price-plunges-150-million-longs-get-rekt"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T16:53:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price of Bitcoin is falling, nearing a one-month low as more than $100 million worth of crypto long positions were liquidated in an hour.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward,Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy Can't Get Enough Bitcoin, Boosting Latest Raise to $700 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235476</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235476/microstrategy-bitcoin-boosts-latest-raise-700-million"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T15:51:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Saylor's firm just boosted its latest convertible notes raise to buy up even more Bitcoin. It already holds $14.3 billion worth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Hamster Kombat’ Daily Combo Guide: How to Earn 5 Million Free Coins in the Telegram Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233516</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/hamster-kombat-daily-combo-guide-earn-5-million-free-coins"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T15:33:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram game Hamster Kombat offers a huge daily bonus of in-game coins ahead of the airdrop. Here’s how to claim it each day.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop Stock Dips After Roaring Kitty Nearly Doubles Stake]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235470</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235470/gamestop-stock-dips-roaring-kitty-nearly-doubles-stake"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T15:16:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price of GME has been choppy early Friday as influencer investor Roaring Kitty ups position ahead of GameStop's board meeting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Greg Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nigeria Drops Tax Charges Against Binance Execs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235442</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235442/nigeria-drops-tax-charges-against-binance-execs"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T13:56:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two Binance execs have been dropped from tax evasion charges by a Nigerian agency but they still face a money laundering case.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Week in Polkadot: Moonbeam Launches $13 Million Funding Initiative]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235215</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235215/the-week-in-polkadot-moonbeam-launches-13-million-funding-initiative"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T13:01:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of Polkadot’s largest parachains is investing big in its ecosystem,  while the Polkadot community pours money into liquidity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will McCurdy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop Solana Meme Coin GME and Iggy Azalea's MOTHER See Big Weekly Losses]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235431</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235431/gamestop-solana-meme-coin-gme-and-iggy-azaleas-mother-see-big-weekly-losses"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T11:03:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MOTHER—a meme coin launched by rapper Iggy Azalea—has plummeted by 38% in the past 7 days.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarang Khaitan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notcoin Posts 10% Gain as TON Daily Active Wallets Match Ethereum Again]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235432</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235432/notcoin-posts-10-gain-as-ton-daily-active-wallets-match-ethereum-again"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T10:52:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram-based games are causing The Open Network to explode, with Notcoin leading the entire crypto market in the last 24 hours.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Cites Terra Settlement in Appeal to Cut Penalty From $2 Billion to $10 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235422</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235422/ripple-terraform-2-billion-to-10-million"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T09:45:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple arguing its penalty is too high, "even though there are no allegations of fraud in this case."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla Is Tops in ‘Real-World AI’, Elon Musk Declares]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235387</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235387/tesla-is-the-leader-in-real-world-ai-elon-musk-tell-shareholders"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T01:23:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With his massive pay package approved, the Tesla CEO touted the automaker's advancements in chip design and robotics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Backlash: Cara and ‘Not By AI’ Rage Against the Machine]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235334</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235334/anti-ai-cara-artists-platform-not-by-ai"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T23:10:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artists draw a line in the sand, declaring creative spaces free of artificial intelligence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SD3 Goes Head-to-Head With SDXL, MidJourney, and Ideogram—Which AI Image Maker Is Best?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235267</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235267/sd3-comparison-sdxl-midjourney-ideogram-best-ai-image-generator"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T22:31:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stability AI's latest release is a strong performer—just don't ask it to depict anyone lying in the grass.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paradigm Raises $850 Million to Invest in Early-Stage Crypto Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235323</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235323/paradigm-raises-850-million-invest-early-stage-crypto"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T22:01:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paradigm, the prominent crypto VC firm, has raised $850 million for its latest fund focused on nascent projects in various categories.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Greg Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roaring Kitty Now Owns $262 Million In GameStop Shares as Options Vanish]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235320</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235320/roaring-kitty-gamestop-shares-options-gone"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T21:38:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Showing a change in his GameStop holdings, the value of Keith Gill's portfolio had decreased 55% from a week prior.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miner Bitfarm Shares Surge as Riot Takeover Turns Hostile]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235304</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235304/bitcoin-miner-bitfarm-shares-up-17-percent-riot-hostile-takeover"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T20:49:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitfarms sets its sights on Pennsylvania as it attempts to shake off Riot Platform’s newfound influence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bill to Kill US Federal Reserve Was Inspired by Bitcoin Book]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235249</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235249/congressman-proposed-bill-to-end-the-fed-bitcoin-standard-book"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T19:42:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“The Bitcoin Standard” inspired Rep. Thomas Massie to bring back legislation to end the Fed for the first time in a decade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump or Biden? Why Crypto Could Decide the Next US President]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235047</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235047/trump-biden-why-crypto-decide-next-us-president"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T19:16:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Polling data shows that crypto support could tip the balance in a close race for the White House. Here's how it could impact Biden and Trump.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tor Constantino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram Games ‘Tapswap’ and ‘Yescoin’ Launching Tokens on The Open Network]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235233</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235233/telegram-games-tapswap-yescoin-tokens-open-network"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T18:53:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After the huge Notcoin airdrop and the Hamster Kombat hype, other Telegram-based games are coming to The Open Network (TON).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop Servers Crash as Fans Flood Board Meeting for Signs of Roaring Kitty]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235226</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235226/gamestop-servers-crash-board-meeting-roaring-kitty"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T18:21:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overwhelming interest from GME investors crashed GameStop’s board meeting servers, leaving investors wondering about Roaring Kitty’s position.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin and Ethereum Are Cooling Off—But Gaming Token Prices Are Down Bad]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235224</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235224/bitcoin-ethereum-cooling-gaming-token-prices-down-bad"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T18:07:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Think Bitcoin and Ethereum losses this week are rough? Many major gaming tokens are plunging, down as much as 40% over the past seven days.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 Sports Fantasy Game Maincard.io Now Live on TON]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235214</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235214/web3-sports-fantasy-game-maincard-io-now-live-on-ton"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T16:15:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Irvine, US, 13th June 2024, GamingWire]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GamingWire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Labs to Dissolve After $4.5 Billion SEC Settlement Over LUNA, UST]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235183</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235183/terraform-labs-dissolve-4-5-billion-sec-settlement"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T16:13:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Labs' CEO said that the company will be winding down operations following a $4.5 billion settlement agreement with the SEC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum ETFs Likely to Launch This Summer, Says SEC's Gensler]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235195</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235195/ethereum-etfs-launch-summer-says-sec-gensler"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T16:03:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gary Gensler expects spot Ethereum ETFs to go live in the U.S. this summer, but still won't answer on the security vs. commodity question.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 137 - CRYPTO DIPS FURTHER]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mJ28rAx5/fomo-hour-137-crypto-dips-further</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mJ28rAx5/fomo-hour-137-crypto-dips-further"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T15:46:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto falls after slightly hawkish Fed speech. BTC whales buy $1.4bn in 24hrs. Miners continue to be large sellers of BTC. BTC ETFs see $100m inflows. MicroStrategy to raise $500m to buy BTC. Egorov CRV debt positions begin to liquidate  . Circle to support SOL for wallets. 4% of Turkey GDP used to buy stablecoins. QuantMatter say $11m stolen from OKX account. Biden to use Coinbase for crypto donations. Terraform Labs & Do Kwon set to pay $4.5bn fine. Franklin Templeton write report on SOL DePin. TON flips ETH for active addresses. Moonpay & Paypal integration goes live in EU & UK.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop Stock Rises Amid Speculation Over Whether Roaring Kitty Sold]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235190</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235190/gamestop-stock-rises-speculation-roaring-kitty-sold"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T15:45:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GME shares are up Thursday as GameStop investors wait to find out whether Keith Gill, aka influencer Roaring Kitty, sold his options.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Many Bitcoin Billionaires Are There?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=32694</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/32694/how-many-bitcoin-billionaires-are-there"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T15:40:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many of Bitcoin's early adopters are now billionaires, among the wealthiest people in the world. But Satoshi Nakamoto's wealth could eclipse them all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ali Shutler,Daniel Phillips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 136 - FIRST MOTHER, NOW DADDY?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LEzSMpGz/fomo-hour-136-first-mother-now-daddy</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LEzSMpGz/fomo-hour-136-first-mother-now-daddy"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T18:01:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETFs see another $200m outflows. Another $190m of liquidations in volatility. $1.2bn BTC leaves exchanges in a day. ETF flows largely driven by basis trades: Pal. ‘Perfect setup’ for longs into macro news today. ETH ETF approvals ‘expected this month’. Crypto in best place it has ever been: Circle CEO. China’s ICBC calls ETH ‘digital oil’. Trump wants ‘made in the USA’ BTC. Crypto hacks $19bn since 2011. Symbiotic restaking protocol sees $150m inflows. Polygon launches $720m grants program. ZKsync accused of insider allocations. CRV drop leaves $90m loans at risk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Has AI Already Changed Gaming Forever?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mZlR3He5/has-ai-already-changed-gaming-forever</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mZlR3He5/has-ai-already-changed-gaming-forever"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T19:51:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt’s Sander Lutz and Rug Radio creator Puke sat down with Simon Davis of Mighty Bear Games and VC Kyle Klemmer to discuss how AI has already remade the gaming industry—for better and for worse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 135 - BTC FALLS ON OUTFLOWS]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/bA3jJ5aA/fomo-hour-135-btc-falls-on-outflows</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/bA3jJ5aA/fomo-hour-135-btc-falls-on-outflows"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T19:03:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto falls as ETFs see first outflow in 19 days. Short positions grow on downwards move in BTC. BTC short-term realised price now at $64k. ETH ETF issuers still waiting for SEC response. UK ETNs continue to see tiny volume. SOL validators get kicked out for sandwich attacks. ZKsync airdrop happening next week. ZKsync to give 17.8% to the community. OP launches Fraud Proofs. Bitfarms plans poison pill to counter takeover bid. OKX sees outflows after security incidents. Bybit considers shutting China offices. COIN may get added to S&P500.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 134 - EU SNAP ELECTIONS LAND]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pZksMKIV/fomo-hour-134-eu-snap-elections-land</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pZksMKIV/fomo-hour-134-eu-snap-elections-land"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T15:46:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Volatility remains low, TL continues to be divisive. 2nd highest weekly close ever for BTC. Crypto funds saw $2bn inflows last week. Rumour that BlackRock will apply for SOL ETF. Base TVL hits $8bn, top of L2s for activity. zk Sync hint at TGE this week. PENDLE enters top 5 for DeFi TVL. Berachain v2 testnet goes live.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 133 - RUGGED BY HOGEN?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MSvAS9qX/fomo-hour-133-rugged-by-hogen</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MSvAS9qX/fomo-hour-133-rugged-by-hogen"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T17:26:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC still just below ATH after $218m ETF inflows. BTC OI hits record $37bn as long-short ratio rises. Amount of ETH on exchanges lowest since 2015. Franklin Templeton explores broader crypto fund. Mining stocks rise on takeover frenzy. Kraken considers $100m funding round. Binance reinstates crypto buys with Mastercard. Phantom & Jito partner for native staking.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 132 - CRYPTO STRENGTH IS GROWING]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/bQBFWC0w/fomo-hour-132-crypto-strength-is-growing</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/bQBFWC0w/fomo-hour-132-crypto-strength-is-growing"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T19:49:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto consolidates near ATH, $488m ETF inflow. BTC correlation to tech stocks highest since 2023. BTC options anticipate $74-80k move. ETH to $22k by 2030: VanEck. Robinhood to acquire Bitstamp.
Coinbase launches Smart Wallet. ByBit opens up explicitly to China users. Global liquidity breaks out to $94T. US President given new powers to block crypto. Cramer & Gensler continue to bash crypto. Gensler hints at prolonged ETH ETF process. Stand with Crypto PAC hits 1m advocates. Turkey denies plans to tax crypto. EigenLayer surpasses $20bn TVL. IONET to launch on Binance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webinar: Unleashing The Power Of Permissionless Markets With Vega Protocol]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OvA845JA/webinar-unleashing-the-power-of-permissionless-markets-with-vega-protocol</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OvA845JA/webinar-unleashing-the-power-of-permissionless-markets-with-vega-protocol"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T08:23:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join our expert panel for an insightful discussion on Vega Protocol's revolutionary approach to decentralized derivatives trading. Discover how Vega's permissionless markets enable anyone to create and trade futures and perpetuals on a fully decentralized network. Explore the potential of Vega's innovative features, such as the ability to add new assets, transfer network assets, and adjust network parameters—as well as the protocol's active markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 131 - BIG BITCOIN INFLOWS!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/a37DNT7n/fomo-hour-131-big-bitcoin-inflows</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/a37DNT7n/fomo-hour-131-big-bitcoin-inflows"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T17:06:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETFs see large $900M inflows, biggest in weeks. $800M of shorts would be liquidated above $72K. BTC to $100K if it breaks $73K in a week: Novogratz. BNB hits new ATH, breaks $100B market cap. FTX reaches $200M tax settlement with IRS. Most investors should hold BTC: Fidelity. Tether CEO criticises EU on stablecoin regulation. Japanese exchange raises $320M to recover funds. ETH ETFs could see $4B inflows in 5 months: K33. Paradigm propose MEV taxes. StarkWare plans ZK scaling for BTC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 130 - $DOG TARGETS 1B MC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ke2mFBwr/fomo-hour-130-dog-targets-1b-mc</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ke2mFBwr/fomo-hour-130-dog-targets-1b-mc"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T22:05:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Runes & Ordinals soar as DOG passes $900M. rekt Brands opens up its shares claim for NFT holders. BTC led NFT trading volume with $6.3M on the day. NodeMonkes +10% 0.289, Puppets +35% at 0.198. Runes up by DOG which soared 23% to $922M mc. BUS won the Blast Jackpot last night for a 3% win. Memecoin majors are mostly red this AM. Trader buys 10k SOL of GME. Base brings back Onchain Summer. Dapper settles massive lawsuit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 129 - ROARING RETURNS, AGAIN!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ABOejLBT/fomo-hour-129-roaring-returns-again</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ABOejLBT/fomo-hour-129-roaring-returns-again"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T21:42:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto bounces, BTC breaks 2-week downtrend. BTC low volatility points to trend continuation. BTC will top at $150k in September 2025: Brandt. $3bn ETH withdrawn from exchanges since ETF. ETH ETF inflows imply ‘base case’ price $5.3k. ETH ETF inflows won’t be like BTC: Fireblocks. BTC logo projected on ECB building. Ethena USDe hits $3bn market cap in 4 months. Maple launches DeFi institutional lending platform. OKX launches in the Netherlands. Matter Labs drops ZK ticker. Linea shuts down chain after hack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 128 - PUMP DOT FUN KEEPS PUMPING!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cziNL3TF/fomo-hour-128-pump-dot-fun-keeps-pumping</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cziNL3TF/fomo-hour-128-pump-dot-fun-keeps-pumping"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T21:41:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto nears break-out then falls on Trump verdict. 13 straight days of BTC ETF inflows, BTC whale accumulation ‘echoes 2020’. Crypto apps next year will onboard millions: Burniske. Elon denies talking crypto policy with Trump. RFK has bought 21 BTC during campaign. TON market cap falls after updating supply data. a16z donates $25m to crypto PAC. Vitalik sends 30ETH to Tornado devs. DBS Bank in Singapore custodies $650m ETH. Backlash grows over zkSync using ZK ticker. Implementing FIT21 a slow process: CFTC. Pierce recommends UK & US cross-border sandbox. Vitalik writes blog on block size wars. Hong Kong government expresses support for web3. Do Kwon & Terraform reach settlement with SEC. Large unlocks for a number of alts next month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 127 - CELEB COINS CRASH!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mGbE2GHV/fomo-hour-127-celeb-coins-crash</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mGbE2GHV/fomo-hour-127-celeb-coins-crash"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T20:28:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NYSE to launch BTC options. CME has ‘no plans’ to offer SOL futures. Stablecoin market cap rises to 2 year high. Inflation below 3.3% ‘means BTC ATH’. Crypto market cap heading to $200T: Yat Siu. Gemini recovers $2.2bn for Earn users. PayPal stablecoin will offer ‘confidential transfers’. Mastercard launches Crypto Credential pilot on BTC. Layer Zero launches on SOL. L2s are cultural extensions of ETH: Vitalik. FTX’s Salame says he will share story. SEI announces 27m SEI airdrop. ASI merger complete, to launch June 13th.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 126 - MEMECOIN MADNESS!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/eA3xqKLr/fomo-hour-126-memecoin-madness</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/eA3xqKLr/fomo-hour-126-memecoin-madness"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T21:30:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock ETF flips Grayscale in size. BTC ETFs see 11 straight days of inflows. ZKasino gives 72hours for ETH withdrawals. ENS to migrate to L2. ADA drops out of top 10 coins. Salame sentenced to 7.5 years in jail. Riot Platforms attempts takeover of Bitfarms. Ripple donates $25m to Fairshake PAC. Pump(.)fun launches live streaming. Iggy Azelea MOTHER coin leads celeb tokens. Beeple Everyday features many coins. Runes bounce, DOG hits $560m. PEPE active wallets double during rally. Cristiano Ronaldo launches 4th NFT. Friend Tech announces club wars.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum DN-404 Tokens Are a Sensation in Asia. Are They the West’s Next Big Trend?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/drcV3Zte/ethereum-dn-404-tokens-are-a-sensation-in-asia-are-they-the-wests-next-big-trend</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/drcV3Zte/ethereum-dn-404-tokens-are-a-sensation-in-asia-are-they-the-wests-next-big-trend"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T19:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz and Rug Radio creator Pukerainbow sat down for a conversation with some of the biggest adopters involved in Ethereum’s newest trend: dividing NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Buying Crypto Simplified with Mika]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/Z9rxTcnJ/buying-crypto-simplified-with-mika</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/Z9rxTcnJ/buying-crypto-simplified-with-mika"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T16:54:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the first part of our series turning crypto beginners into crypto pros, Rug Radio creator Mika guides you through the process of purchasing cryptocurrency using crypto exchange Kraken.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 125 - ETH NEARS 4K]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BrgFfEe8/fomo-hour-125-eth-nears-4k</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BrgFfEe8/fomo-hour-125-eth-nears-4k"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T17:40:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH leads rally on continued bullish ETF sentiment. Previous anti-crypto Trump comments highlighted. Wave of influencers and celebrities hacked, release coins. Phantom becomes no.1 finance app in the US. Argentina & El Salvador hold talks on BTC adoption. LINK to have large announcement on May 30th. PEPE, MOG, TURBO, TRUMP hit ATHs in ETH memes. MOG up 60%, mentioned in Beeple Everyday. Caitlyn Jenner hacker releases JENNER coin. Garga outlines future plans for BAYC. Friend Tech founder offers $200k to migrate off Base.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 124 - THE ETH ETF IS APPROVED!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5ELzjWt4/fomo-hour-124-the-eth-etf-is-approved</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5ELzjWt4/fomo-hour-124-the-eth-etf-is-approved"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T18:43:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH ETFs get approved 19b-4 forms. ETFs won’t trade until July or August: Galaxy. ETF means many coins not securities: Coinbase CLO. Coinbase relists XRP in US. SOL ETF coming: Scaramucci. US House passes vote to ban CBDC. Building a pro-crypto army in congress: Sen. Lummis. Polymarket backlash over if ETH ETF truly approved. Expect ETH ETFs to be 10-15% of BTC: Bloomberg. BTC ETFs see $1.75bn inflows over 9 days. BTC to $150k in 2024 is base case: Tom Lee. ETH co-founder moves $37m ETH to exchanges. Grayscale launches trusts for STX & NEAR. Coinbase loses against SEC on DOGE sweepstakes. ALGO ad attacks BTC, SOL, ETH. Phantom now no.2 finance App on Google Play.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 123 - ETHEREUM KEEPS GOING!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JE3lB00G/fomo-hour-123-ethereum-keeps-going</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JE3lB00G/fomo-hour-123-ethereum-keeps-going"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T15:43:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH soars, ETF S1 approvals expected in hours. US house greenlights FIT21 bill with broad support. Gensler says SEC already has rules for crypto. Hong Kong set to allow ETH staking for ETFs. ETH OI continues to soar. SOL mentioned as next ETF candidate on CNBC. SOL ETF will take years: Bloomberg. MetaMask plans BTC integration. Fed says only 7% of Americans own crypto. SBF heads to a new prison. Hong Kong orders WLD shutdown. TON added to Binance ahead of potential listing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>