<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-06-16T09:14:00.638Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-06-16T09:14:00.638Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Goldman Sachs Faces Fed And SEC Probe For SVB’s Securities Portfolio: Report]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757d150340</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/goldman-sachs-faces-fed-and-sec-probe/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T09:12:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Goldman Sachs is currently under investigation by federal regulators for its involvement in the acquisition of Silicon Valley Bank’s securities portfolio while simultaneously providing advisory services to the struggling lender regarding capital raising, prior to its subsequent collapse this year. 
 
The US Federal Reserve, the Securities and Exchange Commission, and the Department of Justice have requested documentation from Goldman Sachs as part of wider investigations into the downfall of SVB, The Wall Street Journal reports. 
 
The focus of scrutiny lies on potential inappropriate communication between Goldman Sachs’ trading division and its investment banking department in relation to the portfolio sale, as sources informed The Journal.
 
Goldman Sachs Questioned Over Dual Role In SVB…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance to Quit Netherlands After Failing to Acquire License]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757d167c3f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/06/16/binance-to-quit-netherlands-after-failing-to-acquire-license/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T09:01:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto exchange's attempt to secure a virtual asset service provider (VASP) license from the Dutch regulator was unsuccessful.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Central Banks Successfully Test Over 30 CBDC Use Cases, Including Offline Payments]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18589502/Central-Banks-Successfully-Test-Over-30-CBDC-Use-Cases-Including-Offline-Payments</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18589502/Central-Banks-Successfully-Test-Over-30-CBDC-Use-Cases-Including-Offline-Payments"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An API layer could facilitate a wide range of central bank digital currency payment scenarios, a Bank for International Settlements and Bank of England experiment has shown.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[June 16, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18589340/June-16-2023</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18589340/June-16-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T08:57:32.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase customers can now earn 4% USDC rewards despite SEC scrutiny]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18589112/Coinbase-customers-can-now-earn-4-USDC-rewards-despite-SEC-scrutiny</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18589112/Coinbase-customers-can-now-earn-4-USDC-rewards-despite-SEC-scrutiny"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T08:50:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase increased USDC rewards for global customers to 4%, funding the rewards from its own pocket.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Goldman Sachs Faces Fed And SEC Probe For SVB’s Securities Portfolio: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18589072/Goldman-Sachs-Faces-Fed-And-SEC-Probe-For-SVBs-Securities-Portfolio-Report</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18589072/Goldman-Sachs-Faces-Fed-And-SEC-Probe-For-SVBs-Securities-Portfolio-Report"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T08:45:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Goldman Sachs is currently under investigation by federal regulators for its involvement in the acquisition of Silicon Valley Bank’s securities portfolio while simultaneously providing advisory services to the struggling lender regarding capital raising, prior to its subsequent collapse this...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance to Quit Netherlands After Failing to Acquire License]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18589083/Binance-to-Quit-Netherlands-After-Failing-to-Acquire-License</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18589083/Binance-to-Quit-Netherlands-After-Failing-to-Acquire-License"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto exchange's attempt to secure a virtual asset service provider (VASP) license from the Dutch regulator was unsuccessful.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock Joins Race for Spot Bitcoin ETF, Submits Application to SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18588842/BlackRock-Joins-Race-for-Spot-Bitcoin-ETF-Submits-Application-to-SEC</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18588842/BlackRock-Joins-Race-for-Spot-Bitcoin-ETF-Submits-Application-to-SEC"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T08:39:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinspeaker BlackRock Joins Race for Spot Bitcoin ETF, Submits Application to SEC The SEC has received an official application from BlackRock for a spot Bitcoin ETF to help investors benefit from BTC without direct access. BlackRock Joins Race for Spot Bitcoin ETF, Submits Application to SEC]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reports Indicate Venezuela Is Preparing to Liquidate the Petro]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757d125b2f</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/reports-indicate-venezuela-is-preparing-to-liquidate-the-petro/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T08:33:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to reports, the government of Venezuela could be winding down the operations of the petro cryptocurrency. The decision comes after Sunacrip, the Venezuelan cryptocurrency watchdog, was set back by the alleged participation of its former head Joselit Ramirez in a potential $20 billion corruption scheme involving the settlement of Venezuelan oil sales.
Reports Indicate Venezuela Is Prepared to Liquidate Petro Cryptocurrency
The run of the first nation-issued cryptocurrency asset might be close to its end. According to reports from Bloomberg Linea, three people linked to Sunacrip, the Venezuelan crypto watchdog, have stated that the institution has decided to liquidate the petro five years after its issuance.
The decision, allegedly taken by the new restructuring board in charge of …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sturdy stablecoin market reopens three days after $800K exploit]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18588838/Sturdy-stablecoin-market-reopens-three-days-after-800K-exploit</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18588838/Sturdy-stablecoin-market-reopens-three-days-after-800K-exploit"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T08:30:33.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFTs on Bitcoin: the new 3D collection of generative art by OnChainMonkey]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18588846/NFTs-on-Bitcoin-the-new-3D-collection-of-generative-art-by-OnChainMonkey</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18588846/NFTs-on-Bitcoin-the-new-3D-collection-of-generative-art-by-OnChainMonkey"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T08:30:33.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA) Among Celsius' Sell-off List: What to Expect?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18588858/Cardano-ADA-Among-Celsius-Sell-off-List-What-to-Expect</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18588858/Cardano-ADA-Among-Celsius-Sell-off-List-What-to-Expect"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T08:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Is Bitcoin Up Today?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18588444/Why-Is-Bitcoin-Up-Today</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18588444/Why-Is-Bitcoin-Up-Today"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T08:10:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bitcoin price has risen 3.2% since yesterday’s low of $24,827. At press time, BTC was trading at $25,590 and has thus reclaimed two extremely important price levels for the moment: first, the Bitcoin price has once again risen above the 200-day Exponential Moving Average (EMA) currently at...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Shorts Lose $16M as BlackRock ETF Filing Sparks Bullish Outlook]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757d1e720d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/06/16/bitcoin-shorts-lose-16m-as-blackrock-etf-filing-sparks-bullish-outlook/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T08:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Total crypto market capitalization rose nominally with dogecoin (DOGE) leading gains among major tokens.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cash App integrates the Bitcoin wallet of Twitter’s former CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18588242/Cash-App-integrates-the-Bitcoin-wallet-of-Twitters-former-CEO</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18588242/Cash-App-integrates-the-Bitcoin-wallet-of-Twitters-former-CEO"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T07:55:30.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Lender Abra Remains Insolvent since March: Texas Regulator]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757d1faab5</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/crypto-lender-abra-remains-insolvant-since-march-texas-regulator/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T07:52:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Texas State Securities Board has issued an emergency cease and desist order against the crypto lender, Abra, alleging that the company had been insolvent since at least 31 March 2023. 

Abra Faces Enforcement Action 

According to the US state regulator, Plutus Financial (commercially known as Abra), Abra Boost, Plutus Lending, and Abra's Founder, William Barhydt misled the public and committed securities fraud. 

Barhydt founded Abra in 2014 and offers cryptocurrency trading, lending, and borrowing services to retail and institutional investors. It offers investment into Abra Earn and Abra Boost, which allegedly contained misleading statements. 

According to the Texas regulator, Abra "made offers of investments in Abra Earn in Texas containing statements that were materially misleadi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arnab Shome</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto news: Ripple enters Colombia with blockchain pilot project]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18588243/Crypto-news-Ripple-enters-Colombia-with-blockchain-pilot-project</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18588243/Crypto-news-Ripple-enters-Colombia-with-blockchain-pilot-project"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T07:50:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Its CBDC platform will be tested by Banco de la República]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Treasury Secretary: No Alternative Reserve Currency Can ‘Replicate’ Role Played by the Dollar]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757d18a48c</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/us-treasury-secretary-no-alternative-reserve-currency-can-replicate-role-played-by-the-dollar/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T07:43:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[United States Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen recently told members of the U.S. Congress that while some countries are seeking to create alternatives to the greenback, no country, including China, can create a currency which replicates the dollar’s role in the global financial system. The U.S. Treasury secretary also claimed that it will not be easy for any country “to devise a way to get around the dollar.”
 
Using an Alternative Reserve Currency to Skirt U.S. Sanctions
 
United States Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen has told members of the Financial Services Committee of the U.S. Congress that the ongoing trend of countries seeking to establish an alternative reserve currency to rival the greenback “is something that we simply have to expect.” In her June 13 appearance before the committ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ETH’s price reacts to FOMC meeting; will bears stick around?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18587484/ETHs-price-reacts-to-FOMC-meeting-will-bears-stick-around</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18587484/ETHs-price-reacts-to-FOMC-meeting-will-bears-stick-around"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T07:30:13.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock files application for Bitcoin ETF and deposits it with SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18588244/BlackRock-files-application-for-Bitcoin-ETF-and-deposits-it-with-SEC</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18588244/BlackRock-files-application-for-Bitcoin-ETF-and-deposits-it-with-SEC"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T07:28:39.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The reorganization plan of Celsius: convert altcoins to Bitcoin and Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18588245/The-reorganization-plan-of-Celsius-convert-altcoins-to-Bitcoin-and-Ethereum</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18588245/The-reorganization-plan-of-Celsius-convert-altcoins-to-Bitcoin-and-Ethereum"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T07:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Prediction: BTC's Struggle to Break Through $25,600 and Key Factors Affecting its Future]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18586987/Bitcoin-Price-Prediction-BTCs-Struggle-to-Break-Through-25600-and-Key-Factors-Affecting-its-Future</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18586987/Bitcoin-Price-Prediction-BTCs-Struggle-to-Break-Through-25600-and-Key-Factors-Affecting-its-Future"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T07:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin is finally showing signs of recovery, but it continues to face challenges in breaking through the $25,600 level.  As Bitcoin faces resistance at this key price point, market participants eagerly await key developments that could shape the cryptocurrency's trajectory.  What are the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock Bitcoin ETF: Good Or Bad? What Are The Chances? Experts React]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757d04ba4e</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/blackrock-bitcoin-etf-good-or-bad-chances/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T07:09:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The rumor has come true: The world’s largest asset manager, BlackRock, has filed a Bitcoin spot ETF application with the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). For custody and market price data, BlackRock is choosing Coinbase, despite the SEC lawsuit. And while the news sounds extremely bullish for the BTC price, the community is wondering whether BlackRock’s entry into Bitcoin is good or bad.
 
For many years, a Bitcoin spot ETF has been seen as the holy grail for Bitcoin in the US to attract huge amounts of new capital. So far, various asset managers have cut their teeth at the SEC when it comes to Bitcoin spot ETFs.
 
 
The SEC however has a long history of denying spot ETFs citing concerns about market manipulation and the lack of a surveillance-sharing agreement between a “regul…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trader Who Accurately Nailed Bitcoin’s 2022 Bottom Says He Will Re-Enter Market When BTC Hits This Level]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18586804/Trader-Who-Accurately-Nailed-Bitcoins-2022-Bottom-Says-He-Will-Re-Enter-Market-When-BTC-Hits-This-Level</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18586804/Trader-Who-Accurately-Nailed-Bitcoins-2022-Bottom-Says-He-Will-Re-Enter-Market-When-BTC-Hits-This-Level"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T07:04:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A top crypto analyst is unveiling when he could resume Bitcoin (BTC) trading activity amid a market downturn. Pseudonymous analyst DonAlt tells 51,200 subscribers of the TechnicalRoundup YouTube channel that BTC needs to get back above the $27,500 price level for him to trade the flagship crypto...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance.US Reportedly Laid Off Dozens of Staff amid SEC Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757d07b457</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/binanceus-reportedly-laid-off-dozens-of-staff-amid-sec-lawsuit/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T06:43:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US affiliate of Binance has laid off around 50 staff across a few divisions in the latest round of reducing its workforce, Reuters reported citing two anonymous sources.  

A Massive Layoff Round at Binance.US  

The report detailed that the laid-off staff were employed by Binance.US' legal, compliance, and risk departments. Binance.US did not confirm the layoffs officially, however, at least two employees of the US-based crypto exchange confirmed their exit on Wednesday on Linkedin.  

Earlier, independent journalist Colin Wu revealed that Binance had laid off 20 percent of its employees from its total headcount of 8,000. However, Binance's Chief Strategy Officer, Patrick Hillmann, spun the layoff, calling it a "talent density audit and resource allocation exercise."  

Regulatory Tro…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arnab Shome</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Shorts Lose $16M as BlackRock ETF Filing Sparks Bullish Outlook]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18586426/Bitcoin-Shorts-Lose-16M-as-BlackRock-ETF-Filing-Sparks-Bullish-Outlook</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18586426/Bitcoin-Shorts-Lose-16M-as-BlackRock-ETF-Filing-Sparks-Bullish-Outlook"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T06:39:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Total crypto market capitalization rose nominally with dogecoin (DOGE) leading gains among major tokens.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock Bitcoin ETF: Good Or Bad? What Are The Chances? Experts React]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18586263/BlackRock-Bitcoin-ETF-Good-Or-Bad-What-Are-The-Chances-Experts-React</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18586263/BlackRock-Bitcoin-ETF-Good-Or-Bad-What-Are-The-Chances-Experts-React"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T06:30:45.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mark Cuban takes on SEC, John Reed Stark and ‘crypto derangement syndrome’]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18586266/Mark-Cuban-takes-on-SEC-John-Reed-Stark-and-crypto-derangement-syndrome</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18586266/Mark-Cuban-takes-on-SEC-John-Reed-Stark-and-crypto-derangement-syndrome"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T06:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avantgarde, Agio Digital Unveil Institutional Onchain Funds Platform]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757d0ec8ce</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/06/16/avantgarde-agio-digital-unveil-institutional-onchain-funds-platform/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T05:38:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The platform will allow for users to set up fully regulated on-chain funds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lyllah Ledesma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[France’s Macron Hopes to Attend BRICS Summit in South Africa, Report]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757d0f8797</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/frances-macron-hopes-to-attend-brics-summit-in-south-africa-report/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T05:31:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[French President Emmanuel Macron wants to join the leaders of the BRICS nations when they meet in August, according to a press report. While his participation in the multipolar bloc’s summit is uncertain, Macron has already scheduled another summit in Paris to discuss the establishment of a “fairer” financial system.
 
Macron Reportedly Asks Ramaphosa for Opportunity to Visit South Africa During BRICS Summit
 
The heads of state of the BRICS club of emerging economies (Brazil, Russia, India, China, and South Africa) plan to meet late this summer in Johannesburg and Emmanuel Macron is exploring the possibility of attending the summit, the French newspaper L’Opinion reported, quoting sources.
 
The daily remarks that a meeting of the President of France with the leaders of an organization th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lubomir Tassev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinEx Explains How the Intersection of AI and Web3 Will Revolutionize Crypto]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757d0a8c26</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/coinex-explains-how-the-intersection-of-ai-and-web3-will-revolutionize-crypto/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T05:03:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The emergence of cutting-edge artificial intelligence capabilities has ignited the imagination of business strategists worldwide, urging them to envision the future operations of their respective industries in this era of AI. Simultaneously, the advent of Web3 is transforming our very interaction with the internet, which serves as the foundation of the contemporary global economy. Consequently, it is indisputable that the amalgamation of AI and Web3 will reshape business practices across all sectors, including the realm of cryptocurrencies, and give rise to unprecedented models that were previously inconceivable.
 
The Dawn of Intelligent Blockchains, dApps, Protocols and More
 
CoinEx, the preeminent cryptocurrency exchange boasting a user base of over 5 million worldwide, has recently re…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Egypt Applies for BRICS Membership, Seeks Trade in National Currencies]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757ef2da4f</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/egypt-applies-for-brics-membership-seeks-trade-in-national-currencies/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T03:41:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Egypt has filed an application to join the BRICS bloc, Russia’s ambassador to the Arab nation confirmed. The government in Cairo is interested in using alternative currencies in foreign trade, either national fiats or a new common currency, the diplomat unveiled. 
 
Egypt Takes Step to Join BRICS Club, Russia Backs Bid
 
Egypt has applied to become a member of the BRICS bloc of nations, according to the Russian Ambassador to Cairo, Georgy Borisenko. In an interview with the Tass news agency, the diplomat explained:
 

Egypt has submitted its application to join the BRICS group because one of the endeavors that BRICS is currently pursuing is to shift trade to alternative currencies, be it national currencies or a new common currency. Egypt is very much interested in that.
 
Borisenko also p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lubomir Tassev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OKCoin Accused by FDIC of Making False Claims About Customer Protections]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757efeada4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/06/16/okcoin-accused-by-fdic-of-making-false-claims-about-customer-protections/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T03:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OKCoin must scrub misleading statements that suggest its customers’ accounts are protected by the U.S. Federal Deposit Insurance Corp. (FDIC), the U.S. banking regulator ordered late Thursday, complaining the company is making false claims.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Court Will Rule on Terraform Labs' Push to Dismiss SEC Lawsuit Within a Month]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757efeada0</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/06/16/us-court-will-rule-on-terraform-labs-push-to-dismiss-sec-lawsuit-within-a-month/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T03:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Was UST a security because it was designed for practical uses rather than as an investment?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mercedes-Benz Is Adding ChatGPT to Cars for AI Voice Commands]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144872</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144872/mercedes-benz-adding-chatgpt-cars-ai-voice-commands"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T01:55:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The luxury automaker is set to integrate OpenAI's ChatGPT chatbot into its Mercedes-Benz User Experience (MBUX) feature in the U.S.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Firm Abra Said to be Insolvent in Texas State Regulators’ Cease-and-Desist Order]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757ee5d0ff</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/crypto-firm-abra-said-to-be-insolvent-in-texas-state-regulators-cease-and-desist-order/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T01:40:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to an emergency cease-and-desist order from the Texas State Securities Board, the cryptocurrency firm Abra is “insolvent or nearly insolvent.” The filing alleges that a group of state securities regulators has been investigating Abra, and the working group interviewed William Barhydt, the company’s founder, in March 2023.
 
Texas State Regulators Issue Cease-and-Desist Order, Citing Insolvency Claims Against Crypto Firm Abra
 
The Texas State Securities Board (TSSB) has issued an emergency cease-and-desist order against the company Abra and its network of subsidiaries. The notice alleges that Abra and its affiliate companies are “collectively insolvent or nearly insolvent.” The order also named Plutus Financial, Plutus Lending, Abra Boost, and the firm’s founder, William John “Bi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlockFi Sues State Commission for Not Accepting Its Surrendered License]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144879</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144879/blockfi-sues-connecticut-banking-commission"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T01:23:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bankrupt crypto exchange wants to surrender its license, but regulators are insisting on what BlockFi says would be an expensive court proceeding.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Mover Asia: Hong Kong as Crypto Hub? The City's Strict Banking Requirements May Be an Obstacle]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757ee2a242</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/06/16/first-mover-asia-hong-kong-as-crypto-hub-the-citys-strict-banking-requirements-may-be-an-obstacle/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T00:42:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Hong Kong-based entrepreneur says that while the digital assets regulation is "overall friendly," banking regulations will make the industry's growth there difficult. ALSO: Bitcoin surges post-BlackRock iShares ETF filing but the rally sputters.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds, James Rubin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinEx Exchange Banned In New York, Authorities Recover $1.7 Million]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757eecf7a1</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/coinex-banned-in-new-york-recover-1-7-million/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T00:14:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Attorney General Letitia James has issued a ban on CoinEx, a Hong Kong-based cryptocurrency exchange, prohibiting its operations within the state of New York. The ban follows an announcement on June 15 revealing that the exchange’s funds, totaling over $1.7 million, were seized.
 
The seizure was conducted due to allegations of CoinEx’s failure to register as a securities and commodities brokerage, as required by regulation in the United States. A proposed settlement was recently filed in a New York state court in Manhattan, awaiting the judge’s approval.
 
 
The settlement outlines the terms and conditions for CoinEx, the Hong Kong-based cryptocurrency exchange. Specifically, the exchange would be barred from offering, selling, or purchasing securities and commodities in New York.
 
Furth…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>anushsamal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock Files Bitcoin ETF Application, Leveraging Coinbase Custody]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757eef3efc</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/markets/blackrock-nears-filing-bitcoin-etf-application-leveraging-coinbase-custody"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T23:50:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock, the worlds largest asset manager, has filed an application for a spot Bitcoin ETF (exchange-traded fund). 
In their pursuit of a Bitcoin ETF, BlackRock has chosen Coinbase Custody as their trusted custodial solution. The proposed ETF will be benchmarked against indices provided by CF Benchmarks. The indices will be comprised of price data from six exchanges: Coinbase, Kraken, Gemini, Bitstamp, itBit, and LMAX Digital.
It is worth noting that the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), the regulatory authority responsible for overseeing ETFs in the United States, has thus far rejected every application for a spot bitcoin ETF. Nevertheless, the commission has granted approval for several bitcoin futures ETFs, which have been successfully introduced for trading.
BlackRock's filing for a spot Bitcoin ETF signals a turning point in the industry, as a prominent player in the traditional financial space acknowledges the potential of Bitcoin. If approved, the Bitcoin ETF would open doors to a new wave of adoption and provide investors with an unprecedented opportunity to participate in the Bitcoin market through a regulated and accessible investment vehicle.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nik Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Token Sale Ahead: Celsius to Convert Customer ‘Altcoins’ to BTC and ETH]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757ee86f48</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/token-sale-ahead-celsius-to-convert-customer-altcoins-to-btc-and-eth/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T23:37:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amid the regulatory crackdown in the United States, the bankrupt crypto lender Celsius has announced that all of its customers’ “altcoins” will be converted to bitcoin (BTC) and ethereum (ETH). Over $215 million worth of coins such as CEL, ADA, LINK, LTC, and others will be sold beginning on July 1, 2023.
 
Celsius Plans to Convert 15 Different Tokens to Bitcoin and Ethereum
 

 
In mid-February 2023, Celsius announced it would be acquired by Novawulf Digital Management to execute the reorganization plan. The firm filed its plan on June 15, and as per the latest revisions, customers who possess “altcoins” will have their balances converted to BTC and ETH on July 1. The only accounts exempted from this conversion are the “custody and withhold accounts.”
 

 
“Celsius will be selling all alt…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mark Cuban Predicts Crypto Apocalypse: 90% Of Companies Will Go Broke]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757eea8462</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/billionaire-mark-cuban-predicts-crypto-apocalypse/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T23:15:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tech behemoth Mark Cuban and former Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) official John Reed Stark engaged in a heated exchange over the ongoing regulatory crackdown on the crypto industry. 
 
The discussion was sparked by the recent temporary restraining order (TRO) hearing against Binance, which sought to freeze all of the exchange’s U.S. assets.
 
 
Cuban And Stark Clash Over Judge’s Remarks In Binance Case
 
Cuban argued that not all crypto businesses with tokens or considering using tokens are large “enterprises,” as Stark had assumed. He pointed out that most crypto applications are small, with only a few people involved. 
 
He also shared his experience of a small company that had called the SEC for guidance on getting registered. The response they received was to review some cas…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alchemy's ChatGPT Plugin Enables Easier Blockchain Analysis Via AI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144856</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144856/alchemy-chatgpt-ai-plugin-enables-easier-blockchain-analysis"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T23:02:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alchemy’s new GPT-4 plugin harnesses the power of AI to deliver user-friendly, real-time blockchain analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["AI Is Game-Changing But Needs Fact-Checking": AlchemyAI Project Lead]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/HXlThlXv/ai-is-game-changing-but-needs-fact-checking-alchemyai-project-lead</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/HXlThlXv/ai-is-game-changing-but-needs-fact-checking-alchemyai-project-lead"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this interview, Decrypt's Jason Nelson chats with Alchemy product manager and AlchemyAI project lead Elan Halpern on blockchain analysis using ChatGPT, what AI means for better user experience, and the need to fact-check AI. Halpern also gives a demo of the new AlchemyAI ChatGPT plugin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Banned In New York, CoinEx Returns $1.7 Million to Settle Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144820</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144820/banned-in-new-york-coinex-returns-1-7-million-to-settle-lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T22:50:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New York Attorney General Letitia James announced a $1.7 million settlement with Hong Kong-based CoinEx over securities violations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prometheum: What You Need to Know About the SEC’s Poster Child for Crypto Compliance]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144833</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144833/prometheum-sec-poster-child-crypto-compliance"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T22:21:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prometheum's co-CEO gave remarks on Capitol Hill that mirrored the SEC's stance. Now industry observers are poring over the startup’s paper trail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitch's New Favorite Game 'Only Up' Is Loaded With Goblintown NFT Art]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144815</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144815/twitch-new-game-only-up-goblintown-nft"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T21:31:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More than 100,000 simultaneous viewers watched streamers play clumsy climbing game Only Up, which is packed with Goblintown references.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock Files Bitcoin ETF Application With the SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144782</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144782/blackrock-filing-bitcoin-etf-application-soon-reports"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T21:28:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock, with Coinbase as its partner, has submitted an application for a spot Bitcoin ETF following a Thursday morning report.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jack Dorsey's Block Bitcoin Wallet Opens Beta, Announces Coinbase Support]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144825</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144825/jack-dorseys-block-bitcoin-wallet-opens-beta-announces-coinbase-support"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T21:05:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitkey will allow beta users to withdraw Bitcoin from Coinbase and Cashapp using "copy and paste."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFT Artwork Owned by Three Arrows Capital Sells for $6.2 Million at Sotheby's]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144816</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144816/nft-artwork-owned-three-arrows-capital-sells-6-2-million-sothebys"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T20:37:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ringers #879, a.k.a. "The Goose," sold for over $6.2 million with fees at today's Sotheby's Grails: Part II live auction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[As Crypto Burned Stateside, NFT Believers Partied Through the Night in Lisbon]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144748</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144748/crypto-burned-stateside-nft-believers-partied-through-night-lisbon"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T19:22:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC's actions against the largest crypto exchanges were barely a footnote during the NFT extravaganza at NFC Lisbon in Portugal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former FTX Ventures Head Amy Wu Turns to AI After Being 'Duped' by SBF]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144795</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144795/former-ftx-ventures-head-amy-wu-turns-to-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T18:26:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite a dark episode at FTX Ventures, Wu has now joined Menlo Ventures to help spearhead its investments in AI and consumer tech.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Colombia’s Central Bank Taps Ripple to Pilot CBDC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144799</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144799/colombia-central-bank-ripple-cbdc"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T18:15:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Colombia already makes use of Ripple's technology for land distribution efforts in the country.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Devs Cry Foul on Uniswap v4 'Open Source' Promises]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144802</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144802/ethereum-devs-cry-foul-on-uniswap-v4-open-source-promises"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T17:54:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's a few licenses that Ethereum devs consider the mark of a truly open source project. The one Uniswap chose for its v4 isn't one of them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD Debuts AI Chip to Challenge Nvidia]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144788</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144788/amd-debuts-ai-chip-to-challenge-nvidia"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T17:29:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company's new MI300X AI Chip will be a direct competitor to the dominance of Nvidia's H100.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Heads East as Huobi HK Launches Trading Service in Hong Kong]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142955</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142955/crypto-heads-east-as-huobi-hk-launches-trading-service-in-hong-kong"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T17:25:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Huobi has joined the Hong Kong Virtual Assets Consortium (HKVAC), while its Hong Kong arm now offers crypto spot trading and virtual asset custody.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Whale Moves $1.2 Million After 13 Years of Inactivity]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144786</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144786/bitcoin-whale-moves-million-after-13-years"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T16:53:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some long-term investors are moving their stashes after years of remaining dormant.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arbitrum's New 'Layer-3' Xai Network Is Built to Power Web3 Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144775</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144775/arbitrums-new-layer-3-xai-network-built-power-web3-games"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T16:01:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dedicated gaming network Xai is launching with support from Offchain Labs, with games like Final Form and LAMOverse up first.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fedi's Bitcoin Federations Could Onboard Next 1 Billion Users, Says CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144599</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144599/fedis-bitcoin-federations-could-onboard-next-1-billion-users-says-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T14:21:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fedi CEO Obi Nwosu has big plans for kickstarting Bitcoin adoption via a unique, Lightning-powered community app called "Federations."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cyber Criminals Are Turning to Crypto Mining Pools to Wash Ill-Gotten Funds: Chainalysis]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144762</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144762/cyber-criminals-are-turning-crypto-mining-pools-wash-ill-gotten-funds-chainalysis"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T13:01:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ransomware actors are increasingly trying to pass off their own funds as proceeds received from cryptocurrency mining, claims Chainalysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Artificial Intelligence (AI) Take Over Your Job?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137047</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/will-artificial-intelligence-take-over-your-job-decryptu"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T10:39:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jobs requiring human ingenuity or creativity, or which rely heavily on social and emotional skills, might be the safest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Reiff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum, Cardano, and Dogecoin Lead Weekly Crypto Losses]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144741</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144741/ethereum-cardano-dogecoin-lead-weekly-crypto-losses"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T09:59:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After the largest altcoins, Bitcoin is also shedding value as the crypto market continues to digest yesterday’s fed notes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried Trial Can Proceed on Original Charges Only, Says DoJ]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144740</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144740/sam-bankman-fried-trial-can-only-proceed-original-charges-says-doj"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T09:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Government is willing to wait a bit longer to try the FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried on several additional counts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alys Key</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether CTO Says 'Let Them Come' as Stablecoin's Dollar Peg Wobbles]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144735</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144735/tether-cto-says-let-them-come-stablecoin-peg-wobbles"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T08:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the market's largest stablecoin waffling, the Tether CTO took to Twitter to assure investors that redemptions won't be a problem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Take AI Warnings Seriously, Says UN Secretary-General]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144692</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144692/take-ai-warnings-seriously-un-secretary-general"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T23:54:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The official called for the creation of something akin to the International Atomic Energy Agency to regulate AI tech.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Republicans Continue to Defend Crypto in Latest Letter to SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144671</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144671/republicans-continue-to-defend-crypto-in-letter-to-sec"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T23:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[House Financial Services Committee leaders warned that the SEC’s suggested new definition of “exchange” would hurt innovation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Bad Like Brooklyn Dancehall' Brings Shaggy and Jamaican Culture to Tribeca]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144614</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144614/bad-like-brooklyn-dancehall-brings-shaggy-jamaican-culture-tribeca"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T22:54:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The documentary, executive produced by musician Shaggy, debuted at the Tribeca Film Festival with help from Decentralized Pictures.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Gold Rush: Generative AI Poised to Pump $4.4 Trillion Into Global Economy Annually]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144684</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144684/ai-gold-rush-generative-ai-4-trillion-into-global-economy-annually"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T22:53:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Generative AI could be a major player in the AI industry as a whole, which could be worth $15.7 trillion by 2030.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Miami's 'Bitcoin Mayor' Will Challenge Donald Trump for US President]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144682</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144682/miamis-bitcoin-mayor-files-to-run-for-u-s-president"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T22:08:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Francis X. Suarez has been an outspoken advocate of cryptocurrency since taking office in 2017.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Leaders Praise Draft GOP Bill, Dems Raise Concerns]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144663</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144663/crypto-leaders-praise-draft-gop-bill-dems-raise-concerns"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T21:37:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Congress invited crypto executives to testify on a bill that some say may undermine the SEC]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Lender Delio Freezes Withdrawals Citing 'Market Volatility']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144675</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144675/crypto-lender-delio-freezes-withdrawals-citing-market-volatility"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T21:01:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Delio is the second South Korean platform to suspend withdrawals this week after Haru Invest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prime Trust Partner Banq Files for Bankruptcy Following BitGo Deal]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144672</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144672/prime-trust-partner-banq-files-for-bankruptcy-following-bitgo-acquisition-deal"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T20:55:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prime Trust is set to be acquired by BitGo after a period of "garbage" spending last summer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unleash ChatGPT: The Top 7 Plugins You Should Know in 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144661</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144661/unleash-chatgpt-the-top-7-plugins-you-should-know-in-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T20:32:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT plugins integrate other apps into the OpenAI chatbot, enhancing it with diverse, user-friendly AI features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fractal Is Like an Arcade, Says Twitch Co-Founder Justin Kan]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/6r6Mdwt6/fractal-is-like-an-arcade-says-twitch-co-founder-justin-kan</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/6r6Mdwt6/fractal-is-like-an-arcade-says-twitch-co-founder-justin-kan"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Justin Kan was a co-founder of Twitch and now works on Fractal, a Web3 gaming startup. Kan tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about his new company and what he's up to.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Mobile Puzzle Game Earns You Bitcoin or Ethereum for Playing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144601</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144601/this-mobile-puzzle-game-earns-you-bitcoin-ethereum-playing"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T20:23:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[REVIEW: Stack sats or eke out ETH in Ethereum Blast, a solid but simplistic (and ad-heavy) iOS and Android puzzle game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Trade Sideways as Fed Skips Rate Hike]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144620</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144620/bitcoin-ethereum-trade-sideways-fed-skips-rate-hike"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T19:48:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s the first time the Fed has not raised rates at a meeting in 18 months.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Set to Leave Cyprus Ahead of MiCA Legislation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144595</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144595/binance-moves-to-deregister-cyprus-entity-ahead-of-mica-legislation"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T19:13:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The exchange said it's looking to focus elsewhere in Europe—and “will continue to comply with applicable laws of the European Union."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['NFTs Can't Scale' in Current Form, Say Superduper Co-founders]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144579</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144579/nfts-cant-scale-current-format-say-superduper-founders"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T16:44:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At this year’s NFC, the Superduper founders stressed that getting NFTs to mass adoption won’t be easy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Hard Fork to Stave Off SEC? Devs Say It's Not Happening]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144576</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144576/solana-hard-fork-devs-say-its-not-happening"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T15:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“I work on the largest Solana project, with more than 10 developers, and nobody is discussing [a hard fork]” said Matías Kudelski, a cyber security researcher who audits Solana’s code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Firms Should Start Preparing for MiCA ‘Now–Maybe Even Yesterday’: Chainalysis]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144572</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144572/crypto-firms-should-start-preparing-mica-now-maybe-even-yesterday-chainalysis"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T13:49:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MiCA comes into effect next year, but that doesn't mean crypto firms should wait to become compliant, said Chainalysis' EU policy lead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alys Key</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are NFTs the Next SEC Target?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/YaGgY87J/are-nfts-the-next-sec-target</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/YaGgY87J/are-nfts-the-next-sec-target"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T20:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin discusses the current regulatory climate in the U.S. with Gala Games' President of Blockchain Jason Brink.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Collab.Land Co-Founder Said There Was No ‘Aha Moment’ When Launching DAO Toolkit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/kcBRKFGk/collabland-co-founder-said-there-was-no-aha-moment-when-launching-dao-toolkit</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/kcBRKFGk/collabland-co-founder-said-there-was-no-aha-moment-when-launching-dao-toolkit"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T09:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CCO and co-founder of Collab.Land Anjali Young explained at this year’s NFC Lisbon the origins of the crypto community tool kit, which industry niches are turning to its suite of products, and what’s next for the project since its token distribution event last February.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Buying a Slice of H.R. Giger's 'Alien' Is Fine Art, Not Memorabilia: Particle CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/VACG0WVg/buying-a-slice-of-hr-gigers-alien-is-fine-art-not-memorabilia-particle-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/VACG0WVg/buying-a-slice-of-hr-gigers-alien-is-fine-art-not-memorabilia-particle-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T08:49:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With H.R. Giger's original "Alien" statue on full display at this year's NFC Lisbon, Particle CEO Harold Eytan told Decrypt that owning an NFT-ified slice of the piece isn't just for fans of the iconic creature and movie series but also for fine art collectors. Interested in owning a piece? Be prepared to cough up half an ETH for one of the 500 tranches of the digitized sculpture.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Community Co-Creation 'Is a Big Step for Fashion Brands' Entering the Metaverse: BNV Founder and CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/z6NSMnNm/community-co-creation-is-a-big-step-for-fashion-brands-entering-the-metaverse-bnv-founder-and-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/z6NSMnNm/community-co-creation-is-a-big-step-for-fashion-brands-entering-the-metaverse-bnv-founder-and-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T08:49:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The founder and CEO of metaverse fashion platform BNV Richard Hobbs said big brands are still nervous to let fans and community members customize their favorite garments. Still, he believes that as long as you can meet a firm's commercial bottom lines while stirring engagement, there's nothing to lose.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Standard Crypto VC Co-Founder on NFTs and Their Stigma in Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/bmtrrLio/standard-crypto-vc-co-founder-on-nfts-and-their-stigma-in-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/bmtrrLio/standard-crypto-vc-co-founder-on-nfts-and-their-stigma-in-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T18:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alok Vasudev is a co-founder of venture capital firm Standard Crypto. In an interview with Decrypt's Kate Irwin, he shares his thoughts on NFT marketing, NFT utility in gaming, and the stigma that pervades the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ava Labs Announces Avalanche Arcad3 for Game Developers at 3XP]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XPHp9r4j/ava-labs-announces-avalanche-arcad3-for-game-developers-at-3xp</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XPHp9r4j/ava-labs-announces-avalanche-arcad3-for-game-developers-at-3xp"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T15:21:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ava Labs Head of Gaming Ed Chang shares news with Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the crypto firm's latest push to help traditional game developers break into blockchain gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Like a Middle Finger to Western Culture’: YuYu Unpacks Inspiration Behind NFT Expo GAG]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Vuoplr6a/like-a-middle-finger-to-western-culture-yuyu-unpacks-inspiration-behind-nft-expo-gag</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Vuoplr6a/like-a-middle-finger-to-western-culture-yuyu-unpacks-inspiration-behind-nft-expo-gag"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T13:33:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At this year’s NFC Lisbon, multimedia artist and photographer YuLiang "YuYu" Liu broke down how themes from traditional painting and BDSM informed his latest NFT exhibition called “GAG.” He also shared exclusively with Decrypt a yet-to-be-launched drop for fans of his work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Competition Was Rather Low' in Mobile Wallet Space, Says Zerion Head of Growth]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/vCg8O2oy/competition-was-rather-low-in-mobile-wallet-space-says-zerion-head-of-growth</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/vCg8O2oy/competition-was-rather-low-in-mobile-wallet-space-says-zerion-head-of-growth"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T13:33:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zerion's move to launch a mobile-first crypto wallet not only helped NFT users swap jpegs on the go but was also a play to get away from crypto's desktop-centric user experience. And with such little competition, Zerion's head of growth Alexander Guy told Decrypt at NFC Lisbon it's managed to rake in 150,000 funded wallets. Next step? Taking on MetaMask and contending as a browser-extension wallet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘We’ve Never Seen Anything Like This in VR’, Says The Sandbox COO on Apple’s Vision Pro Headset]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/GQ29RaHw/weve-never-seen-anything-like-this-in-vr-says-the-sandbox-coo-on-apples-vision-pro-headset</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/GQ29RaHw/weve-never-seen-anything-like-this-in-vr-says-the-sandbox-coo-on-apples-vision-pro-headset"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T13:33:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Sandbox COO Sebastien Borget told Decrypt at this year’s NFC Lisbon that despite the high price point, Apple’s new VR headset is nonetheless “groundbreaking.” And though the tech giant never used the term “metaverse” in its reveal, Borget is sure that the technology will be key in growing participation in various digital worlds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Gala Safe? Gala Games Head of Blockchain on GALA, Crypto, and SEC Regulatory Turmoil]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5bcrE8nL/is-gala-safe-gala-games-head-of-blockchain-on-gala-crypto-and-sec-regulatory-turmoil</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5bcrE8nL/is-gala-safe-gala-games-head-of-blockchain-on-gala-crypto-and-sec-regulatory-turmoil"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T15:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gala Games President of Blockchain shares his thoughts on the GALA token upgrade and the latest SEC turmoil with Decrypt's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Artists Adopting NFTs Has Been ‘Really Market Dependent’, Says NFT Club Berlin’s Rebekka Revel]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/QKlIVlj3/artists-adopting-nfts-has-been-really-market-dependent-says-nft-club-berlins-rebekka-revel</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/QKlIVlj3/artists-adopting-nfts-has-been-really-market-dependent-says-nft-club-berlins-rebekka-revel"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T15:07:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Getting non-crypto artists to make the leap into Web3 comes in ebbs and flows according to the market’s bear and bull waves, says co-founder of NFT Club Berlin and Superteam Germany Rebekka Revel. But she’s hoping to change that by changing the narrative around digital collectibles, regardless of the market, one word at a time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big Brands Exploring Web3 to ‘Scale Up Their Super-fan Base’: Superduper Co-founder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/he6UzJwz/big-brands-exploring-web3-to-scale-up-their-super-fan-base-superduper-co-founder</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/he6UzJwz/big-brands-exploring-web3-to-scale-up-their-super-fan-base-superduper-co-founder"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T14:49:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Co-founder and co-CEO of Web3 media brand Superduper Dom Smith says big brands are eager to enter the space—they just don’t know how. Still, they all maintain a thesis of turning their communities into “super fans” that generate value for users as well as a firm’s bottom line.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How 1 Simple Question Kickstarted Performance Artist Foodmasku's Plunge Into NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/w86DMn3p/how-1-simple-question-kickstarted-performance-artist-foodmaskus-plunge-into-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/w86DMn3p/how-1-simple-question-kickstarted-performance-artist-foodmaskus-plunge-into-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T10:10:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As his food mask creations went viral on the Internet during the COVID lockdowns, reposted on TikTok and Instagram without his consent, he soon asked: "How do I protect my digital files?" Performance artist Foodmasku describes at this year's NFC Lisbon how that simple question spiraled into a minting collection after collection of his edible works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arianee CEO Pegs Wine and Spirits as Next 'Exciting' Industry to Make Web3 Leap]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Bo2NeG9Z/arianee-ceo-pegs-wine-and-spirits-as-next-exciting-industry-to-make-web3-leap</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Bo2NeG9Z/arianee-ceo-pegs-wine-and-spirits-as-next-exciting-industry-to-make-web3-leap"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T09:28:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CEO and co-founder of Arianee Pierre Nicolas Hurstel unpacks the wide spectrum of digital collectibles from 10,000 PFP collections to access passes for exclusive events. And with an unannounced big brand soon joining, Hurstel revealed at NFC Lisbon which kind of NFTs big brands are moving towards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why 'Words With Friends' Creator Paul Bettner is 'Allergic' to Pay-to-Win NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JkfOleb4/why-words-with-friends-creator-paul-bettner-is-allergic-to-pay-to-win-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JkfOleb4/why-words-with-friends-creator-paul-bettner-is-allergic-to-pay-to-win-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T20:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Words With Friends and Wildcard creator Paul Bettner tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about his perspective on what to do when NFTs become in-game characters and assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitch Co-Founder Justin Kan: 18 Months is 'Several Decades' in Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rKVvsPFb/twitch-co-founder-justin-kan-18-months-is-several-decades-in-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rKVvsPFb/twitch-co-founder-justin-kan-18-months-is-several-decades-in-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fractal and Twitch co-founder Justin Kan gives Decrypt's Kate Irwin an update on all things Fractal and his perspective on blockchain technology in gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Playing for Money in Web3 Games Not 'Durable,' Says Fractal's Justin Kan]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MQG3SaBM/playing-for-money-in-web3-games-not-durable-says-fractals-justin-kan</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MQG3SaBM/playing-for-money-in-web3-games-not-durable-says-fractals-justin-kan"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twitch and Fractal co-founder Justin Kan and Fractal co-founder Dan Borstelmann share their perspectives on Web3 gaming's changing landscape with Decrypt's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Cyber Cafe to Web3: How Everquest Dev Jeffrey Butler Got Into Game Development]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/hRlI4WXe/from-cyber-cafe-to-web3-how-everquest-dev-jeffrey-butler-got-into-game-development</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/hRlI4WXe/from-cyber-cafe-to-web3-how-everquest-dev-jeffrey-butler-got-into-game-development"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T14:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everquest developer turned Avalon Chief Product Officer Jeffrey Butler tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how he got into game development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>