<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-05-21T19:13:29.082Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-05-21T19:13:29.082Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gala Games says it resolved exploit within 45 minutes, identified culprit]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19509702/Gala-Games-says-it-resolved-exploit-within-45-minutes-identified-culprit</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19509702/Gala-Games-says-it-resolved-exploit-within-45-minutes-identified-culprit"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T19:06:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gala Games said it responded swiftly to the significant security breach on May 20 that resulted in the unauthorized sale of $21 million worth of GALA tokens and the “effective burn” of an additional 4.4 billion tokens. The exploit has highlighted vulnerabilities within the project’s internal...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC’s Feedback Propels Ethereum ETF Listings Closer To Approval, Insiders Claim]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7426ee6aa6</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/secs-feedback-ethereum-etf-closer-to-approval/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T19:02:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a move that has the crypto community buzzing, the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has asked major exchanges to refine their applications for spot Ethereum ETFs. 
 
According to a Reuters report, sources familiar with the process say this request is interpreted as a positive signal that the regulator may be ready to greenlight these long-awaited products.
 
Ethereum ETF Approvals Inch Closer
 
The exchanges in question – Nasdaq, CBOE, and NYSE – have been working on submissions to list Ethereum ETFs provided by asset managers like VanEck and ARK Investments/21Shares. Typically, such regulatory feedback from the SEC precedes approval rather than rejection. 
 
“The SEC’s engagement with the exchanges on the ether ETF filings is a surprising and encouraging development for the c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Whistleblowing In The Surveillance Age]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19509698/Whistleblowing-In-The-Surveillance-Age</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19509698/Whistleblowing-In-The-Surveillance-Age"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T19:02:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A consideration of the challenges in being a whistlebower in the modern age of omnipresent digital surveillance. From "The Inscription Issue."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC’s Feedback Propels Ethereum ETF Listings Closer To Approval, Insiders Claim]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19509689/SECs-Feedback-Propels-Ethereum-ETF-Listings-Closer-To-Approval-Insiders-Claim</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19509689/SECs-Feedback-Propels-Ethereum-ETF-Listings-Closer-To-Approval-Insiders-Claim"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T19:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a move that has the crypto community buzzing, the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has asked major exchanges to refine their applications for spot Ethereum ETFs. According to a Reuters report, sources familiar with the process say this request is interpreted as a positive signal...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a falling Yen could fuel a crypto market boom, per Arthur Hayes]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19509684/How-a-falling-Yen-could-fuel-a-crypto-market-boom-per-Arthur-Hayes</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19509684/How-a-falling-Yen-could-fuel-a-crypto-market-boom-per-Arthur-Hayes"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T19:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The weakening Japanese Yen could force the US to induce liquidity and fuel a crypto rally.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta, Coinbase, Form Coalition to Tackle Global Online Fraud]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19509678/Meta-Coinbase-Form-Coalition-to-Tackle-Global-Online-Fraud</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19509678/Meta-Coinbase-Form-Coalition-to-Tackle-Global-Online-Fraud"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T18:58:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meta, Coinbase, and other leading players in the technology and crypto industries have formed a new coalition called “Tech Against Scams” to combat scams in dating apps, social media, and crypto. According to a statement released on Tuesday, the group will collaborate to find ways to fight back...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apeiron embraces competitiveness to drive Web3 gaming growth]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19509660/Apeiron-embraces-competitiveness-to-drive-Web3-gaming-growth</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19509660/Apeiron-embraces-competitiveness-to-drive-Web3-gaming-growth"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T18:55:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 game Apeiron announced the start of its Guild Wars tournament on May 21, featuring a $1 million prize pool. The competition will start with different regional online preliminaries up until June 25, followed by an in-person showdown set to happen in Hong Kong in Q3.Frank Cheng, co-founder of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OP_CAT & Bitcoin Ossification With Blockstream’s Andrew Poelstra]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19509664/OP_CAT-Bitcoin-Ossification-With-Blockstreams-Andrew-Poelstra</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19509664/OP_CAT-Bitcoin-Ossification-With-Blockstreams-Andrew-Poelstra"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T18:52:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shinobi interviews Andrew Poelstra, Head of Research, at Blockstream to discuss a plan to restore abandoned script functionalities in Bitcoin. They discuss the introduction of a new costing model, the challenges of adapting script to these new functionalities, and the potential of proposals like...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US lawmaker addresses House before FIT21 vote: Bill ‘will stop another FTX’]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19509655/US-lawmaker-addresses-House-before-FIT21-vote-Bill-will-stop-another-FTX</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19509655/US-lawmaker-addresses-House-before-FIT21-vote-Bill-will-stop-another-FTX"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T18:51:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Representative Wiley Nickel called on Democrats and Republicans to support the bill to stop the SEC from “turning cryptocurrency regulation into a political football.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trader Turns $16K Into $2.8 Million In 10 Months With A Cat-Themed Meme Coin On Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19509700/Trader-Turns-16K-Into-28-Million-In-10-Months-With-A-Cat-Themed-Meme-Coin-On-Ethereum</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19509700/Trader-Turns-16K-Into-28-Million-In-10-Months-With-A-Cat-Themed-Meme-Coin-On-Ethereum"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T18:46:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mog (CRYPTO: MOG), a cat-themed meme coin on Ethereum, spiked 46% on Tuesday, with a trader registering a multi-million dollar unrealized profit read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New York Man Arrested for Swindling $1,300,000 in Scheme Involving Fictitious Crypto Wallet]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19509637/New-York-Man-Arrested-for-Swindling-1300000-in-Scheme-Involving-Fictitious-Crypto-Wallet</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19509637/New-York-Man-Arrested-for-Swindling-1300000-in-Scheme-Involving-Fictitious-Crypto-Wallet"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T18:45:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A New York man pled guilty to fraud charges last week after using various fake crypto and real estate schemes to swindle investors out of more than $1.3 million. Thomas John Sfraga, who went by the alias “T.J. Stone,” defrauded more than a dozen victims, including friends and neighbors,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CFTC Commissioner Summer Mersinger on Overzealous Crypto Regulation and the Need for Legislative Action]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19509654/CFTC-Commissioner-Summer-Mersinger-on-Overzealous-Crypto-Regulation-and-the-Need-for-Legislative-Action</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19509654/CFTC-Commissioner-Summer-Mersinger-on-Overzealous-Crypto-Regulation-and-the-Need-for-Legislative-Action"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T18:44:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The commodities regulator has been clear about the dangers of regulating a burgeoning industry through enforcement actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Democrats To Abruptly Reverse Party Stance on Crypto To Avoid Election Disaster: Mike Novogratz]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19509626/Democrats-To-Abruptly-Reverse-Party-Stance-on-Crypto-To-Avoid-Election-Disaster-Mike-Novogratz</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19509626/Democrats-To-Abruptly-Reverse-Party-Stance-on-Crypto-To-Avoid-Election-Disaster-Mike-Novogratz"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T18:41:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CEO of the crypto investment firm Galaxy Digital says Democrats are changing their tune on crypto as the 2024 US Presidential election approaches. In a new interview with CNBC’s Squawk Box, Mike Novogratz says the Biden administration is listening to the markets and shifting its standpoint...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diamonds Standard Co. uses precious gems to back payment network]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19509619/Diamonds-Standard-Co-uses-precious-gems-to-back-payment-network</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19509619/Diamonds-Standard-Co-uses-precious-gems-to-back-payment-network"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T18:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Diamond Standard Co. has introduced a blockchain payments system that uses diamonds as backing collateral for transactions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gracy Chen Steps in as Bitget CEO: What to Expect Next]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19509621/Gracy-Chen-Steps-in-as-Bitget-CEO-What-to-Expect-Next</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19509621/Gracy-Chen-Steps-in-as-Bitget-CEO-What-to-Expect-Next"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T18:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitget appoints Gracy Chen as CEO, after six years of working with the company to attract new users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ether Futures Surge to Record Highs as Open Interest Tops $14 Billion]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19509657/Ether-Futures-Surge-to-Record-Highs-as-Open-Interest-Tops-14-Billion</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19509657/Ether-Futures-Surge-to-Record-Highs-as-Open-Interest-Tops-14-Billion"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T18:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ether’s open interest futures on centralized exchanges (CEX) have surpassed their previous highs, reflecting increased trading volume. Open interest (OI) measures the aggregated number of open positions in a particular contract, making it a key indicator of market sentiment, liquidity, and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uniswap Labs claims SEC will fail, urges agency to drop enforcement action]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19509600/Uniswap-Labs-claims-SEC-will-fail-urges-agency-to-drop-enforcement-action</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19509600/Uniswap-Labs-claims-SEC-will-fail-urges-agency-to-drop-enforcement-action"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T18:28:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Uniswap Labs has urged the SEC to drop its pending enforcement action against the company. Arguing through a response to the agency's Wells notice, Uniswap Labs CLO Martin Ammori said that the SEC would have to redefine what an exchange is to have jurisdiction over...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Leans Towards Approving Spot Ethereum ETFs, Notifies Exchanges]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19509606/SEC-Leans-Towards-Approving-Spot-Ethereum-ETFs-Notifies-Exchanges</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19509606/SEC-Leans-Towards-Approving-Spot-Ethereum-ETFs-Notifies-Exchanges"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T18:27:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC is reportedly moving towards approving Ethereum ETFs, bringing huge market access for Ether.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum-Based Twitter Rival Farcaster Raises $150 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231644</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231644/ethereum-based-twitter-rival-farcaster-raises-150-million"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T18:26:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Farcaster, a decentralized social media protocol built on Ethereum, just got a sizable infusion of funding as it eyes expansion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SKALE Labs names veteran Andrew Saunders as its new CMO]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19509599/SKALE-Labs-names-veteran-Andrew-Saunders-as-its-new-CMO</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19509599/SKALE-Labs-names-veteran-Andrew-Saunders-as-its-new-CMO"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T18:26:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SKALE Labs, the entity behind the gasless blockchain SKALE, has announced the appointment of Andrew Saunders as its Chief Marketing and Growth Officer. Saunders' previous roles include Global Head of Entertainment and Culture at Amazon, Vice President of Content Innovation and Creative at...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Running The Self-Sovereign Bitcoin Business]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7426eb734e</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/running-the-self-sovereign-bitcoin-business"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T18:26:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As we take the concluding tenth and final step in “10 Steps to Self-Sovereignty”, we’ve articulated nine ways that Bitcoin can enable the sovereign individual. But what about building the sovereign Bitcoin business? From longer timeframe accounting practices to managing a bi-weekly payroll, to using a volatile asset that operates on a 24/7 market, there is no shortage of needed techniques and technologies that enable entrepreneurs to leverage bitcoin for their companies.
As companies delve into the state-change of money that is Bitcoin, they are confronted with a myriad of novel questions and considerations that demand careful attention and strategic planning. From security concerns to regulatory compliance and operational efficiency, managing Bitcoin on a company’s balance sheet requires …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum ETFs may capture only 15% of Bitcoin ETF assets, says Bloomberg analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19509588/Ethereum-ETFs-may-capture-only-15-of-Bitcoin-ETF-assets-says-Bloomberg-analyst</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19509588/Ethereum-ETFs-may-capture-only-15-of-Bitcoin-ETF-assets-says-Bloomberg-analyst"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T18:24:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bloomberg Senior ETF Analyst Eric Balchunas tempered the excitement over spot Ethereum exchange-traded funds (ETFs), suggesting they may attract only a fraction of the investments seen in Bitcoin ETFs. On May 20, reports indicated a 75% chance that the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC)...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fantasy.Top Creators to Receive Nearly 600 ETH in Rewards]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19509584/FantasyTop-Creators-to-Receive-Nearly-600-ETH-in-Rewards</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19509584/FantasyTop-Creators-to-Receive-Nearly-600-ETH-in-Rewards"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T18:20:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Heroes featured in the on-chain trading card game have collectively earned almost 600 ETH, but not everyone is happy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Standard Chartered Now Expects SEC to Approve Spot Ethereum ETFs This Week]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7426d50439</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/standard-chartered-now-expects-sec-to-approve-spot-ethereum-etfs-this-week/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T18:15:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Standard Chartered Bank has revised its forecast and now expects the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to approve spot ethereum exchange-traded funds (ETFs) this week, with the bank’s head of digital asset research expressing 80% to 90% confidence. He estimates potential inflows of $15 billion to $45 billion into ether within the first year […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Nyan Heroes’ Launches Solana Token, Up 27% as Airdrop Claims Open]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231632</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231632/nyan-heroes-launches-solana-token-airdrop-claims-open"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T18:09:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana hero shooter Nyan Heroes launched its NYAN token as the current Epic Games Store play-to-airdrop campaign continues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum’s Massive Surge Imminent: Standard Chartered Predicts ETF Approval And $8,000 Price Target]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7426d6faf1</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereums-massive-surge-imminent-standard-chartered/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T18:01:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amid the buzz and anticipation, Standard Chartered, a British cross-border bank, has projected that Ethereum spot ETFs will likely be approved by the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) this week.
 
According to the bank, the approval of these spot ETFs could catalyze significant market inflows, with estimates ranging from $15 billion to $45 billion in the first year alone.
 
Additionally, this anticipated influx of capital is expected to substantially boost Ethereum’s market dynamics, potentially driving its price toward the $8,000 mark by the end of 2024.
 
 
Implications Of Ethereum ETFs Approval:
 
Notably, the bullish outlook from Standard Chartered is supported by the imminent deadlines for the first round of spot Ethereum ETFs, with VanEck’s deadline on May 23 and Ark Invest…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Biden Administration Is Easing Up on Crypto (a Vibes Analysis)]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7426d6f9ae</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/opinion/2024/05/21/the-biden-administration-is-easing-up-on-crypto-a-vibes-analysis/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T18:01:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A wave of positive regulatory developments for crypto could be coincidence. Or they could be the Biden Administration reacting to Donald Trump’s recent embrace of the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Kuhn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop Who? Ethereum ETF Hype Sends Crypto Memes Flying]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231627</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231627/gamestop-who-ethereum-etf-hype-sends-crypto-memes-flying"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T17:52:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meme coins are hitting record highs on one of crypto’s biggest days in recent memory, with Ethereum's PEPE setting a new peak price.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uniswap Labs Urges SEC to Drop Pending Enforcement Action in Wells Response]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7426d0a2b0</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/05/21/uniswap-labs-urges-sec-to-drop-pending-enforcement-action-in-wells-response/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T17:50:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Uniswap Labs moved Tuesday to quash a looming regulatory battle over Ethereum's dominant decentralized crypto exchange, imploring the Securities and Exchange Commission in legal filings that its planned lawsuit wasn't worth the fight.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cheyenne Ligon, Danny Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BREAKING: SEC Primed To Approve Ethereum ETFs This Week, Report Claims]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7426d22831</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/breaking-sec-primed-approve-ethereum-etfs-this-week/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T17:40:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a significant departure from their previous skeptical stance, US regulators are reportedly leaning toward approving the long-awaited spot Ethereum ETFs for the second-largest cryptocurrency by market capitalization. 
 
SEC Staff Signals Spot Ethereum ETFs Approval
 
According to a report by Barron’s, the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) staff communicated to exchanges on Monday that they are leaning towards approving these products. 
 
 
The agency has provided comments and guidance on the ETF applications, and if the “outstanding issues” are resolved in time, approvals could be granted as early as this week.
 
Furthermore, the SEC’s recent engagement with exchanges further underscores the regulator’s consideration of spot Ethereum ETFs. The commission reportedly contacted th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dismantling The Cash-flow Narrative: Real Estate vs. Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7426d3b06c</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/markets/dismantling-the-cash-flow-narrative-real-estate-vs-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T17:31:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin sceptics frequently argue that bitcoin lacks intrinsic value, claiming that investments like real estate, with their tangible cash flows, are superior. 
In this article, I will debunk the myth of 'intrinsic value' and illustrate why cash flow has no direct impact on an asset's ability to serve as a reliable store of value, even in the context of real estate.

The myth of intrinsic value
The idea that value is inherently embedded in objects is a misconception. This common belief, influenced by the labor theory of value (LTV) - a flawed concept used in classical economics, Marxism and modern economic theories, which posits that value is inherently tied to labor, energy invested or output, misinterprets how value is perceived in the economy. This belief extends to real estate, with th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leon Wankum</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ecash Makes Bitcoin (And Fiat) Private With Calle’s Cashu]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7426d3b05f</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/ecash-makes-bitcoin-and-fiat-private-with-calle-cashu"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T17:31:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Editor’s note: Cashu is a protocol, not a company.
Founders: Calle
Date Founded: October 2022
Location of Headquarters: Remote
Amount of Bitcoin Held in Treasury: N/A
Number of Employees: 20-30 open-source developers
Website: https://cashu.space/
Public or Private? N/A
Of Bitcoin’s many notable properties, privacy isn’t one of them.
In fact, the transparency of the Bitcoin blockchain contrasts starkly with the privacy that Chaumian ecash, a form of digital cash created by legendary cryptographer Dr. David Chaum in 1982, offers.
So, what do these two technologies have to do with one another?
Well, 40 years after the invention of ecash and after a failed attempt to integrate it into the traditional financial infrastructure in the 1990s, a developer who goes by the pseudonym “Calle” found a p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Frank Corva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Short Liquidations Near $300 Million as Bitcoin and Ethereum Prices Spike]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231619</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231619/crypto-short-liquidations-near-300-million-bitcoin-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T17:07:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Short traders are “swimming against the tide” before an incoming second wave of ETF demand, says one Glassnode analyst.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Second Ethereum Foundation Researcher Acknowledges Advisory Deal Paid in EIGEN]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7426df55c3</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2024/05/21/second-ethereum-foundation-researcher-acknowledges-advisory-deal-paid-in-eigen/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T17:07:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The news set off a debate on the social-media platform X about whether advising the EigenFoundation might constitute a conflict of interest – given the flagged risks to Ethereum from restaking protocol EigenLayer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Margaux Nijkerk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Farcaster, Blockchain-Based Social Media Startup, Raises $150M, Led by Paradigm]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7426df55b6</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2024/05/21/farcaster-blockchain-based-social-media-startup-raises-150m-led-by-paradigm/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T17:07:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dan Romero's Farcaster made waves earlier this year with the introduction of "Frames," a feature allowing apps to run within posts, so users don't have to click off to another site.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bradley Keoun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Power the Decentralized Artificial Intelligence Revolution – HyperCycle CEO Toufi Saliba]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7426dfb0c5</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/how-to-power-the-decentralized-artificial-intelligence-revolution-hypercycle-ceo-toufi-saliba/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T17:05:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HyperCycle was founded in October 2022 following discussions between CEO Toufi Saliba and Ben Goertzel, founder of SingularityNet, at the global AGI summit in 2021. The company focuses on developing a General Purpose Technology supporting a decentralized network for AI-to-AI communication, designed to scale with the worldwide demand for AI consumption. Leveraging technologies such as […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Pundit Says Shiba Inu Bullish Pennant Will Push Price To New Highs, Here’s The Target]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7426d83a14</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-bullish-pennant/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T17:02:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A crypto analyst has predicted a massive bull rally for doggy-themed cryptocurrency, Shiba Inu (SHIB). The analyst points to a new technical pattern emerging for SHIB, indicating the potential for a surge to new highs. 
 
SHIB Sets Sights For Next Upside Target
 
A crypto and Bitcoin analyst identified as ‘Clifton Fx’ on X (formerly Twitter) shared a Shiba Inu/Tether (USDT) price chart depicting the next price target for the popular doggy-themed meme coin. The analyst unveiled a new technical trading pattern exhibited in SHIB’s price movements, emphasizing the meme coin’s price chart was displaying a bullish pennant formation in the daily time frame. 
 
 
 
A bullish pennant formation is a technical pattern that occurs after an uptrend and indicates the potential continuation of the strong…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hex Trust to Launch USDX Stablecoin on Flare, Offering Real-World Yield]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7426d94033</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/hex-trust-to-launch-usdx-stablecoin-on-flare-offering-real-world-yield/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T16:55:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On May 21, 2024, Hex Trust Group announced the introduction of a native stablecoin, USDX, for the Flare network. Hex Trust also revealed that a Clearpool vault, enabling holders to earn a real-world yield, will debut alongside USDX. Hex Trust’s USDX Stablecoin and Clearpool Vault Aim to Enhance Flare’s Defi Ecosystem Founded in 2018, the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gala Games Hacker Returns $23M in ETH; Founder Proposes 'Buy and Burn']]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7426c45a74</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/05/21/gala-games-hacker-returns-23m-in-eth-founder-proposes-buy-and-burn/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T16:36:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gala investor DWF Labs also said that it had purchased 28 million GALA tokens "to alleviate market selling pressures."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 121 - ETHEREUM GOD CANDLES!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/EE1S4Hf4/fomo-hour-121-ethereum-god-candles</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/EE1S4Hf4/fomo-hour-121-ethereum-god-candles"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T16:17:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH ETF suddenly seems likely, flurry of amendments. ETH biggest daily gain ever, gains SOL market cap. ETF approval shifted due to political pressure. ETF approval may come as soon as tomorrow. Squeeze liquidates $230M of shorts. ETH OI hits record of $14B on exchanges. BTC nears ATH amid 6th straight day of ETF inflows. SOL flips ETH in Google search trends. House Democrats will not whip against crypto bills. Anti-crypto FDIC chair Gruenberg to step-down. Grayscale CEO steps down, ETHE discount narrows. Genesis settles for $2B with creditors. Binance to focus launchpad on higher float projects. SEI v2 launch coming next week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Isn't 'Unified' Enough Amid Layer-2 Expansion, Says Vitalik Buterin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231612</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231612/ethereum-isnt-unified-enough-says-vitalik-buterin"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T16:12:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum creator Vitalik Buterin believes the network isn’t "unified"—and that a new guild should be formed to resolve this issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Crypto Startup Says You Can Earn Rewards By Training Its AI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231542</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231542/this-crypto-startup-says-you-can-earn-rewards-by-training-its-ai"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T16:01:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FLock says community engagement and user-generated “quality data” will help decentralized AI compete with big tech.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum ETFs: Here Are All the Applications Awaiting SEC Approval]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230228</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230228/ethereum-etfs-all-applications-awaiting-sec-approval"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T15:50:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many major investment firms hope to get the green light from the SEC to list spot Ethereum ETFs in the U.S. Here's the running list.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Spot Bitcoin ETFs Maintain Momentum With Sixth Day of Positive Gains]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7426cda097</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/us-spot-bitcoin-etfs-maintain-momentum-with-sixth-day-of-positive-gains/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T15:44:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to the latest data, U.S. spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) have experienced positive inflows for six consecutive days. Over this period, the spot bitcoin ETFs attracted a total of $1.186 billion. Ark Invest’s ARKB Tops Inflows as U.S. Bitcoin ETFs Gain $237 Million Spot bitcoin ETFs in the U.S. continued their streak of positive […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum’s Explosion To $3,800 Puts 90% Investors In Profit: Data]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7426ce4b0f</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereums-explosion-3600-90-investors-profit-data/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T15:41:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data shows 90% of all Ethereum investors are now in profit following the sharp surge that the asset’s price has seen beyond $3,800.
 
Ethereum Investors Overwhelming In The Green After ETF Rally
 
According to data from the market intelligence platform IntoTheBlock, ETH’s latest rally has meant that a shift in investor profitability has occurred on the network.
 
To keep track of holder profitability, the analytics firm makes use of on-chain data to find what the average acquisition price or cost basis of each address on the blockchain is.
 
 
If this price is less than the current spot value of the cryptocurrency for any address, then that particular investor is considered to be in profit, or “in the money”, as IntoTheBlock defines.
 
On the other hand, the cost basis being lower…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Will Hit All-Time Highs Amid ETH ETF Approval: Standard Chartered]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231601</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231601/bitcoin-ethereum-all-time-highs-eth-etf-approval-standard-chartered"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T15:28:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum ETFs could get the green light this week, says Standard Chartered—and both Bitcoin and Ethereum will set new high prices as a result.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Derivatives DEX Aevo's Token Jumps 10% as Binance Labs Discloses Investment]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7426c90cd6</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/05/21/crypto-derivatives-dex-aevos-token-jumps-10-as-binance-labs-discloses-investment/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T15:25:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AEVO hit $0.9, its highest price since mid-May. Even so, it's still nearly 70% below where it started trading in March at around $3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Sleuth Ogle Proposes Security-Centric 'Glue' Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7426cb143c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2024/05/21/crypto-sleuth-ogle-proposes-security-centric-glue-blockchain/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T15:14:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The upcoming layer-1 takes a hands-on approach to ensuring project security.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Filip Wielanier: 'Web3 Marketing Is a Win-Win']]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7426b4de2c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2024/05/21/filip-wielanier-web3-marketing-is-a-win-win/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T15:04:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cookie3’s co-founder and CEO explains how Web3 marketing can create a shared economy of users, creators and businesses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff  Wilser</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum ETF Applicants Ditch Staking Language in 'Temporary Concession' to SEC: Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231602</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231602/ethereum-etf-applicants-ditch-staking-temporary-concession-sec"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T14:55:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spot Ethereum ETF filers have removed mentions of staking funds from their registration statements. One analyst says they "bent the knee" to the SEC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Still Above $3,600 as ETF Approval Hopes Swell]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231587</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231587/ethereum-above-3600-etf-approval-hopes"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T08:47:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The late rumor yesterday caused Ethereum trading volume to spike by 219% in the past day, according to Coinglass.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New CryptoPunks NFT Collection Unravels After Backlash to 'Woke' Artwork]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231563</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231563/new-cryptopunks-nft-project-unravels-backlash-woke-artwork"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T03:15:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yuga Labs revealed Nina Chanel Abney's Super Punks World NFT collection Monday, but will "no longer touch" CryptoPunks following backlash.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward,Erika Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['We Messed Up': Gala Games Confirms $240 Million Worth of Tokens Swiped via Exploit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231528</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231528/gala-games-240-million-worth-tokens-swiped-exploit"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T02:04:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An attacker used an exploit to mint and swipe 5 billion Gala Games (GALA) tokens Monday, with the firm calling it an "isolated incident."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Soars 20%, Lifting Arbitrum and Optimism]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231530</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231530/ethereum-arbitrum-optimism-soar-20-percent"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T00:39:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ETH ecosystem is mooning on the renewed belief that an ETF approval is near, and most cryptocurrencies are rising with it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Kawailani Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Is Booming—You Can Earn More by Playing These Free Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=205392</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/205392/bitcoin-booming-you-earn-more-playing-free-games"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T22:53:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATE: With Bitcoin rising again after its recent all-time high surge, here's an expanded list of games that pay out BTC rewards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prometheum's Ethereum Custody Controversy Reignites SEC Security Label Fears]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231468</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231468/prometheums-ethereum-custody-controversy-sec-security-fears"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T22:41:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prometheum's move to offer Ethereum custody services sparked backlash from a crypto advocacy group that claims it's in cahoots with the SEC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Debuts AI PCs That Will ‘Recall‘ Everything You Do]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231509</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231509/microsoft-ai-pc-recall-everything-laptops-tablets"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T22:12:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Redmond tech giant unveiled the “designed for AI” Copilot+ PC that indexes everything displayed on screen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana, Avalanche Soar as Ethereum Price Tops $3,500]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231498</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231498/solana-avalanche-up-bitcoin-over-70k-ethereum-over-3500"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T21:35:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The two top cryptocurrencies are leading a parade of rising coins today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feds Nab Incognito Market Owner Accused of Running World's Biggest Narcotics Shop]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231483</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231483/incognito-market-darkweb-owner-indicted-nyc-arrest"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T20:51:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Taiwanese national was arrested in New York over the weekend, indicted for facilitating $100 million in illicit drug sales on the dark web.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Kawailani Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Hits $70,000 as Crypto Liquidations Top $235 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231480</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231480/bitcoin-price-hits-70000-liquidations-top-235-million"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T20:13:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin is back above $70,000 for the first time in over a month as investors throw money at ETFs again—and hype over Ethereum ETFs grows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Spikes 9% Within Minutes on ETF Approval Rumors]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231481</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231481/ethereum-spikes-etf-approval-rumors"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T19:57:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price of Ethereum jumped by 9% in about 20 minutes on Monday amid fresh speculation that spot ETFs will indeed be approved this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward,André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bored Ape Trader Who Bought 1% of the Supply in January Is Down Nearly $2 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231467</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231467/bored-ape-trader-bought-1-percent-supply-down-2-million"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T19:25:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The once-dominant Ethereum NFT collection continues to shed value. How low can the Bored Ape Yacht Club go?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETFs Are Back With Nearly $1 Billion In Fresh Cash]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231473</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231473/bitcoin-etf-surge-1-billion-btc-above-68000"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T18:37:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price of BTC has risen above $68K and ETF flows last week reflect the rebound, both surging thanks to promising inflation data, one analyst says.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Do A Little With Chikai]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BGCnTbKb/we-do-a-little-with-chikai</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BGCnTbKb/we-do-a-little-with-chikai"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T18:21:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week’s episode, we sit down with our good friend and one of the biggest supporters of the pod, Chikai Ohazama. Chikai is the co-founder of Keyhole which was acquired by Google and became Google Earth. He is one of the most caring art collectors in our space, as well as an extremely talented AI artist.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trading Memes: Dogecoin Still Outperformed GameStop Over the Last Week]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231453</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231453/trading-memes-dogecoin-outperformed-gamestop-gme"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T18:13:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The GameStop stock trading frenzy has faded, but leading meme coin Dogecoin is still in the green over the last week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 120 - SOLANA LEADS THE CHARGE]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/7jrsiszc/fomo-hour-120-solana-leads-the-charge</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/7jrsiszc/fomo-hour-120-solana-leads-the-charge"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T18:08:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SOL again leads majors, DEX volume dwarfs others. BTC whales buys $106M in 24hrs. ETH ETF decision on Thursday or Friday. 5 of 7 onchain indicators ‘point to bull-run’. ETH ETF may be rejected due to weak link to futures. AI coins in focus ahead of Nvidia earnings. Cobie inks new article on low float, high FDV coins. ETH foundation staff reveal links to EigenLayer. 12 L2 & L3s controlled by single multisig. Layer Zero pauses sybil rewards. Aevo to airdrop pre-launch tokens on platform. FTM to migrate one-to-one to Sonic S coin. UK judge rules Craig Wright is not Satoshi.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacker Who Exploited Solana Meme Coin Factory Pump.fun Says He Faces Theft, Conspiracy Charges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231428</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231428/hacker-who-exploited-solana-meme-coin-factory-pump-fun-says-he-faces-theft-conspiracy-charges"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T16:52:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After admitting to being responsible for an exploit which drained $2 million from Pump.fun, the attacker claims to have been arrested.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miners Targeted by Venezuela in Latest Crypto Crackdown]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231450</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231450/bitcoin-miners-targets-venezuela-crypto-crackdown"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T16:40:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Venezuelan authorities have launched a crackdown on Bitcoin miners, and don't want any crypto mining operations to use the energy grid.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI Pulls ‘Horny’ ChatGPT Voice, Denies It's a Scarlett Johansson Knockoff]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231436</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231436/openai-pulls-horny-chatgpt-voice-denies-scarlett-johansson"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T16:20:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATE: The Hollywood actress says OpenAI CEO Sam Altman had tried to get her permission—twice—and that she is “shocked, angered, and in disbelief.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bankrupt Crypto Lender Genesis Agrees to $2 Billion Settlement to Repay Users]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231431</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231431/bankrupt-crypto-lender-genesis-2-billion-settlement"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T15:32:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Genesis will pay a $2 billion settlement to partially repay customers of the firm's bankrupt crypto lending division.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Notcoin? The Telegram-Based Game, NOT Token, and Future Plans]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=223640</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-notcoin-telegram-based-game-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T15:08:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATED: NOT is live and it's 2024's biggest gaming token launch so far. But Notcoin isn't over: Here's what to expect in the game's future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery,Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale CEO Michael Sonnenshein Steps Down]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231425</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231425/grayscale-ceo-michael-sonnenshein-steps-down"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T13:42:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The leading crypto asset manager, Grayscale, has announced its CEO, Michael Sonnenshein, is stepping down.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roaring Kitty Has Stopped Posting. Is This the End of GameStop Mania?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231421</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231421/roaring-kitty-has-stopped-posting-is-this-the-end-of-gamestop-mania"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T13:13:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It appears the GameStop bull has stopped tweeting after the company filed to increase its total number of shares by 15%. Is this the end?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chain of Alliance Game Guide: Getting Started With the Turn-Based RPG]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230997</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230997/chain-of-alliance-game-guide-getting-started-with-the-turn-based-rpg"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain RPG Chain of Alliance sees you assemble a party of Heroes to take on all comers in turn-based battles. Here’s how to play.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 119 - GOOD MORNING BULLS!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ikMRioZH/fomo-hour-119-good-morning-bulls</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ikMRioZH/fomo-hour-119-good-morning-bulls"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T11:02:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SOL leads majors higher again, BTC stable. ETFs see $257M inflow, volumes hit 2 month high. 414 holders of BlackRock ETF ‘blows away record’. SOL continues to be fastest blockage despite usage. Pump. fun exploited for $1.9M by ex-employee. LINK up 20% after partnership with top banks. Senate also repeals SEC crypto rule. US Senator uses laser eyes PFP. Tether mints another $1B USDT. Bitcoin production costs now $45K: JP Morgan. Pink Drainer retires after stealing $85m assets. PancakeSwap to reimburse fees on Uniswap. TON & Tether partnership on payment solution. Trabucco writes character defence of Ryan Salame.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 118 - ARE THE ETFS BACK?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/KJXI4MVU/fomo-hour-118-are-the-etfs-back</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/KJXI4MVU/fomo-hour-118-are-the-etfs-back"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T11:02:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin has best day in 2 months after dovish CPI. ETFs see $300M inflow, highest in weeks. ETH continues to underperform ahead of ETF ruling. Millennium buys $2B of BTC ETF. CME group to launch BTC spot trading. Fed’s Kashkari compares BTC to beanie babies. Tate says he will buy $100M BTC. El Salvador now owns 5750 BTC. Binance creates ‘antidote’ to address poisoning. Tornado Cash developer appeals conviction. China busts $1.9B USDT banking racket. MEV bot operators charged with fraud by DoJ. Swiss to adopt global crypto tax rules. FTX repayments create ‘bullish overhang’ for crypto. SEI up 30% after proposing v2 upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 117 - BITCOIN GAINS ON CPI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JMdi3Lp7/fomo-hour-117-bitcoin-gains-on-cpi</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JMdi3Lp7/fomo-hour-117-bitcoin-gains-on-cpi"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T11:02:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC bounces driven by spot buying. US ETF sees $100M+ inflow for first time in weeks. State of Wisconsin buys $170M of BTC ETF. Vanguard appoints Bitcoin friendly CEO. Coinbase sees billions of BTC leave exchange. BTC to consolidate between $55-75K: Novogratz. SOL beats ETH TEV for first time ever. ETH may be labelled a security by SEC next week. AI & memes the only two positive sectors this week. Crypto hostility led by TradFi: Lubin. Tornado Cash developer guilty of money laundering. Circle shifts legal hope to US ahead of IPO. Cypher developer gambled $300K of customer funds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 116 - ROARING KITTY RETURNS!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cXfQ3AJh/fomo-hour-116-roaring-kitty-returns</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cXfQ3AJh/fomo-hour-116-roaring-kitty-returns"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T11:02:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto falls, stays in range ahead of CPI tomorrow. US ETFs see small net inflow led by Fidelity HK ETFs wipe 2 weeks of inflows in a single day. Bracebridge bought $363m of BTC ETFs. Coinbase has system wide outage. Poloniex hacker sends funds to Tornado Cash. Brazil biggest in LATAM for crypto trading. Biden removes China BTC miner near military base. CertiK patches $5m flaw in Aptos bridge. LayerZero sees 100k bot accounts self-report. DYDX CEO set to leave. Tate sells $500k BTC to buy GME.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Edges Past $67K as Analysts Predict It'll Keep Climbing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231418</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231418/bitcoin-edges-past-67k-as-analysts-predict-itll-keep-climbing"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T10:24:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's growing accumulation of Bitcoin call options for the December 2024 expiry on Deribit, indicating traders' optimism for the year end.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iconic Japanese Soccer Game Captain Tsubasa Launches on Oasys Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231410</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231410/iconic-japanese-soccer-game-captain-tsubasa-launches-on-oasys-blockchain"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T01:05:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a significant development for gaming and soccer fans, the blockchain version of beloved Japanese soccer manga series Captain Tsubasa has officially launched on the gaming-centric blockchain Oasys.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GamingWire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Epik Duck: From Joke to $25 Million Solana Meme Coin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231317</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231317/epik-duck-from-joke-25-million-solana-meme-coin"/>
        <updated>2024-05-19T20:29:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meme coins like EPIK are looking more and more like crypto’s future. Is that good or bad?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week on Crypto Twitter: Roaring Kitty Returns, Pump.fun Attacker Bares All]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231347</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231347/this-week-crypto-twitter-roaring-kitty-gamestop-pump-fun-attacker"/>
        <updated>2024-05-19T16:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dominant personalities stole the narrative this week. Industry leaders also decried the conviction and sentencing of a Tornado Cash developer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Crypto Games: Notcoin Token Launches, GameStop Mania, and NYAN Incoming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231333</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231333/this-week-crypto-games-notcoin-gamestop-nyan"/>
        <updated>2024-05-19T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Catch up on this week’s biggest crypto and NFT gaming news and find some weekend reads in our latest roundup.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Do A Little With  Roger Dickerman]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/F6mt1fXu/we-do-a-little-with-roger-dickerman</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/F6mt1fXu/we-do-a-little-with-roger-dickerman"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T14:38:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week’s episode, we sit down with our good friend and founder of the 24 Hours of Art, Roger Dickerman. We dive into Roger’s background in trading and fitness, his love of art, founding Artifex and 24 Hours of Art, the power of routines, and so much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Do A Little With Funghi]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9USXAFZb/we-do-a-little-with-funghi</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9USXAFZb/we-do-a-little-with-funghi"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T13:44:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week’s episode, we sit down with our good friend and co-founder of Shillr, Funghibull. Funghi is one of our favorite collectors, builders and overall people in the space. 

We dive into Funghi’s background playing rugby, going to medical school in Scotland, 10 gram mushroom trips, finding punks, forming Shillr, and so much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mika Breaks Down Solana Congestion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/5lkvPCM1/mika-breaks-down-solana-congestion</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/5lkvPCM1/mika-breaks-down-solana-congestion"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T10:12:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rug Radio Creator and crypto influencer Mika explains what happened during Solana's Q1 2024 network congestion through Kraken's Learn Center.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mika Explains the Bitcoin Halving]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/f9rUBkUS/mika-explains-the-bitcoin-halving</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/f9rUBkUS/mika-explains-the-bitcoin-halving"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T10:08:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rug Radio Creator and crypto influencer Mika explains the recent Bitcoin halving and how you can build your understanding through Kraken's Learn Center.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Neighbor Alice Season 1 Beta Goes Live]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/sGfYcHuB/my-neighbor-alice-season-1-beta-goes-live</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/sGfYcHuB/my-neighbor-alice-season-1-beta-goes-live"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T09:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rug Radio Creator Orangie plays the new season of multiplayer builder-game My Neighbor Alice and tries out all its features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Leads The Bounce]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QoXLhFzb/solana-leads-the-bounce</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QoXLhFzb/solana-leads-the-bounce"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T11:06:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto up despite ETF outflow, SOL outperforms. HK ETFs also see another net daily outflow. SOL flips ETH again in 24hr DEX volume. SOL revenue now 50% of ETH. Bitcoin above $1m by 2030: Dorsey. Bitcoin & Kucoin get license in India. Kraken tries to get SEC case dismissed. Stand with Crypto sets up election war chest. VIP customers make up two thirds of Binance volume. NOT to launch on Binance & OKX. TON up 20%, speculation it will be listed after NOT. Securitize & BlackRock look to launch on ARB. Franklin Templeton calls for ‘Base season’. EIGEN claims go live today, will be un-transferable. Eclipse founder leaves after harassment claims.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Manhattan’s Newest On-Chain Fashion Store: 9dcc]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Oyjyb2JX/inside-manhattans-newest-on-chain-fashion-store-9dcc</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Oyjyb2JX/inside-manhattans-newest-on-chain-fashion-store-9dcc"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T20:25:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At NFT NYC, Decrypt’s Sander Lutz explored the on-chain fashion brand’s latest pop-up, and spoke to its founder Gmoney about 9dcc’s future expansion plans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BTC Sinks Lower]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rUBpJmbc/btc-sinks-lower</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rUBpJmbc/btc-sinks-lower"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T19:54:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HK ETF volumes disappoint at $11M, crypto sinks. US ETFs see another $52M outflow, 4th straight day. EigenLayer FUD after 5% non-transferable airdrop. EigenLayer also geoblocks USA for claims. 5K+ withdrawals after EigenLayer announcement. Microstrategy bought another $8M BTC in April. Miner revenue drops to 2023 lows. Consensys vs SEC litigation will take years: Cowen. SEC had been investigating ETH for a year. Gensler may have misled Congress with ETH stance.KMNO hits $363M on launch. Decentralised Rune airdrop opens at $102M. Friend Tech airdrop delayed until Thursday. NFTfi airdrop claim today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Very Red Week For Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XVGCQVOH/a-very-red-week-for-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XVGCQVOH/a-very-red-week-for-crypto"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T19:54:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Majors hit locals lows, break key support levels. Liquidations hit $420M, funding remains neutral. ETFs saw $344M withdrawals in April. CZ gets 4-month jail sentence. FTX sells $232M locked SOL at ‘around $100’. Final integration of SOL Firedancer ‘well underway’. SOL, DOGE, XRP open interest down 51% in a month. BlackRock BUIDL largest tokenised treasury fund. Uniswap integrates with Robinhood connect. Stablecoin bill may be coming very soon. Gensler lied to Congress: McHenry. KSI steps back from crypto trading. Coinbase supports Lightning network. BCH creator arrested in Spain. EigenLayer sees 12K queued withdrawals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Full Send]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zCrCMabk/solana-full-send</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zCrCMabk/solana-full-send"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T19:51:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SOL leads majors higher, DEX volume flips ETH. ETH burn rate hits yearly low. BTC needs to reach $67k for a ‘higher high’. Robinhood receives Wells Notice from SEC. Only 10% of stablecoin transactions are real: Visa. May 15th will see corporate filings of BTC purchases. Hayes continues to OTC buy PENDLE. Cartier arrested for USDT money laundering. ENA up 20% on rumours of integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Memecoin Bounce]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yw5MtFvY/memecoin-bounce</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yw5MtFvY/memecoin-bounce"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T19:38:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto volatile but bounces after dovish Fed speech. ETFs see record $563m outflow. BlackRock ETF sees first outflow in 77 days. BlackRock expects more institutions to buy BTC. BNP bank buys BlackRock ETF. BTC continues to sit below STH average cost. Coinbase earnings today. Tether made $4.5bn profit in Q1. MicroStrategy building identity protocol on Ordinals. Dorsey’s Block Inc investigated in US. BlackRock leads investment in RWA firm. STX Nakamoto upgrade delayed by 8 weeks. LayerZero 1st snapshot taken ahead of airdrop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Do A Little With Mike Demarais]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ajrh0oiK/we-do-a-little-with-mike-demarais</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ajrh0oiK/we-do-a-little-with-mike-demarais"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T15:11:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week’s episode, we sit down with our friend and co-founder of Rainbow Wallet, Mike Demarais. We dive into Mike’s background as a software engineer, how he fell into the crypto rabbithole, co-founding Rainbow, important lessons learned from raising capital, and so much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eth Rally Fails]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Gj7TMrbP/eth-rally-fails</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Gj7TMrbP/eth-rally-fails"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T12:45:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto falls, ETH/BTC rally again marks mini sell-off. Yen carry-trade implosion linked to worries. ETH gas fees hit 6-month lows. 3rd straight week of institutional outflows. Slowing BTC ETF flows are just a pause: Bernstein. BTC now on track for 5 red weeks in a row. BTC may have topped, could hit $35k: Brandt. ETFs may become big sellers: Bianco. Consensys list 4 reasons ETH isn’t a security. Rumours continue to grow of EigenLayer airdrop. Perp DEX volumes continue fall, GMX underperforms. Wallets begin to block US users after Samourai case. WLD in reported partnership talks with OpenAI. Large unlocks this week for SUI, PYTH & MEME.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>