<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-12-14T05:14:48.040Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-12-14T05:14:48.040Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Indian Government Provides Update on Crypto Regulation]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748843f1d0</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/indian-government-provides-update-on-crypto-regulation/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T05:12:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Indian government has responded to questions during a parliamentary session regarding crypto regulation in India. The government emphasized the valuable guidance provided by the IMF-FSB synthesis paper presented at the G20 summit, noting that this paper offers a framework for both G20 and non-G20 nations to develop “clearer policies on crypto assets.”
 
Government Provides Indian Crypto Framework Progress Update
 
The Indian government provided some answers on Monday regarding cryptocurrency regulation in India. The Indian government has been grappling with the question of crypto regulation since July 2019, when a draft bill was introduced.
 
Parliament Member Rajeev Shukla asked the Minister of Finance in Rajya Sabha, the upper house of India’s parliament, whether the government “inte…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FASB Confirms 'Fair Value' Approach for Corporate Crypto Holdings]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74884d249d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/12/13/fasb-confirms-fair-value-approach-for-corporate-crypto-holdings/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T05:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Financial Accounting Standards Board, a U.S. entity that details how companies should report assets on their balance sheet, published a standards update on Wednesday that will let corporations recognize "fair value" changes in crypto holdings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not Everything Is Better On-Chain]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19107970/Not-Everything-Is-Better-On-Chain</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19107970/Not-Everything-Is-Better-On-Chain"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T04:40:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A number of on-chain transactions are at times volatile, which could also be impacted by investors selling. Analysts are suggesting a reevaluation in price or a drastic increase in on-chain activity to rectify the metric. However, what we are witnessing is yet another implication of a model...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smart AI Model Boosts Heart Checks – Finding Heartbeat Issues Made Easy]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19107957/Smart-AI-Model-Boosts-Heart-Checks-Finding-Heartbeat-Issues-Made-Easy</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19107957/Smart-AI-Model-Boosts-Heart-Checks-Finding-Heartbeat-Issues-Made-Easy"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T04:39:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers at Scripps Research have unveiled an AI model poised to revolutionize the screening process for atrial fibrillation (AFib). This heart condition, characterized by irregular and rapid heartbeats, poses a significant risk of stroke and heart failure. The newly developed AI model...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brian May Proclaims 2023 as the Last Year of Human Songwriting in the Era of AI Dominance]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19107950/Brian-May-Proclaims-2023-as-the-Last-Year-of-Human-Songwriting-in-the-Era-of-AI-Dominance</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19107950/Brian-May-Proclaims-2023-as-the-Last-Year-of-Human-Songwriting-in-the-Era-of-AI-Dominance"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T04:20:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[legendary Queen guitarist and astrophysicist Brian May predicts that 2023 will mark the culmination of an era where discerning whether a song was crafted by a human or artificial intelligence (AI) becomes nearly impossible. May explores the growing importance of AI in the music industry in a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche Flips Dogecoin To Capture Top 9 Crypto Ranking As Market Cap Hits Past $14B]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19107935/Avalanche-Flips-Dogecoin-To-Capture-Top-9-Crypto-Ranking-As-Market-Cap-Hits-Past-14B</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19107935/Avalanche-Flips-Dogecoin-To-Capture-Top-9-Crypto-Ranking-As-Market-Cap-Hits-Past-14B"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T03:47:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche (CRYPTO: AVAX) has eclipsed Dogecoin (CRYPTO: DOGE) to claim the ninth spot on CoinMarketCap’s leaderboard of the top 100 cryptocurrencies. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain.com Plans to Increase Staff in European Expansion Effort]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19107965/Blockchaincom-Plans-to-Increase-Staff-in-European-Expansion-Effort</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19107965/Blockchaincom-Plans-to-Increase-Staff-in-European-Expansion-Effort"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T03:44:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin exchange and infrastructure provider Blockchain.com is bucking the bear market with a commitment to hire more staff in 2024. Moreover, the company is looking to expand into Europe and emerging markets.  On December 13, Bloomberg reported that Blockchain.com, an early adopter of crypto...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vaneck Expects Bitcoin Price to Reach All-Time High After Donald Trump Wins US Presidency]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7488358d3d</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/vaneck-expects-bitcoin-price-to-reach-all-time-high-after-donald-trump-wins-us-presidency/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T03:31:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Asset management firm Vaneck has predicted that bitcoin’s price will reach an all-time high on Nov. 9, following a “combative election that saw Donald Trump win 290 electoral votes and regain the presidency, raising optimism that the SEC’s hostile regulatory approach will be dismantled.” Vaneck further predicted that Satoshi Nakamoto could be named Time Magazine’s “Man of the Year” if bitcoin hits $100K by next December.
 
Bitcoin’s Next All-Time High Prediction
 
Asset management firm Vaneck has predicted that “bitcoin will make an all-time high” in the fourth quarter of next year. This is one of the firm’s 15 crypto predictions for 2024.
 
“In the second half of 2024, bitcoin will climb a presidential-sized wall of worry,” Vaneck described. “The percentage of the global population voting…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin: Is this cohort to blame for BTC’s correction?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19107900/Bitcoin-Is-this-cohort-to-blame-for-BTCs-correction</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19107900/Bitcoin-Is-this-cohort-to-blame-for-BTCs-correction"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T03:30:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s inability to rally above $44,000 was due to the profit-taking activity of its short-term holders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum, Dogecoin Surge As Fed Predicts 2024 Rate Cuts: Analyst Foresees 'Bounce' For King Crypto, Predicts $50K Levels]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19107901/Bitcoin-Ethereum-Dogecoin-Surge-As-Fed-Predicts-2024-Rate-Cuts-Analyst-Foresees-Bounce-For-King-Crypto-Predicts-50K-Levels</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19107901/Bitcoin-Ethereum-Dogecoin-Surge-As-Fed-Predicts-2024-Rate-Cuts-Analyst-Foresees-Bounce-For-King-Crypto-Predicts-50K-Levels"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T03:07:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cryptocurrency market experienced mixed trading on Wednesday evening, largely influenced by the Federal Reserve’s (Fed) announcement of potential interest rate cuts in the upcoming year. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Integration of Crypto and TradFi]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19107844/The-Integration-of-Crypto-and-TradFi</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19107844/The-Integration-of-Crypto-and-TradFi"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T02:04:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the Bitcoin Spot ETF gets closer and closer, NLW covers a number of stories relating to the growing integration of crypto into the mainstream financial system. Today's Sponsor: KrakenKraken: See what crypto can be - https://kraken.com/TheBreakdownEnjoying this content?SUBSCRIBE to the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DEX Volume In Crypto: November Sees $29 Billion Surge, Yet CEXs Hold 97% Market Grip]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74883df0e7</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dex-volume-in-crypto-november-sees-29-billion-surge/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T02:03:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite decentralized exchanges (DEXs) emerging as pivotal players in the crypto world, recent reports indicate a significant shift in their market share relative to centralized exchanges (CEXs). According to the latest analysis by crypto analytics firm Kaiko, DEX trading volumes experienced a notable increase in November, reaching $29 billion.
 
This resurgence marks a recovery from the multi-year low observed in September, yet it remains a stark contrast to the all-time high of approximately $124 billion recorded in May 2021, according to Kaiko.
 
 
The Shift In Crypto Market Share: DEX Vs. CEX
 
The rise in DEX trading volume, while substantial, seems less influenced by major platforms such as Uniswap and Curve on the Ethereum blockchain and PancakeSwap on the BNB Chain, which have show…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DEX Volume In Crypto: November Sees $29 Billion Surge, Yet CEXs Hold 97% Market Grip]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19107841/DEX-Volume-In-Crypto-November-Sees-29-Billion-Surge-Yet-CEXs-Hold-97-Market-Grip</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19107841/DEX-Volume-In-Crypto-November-Sees-29-Billion-Surge-Yet-CEXs-Hold-97-Market-Grip"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T02:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite decentralized exchanges (DEXs) emerging as pivotal players in the crypto world, recent reports indicate a significant shift in their market share relative to centralized exchanges (CEXs). According to the latest analysis by crypto analytics firm Kaiko, DEX trading volumes experienced a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Bankruptcy Judge Takes Step to Shorten Timeline for Customers' Recoveries]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74883e4467</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/12/14/ftx-judge-takes-step-to-shorten-timeline-for-ftx-customers-recoveries/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T01:59:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A federal judge took steps to end a protracted dispute between FTX and its largest creditor at a bankruptcy hearing, signaling the court could try to speed up efforts to recover FTX customer's funds from the failed crypto firm's estate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Napolitano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto and Mainstream Markets Rally After Fed Foreshadows 2024 Interest Rate Cuts]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19107817/Crypto-and-Mainstream-Markets-Rally-After-Fed-Foreshadows-2024-Interest-Rate-Cuts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19107817/Crypto-and-Mainstream-Markets-Rally-After-Fed-Foreshadows-2024-Interest-Rate-Cuts"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T01:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Federal Reserve leaves interest rates unchanged for now]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s Resilience Shines Amidst Price Correction – Bulls Eye $44,000 Breakout]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19107798/Bitcoins-Resilience-Shines-Amidst-Price-Correction-Bulls-Eye-44000-Breakout</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19107798/Bitcoins-Resilience-Shines-Amidst-Price-Correction-Bulls-Eye-44000-Breakout"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T01:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s price experienced a 5% dip within the last 24 hours, settling at $41,645 on...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Postpones Verdict on Invesco Galaxy Ethereum ETF Until 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19107840/SEC-Postpones-Verdict-on-Invesco-Galaxy-Ethereum-ETF-Until-2024</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19107840/SEC-Postpones-Verdict-on-Invesco-Galaxy-Ethereum-ETF-Until-2024"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T01:18:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC has opted to extend the deadline to February 6, 2024, to approve or deny the application for the Invesco Galaxy Ethereum ETF. Cboe BZX Exchange recently submitted a proposed rule change to the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) concerning the listing and trading of shares for the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2023 Will Be the ‘Last Year You’ll Know A Song Was Written by a Human’: Queen Guitarist]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209761</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209761/2023-will-be-the-last-year-youll-know-a-song-was-written-by-a-human-queen-guitarist"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T01:16:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Legendary guitarist and astrophysicist Brian May reflects on AI's current and future impact on the music industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2023 Will Be the ‘Last Year You’ll Know A Song Was Written by a Human’: Queen Guitarist]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19107794/2023-Will-Be-the-Last-Year-Youll-Know-A-Song-Was-Written-by-a-Human-Queen-Guitarist</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19107794/2023-Will-Be-the-Last-Year-Youll-Know-A-Song-Was-Written-by-a-Human-Queen-Guitarist"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T01:16:13.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Layer-1 Coins Like Solana Outperform Layer-2 and DeFi Tokens: Will This Continue In 2024?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74883b9efc</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/layer-1-solana-outperform-layer-2-defi-tokens/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T01:02:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the current bull run, a curious trend has emerged: layer-1 coins like Solana (SOL), Avalanche (AVAX), and Cardano (ADA) are outperforming layer-2 tokens like Arbitrum (ARB) and decentralized finance (DeFi) assets like Uniswap (UNI) and MakerDAO (MKR). 
 
Layer-1 Tokens Like Solana Leads The Performance Chart
 
Taking to X on December 13, Thor Hartvigsen, a data-driven decentralized finance (defi) researcher, noted that layer-1 coins under observation, like AVAX and SOL, are, on average, up 50% in the past month. 
 
On the other hand, layer-2 coins like ARB and OP and DeFi tokens, like UNI and DYDX, are trailing, only adding around 10% during the same period. 
 
 
Overall, the broader crypto market is on an uptrend, edging higher, with some, like Solana (SOL) and Bitcoin (BTC), completel…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dalmas Ngetich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple-Backed Flare Network Launches New Airdrop for WFLR Token Holders]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19107781/Ripple-Backed-Flare-Network-Launches-New-Airdrop-for-WFLR-Token-Holders</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19107781/Ripple-Backed-Flare-Network-Launches-New-Airdrop-for-WFLR-Token-Holders"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T01:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Flare network, a layer-1 Ethereum Virtual Machine-compatible blockchain, has announced the release of a new FlareDrop, part of an ongoing series of FLR token distributions. This latest batch is now available for users who have maintained a holding of Wrapped FLR (WFLR) for a minimum of 23...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Gaming Altcoin Rallies As Massive Whale Withdraws From Binance: On-Chain Data]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19107785/Ethereum-Gaming-Altcoin-Rallies-As-Massive-Whale-Withdraws-From-Binance-On-Chain-Data</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19107785/Ethereum-Gaming-Altcoin-Rallies-As-Massive-Whale-Withdraws-From-Binance-On-Chain-Data"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T01:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto’s Silver Lining: Market Dips Are Stepping Stones To Soaring Heights – Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19107782/Cryptos-Silver-Lining-Market-Dips-Are-Stepping-Stones-To-Soaring-Heights-Analyst</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19107782/Cryptos-Silver-Lining-Market-Dips-Are-Stepping-Stones-To-Soaring-Heights-Analyst"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T01:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Layer-1 Coins Like Solana Outperform Layer-2 and DeFi Tokens: Will This Continue In 2024?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19107778/Layer-1-Coins-Like-Solana-Outperform-Layer-2-and-DeFi-Tokens-Will-This-Continue-In-2024</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19107778/Layer-1-Coins-Like-Solana-Outperform-Layer-2-and-DeFi-Tokens-Will-This-Continue-In-2024"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T01:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We are SICK and TIRED #bitcoin #crypto #shorts]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19107783/We-are-SICK-and-TIRED-bitcoin-crypto-shorts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19107783/We-are-SICK-and-TIRED-bitcoin-crypto-shorts"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T01:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're sick and tired of getting screwed over by the money printer, then buy bitcoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BITCOIN OR GOLD? (part 1) #bitcon #crypto #shorts]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19107784/BITCOIN-OR-GOLD-part-1-bitcon-crypto-shorts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19107784/BITCOIN-OR-GOLD-part-1-bitcon-crypto-shorts"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T01:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB) Golden Cross Invalidated? Price Makes Unexpected Move]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19107786/Shiba-Inu-SHIB-Golden-Cross-Invalidated-Price-Makes-Unexpected-Move</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19107786/Shiba-Inu-SHIB-Golden-Cross-Invalidated-Price-Makes-Unexpected-Move"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T01:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Meets With Blackrock, Fidelity, Franklin Templeton, and Grayscale to Discuss Their Spot Bitcoin ETF Applications]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7488256f83</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/sec-meets-with-blackrock-fidelity-franklin-templeton-and-grayscale-to-discuss-their-spot-bitcoin-etf-applications/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T00:43:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has held multiple meetings with spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) issuers regarding their applications. “The SEC is busier than Santa’s elves,” said a Bloomberg ETF analyst, noting that Blackrock, the world’s largest asset manager, recently met with the SEC three times.
 
More Spot Bitcoin ETF Issuers Meeting With SEC
 
The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) recently held meetings with four different issuers regarding their spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) filings.
 
Bloomberg analyst James Seyffart shared on social media X Tuesday that Blackrock, the world’s largest asset manager, returned to the SEC on Monday for the third time in recent weeks to discuss its spot bitcoin ETF application. He noted that the securitie…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do Kwon’s Detention Prolonged Until 2024 As Montenegro Responds To Extradition Requests]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748820bd31</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/montenegro-extends-terra-founder-do-kwon-until-2024/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T00:11:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to an International Business Times report, Montenegro’s Supreme Court decided to extend the detention of TerraForm Labs founder and CEO Do Kwon until February 2024, following extradition requests from the United States and South Korea.
 
Closed-Door Discussions Reveal Montenegro’s Plan For Do Kwon
 
Initially set to be extradited to the US on December 15, Do Kwon’s fate turned when the Montenegrin High Court ruled to prolong his stay until February 15, 2024. 
 
The decision stems from charges related to the collapse of the TerraUSD stablecoin, which led to significant financial losses.
 
The High Court had previously ordered Kwon’s extradition by Friday, but his defense team appealed the decision in the appellate court in Podgorica, the capital of Montenegro. 
 
The Montenegrin C…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI Joins Rolling Stone Publisher to Merge AI With Journalism]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209754</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209754/openai-joins-rolling-stone-publisher-to-merge-ai-with-journalism"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T00:08:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Readers get better summaries, and LLMs get more training data—could AI enhance journalism while disrupting it?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bounces Over $43K, Altcoins, Crypto Stocks Burst Higher as Fed Projects Rate Cuts Next Year]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74882cf530</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/12/13/bitcoin-bounces-over-43k-altcoins-crypto-stocks-burst-higher-as-fed-projects-rate-cuts-next-year/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T23:31:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[tktk]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Lords of Light' NFT Game Studio Raini Reveals New Owners, RST Token on Beam]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209730</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209730/lords-light-nft-game-studio-raini-reveals-new-owners-launches-rst-token-beam"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T23:29:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Raini Studios is now part of a joint venture, and the firms have already begun development on a new unannounced combat game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Meme Coin BONK Hits Another All-Time High Ahead of Coinbase Listing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209745</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209745/solana-meme-coin-bonk-hits-another-all-time-high-ahead-of-coinbase-listing"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T23:10:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BONK bounces back, jumping 21% on the day after top exchange Coinbase said it would list the Solana token on Thursday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Dogecoin Rising Above $0.11 Is Important For A DOGE Rally]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74882819f2</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-0-11-doge-rally/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T23:01:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin is still following the same trajectory as the broader crypto market which is being led by Bitcoin. On its own, Dogecoin has also seen some significant negative headwinds as large sell-offs sent its price spiraling down by another 8%. However, this may not be for long if the meme coin is able to break through this crucial level.
 
Dogecoin Must Invalidate Bears Above $0.11
 
In a post on X (formerly Twitter), crypto analyst Ali Martinez explained the complex scenario that the Dogecoin price has encountered. The analyst starts out by showing that the meme coin had flashed a sell signal this week, as evidenced by the price decline between Sunday and Monday.
 
 
This sell signal was observed by the crypto analyst using the TD Sequential on the DOGE weekly chart. The altcoin is already…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Best Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CFTC Pushes FTX-Inspired Rule to Protect Customers' Money]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748828eb70</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/12/13/cftc-pushes-ftx-inspired-rule-to-protect-customers-money/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T22:54:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Commissioners took a step toward requiring derivatives clearing organizations, a key type of middleman in the industry, to keep their customers' money segregated from their own funds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De, Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anonymous Crypto Interests Bombard Key Senator Sherrod Brown With Political Ads]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748828eb5f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/12/13/anonymous-crypto-interests-bombard-key-senator-sherrod-brown-with-political-ads/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T22:54:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Sen. Sherrod Brown (D-Ohio), the chairman of the Senate Banking Committee, is arguably the most important lawmaker currently standing in the way of a crypto regulation bill, and industry interests have paid for a new campaign in his own back yard to nudge him.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protocol Village: Immutable zkEVM Will Allow Developers to 'Abstract' Transaction Fees]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74882b96f8</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/12/13/protocol-latest-tech-news-crypto-blockchain/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T22:29:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest in blockchain tech upgrades, funding announcements and deals. For the period of Dec 14-Dec. 20, with live updates throughout.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bradley Keoun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Social Giant Line Raises $140 Million for NFT Push, 'Brown and Friends' Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209736</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209736/social-giant-line-raises-140-million-nft-push-brown-friends-games"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T22:26:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Japanese messaging firm Line is advancing its NFT plans with a raise led by Crescendo, with Line Friends crypto games in the works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Analyst Says XRP Will Be A Market Leader In The Bull Run, Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748815d1d9</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/xrp-market-leader-bull-run/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T22:08:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The potential of XRP to be a top performer in the next bull run has been one that has been widely discussed in the crypto space. The token’s growth which was stunted in the 2020-2021 bull run due to Ripple’s fight with the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) seems to be back on a good trajectory and is expected to carry on into the upcoming bull run. One crypto analyst in particular, Ben Armstrong, has given reasons why the XRP price will lead the market gains in the bull market.
 
XRP Is Primed To Lead The Bull Run
 
Crypto analyst Ben Armstrong, popularly known in crypto spaces as BitBoy Crypto, has listed the reasons that he believes the XRP token will be a market leader in the next bull run. The next bull run is expected to take place between 2024 and 2025, and Armst…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Tether Killer? A True Stablecoin Would Enhance Banking and Crypto]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7488169aed</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/12/13/the-tether-killer-a-true-stablecoin-would-enhance-banking-and-crypto/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T22:02:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A U.S. dollar pegged stablecoin backed only by cash in a bank could help expand the money supply without causing inflation and improve the banking sector, attorney Daniel Wheeler argues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Wheeler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No Gas for Gamers: Ethereum Scaler Immutable zkEVM Will Let Developers Cover Fees]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=205906</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/205906/no-gas-gamers-ethereum-scaler-immutable-zkevm-developers-cover-fees"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T22:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eliminating transaction fees will make blockchain games more accessible and appealing to mainstream gamers, Immutable believes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Bitcoin Billionaire' Who Supposedly Offered Rubi Rose $430K in BTC Says It Was All a Hoax]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209696</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209696/bitcoin-billionaire-who-supposedly-offered-rubi-rose-430k-btc-says-hoax"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T21:48:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[He says he’s just a humble dogsitter for porn stars, who had no idea what he was getting into when he got a call from Rubi Rose's agents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. CFTC Approves Bitcoin Futures Platform Bitnomial's Derivatives Clearing Application]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7488113af1</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/12/13/us-cftc-approves-bitcoin-futures-platform-bitnomials-derivatives-clearing-application/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T21:38:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Commodity Futures Trading Commission granted crypto derivatives company Bitnomial approval to register as a derivatives clearing organization in the U.S., letting it settle margined futures and options contracts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nigerian Central Bank Warns Counterfeiters as Residents Reportedly Grapple With Cash Shortages]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7488113d11</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/nigerian-central-bank-warns-counterfeiters-as-residents-reportedly-grapple-with-cash-shortages/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T21:38:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Nigeria grapples with cash shortages, the country’s central bank warned of the presence of counterfeit, higher-denomination naira banknotes. The bank has urged members of the public to report anyone suspected of falsifying or counterfeiting the banknotes. 
 
Central Bank Collaborates With Nigerian Agencies
 
The Central Bank of Nigeria (CBN) has issued a warning to residents of the West African nation to be on the lookout for counterfeit naira banknotes that are circulating “in food markets and other commercial centres across major cities in the country.” The bank has warned that individuals caught falsifying or counterfeiting the banknotes face a prison term of no less than five years.
 
 
Press Release: Beware of Counterfeit Naira Banknotes in Circulation. pic.twitter.com/CWxGDyiSmZ
 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Assets Triumph As Commodities, But Face Regulatory “Turf War,” Says US CFTC Chair]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74881825b6</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/us-cftc-chair-affirms-crypto-assets-as-commodities/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T20:37:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the ongoing clash between regulatory bodies over the classification and regulation of the crypto industry, CFTC Chair Rostin Behnam has added fuel to the fire by stating that most crypto assets are commodities under existing laws. 
 
However, Behnam also acknowledged the existence of a “turf war” between regulatory bodies regarding the oversight of the cryptocurrency industry.
 
CFTC And SEC Clash Over Crypto Regulation
 
In an interview with CNBC’s Squawk Box, Behnam highlighted that many tokens are considered commodities under current law, providing some regulatory clarity on the status of crypto assets in the United States. 
 
A major challenge in regulating digital assets is the ongoing jurisdictional battle between regulators, particularly the SEC and CFTC. Behnam acknowledged this…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitter User Finds Critical Bug That Could Have Wrecked Your X Account—And Gets Banned for It]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209707</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209707/twitter-user-finds-critical-bug-that-could-have-wrecked-your-x-account-and-gets-banned-for-it"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T20:14:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every account was just one click away from a takeover, but the person who reported it has been dropped from the bug bounty program.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum's Buterin Floats Prospect of Taking Some Layer-2 Functions Back on Main Chain]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7488047ea1</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/12/13/ethereums-buterin-floats-prospect-of-taking-some-layer-2-functions-back-on-main-chain/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T20:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin, a member of the Ethereum Foundation's executive board, once pushed "layer-2" networks as a way to provide faster and cheaper transactions. Now he's got ideas for "enshrining" some of those functions on the main chain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bradley Keoun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Protocol: Crypto Spring Is Airdrop Season With Tokens From Starknet, LayerZero]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748804c1e3</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/12/13/the-protocol-crypto-spring-is-airdrop-season-with-tokens-from-starknet-layerzero/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T19:58:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week's issue of The Protocol newsletter, we're covering Worldcoin's latest update, airdrop season, the new Bitcoin wallet from Jack Dorsey's company and the "data availability" network Celestia's market-moving plan to plug into Polygon's blockchain development kit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bradley Keoun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Above $42K Again as Fed Holds Interest Rates Steady]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209693</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209693/bitcoin-above-42k-again-fed-holds-interest-rates-steady"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T19:35:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The FOMC "decided to maintain the target range for the federal funds rate at 5.25% to 5.5%."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SCENE's Person of the Year: Ghostwriter]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209633</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209633/scene-2023-person-of-the-year-ghostwriter-ai-drake-weeknd"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T19:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shadowy producer Ghostwriter's AI-augmented song "Heart on My Sleeve" upended the music industry, AI discourse, and American politics. How?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ubisoft Reveals Mint Date for Free 'Champions Tactics' Ethereum NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209641</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209641/ubisoft-reveals-mint-date-free-champions-tactics-ethereum-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T18:51:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A free mint is coming soon for Ubisoft’s first original NFT game. Here's a look at Champions Tactics: Grimoria Chronicles and its NFT plans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rainbow Wallet Teases Airdrop on Ethereum in 'Fox Hunt' Against MetaMask]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209663</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209663/rainbow-wallet-teases-airdrop-ethereum-fox-hunt-against-metamask"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T18:32:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rainbow's new points program aims to lure away MetaMask users with rewards based on Ethereum wallet activity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Meme Coin BONK Down 11% After Coinbase Reveals Plans to List]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209654</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209654/solana-meme-coin-bonk-down-after-coinbase-listing-plans"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T18:11:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A week after BONK set a new all-time high and flipped the Elon Musk-themed coin FLOKI, it's looking sluggish after yesterday's Coinbase announcement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To AI: Best AI Tools for Writers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209639</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209639/how-to-ai-best-ai-tools-for-writers"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T18:03:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While some scribes are scared of artificial intelligence, tools like Grammarly and Hemingway are helping many with grammar, creativity, and productivity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cantor Fitzgerald CEO 'Fan' of Tether, Bullish on Bitcoin Halving]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209640</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209640/cantor-fitzgerald-ceo-tether-bullish-bitcoin-halving-etf"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T17:52:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Howard Lutnick dismissed other cryptocurrencies as “make believe” and lauded Bitcoin’s “uncontrollable” nature.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3AC Liquidators Question Su Zhu in Court Over Hunt for Billions of Dollars in Assets]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209618</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209618/3ac-liquidators-question-su-zhu-in-court-over-hunt-for-billions-of-dollars-in-assets"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T14:46:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lawyers for 3AC liquidator Teneo are attempting to recover $1.3 billion from Zhu and 3AC co-founder Kyle Davies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Pushes to Dismiss SEC Lawsuit With Flurry of Filings]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209595</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209595/binance-pushes-to-dismiss-sec-lawsuit-with-flurry-of-filings"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T12:24:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto exchange Binance argued that its $4.3 billion settlement with regulators should not be included in the SEC's case.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Goes Phygital, Borrowing From Digital Fashion Playbook]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209569</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209569/trump-goes-phygital-borrowing-digital-fashion-playbook"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T01:49:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former U.S. President Donald Trump has embraced a popular digital fashion trend in his latest NFT collection. What's next?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Packs Power Into Its New Small AI Model Phi-2]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209570</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209570/microsoft-phi-2-ai-small-language-model"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T01:04:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Size isn’t everything in artificial intelligence language models, as Redmond’s latest release stands up to challengers 25 times its size.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FIFA Will Mint Soccer NFTs on Polygon—But Isn't Ditching Algorand]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209556</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209556/fifa-mint-soccer-nfts-polygon-isnt-ditching-algorand"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T23:42:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The FIFA+ Collect platform will continue to launch NFTs on Algorand, but the soccer giant is also expanding to Polygon via drops on OpenSea.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral AI Picks ‘Mixture of Experts’ Model to Challenge GPT 3.5]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209540</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209540/mistral-ai-picks-mixture-of-experts-model-to-challenge-gpt-3-5"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T23:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fresh from a fundraising round at a $2 billion valuation, the French startup tout its LLM's strengths against established rival OpenAI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Checkmate: Immortal Game Ditches Chess NFTs, Crypto Token Over 'Heavy Cheating']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209533</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209533/checkmate-immortal-game-ditches-chess-nfts-crypto-token-over-heavy-cheating"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T22:58:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After raising millions from crypto investors, the Immortal Game chess platform will no longer support its token or "play-to-earn" elements.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What 'The Merge' Means for Decrypt, Rug Radio and You]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209525</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209525/what-the-merge-means-for-decrypt-rug-radio-and-you"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T21:16:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt is merging with Rug Radio with plans to change the way “crypto media” is done. You’ve got questions, we’ve got answers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Guillermo Jimenez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Demand $2 Million in Bitcoin After Stealing Insomniac Games Data: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209478</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209478/hackers-demand-2-million-in-bitcoin-after-stealing-insomniac-games-data-report"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T20:47:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sony has said it's investigating the breach after a hacking group reportedly stole data about employees and the upcoming Wolverine game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump Is Selling More NFTs—And the Original Sets Are Crashing Again]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209514</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209514/donald-trump-selling-more-nfts-original-sets-crashing-again"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T20:30:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two words: Cyborg Trump. Former U.S. President Donald Trump goes back to the well on NFTs, and prices are falling yet again.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emerge 2023 Person of the Year: OpenAI CEO Sam Altman]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209445</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209445/emerge-2023-person-of-the-year-openai-ceo-sam-altman"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T19:40:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The man who had the most infamous firing and re-hiring in corporate history shaped a juggernaut of a new global industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock Bitcoin ETF Shifts Risk to Crypto Market Makers, Not Banks]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209451</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209451/blackrock-bitcoin-etf-risk-crypto-market-makers-banks"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T19:02:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An SEC memo shares new details of a late November meeting the Commission held with BlackRock to discuss the asset manager's pending Bitcoin ETF application.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KuCoin Leaving New York After $22M NYAG Settlement—But Won't Call Ethereum a Security]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209479</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209479/kucoin-leaving-new-york-after-22-million-nyag-settlement-wont-call-ethereum-security"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T18:35:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto exchange KuCoin will offer users $16.7 million in refunds, and will owe a further $5.3 million to the Office of the Attorney General.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Is Down—But These Altcoins Are Soaring]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209440</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209440/bitcoin-price-down-altcoins-soaring"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T16:47:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin may have retraced ground, but APT, ATOM, and other alts are on the rise today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Electronic Music Duo Disclosure Drop AI-Powered NFTs on Beatport]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209363</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209363/electronic-music-duo-disclosure-drop-ai-powered-nfts-beatport"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T16:01:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grammy-nominated electronic music duo Disclosure are releasing NFTs that each offer a different, AI-generated take on one of their songs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche Flips Dogecoin Market Cap With Double-Digit Surge]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209423</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209423/avalanche-flips-dogecoin-market-cap-with-double-digit-surge"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T14:04:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche has risen to become the 10th biggest cryptocurrency by market capitalization, overtaking meme coin Dogecoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Champions Arena is Ushering In a ‘New Generation’ of In-Game NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207871</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207871/champions-arena-is-ushering-in-a-new-generation-of-in-game-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T14:01:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following its launch on Gala Games, OneUniverse’s turn-based mobile battler is pioneering next-gen NFT tech.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ultra Reveals First Digital PC Game That Can Be Resold via NFT License]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209425</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209425/ultra-reveals-first-digital-pc-game-resold-nft-license"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T14:01:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A 'Web2' action game previously released via Steam and console systems will be the first tradable digital PC title on Ultra.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[El Salvador's Bitcoin 'Volcano Bonds' Receive Regulatory Approval for Q1 2024 Issuance]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209418</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209418/el-salvadors-bitcoin-volcano-bonds-receive-regulatory-approval-for-q1-2024-issuance"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T12:07:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[El Salvador's planned Bitcoin bonds have received approval from its Digital Assets Commission, paving the way for their issuance in 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['My Neighbor Alice' Launches New Game Season on Chromia After BNB Migration]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209399</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209399/my-neighbor-alice-game-migrates-bnb-chain-chromia-new-season"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T12:01:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the run-up to Chromia’s mainnet launch, players can move their NFTs from BNB Chain and play new Season 4 content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating peaceful money & taking over your local government w/ Joseph Schiarizzi]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zb0VG27G/creating-peaceful-money-taking-over-your-local-government-w-joseph-schiarizzi</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zb0VG27G/creating-peaceful-money-taking-over-your-local-government-w-joseph-schiarizzi"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T23:23:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week our host Reza Jafery is joined by Joseph Schiarizzi, founder of OpenDollar and prolific solidity developer. 


We discuss: 
- Onchain beer
- Taking over your local government
- His Emmy and 3 patents?!?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INTERVIEW: Ember Sword CEO Says NFT Games Are More 'Transparent']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/M9OHCVpA/interview-ember-sword-ceo-says-nft-games-are-more-transparent</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/M9OHCVpA/interview-ember-sword-ceo-says-nft-games-are-more-transparent"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T21:58:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ember Sword CEO Mark Laursen shares why some big game studios "irk" him—and why he got into game development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Director Jordan Bayne on the State of Film3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZLoEDkL9/director-jordan-bayne-on-the-state-of-film3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZLoEDkL9/director-jordan-bayne-on-the-state-of-film3"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T00:11:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the 2023 Film3 Summit, Jordan Bayne—director and founder of The Squad—spoke with Decrypt's Sander Lutz about how the Film3 world has progressed over the last year and what decentralized technologies can offer to creators that want to buck the Hollywood system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Questions With SCENE: Phil Mohun]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TwOjXfOR/5-questions-with-scene-phil-mohun</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TwOjXfOR/5-questions-with-scene-phil-mohun"/>
        <updated>2023-12-01T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bright Moments co-founder Phil Mohun joins 5 Questions With SCENE to recount some favorite moments from the road, including negotiating with Patagonian gauchos, falling in love with Tokyo, and gaining a newfound appreciation for shrooms chocolate bars.

Shot and edited by Vincent Roazzi Jr.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are NFTs Ever Coming Back?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qLmFpNKE/are-nfts-ever-coming-back</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qLmFpNKE/are-nfts-ever-coming-back"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T18:38:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this weeks episode we sit down with Cashtro from Arcade.xyz to discuss NFTs, shitcoins, what collections have held onto their floor prices, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Summit: Will Web3 Gaming Ever be Mainstream?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OvVWhGbW/web-summit-will-web3-gaming-ever-be-mainstream</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OvVWhGbW/web-summit-will-web3-gaming-ever-be-mainstream"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T19:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animoca Brands CEO Robby Yung, EndeavorXR CEO Amy Peck and Gamee co-founder CEO Bozena Rezab joined Decrypt's Stephen Graves on stage at Web Summit to talk about the future of Web3 gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Allie Eve Knox on Spankchain and the life of a Crypto Financial Dominatrix]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/16rVeg6o/allie-eve-knox-on-spankchain-and-the-life-of-a-crypto-financial-dominatrix</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/16rVeg6o/allie-eve-knox-on-spankchain-and-the-life-of-a-crypto-financial-dominatrix"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T21:20:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the first IRL episode of This Time Will Be Different!

In this week's episode, our host, Reza Jafery, is joined by Allie Eve Knox, the Spankchain Chief of Staff and FinDomme. 

They discuss
- How to sell feet pics
- If crypto is really as permissionless as it seems
- the intersections between crypto and sex work]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Questions With SCENE: Jeff Davis]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PChJu1R8/5-questions-with-scene-jeff-davis</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PChJu1R8/5-questions-with-scene-jeff-davis"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artist Jeff Davis joins 5 Questions with SCENE to answer burning questions about his artistic practice, the path that brought him to Art Blocks, and his quietly sophisticated DJ abilities.

Video shot and edited by Vincent Roazzi Jr.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Heatbit Founder Alex Busarov on the Bitcoin Miner That Heats Your Home]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DJuHqcGT/heatbit-founder-alex-busarov-on-the-bitcoin-miner-that-heats-your-home</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DJuHqcGT/heatbit-founder-alex-busarov-on-the-bitcoin-miner-that-heats-your-home"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T18:12:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt joined Heatbit founder Alex Busarov at Web Summit for a walkthrough of the firm's flagship product, a Bitcoin miner that acts as a domestic space heater—aimed at the casual user.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nym CEO Harry Halpin on Privacy, Decentralized VPNs and Tornado Cash]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/aLTtY2aq/nym-ceo-harry-halpin-on-privacy-decentralized-vpns-and-tornado-cash</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/aLTtY2aq/nym-ceo-harry-halpin-on-privacy-decentralized-vpns-and-tornado-cash"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T18:08:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The founder of privacy-preserving mixnet Nym sat down with Decrypt at Web Summit to talk about its new decentralized VPN, the Web3 privacy landscape and why "devs should be defended" in the wake of the Tornado Cash crackdown.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pat Felder - The worst is over [Macro Deep Dive Episode]]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MdcKPVo0/pat-felder-the-worst-is-over-macro-deep-dive-episode</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MdcKPVo0/pat-felder-the-worst-is-over-macro-deep-dive-episode"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T17:10:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the first Markets Edition of This Time Will Be Different! In this episode we dive into the current macroeconomic conditions around crypto and look at the data behind the price action. 


Reza sits down with Pat Felder, founder of Prismatic Capital to discuss the current macro environment, and to answer the question on everyone's mind-- is the bear market really over?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Sandbox Co-Founder Sebastien Borget: 'We're Already Integrating AI']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/HlARjhG1/the-sandbox-co-founder-sebastien-borget-were-already-integrating-ai</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/HlARjhG1/the-sandbox-co-founder-sebastien-borget-were-already-integrating-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T16:09:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt sat down with The Sandbox co-founder Sebastien Borget at Web Summit to talk about AI, the open metaverse and the creative challenges of interoperability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dacoco CEO Saro McKenna: How Alien Worlds is Creating an AI-Powered 'Lore DAO' with Kevin J Anderson]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QrQTrsjH/dacoco-ceo-saro-mckenna-how-alien-worlds-is-creating-an-ai-powered-lore-dao-with-kevin-j-anderson</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QrQTrsjH/dacoco-ceo-saro-mckenna-how-alien-worlds-is-creating-an-ai-powered-lore-dao-with-kevin-j-anderson"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T16:06:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt joined Dacoco CEO Sarojini McKenna at Web Summit 2023 to talk about Alien Worlds' new Lore DAO and its AI-powered collaboration with sci-fi author Kevin J Anderson.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avalon's Jeffrey Butler on Designing a Metaverse MMO That Lets Players Co-Create]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XDz9vsvT/avalons-jeffrey-butler-on-designing-a-metaverse-mmo-that-lets-players-co-create</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XDz9vsvT/avalons-jeffrey-butler-on-designing-a-metaverse-mmo-that-lets-players-co-create"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T00:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avalon Chief Product Officer Jeffrey Butler speaks with Decrypt reporter Jason Nelson and details his studio's new MMO game with interoperable assets—and how it will enable players to create and monetize their own content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>