<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-05-03T10:16:26.621Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-05-03T10:16:26.621Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SHIB Shows Meme Token Resilience, Hard Fork Expected to Add New Features]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19456880/SHIB-Shows-Meme-Token-Resilience-Hard-Fork-Expected-to-Add-New-Features</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19456880/SHIB-Shows-Meme-Token-Resilience-Hard-Fork-Expected-to-Add-New-Features"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T10:01:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SHIB survived the worst of this week’s correction, and even briefly rallied along with Dogecoin (DOGE). But SHIB goes beyond the pure meme narrative of tokens like BONK, SLERF, Dogwifhat and FLOKI. SHIB traded at $0.000023, its mid-range level for the past month. SHIB also shows it can rally...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friend.Tech Launches V2 Upgrade Alongside Native Token Airdrop]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19456876/FriendTech-Launches-V2-Upgrade-Alongside-Native-Token-Airdrop</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19456876/FriendTech-Launches-V2-Upgrade-Alongside-Native-Token-Airdrop"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T10:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinspeaker Friend.Tech Launches V2 Upgrade Alongside Native Token Airdrop Decentralized social network Friend.Tech just bagged a new upgrade by pushing out its new naive token for trading on its native decentralized exchange on the Base network. According to DexScreener, the new token is...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weekly Roundup 05/03/24 (CZ sentenced, Roger Ver arrested, Coinbase earnings) (EP.525)]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19456861/Weekly-Roundup-050324-CZ-sentenced-Roger-Ver-arrested-Coinbase-earnings-EP525</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19456861/Weekly-Roundup-050324-CZ-sentenced-Roger-Ver-arrested-Coinbase-earnings-EP525"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matt and Nic are back for more news and deals. In this episode: Matt get’s 2nd in Jeopardy at ETH Boston We reminisce over Nic’s 2020 holiday quiz Ian Cain’s Senate candidacy in MA CZ get 4 months in prison The significance of ‘4’ Did CZ deserve his sentence? Roger Ver arrested for tax fraud...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Will Lose Motion To Stop The SEC’s Opposition Filing – Lawyer]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19456843/Ripple-Will-Lose-Motion-To-Stop-The-SECs-Opposition-Filing-Lawyer</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19456843/Ripple-Will-Lose-Motion-To-Stop-The-SECs-Opposition-Filing-Lawyer"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T09:56:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Foremost crypto lawyer Bill Morgan thinks Ripple will lose its “Motion to Strike” filing in the ongoing lawsuit against the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). Morgan highlighted this in a recent post on X, noting that he believes the Judge will accept the SEC’s summary witness Andrea...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BTCC Sets 10M USDT Rewards for Its World Trading Contest]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19456841/BTCC-Sets-10M-USDT-Rewards-for-Its-World-Trading-Contest</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19456841/BTCC-Sets-10M-USDT-Rewards-for-Its-World-Trading-Contest"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T09:54:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTCC entices crypto traders into a global competition with a prize pool of 10 million USDT.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bold Statements About Ethereum (ETH), XRP and Altcoins from Bitcoin Bull Michael Saylor!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19456840/Bold-Statements-About-Ethereum-ETH-XRP-and-Altcoins-from-Bitcoin-Bull-Michael-Saylor</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19456840/Bold-Statements-About-Ethereum-ETH-XRP-and-Altcoins-from-Bitcoin-Bull-Michael-Saylor"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T09:53:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Famous Bitcoin (BTV) supporter Michael Saylor claimed that Ethereum (ETH) as well as BNB, Solana and XRP are securities. Continue Reading: Bold Statements About Ethereum (ETH), XRP and Altcoins from Bitcoin Bull Michael Saylor!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Upbit Announced the Listing of Two New Altcoins, There was a Big Jump in Prices!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19456838/Upbit-Announced-the-Listing-of-Two-New-Altcoins-There-was-a-Big-Jump-in-Prices</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19456838/Upbit-Announced-the-Listing-of-Two-New-Altcoins-There-was-a-Big-Jump-in-Prices"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T09:53:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Upbit, South Korea's largest cryptocurrency exchange, said that it has listed altcoins named Zetachain (ZETA) and Omni Network (OMNI). Continue Reading: Upbit Announced the Listing of Two New Altcoins, There was a Big Jump in Prices!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Community split on ENS petition against Unstoppable Domains patent]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19456847/Community-split-on-ENS-petition-against-Unstoppable-Domains-patent</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19456847/Community-split-on-ENS-petition-against-Unstoppable-Domains-patent"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T09:53:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some crypto community members argued against the petition, while others supported ENS’ move against Unstoppable Domains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update! EIGEN Foundation makes new announcements on EIGEN Stakedrop]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19456832/Update-EIGEN-Foundation-makes-new-announcements-on-EIGEN-Stakedrop</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19456832/Update-EIGEN-Foundation-makes-new-announcements-on-EIGEN-Stakedrop"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T09:50:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Opinions on the EIGEN Stakedrop have flooded Crypto Twitter after its recent launch. Some excited, some cautious, and all in all, the Eigen Foundation is continuing to benefit from large media coverage and engagements on Twitter. The Eigen Foundation recently launched the EIGEN token and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto exchanges to meet Nigerian SEC chief for regulatory talks]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19456829/Crypto-exchanges-to-meet-Nigerian-SEC-chief-for-regulatory-talks</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19456829/Crypto-exchanges-to-meet-Nigerian-SEC-chief-for-regulatory-talks"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T09:47:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The meeting is anticipated to ignite positive changes that benefit all crypto stakeholders in Nigeria and on the international scene.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BREAKING: HUGE Money To Enter Bitcoin Market, Rich People Are Looking TO BUY CRYPTO RIGHT NOW]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19456826/BREAKING-HUGE-Money-To-Enter-Bitcoin-Market-Rich-People-Are-Looking-TO-BUY-CRYPTO-RIGHT-NOW</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19456826/BREAKING-HUGE-Money-To-Enter-Bitcoin-Market-Rich-People-Are-Looking-TO-BUY-CRYPTO-RIGHT-NOW"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T09:37:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite current market movements, it looks like (gasp) rich people are still buying and looking to get further into the Bitcoin market. As BTC ETF popularity expands across the globe more and more companies are looking to buy, and its this world wide expansion of spot Bitcoin ETF products that...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pantera Capital invests in TON, eyes support for crypto adoption via Telegram]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19456781/Pantera-Capital-invests-in-TON-eyes-support-for-crypto-adoption-via-Telegram</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19456781/Pantera-Capital-invests-in-TON-eyes-support-for-crypto-adoption-via-Telegram"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T09:32:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pantera Capital has announced it invested an undisclosed amount in TON. The venture capital firm says TON’s integration with messaging platform Telegram could be a game-changer in crypto adoption. Venture capital firm Pantera Capital has invested in The Open Network (TON) blockchain, the layer-1...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dormant Ethereum holder moves $5.8M in ETH – Time to lock in your profits?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19456776/Dormant-Ethereum-holder-moves-58M-in-ETH-Time-to-lock-in-your-profits</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19456776/Dormant-Ethereum-holder-moves-58M-in-ETH-Time-to-lock-in-your-profits"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T09:30:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Realization of profits could be the driving factor, but nothing was concrete at press time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Block Co-Founder Jack Dorsey Planning To Buy BTC]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19456754/Block-Co-Founder-Jack-Dorsey-Planning-To-Buy-BTC</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19456754/Block-Co-Founder-Jack-Dorsey-Planning-To-Buy-BTC"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Block’s Co-founder Jack Dorsey discusses a plan with the shareholders to invest a gross profit of 10% of Bitcoin products in buying Bitcoin (BTC) every month. This planning by Dorsey is an investment for the economically empowered future of Block.What's The NewsThe Co-founder Jack Dorsey of the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ZKSNACKS Coinjoin Coordination Service Will Stop Functioning From June 1]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19456744/ZKSNACKS-Coinjoin-Coordination-Service-Will-Stop-Functioning-From-June-1</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19456744/ZKSNACKS-Coinjoin-Coordination-Service-Will-Stop-Functioning-From-June-1"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T09:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ZKSNACKS, the company pioneering the development of the Wasabi wallet, has announced it is shutting down its Coinjoin coordination service from June 1, 2024. In a recent report, the company cited regulatory uncertainty as the main reason for discontinuing the privacy-focused service. Posting on...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BNP Paribas reveals to have bought shares of BlackRock’s Bitcoin spot ETF]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19456798/BNP-Paribas-reveals-to-have-bought-shares-of-BlackRocks-Bitcoin-spot-ETF</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19456798/BNP-Paribas-reveals-to-have-bought-shares-of-BlackRocks-Bitcoin-spot-ETF"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T09:18:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BNP Paribas, the second largest bank in Europe, has announced its investment in Bitcoin using BlackRock's spot ETF.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dutch Anti-Fraud Agency Arrests Man Allegedly Involved in ZKasino Rug Pull]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19456747/Dutch-Anti-Fraud-Agency-Arrests-Man-Allegedly-Involved-in-ZKasino-Rug-Pull</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19456747/Dutch-Anti-Fraud-Agency-Arrests-Man-Allegedly-Involved-in-ZKasino-Rug-Pull"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T09:18:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a notable crackdown on crypto fraud, the Dutch anti-fraud agency FIOD has arrested a 26-year-old man. He is suspected of fraud, embezzlement, and money laundering concerning the ZKasino rug pull, marking a critical development in combating crypto-related scams. Dutch Agency Investigates...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Mirroring Price Action That Preceded Massive Bull Runs in the Past, Says Trader – Here’s His Outlook]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19456731/Dogecoin-Mirroring-Price-Action-That-Preceded-Massive-Bull-Runs-in-the-Past-Says-Trader-Heres-His-Outlook</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19456731/Dogecoin-Mirroring-Price-Action-That-Preceded-Massive-Bull-Runs-in-the-Past-Says-Trader-Heres-His-Outlook"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T09:15:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency analyst and trader Ali Martinez is saying that the price of Dogecoin (DOGE) is exhibiting behavior it has previously displayed before embarking on massive rallies. Martinez tells his 61,200 followers on the social media platform X that the largest memecoin by market cap earlier...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All Bitcoin ETFs Are Dropping Their Holdings]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19456732/All-Bitcoin-ETFs-Are-Dropping-Their-Holdings</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19456732/All-Bitcoin-ETFs-Are-Dropping-Their-Holdings"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T09:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF outflows are creating dangerous pressure on market]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friend.Tech's Native Token Tanks to $2.5 After Debut]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742a70ae0f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/05/03/friendtechs-native-token-tanks-to-25-after-debut/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T09:08:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Early Friday, Friend.Tech airdropped its native token, FRIEND, while debuting version 2 of the platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Option Data of May Announced! Has the Expected Rise Signal Arrived for Bitcoin and Etherem?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19456714/First-Option-Data-of-May-Announced-Has-the-Expected-Rise-Signal-Arrived-for-Bitcoin-and-Etherem</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19456714/First-Option-Data-of-May-Announced-Has-the-Expected-Rise-Signal-Arrived-for-Bitcoin-and-Etherem"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T09:08:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to data, 23,000 Bitcoin and 330,000 Ethereum options will expire on May 3. What does it mean for BTC and ETH price? Continue Reading: First Option Data of May Announced! Has the Expected Rise Signal Arrived for Bitcoin and Etherem?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fear Back For 1st Time Since October As Crypto Greed Takes The Backseat]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742a71adf0</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-news-fear-back-for-1st-time-since-october/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T09:02:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The luster appears to have faded from Bitcoin’s crown. After a stellar run culminating in a record-breaking price in late March, the world’s leading cryptocurrency has experienced a sharp correction, plunging investor sentiment into the abyss. This sudden shift can be attributed to a confluence of factors, with the “Fear and Greed Index” playing a fascinating role in this rollercoaster ride, alongside a record exodus from a key investment vehicle.
 
 
Bitcoin And The Fear Gauge: A Delicate Dance
 
The Crypto Fear and Greed Index is a sentiment analysis tool that attempts to capture the overall emotional temperature of the cryptocurrency market. It operates on a scale of 0 to 100, with 0 signifying “Extreme Fear” and 100 representing “Extreme Greed.” This psychological barometer plays a sur…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ASIC Scores Legal Victory: BPS Financial Found Guilty in Qoin Wallet Case]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742a7d20ef</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/asic-scores-legal-victory-bps-financial-found-guilty-in-qoin-wallet-case/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T08:36:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Federal Court has found BPS Financial Pty Ltd (BPS)  
guilty of engaging in unlicensed conduct concerning the 'Qoin Wallet', a  
non-cash payment facility utilizing a crypto-asset token known as 'Qoin.' The  
judgment was delivered by Justice Downes in proceedings brought by ASIC.
Further Proceedings Ordered by the Court 
The court determined that BPS, from January 2020 onwards  
(with a brief exception of a 10-month period), violated the Corporations Act by  
lacking an Australian Financial Services Licence. Furthermore, BPS was not  
authorized by any licensee to issue or provide financial advice regarding the  
Qoin Wallet. Justice Downes also found BPS guilty of misleading or deceptive  
conduct and propagating false representations about the Qoin Wallet.
Among the misleading claim…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tareq Sikder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: 30% of UK Watchdog’s Financial Crime Experts Focused on Crypto Businesses in 2022-23]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742a7e1a2e</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/report-30-of-uk-watchdogs-financial-crime-experts-focused-on-crypto-businesses-in-2022-23/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T08:29:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to a report, the Financial Conduct Authority, a watchdog for the financial services industry in the U.K., had 30% of its financial crime specialists focused on crypto-asset businesses. Assessments conducted by supervisors in the U.K. found that not only crypto-asset businesses, but nearly all participants in the country’s financial services sector, are susceptible to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jack Dorsey’s Block To Invest 10% Of Bitcoin Profits Into Monthly BTC Buys]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742a67d9fb</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dorsey-block-10-bitcoin-profits-into-monthly-buys/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T07:11:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jack Dorsey’s financial services and digital payments company, Block Inc., announced it will begin investing 10% of its monthly Bitcoin-related gross profits into BTC purchases. This announcement was made following the release of Block’s first-quarter earnings for 2024, which demonstrated substantial profits from its Bitcoin operations.
 
Dorsey’s Block Will DCA Into Bitcoin
 
Block reported Bitcoin-related gross profits amounting to $80 million in the first quarter alone. If this trend continues, the implementation of the new dollar cost averaging (DCA) program could see the company investing approximately $24 million in BTC within one year. This initiative aims to enhance the company’s BTC holdings, strategically buying into the market in a manner that minimizes the impact on Bitcoin’s p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blackrock Reinforces Tokenization Drive Leading $47 Million Funding Round in Digitization Company Securitize]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742a6b23a7</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/blackrock-reinforces-tokenization-drive-leading-47-million-funding-round-in-digitization-company-securitize/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T05:30:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blackrock, the largest asset management company in the world, has led a strategic funding round of $47 million in Securitize, a capital markets digitalization company. The round, which had the participation of other financial markets and crypto native companies, shows Blackrock is betting on the transformative capabilities of tokenization for global capital markets. Blackrock Leads […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will SocialFi Fizzle? Dogecoin Founder Expresses A Cynical View]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742a518166</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/will-socialfi-fizzle-dogecoin-founder-sounds-alarm/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T04:29:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Social media, once a platform for cat videos and vacation photos, is undergoing a potential revolution with the rise of SocialFi. This burgeoning trend promises to merge the familiar world of social networking with the decentralized power of cryptocurrency.
 
But is SocialFi destined to be the next big thing, or just another flash in the pan? A recent exchange between Dogecoin creator Billy Markus and a SocialFi enthusiast has ignited a discourse about the movement’s true potential.
 
 
SocialFi: A Glittering Promise?
 
SocialFi platforms aim to empower users by putting them in control of their data and online interactions. Imagine a social network where you can not only connect with friends and follow influencers, but also earn rewards for creating content, curate your own digital space, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Mining Restrictions: Arkansas Lawmakers Approve New Bills To Regulate Sector]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742a59514d</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-mining-restrictions-arkansas-lawmakers-approve-new-bills-to-regulate-sector/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T03:07:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the last couple of years, the US government has tried to tighten its grip on different sectors of the crypto industry. As a result, these efforts have received significant backlash from politicians and central figures within the crypto space.
 
This week, another crackdown on the crypto industry occurred after Arkansas lawmakers approved two bills to address criticism over previous regulations on mining operations.
 
 
New Crypto Mining Regulations In Arkansas
 
News media outlet The Associated Press (AP) reported on Wednesday that Arkansas’ House of Representatives gave final approval to two bills related to crypto mining operations in the state.
 
The two Senate-backed bills, SB78 and SB79, were among the few non-budget subjects on the legislative session’s agenda and were “overwhel…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rubmar Garcia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether Q1 2024 Attestation Reveals Record $4.52 Billion Profits]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742a4535a9</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/tether-q1-2024-attestation-reveals-record-4-52-billion-profits/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T02:24:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tether, one of the largest cryptocurrency companies, has recently released an attestation of its financial activity corresponding to Q1 2024. Tether registered a record-breaking $4.52 billion in profits, and disclosed its net equity levels, reporting $11.37 billion as of March 31, 2024. Tether issued over $12.5 billion USDT during this period. Tether Attestation Registers Record-Breaking […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MoonPay Expands Crypto Purchasing Options For US Users With PayPal Integration]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742a46b59e</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/moonpay-crypto-options-users-paypal-integration/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T02:08:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a significant development, MoonPay, a crypto payment platform, has announced that users in the United States can now easily buy and sell over 110 cryptocurrencies using PayPal. 
 
The integration, unveiled Thursday, simplifies transactions for new MoonPay users who already have a PayPal account and regularly use it for online transactions. Users can fund their cryptocurrency purchases via their PayPal balance, direct bank withdrawal, or debit card without manually entering payment information.
 
MoonPay And PayPal Join Forces
 
Per the announcement, one of the key advantages of this collaboration is the added layer of security provided by PayPal, which does not disclose full financial details during transactions. MoonPay co-founder and CEO, Ivan Soto-Wright, emphasized the significance …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JPMorgan Waves Red Flag: Urges Caution As Crypto Market Teeters on Edge]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742a43b5d6</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/jpmorgan-waves-urges-caution-as-crypto-market/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T01:09:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In recent evaluations by JPMorgan analysts, cryptocurrencies’ future appears to be uncertain. Despite the sector’s rapid expansion and increasing mainstream acceptance, the financial giant advises a cautious approach in the short term.
 
This conservative stance stems from “diminishing retail interest” and a “scarcity of positive market catalysts.”
 
 
Analyzing The Shifts: From Enthusiasm To Caution
 
JPMorgan’s scrutiny reveals a marked shift in market dynamics. Over recent weeks, significant selling and profit-taking activities have been observed, particularly from retail investors who seem to be retreating from crypto and equity markets.
 
According to JPMorgan analysts, this trend is corroborated by a notable decrease in net inflows to equity funds, turning negative for the first time…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Saylor Delivers Bitcoin Masterclass To Fortune 1000 Companies]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742a4b2d9a</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/michael-saylor-delivers-bitcoin-masterclass-to-fortune-1000-companies"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T23:45:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a Keynote address at MicroStrategy World: Bitcoin for Corporations, MicroStrategy Executive Chairman Michael Saylor delivered a masterclass on corporate finance and the power of bitcoin to supercharge corporate balance sheets. Saylor made a point to emphasize Bitcoin as the single solution for capital appreciation in an inflationary environment.

In his speech, Saylor likened the cost of capital to being the benchmark which a company must surpass to increase its purchasing power, arguing that “Bitcoin is the only asset that exceeds the cost of capital. Another way to say that, is everything else is dilutive.”
Further describing the true cost of capital, he noted that the “S&P is the modern surrogate for the cost of capital… If you had to pick one metric and say, what's the metric that g…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spencer Nichols</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Rides Bitcoin ETF Wave as Profits Soar past $1B in Q1]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742a4b318e</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/coinbase-rides-bitcoin-etf-wave-as-profits-soar-past-1b-in-q1/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T23:45:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase has released its first quarter report for  
2024, showcasing a substantial 72% quarter-on-quarter increase in total revenue  
to $1.6 billion. This surge was accompanied by a notable net income  
of $1,176 billion, representing an increase of 1,588% YoY. This figure represents a turnaround from a net loss of $79 million in the same period last year. Compared to last quarter, Coinbase's net income surged 331%.
The cryptocurrency exchange experienced an uptick in  
its market share across US spot and derivatives trading, along with reaching record highs in Coinbase Prime usage and USDC market capitalization. According to the company, notable international operations significantly contributed to the overall growth.
Impact of Bitcoin ETFs
Coinbase mentioned: "While we cannot attribute…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Massive $43M Crypto Ponzi Scheme Uncovered In New York, Leading To Wire Fraud Arrest]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742a4bcbe7</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/massive-43m-crypto-ponzi-scheme-uncovered-in-ny/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T23:39:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[United States Attorney Damian Williams and FBI Assistant Director James Smith announced the unsealing of an indictment charging Idin Dalpour with wire fraud concerning a multi-year crypto Ponzi scheme that defrauded investors of at least $43 million. 
 
Wire Fraud Indictment Unveils $43M Ponzi Scheme
 
The indictment alleges that from approximately 2020 to April 2024, Dalpour orchestrated a crypto-related Ponzi scheme targeting investors both in the United States and abroad. 
 
Dalpour purportedly solicited investments through an entity he controlled, Entity-1, which claimed to be involved in a Las Vegas hospitality enterprise and a crypto trading venture. 
 
However, instead of utilizing the funds as promised, Dalpour used money from new investors to pay earlier investors, employing a cla…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Standard Chartered Warns Bitcoin Price Could Fall to $50K]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742a356133</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/standard-chartered-warns-bitcoin-price-could-fall-to-50k/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T23:23:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Standard Chartered Bank has warned that bitcoin’s price could potentially decline to $50,000. The head of digital asset research at the bank attributed this forecast to a mix of crypto-specific factors and broader macroeconomic influences. Additionally, he warned about the risk of liquidation for some spot exchange-traded fund (ETF) positions, emphasizing that over half of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Scaling Bitcoin Together” Event Set to Unite Bitcoin Leaders in Hong Kong]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742a364877</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/scaling-bitcoin-together-event-set-to-unite-bitcoin-leaders-in-hong-kong/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T23:14:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. As a part of Bitcoin Asia Week 2024, the “Scaling Bitcoin Together” event will take place on May 11, 2024, in Hong Kong. This event will bring together top blockchain experts to discuss how to grow the Bitcoin ecosystem. The “Scaling Bitcoin Together” aims to foster discussions that propel the development of the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Script State from Lamport Signatures]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742a338179</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/technical/script-state-from-lamport-signatures-"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T22:24:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The last six months or so have seen several proposals for improvements to Bitcoin Script: CAT, 64-bit arithmetic, as well as some older ideas (CTV) and far-future ideas (Chialisp and Simplicity). This activity has largely overshadowed some revolutionary changes in our understanding of the existing Bitcoin Script, changes which form the basis of BitVM but which may also form the basis of other, equally-exciting improvements.
This article tries to summarize and organize research into Script by other people. I make no claim to originality or authorship of anything described here.
Bitcoin Script
As many readers are aware, Bitcoin Script is a simple programming language embedded in the Bitcoin blockchain, which is used to control under what conditions coins may move. By far the most common use …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Poelstra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analyst Identifies Crucial Dogecoin Support At $0.112-$0.123, Will Price Crash Further?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742a3e21bd</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-support-at-0-112-0-123/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T22:01:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin suffered a significant crash in the bloodbath that rocked the crypto market earlier this week, notching double-digit losses in the process. This has sent its support lower, and $0.112-$0.123 is now the level to hold for the meme coin. But what if it falls below this support?
 
Dogecoin Must Hold Support At $0.112-$0.123
 
Crypto analyst YG Crypto, in an analysis, identified $0.112-$0.123 as the major support levels for Dogecoin after the price crash. In the post that was made on X (formerly Twitter), the crypto analyst explained that these levels are important due to the fact that they have prevent massive price crashes for Dogecoin in the past.
 
 
As such, the meme coin needs to maintain above this level to continue its bullish trend. As of the early hours of Thursday, the DOGE …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jito Price Jumps After Topping Solana DeFi Protocols With $1 Billion Locked]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229227</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229227/jito-price-jumps-after-topping-solana-defi-protocols-with-1-billion-locked"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T21:36:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jito Network became the top DeFi protocol on Solana, with liquid staking pool token JitoSOL rising by 8.5%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bulletproof Cadillac, Butler, and $1.5M Titanic Watch: FTX Exec's Lavish Spending Continues]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229212</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229212/ftx-exec-lavish-spending-continues-1-5-million-watch-titanic"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T21:20:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former FTX Europe head Patrick Gruhn is spending his crypto riches— but his fortune is not without controversy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jack Dorsey's Block Adding More Bitcoin to Balance Sheet, Presents Road Map for Others]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742a3b21c8</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2024/05/02/jack-dorseys-block-adding-more-bitcoin-to-balance-sheet-presents-road-map-for-others/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T21:18:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The payments firm announced the news alongside its first quarter earnings report on Thursday afternoon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen  Alpher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JPMorgan: Retail Investors Drive Selloff in Both Crypto and Equity Markets]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742a3b85ad</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/jpmorgan-retail-investors-drive-selloff-in-both-crypto-and-equity-markets/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T21:15:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JPMorgan has highlighted a significant increase in selling and profit-taking across equity and crypto markets, driven largely by retail investors. The global investment bank also observed institutional momentum traders and quantitative funds reducing positions, particularly in stocks, bitcoin, and gold. Insights on Market Trends by JPMorgan JPMorgan, a global investment bank, has provided insights on […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase $1.6 Billion Quarterly Profits Boosted By Stablecoins, Rising Crypto Prices]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229217</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229217/coinbase-first-quarter-profit-report"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T21:10:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The San Francisco-based exchange has reported better-than-expected 2024 Q1 results.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo,André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will the Fed Cut Rates? Crypto and Wall Street Traders Aren’t Betting on It]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229213</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229213/fed-rate-cut-odds-crypto-polymarket-cme-tradfi"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T20:13:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Just cut the rates bro please,” pleaded a down-bad trader on Polymarket.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Transactions Plummet Following Absurd Runes and Halving Surge]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229185</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229185/bitcoin-transaction-fees-fall-after-halving-highs"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T18:50:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cost to send BTC skyrocketed immediately following the halving, but fees have since fallen back to Earth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elizabeth Warren's Latest Crypto Crusade: Bitcoin Mining In Iran]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229189</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229189/elizabeth-warren-iran-bitcoin-mining-terrorism"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T18:39:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The leading crypto critic in the U.S. Senate says the Iranian mining sector supports terrorism.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mom Sexualizes Herself on Livestream for Son’s Meme Coin—Then Ghosts]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229175</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229175/livemom-livestream-mom-son-meme-coin"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T17:41:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A mom used her boobs to help her son pump a meme coin, called LIVEMOM, to a $300K market cap before the token crashed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETFs Shed $563 Million as BlackRock's IBIT Marks First Daily Loss]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229168</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229168/bitcoin-etfs-shed-563-million-blackrock-ibit-losses"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T16:46:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spot Bitcoin ETFs posted record daily net outflows on Wednesday as BlackRock's IBIT faltered for the very first time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum and Solana Meme Coin Prices Surge Amid Modest Bitcoin Gains]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229150</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229150/ethereum-solana-meme-coins-surge-modest-bitcoin-gains"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T16:29:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin is rising after a rough week, but meme coins like Pepe, Bonk, Dogwifhat, and Dogecoin are the biggest winners today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are Parachains? Polkadot's Secret Weapon Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229149</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-are-parachains-polkadots-secret-weapon-explained"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T15:44:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Polkadot’s parachains offer a unique technical approach to achieving scalability and interoperability for blockchains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will McCurdy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Blogging Protocol Mirror Embraces Farcaster in Social Media Pivot]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229077</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229077/ethereum-blogging-protocol-mirror-farcaster-social-media-pivot"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T15:10:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mirror's team is now building a Farcaster-based social app called Kiosk, while Paragraph will take over Mirror. Collectively, they've raised $15 million.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FBI Arrests Man For Running Alleged $43 Million Crypto Trading Ponzi Scheme]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229132</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229132/fbi-arrests-man-for-running-alleged-43-million-crypto-trading-ponzi-scheme"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T13:21:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Manhattan man allegedly spent $1.7 million of investors' money on gambling debts, $400,000 on Art Direct, and his kids' private school tuition.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana GameShift Adds Google Cloud Integration for Crypto Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229078</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229078/solana-gameshift-google-cloud-integration-crypto-games"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T13:01:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creators building blockchain games with Solana Labs’ GameShift platform will be able to tap into Google Cloud features via the integration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PayPal Expands Crypto Offerings With  MoonPay Integration]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229096</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229096/paypal-adds-moonpay-for-crypto-purchases-debit"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PayPal has linked up with MoonPay to offer its millions of users access to over 100 cryptocurrencies]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Second-Largest European Bank BNP Paribas Bought BlackRock Bitcoin ETF Shares: SEC Filing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229113</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229113/second-largest-european-bank-bnp-paribas-bought-blackrock-bitcoin-etf-shares-sec-filing"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T11:45:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to a 13F report, BNP Paribas purchased IBIT shares in the first quarter of 2024—albeit less than 1 BTC worth at current prices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin and Ethereum Rebound as Interest Rates Remain Unchanged in US]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229103</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229103/bitcoin-and-ethereum-rebound-as-interest-rates-remain-unchanged-in-us"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T10:50:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin and Ethereum are rebounding after a rough couple of days leading up to the Federal Reserve deciding not to change interest rates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy Is Building ‘Decentralized ID’ on Bitcoin Using Ordinals-Like Inscriptions]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229087</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229087/orange-decentralized-identity-ordinals-inscriptions-microstrategy"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T00:25:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Saylor announced the Orange protocol for decentralized identification, hoping to anchor digital identities in the dominant blockchain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build on Bitcoin Launches Mainnet With Over 40 Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229079</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229079/build-on-bitcoin-launches-mainnet-with-over-40-apps"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T23:54:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BOB launches its Bitcoin layer-2 Ethereum rollup, with more to come over the next three weeks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[If the SEC Thinks Ethereum Is a Security, Are ETH ETFs Doomed?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229065</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229065/sec-ethereum-security-eth-etfs-doomed"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T20:54:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s now looking like a long road ahead for ETH to come to Wall Street. But that’s a surprise to few.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ronin's Path From Curated Ethereum Gaming to 'Pervasively Permissionless']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228301</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228301/ronin-path-curated-ethereum-gaming-pervasively-permissionless"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T20:41:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum gaming chain Ronin currently curates the games on its network. But it’s starting to eye up a permissionless future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Notcoin? The Telegram-Based Game, NOT Token, and Future Plans]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=223640</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-notcoin-telegram-based-game-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T19:39:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATED: When is the NOT token actually launching? Here's the latest, along with everything else you need to know about Notcoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery,Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here's How AI Can Help Find Money Laundering on Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229030</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229030/heres-how-ai-can-detect-money-laundering-on-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T18:46:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An Elliptic report shows how MIT-IBM AI Labs used deep learning AI techniques to detect fraud on the world’s dominant blockchain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Trade Sideways as Fed Leaves Interest Rates Untouched]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229041</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229041/bitcoin-ethereum-trade-sideways-as-fed-leaves-interest-rates-untouched"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T18:27:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amid signs of stubborn inflation in the U.S., the central bank kept its key interest rate at its highest level in over 23 years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Could Rebound As ‘Paper Hands’ Investors Flee, Analysts Say]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229046</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229046/bitcoin-paper-hands-correction-glassnode"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T18:18:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Investors often leave during the “local bottom.” and one analyst suggests BTC is reaching that point.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feds Are Investigating Jack Dorsey's Block Over Bitcoin Biz: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229047</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229047/feds-investigating-jack-dorsey-block-bitcoin-biz-report"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T18:06:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jack Dorsey's Block is reportedly under investigation for compliance issues, including with its Bitcoin business.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Hasn't Hit the Bottom Yet, Says Standard Chartered]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229039</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229039/bitcoin-could-fall-to-50000-standard-chartered"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T17:26:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The biggest digital coin still has room to fall, the British firm said in a new report.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Bitcoin Senator' Cynthia Lummis Blasts DOJ Stance on Private Crypto Wallets]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229020</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229020/bitcoin-senator-cynthia-lummis-blasts-doj-stance-crypto-wallets"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T17:09:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lummis argued the Department of Justice's position on self-custody "contradicts existing Treasury guidance" and "violates the rule of law."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF Leader BlackRock Leads $47M Funding Round in Securitize]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228992</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228992/bitcoin-etf-blackrock-leads-47-million-funding-round-securitize"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T16:48:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock’s BUIDL fund, created with Securitize, has $375 million in assets under management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Redstone Network Launches to Power Fully On-Chain Ethereum Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229005</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229005/redstone-network-launches-fully-on-chain-ethereum-games"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T16:01:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Powered by the Optimism OP Stack, Redstone enables “autonomous worlds” and other intriguing new types of on-chain Ethereum games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether Netted $4.52 Billion Q1 Profit Thanks To Bitcoin Gains]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228991</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228991/tether-netted-4-52-billion-q1-profit-thanks-to-bitcoin-gains"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T15:42:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tether’s Bitcoin investment is paying off, achieving much greater profit than the company’s immense bond portfolio.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BNB Chain's $1M Meme Innovation Contest Is 'Unleashing Meme Coin Creativity']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228494</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228494/bnb-chains-1m-meme-innovation-contest-is-unleashing-meme-coin-creativity"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T15:40:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The competition aims to encourage developers to create, launch and trade their meme coins on BNB Chain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Ethereum Founder Vitalik Buterin Keeps His Crypto Safe]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228946</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228946/how-ethereum-founder-vitalik-buterin-keeps-crypto-safe"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T14:38:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Decentralize your own security," says Ethereum founder Vitalik Buterin—but he doesn't use a cold wallet for his own personal crypto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Do A Little With Mike Demarais]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ajrh0oiK/we-do-a-little-with-mike-demarais</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ajrh0oiK/we-do-a-little-with-mike-demarais"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T15:11:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mike dropped knowledge bombs from years of building in the trenches alongside some deep cuts on the early Williamsburg crypto mafia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eth Rally Fails]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Gj7TMrbP/eth-rally-fails</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Gj7TMrbP/eth-rally-fails"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T12:45:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto falls, ETH/BTC rally again marks mini sell-off. Yen carry-trade implosion linked to worries. ETH gas fees hit 6-month lows. 3rd straight week of institutional outflows. Slowing BTC ETF flows are just a pause: Bernstein. BTC now on track for 5 red weeks in a row. BTC may have topped, could hit $35k: Brandt. ETFs may become big sellers: Bianco. Consensys list 4 reasons ETH isn’t a security. Rumours continue to grow of EigenLayer airdrop. Perp DEX volumes continue fall, GMX underperforms. Wallets begin to block US users after Samourai case. WLD in reported partnership talks with OpenAI. Large unlocks this week for SUI, PYTH & MEME.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Sasha Stiles’ Experiential, AI-Infused NFT Drop with Bang & Olufsen]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/6Vi2IgYj/inside-sasha-stiles-experiential-ai-infused-nft-drop-with-bang-olufsen</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/6Vi2IgYj/inside-sasha-stiles-experiential-ai-infused-nft-drop-with-bang-olufsen"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T22:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At a launch party for the collection in New York’s SoHo neighborhood, the artist broke down her latest art experiment, “Four Core Texts,” with Decrypt’s Sander Lutz.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interview: How 'Notcoin' Will Evolve After the NOT Token Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PprnGP14/interview-how-notcoin-will-evolve-after-the-not-token-launch</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PprnGP14/interview-how-notcoin-will-evolve-after-the-not-token-launch"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Open Builders founder Sasha Plotvinov speaks with Decrypt's Sander Lutz at Token 2049 Dubai about how he envisions Notcoin's expansion and evolution after the token drop—into something akin to the "Netflix of social, viral games."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Magic Runes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IGWg0R64/magic-runes</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IGWg0R64/magic-runes"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T13:59:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC stables at $66k, liquidations in narrow range. BTC funding again turns negative in bullish sign. ETFs net inflow after Grayscale moves to lower fees. BTC demand 5x vs supply post-halving: Bitfinex. SOL congestion issue now largely solved. Two SEC lawyers resign after ‘gross abuse of power’. Ripple fights to lower $2bn SEC fine. SAFE trades at $2.8bn FDV after OKX lists. MANEKI hits $150m on first day, China memes pump. Memecoins are ‘black hole you can’t ignore’. DeGods up 20%, may switch back to SOL. Magic Eden launches Runes platform ahead of time.  Louis Vuitton gifts Pharrell jacket to NFT holders. Melania Trump launches necklace with SOL NFTs. Hoodie Punk trades for $620K.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Luxury Watches, Designer Shoes Will Soon Trade Like NFTs: Arianee CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/CSNQG2md/luxury-watches-designer-shoes-will-soon-trade-like-nfts-arianee-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/CSNQG2md/luxury-watches-designer-shoes-will-soon-trade-like-nfts-arianee-ceo"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arianee CEO Pierre-Nicolas Hurstel sat down with Rug Radio founder Farokh and Decrypt’s Sander Lutz at NFT Paris to discuss everything from the future of on-chain luxury to the secret hack to finding the best restaurants in France.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notcoin's Co-Creator Explains the Game's Token Delay—And When to Expect NOT Now]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/7Zx33xo5/notcoins-co-creator-explains-the-games-token-delayand-when-to-expect-not-now</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/7Zx33xo5/notcoins-co-creator-explains-the-games-token-delayand-when-to-expect-not-now"/>
        <updated>2024-04-22T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Notcoin co-creator Sasha Plotvinov spoke with Decrypt's Sander Lutz at Token 2049 Dubai to discuss why the NOT token launch was pushed back from the original 4/20 target, when to expect the listing, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TON’s Justin Hyun Breaks Down The Importance of USDT Coming to Telegram]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ODQI6ACA/tons-justin-hyun-breaks-down-the-importance-of-usdt-coming-to-telegram</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ODQI6ACA/tons-justin-hyun-breaks-down-the-importance-of-usdt-coming-to-telegram"/>
        <updated>2024-04-19T10:14:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Token 2049 in Dubai, The Open Network’s director of investments sat down with Decrypt’s Sander Lutz to discuss what he sees as the game-changing integration of USDT onto TON, and his plans for getting Telegram’s 900 million users to start using crypto in the immediate future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Influencer Ansem Explains His Meme Coin Thesis and Why He’s Bullish on Bitcoin Runes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/u9DHFoK0/crypto-influencer-ansem-explains-his-meme-coin-thesis-and-why-hes-bullish-on-bitcoin-runes</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/u9DHFoK0/crypto-influencer-ansem-explains-his-meme-coin-thesis-and-why-hes-bullish-on-bitcoin-runes"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T21:56:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ansem, the crypto trader who's amassed a sizable following on the back of meme coin Dogwifhat (WIF) and other calls, chats with Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz at Token 2049 Dubai about his meme coin thesis, why he's bullish on Bitcoin Runes, and what he sees ahead for the crypto markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Sander Lutz Braves the Dubai Floods for a Crypto Conference]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/mtjVHGa3/decrypts-sander-lutz-braves-the-dubai-floods-for-a-crypto-conference</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/mtjVHGa3/decrypts-sander-lutz-braves-the-dubai-floods-for-a-crypto-conference"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T21:33:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz reports from Dubai amid a historic storm that flooded the famed city, trudging through the streets to complete his essential task: Attending the Token 2049 crypto conference.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gold Beats Its All Time High]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/6ULgUKVk/gold-beats-its-all-time-high</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/6ULgUKVk/gold-beats-its-all-time-high"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T09:53:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) maintains its trend of reaching higher lows amidst choppy market conditions. Exchange-traded funds (ETFs) witness another influx of $125 million. There's anticipation of Hong Kong approving ETFs for both Bitcoin and Ethereum (ETH) come Monday. Notable institutional investor BlackRock shows interest in Bitcoin. Recent filings reveal increased Bitcoin purchases by banks. A Bitcoin-friendly political party secures victory in the South Korean election. Analyst Kang predicts Bitcoin could surge to $80-100k by May. Meanwhile, Ethereum sees accumulation by stablecoin whales on the rise. A new Ethereum Improvement Proposal (EIP) aims to streamline signing requests. Solana (SOL) experiences a resurgence in activity, reaching yearly highs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NASA’s Next Deep Space Mission Won’t Use Artificial Intelligence]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/0WGP33Rp/nasas-next-deep-space-mission-wont-use-artificial-intelligence</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/0WGP33Rp/nasas-next-deep-space-mission-wont-use-artificial-intelligence"/>
        <updated>2024-04-13T18:42:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Thursday, Decrypt Media visited NASA's Jet Propulsion Laboratory in Pasadena, CA to meet with the Engineering team behind the Europa Clipper before its launch to Jupiter's Europa moon in October.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Do A Little with Weesh]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LnaOT9bF/we-do-a-little-with-weesh</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LnaOT9bF/we-do-a-little-with-weesh"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T07:46:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week’s episode, we did a little something different. We took the man who is usually behind the camera and put him in front of it. We sat down with our producer Weesh to dive into how in fell in love with art and became a collector, how he met Andy and fun childhood memories together, his biggest wins in crypto, and so much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside VanEck’s Crypto Takeover of the New York Stock Exchange]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9YAY4wGD/inside-vanecks-crypto-takeover-of-the-new-york-stock-exchange</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9YAY4wGD/inside-vanecks-crypto-takeover-of-the-new-york-stock-exchange"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T14:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worlds collide as Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz heads to the floor of the NYSE to witness a special closing bell ceremony hosted by VanEck in honor of Web3. Featuring Choose Rich Nick, VanEck Head of Web3 Matt Bartlett, and more!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wormhole Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9SNiIVfU/wormhole-wednesday</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9SNiIVfU/wormhole-wednesday"/>
        <updated>2024-04-07T17:42:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC hits $64.5K then rebounds, SOL outperforms. Government sends $2B BTC to Coinbase to sell. Funding rates stay low after sweep lower. ETFs see small inflow, Ark outflow more than GBTC. Wormhole W launches at $15B FDV. BTC ‘inflection point’ if it follows rates or gold. Gold & BTC very correlated for the last year. Expect slower ETF volume this month: Bloomberg. BTC 2x and 3x levered ETFs launch yesterday. BTC ETFs now half the size of gold.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>