<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-01-14T06:19:25.938Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-01-14T06:19:25.938Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blackrock CEO Larry Fink on Bitcoin: I’m a Big Believer — Its Bigger Than Any Government]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fe52243d</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/blackrock-ceo-larry-fink-on-bitcoin-im-a-big-believer-its-bigger-than-any-government/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-14T05:40:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Larry Fink, the CEO of Blackrock, the world’s largest asset manager, says he has become “a big believer” in bitcoin, emphasizing that it is “bigger than any government.” Calling the cryptocurrency “digital gold,” the executive stressed: “Unlike gold, where we manufacture new gold, we’re almost at the ceiling of the most of the amount of bitcoin that could be created.” Blackrock’s chief also sees value in having Ethereum exchange-traded funds (ETFs).
 
Blackrock CEO Larry Fink Is a ‘Big Believer’ in Bitcoin
 
Larry Fink, the CEO of Blackrock, the world’s largest asset manager, shared his outlook on bitcoin, crypto, and the spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) market, in an interview with CNBC and Fox Business Friday. Blackrock’s spot bitcoin ETF, the Ishares Bitcoin Trust (IBIT), was amo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop to shut down NFT marketplace due to regulatory limbo]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19174128/GameStop-to-shut-down-NFT-marketplace-due-to-regulatory-limbo</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19174128/GameStop-to-shut-down-NFT-marketplace-due-to-regulatory-limbo"/>
        <updated>2024-01-14T05:33:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop's decision to close its NFT marketplace comes after a series of cutbacks in its crypto services throughout the last two years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vanguard’s Exclusion of Spot Bitcoin ETFs Spurs Investor Exodus to Alternative Platforms]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19174117/Vanguards-Exclusion-of-Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-Spurs-Investor-Exodus-to-Alternative-Platforms</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19174117/Vanguards-Exclusion-of-Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-Spurs-Investor-Exodus-to-Alternative-Platforms"/>
        <updated>2024-01-14T05:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vanguard’s recent decision to exclude spot Bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) from its platform has raised...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Billion-Dollar Bank Clears Fake Check As Grieving Widow’s Bank Account Drained To -$5,034: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19174098/Billion-Dollar-Bank-Clears-Fake-Check-As-Grieving-Widows-Bank-Account-Drained-To-5034-Report</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19174098/Billion-Dollar-Bank-Clears-Fake-Check-As-Grieving-Widows-Bank-Account-Drained-To-5034-Report"/>
        <updated>2024-01-14T04:08:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An Indiana woman is issuing a warning after she was targeted by online scammers days after losing her husband. Selena Bell was grieving the loss of her husband Tyrone, who served three tours in Iraq and was awarded the Purple Heart, when she received a fraud alert via text message, reports CBS 2...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hedera Network commits over $400 million in HBAR]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19174087/Hedera-Network-commits-over-400-million-in-HBAR</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19174087/Hedera-Network-commits-over-400-million-in-HBAR"/>
        <updated>2024-01-14T03:48:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shaking up the crypto world with a bold move, the Hedera Global Governing Council has earmarked a colossal sum of 4.86 billion Hedera HBAR, translating to roughly $400 million, for pushing the boundaries of decentralized governance and network development. This isn’t just a financial strategy;...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Lawmaker Expects Donald Trump to Become ‘a Lot More’ Crypto Friendly in Second Term as President]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fe5a67e8</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/us-lawmaker-expects-donald-trump-to-become-a-lot-more-crypto-friendly-in-second-term-as-president/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-14T03:40:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Representative Tom Emmer expects former U.S. President Donald Trump to become “a lot more” friendly toward cryptocurrency if he returns to the White House. Trump has launched three non-fungible token (NFT) collections since leaving office. Meanwhile, some analysts predict that bitcoin’s price could reach record highs if Trump wins the presidential election this year.
 
Donald Trump Expected to Become Much More Crypto-Friendly
 
House Majority Whip Tom Emmer (R-MN) believes that former U.S. President Donald Trump’s potential return to the White House could usher in a regulatory landscape more favorable to the crypto industry. Emmer, who endorsed Trump in the 2024 Republican presidential primary, is a vocal crypto supporter. The congressman was quoted as saying:
 

If the second Trump a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BRICS’ banks ramps up effort to completely ditch dollar]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19174088/BRICS-banks-ramps-up-effort-to-completely-ditch-dollar</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19174088/BRICS-banks-ramps-up-effort-to-completely-ditch-dollar"/>
        <updated>2024-01-14T03:33:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The BRICS nations, a coalition of five major emerging economies, are boldly steering towards a future less reliant on the US dollar. This move, characterized by the launch of substantial funding initiatives in local currencies, marks a significant pivot in the global financial landscape....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morgan Stanley Exec’s Take on Bitcoin: ‘From an Internet Forum Idea to a Sovereign Reserve Asset’]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19174083/Morgan-Stanley-Execs-Take-on-Bitcoin-From-an-Internet-Forum-Idea-to-a-Sovereign-Reserve-Asset</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19174083/Morgan-Stanley-Execs-Take-on-Bitcoin-From-an-Internet-Forum-Idea-to-a-Sovereign-Reserve-Asset"/>
        <updated>2024-01-14T03:32:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Andrew Peel, Head of Digital Asset Markets at Morgan Stanley, recently published an article discussing the evolving role of digital assets like Bitcoin, stablecoins, and Central Bank Digital Currencies (CBDCs) in the global financial system. His analysis delves into how these innovations could...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BRICS targets $5 billion in exports for 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19174075/BRICS-targets-5-billion-in-exports-for-2024</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19174075/BRICS-targets-5-billion-in-exports-for-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-01-14T03:23:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The BRICS bloc, a robust economic alliance, is on a steadfast march towards a landmark target of $5 billion in exports for 2024, a move that might rattle the US dollar’s dominance. This goal is not just a number; it’s a chess move in the intricate game of global economics. With the backdrop of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wall Street’s Bitcoin infiltration sparks frustration]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19174073/Wall-Streets-Bitcoin-infiltration-sparks-frustration</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19174073/Wall-Streets-Bitcoin-infiltration-sparks-frustration"/>
        <updated>2024-01-14T03:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin vs. asset managers: Can they actually coexist peacefully?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19174068/Bitcoin-vs-asset-managers-Can-they-actually-coexist-peacefully</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19174068/Bitcoin-vs-asset-managers-Can-they-actually-coexist-peacefully"/>
        <updated>2024-01-14T03:05:56.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tron decouples from the market – What next for TRX?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19174060/Tron-decouples-from-the-market-What-next-for-TRX</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19174060/Tron-decouples-from-the-market-What-next-for-TRX"/>
        <updated>2024-01-14T02:30:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tron’s daily chart turned green while it achieved a new milestone, reflecting its rising adoption and usage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock & Fidelity Top Bitcoin ETF Inflow: $1B in Two Days]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19174055/BlackRock-Fidelity-Top-Bitcoin-ETF-Inflow-1B-in-Two-Days</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19174055/BlackRock-Fidelity-Top-Bitcoin-ETF-Inflow-1B-in-Two-Days"/>
        <updated>2024-01-14T02:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock and Fidelity dominate the Bitcoin ETF scene, securing over half the cash influx.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blackrock’s Spot Bitcoin ETF Now Holds 11,439 BTC]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fe4293e2</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/blackrocks-spot-bitcoin-etf-now-holds-11439-btc/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-14T01:38:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blackrock’s spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) has acquired 11,439 bitcoin, with a market value of nearly $500 million, within two days of trading on the Nasdaq stock exchange. Blackrock’s Ishares Bitcoin Trust was among the 11 spot bitcoin ETFs approved by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) this week.
 
Ishares Bitcoin Trust’s BTC Holdings
 
Blackrock’s spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF), the Ishares Bitcoin Trust (IBIT), now holds 11,439 bitcoin.
 
According to Ishares ETFs’ website, IBIT’s holdings comprised 11,439.2198 bitcoin with a market value of $497,994,992.41 as of Jan. 12. The largest cryptocurrency now represents 99.99% of the trust holdings. Blackrock explained: “The value shown for ‘shares’ represents [the] total number of bitcoins held by the Ishares…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Chair Gensler addresses X account hack in statement: ‘Still assessing the impacts’]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19174040/SEC-Chair-Gensler-addresses-X-account-hack-in-statement-Still-assessing-the-impacts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19174040/SEC-Chair-Gensler-addresses-X-account-hack-in-statement-Still-assessing-the-impacts"/>
        <updated>2024-01-14T01:28:56.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frantic Customer Calls JPMorgan Chase As $10,700 Exits Bank Account – Now the Banking Giant Says It’s Not To Blame: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19174036/Frantic-Customer-Calls-JPMorgan-Chase-As-10700-Exits-Bank-Account-Now-the-Banking-Giant-Says-Its-Not-To-Blame-Report</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19174036/Frantic-Customer-Calls-JPMorgan-Chase-As-10700-Exits-Bank-Account-Now-the-Banking-Giant-Says-Its-Not-To-Blame-Report"/>
        <updated>2024-01-14T01:04:16.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized Exchange Altcoin Flashing Signs of Upcoming Rally, Says Crypto Trader – Here’s His Forecast]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19174031/Decentralized-Exchange-Altcoin-Flashing-Signs-of-Upcoming-Rally-Says-Crypto-Trader-Heres-His-Forecast</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19174031/Decentralized-Exchange-Altcoin-Flashing-Signs-of-Upcoming-Rally-Says-Crypto-Trader-Heres-His-Forecast"/>
        <updated>2024-01-14T01:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum: Should holders wait before selling ETH for profits]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19174026/Ethereum-Should-holders-wait-before-selling-ETH-for-profits</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19174026/Ethereum-Should-holders-wait-before-selling-ETH-for-profits"/>
        <updated>2024-01-14T00:30:24.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terra’s Do Kwon Seeks Trial Delay, Citing Extradition Holdup]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fe4afc30</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/terras-do-kwon-seeks-trial-delay-citing-extradition-holdup/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-13T23:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Labs co-founder Do Kwon has requested that the judge in his fraud case delay the trial date, currently set for Jan. 29, 2024, because Kwon is still tied up in extradition proceedings in Montenegro.
 
Terra’s Do Kwon Requests Trial Postponement Due to Extradition Issues
 
In a letter to U.S. District Judge Jed Rakoff dated Jan. 11, Kwon’s lawyers said they had hoped he would be extradited in time for the trial but that now appears unlikely until February or March. The letter was first shared by Inner City Press reporter Matthew Russell Lee. Kwon and his legal team said in the letter that he wishes to attend the trial in person but needs more time for the extradition process to play out.
 
“Unfortunately, it now appears that Mr. Kwon is not likely to be extradited until February or March at the earliest. We understand the court cannot put the trial on hold indefinitely, but an adjournment until mid-March would provide a realistic possibility for Mr. Kwon to attend,” the letter states.
 
The request comes after a Montenegro appeals court in December overturned an earlier ruling approving Kwon’s extradition to the U.S. to face charges related to the spectacular collapse in 2022 of the Terra ecosystem and its signature stablecoin terrausd (UST). Federal prosecutors charged Kwon with various counts of fraud for his role in developing the stablecoin and blockchain system.
 
 
Kwon’s lawyer said in the letter that if the judge declines to postpone the trial date, Kwon intends to ask that the jury receive an instruction about his absence that is fair to him. The letter indicates Kwon strongly desires to be present for the fraud trial stemming from the implosion of his brainchild that cost investors billions of dollars in the aftermath.
 
What do you think about Do Kwon’s latest request? Share your thoughts and opinions about this subject in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop axes NFT marketplace, citing regulatory uncertainty]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19173965/GameStop-axes-NFT-marketplace-citing-regulatory-uncertainty</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19173965/GameStop-axes-NFT-marketplace-citing-regulatory-uncertainty"/>
        <updated>2024-01-13T23:09:43.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk’s Tesla Supercharging Station Which Will Accept Dogecoin Payments Set To Open – Details]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fe35109c</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/elon-musk-tesla-dogecoin-payments/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-13T23:08:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin (DOGE) is set to gain another use case thanks to the world’s richest man, Elon Musk. This comes following a revelation that the foremost meme coin will be a payment when one of Musk’s groundbreaking projects finally launches. 
 
Dogecoin To Be Accepted When This Tesla Project Launches 
 
DogeMemeGirl, a member of the Dogecoin community, recently drew the community’s attention to the fact that DOGE was going to be accepted when Tesla’s supercharging station in Hollywood finally launched. Her comment came as another X (formerly Twitter) user provided an update on the station, which was already coming together and could launch this year.
 
 
Indeed, DOGE is going to be a payment option when this happens. Musk himself confirmed in an X post in 2022 that customers will be able to pay w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock scoops up 11,500 BTC during dip as ETF leads the pack]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19173964/BlackRock-scoops-up-11500-BTC-during-dip-as-ETF-leads-the-pack</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19173964/BlackRock-scoops-up-11500-BTC-during-dip-as-ETF-leads-the-pack"/>
        <updated>2024-01-13T23:06:11.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk’s Tesla Supercharging Station Which Will Accept Dogecoin Payments Set To Open – Details]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19173962/Elon-Musks-Tesla-Supercharging-Station-Which-Will-Accept-Dogecoin-Payments-Set-To-Open-Details</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19173962/Elon-Musks-Tesla-Supercharging-Station-Which-Will-Accept-Dogecoin-Payments-Set-To-Open-Details"/>
        <updated>2024-01-13T23:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analyst: Vanguard May Reconsider Bitcoin Stance as Cryptocurrency Gains Momentum]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19173949/Analyst-Vanguard-May-Reconsider-Bitcoin-Stance-as-Cryptocurrency-Gains-Momentum</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19173949/Analyst-Vanguard-May-Reconsider-Bitcoin-Stance-as-Cryptocurrency-Gains-Momentum"/>
        <updated>2024-01-13T22:36:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vanguard, a prominent investment firm, is currently at the center of speculation regarding a potential shift in its long-standing anti-Bitcoin stance. According to insights from Bloomberg’s senior analyst, Eric Balchunas, the investment firm may be reevaluating its position on Bitcoin as market...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 Apps Surged 124% in 2023, According to DappRadar]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19173936/Web3-Apps-Surged-124-in-2023-According-to-DappRadar</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19173936/Web3-Apps-Surged-124-in-2023-According-to-DappRadar"/>
        <updated>2024-01-13T22:10:31.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Bitcoin Flashes and Fades as ETFs Launch—But Ethereum Soars]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212773</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212773/this-week-coins-bitcoin-fanaticism-flashes-fades-etfs-launch-ethereum-soars"/>
        <updated>2024-01-13T21:38:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin's big week was a rollercoaster. Ethereum closed up. And the rest of the top five were largely flat for the past seven days.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Kawailani Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance and Coinbase Hold 11% of Crypto Economy’s Net Value, Leading in BTC and ETH Reserves]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fe3c04dd</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/binance-and-coinbase-hold-11-of-crypto-economys-net-value-leading-in-btc-and-eth-reserves/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-13T21:34:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Statistical data reveals that Binance and Coinbase, two titans in the cryptocurrency exchange arena, cumulatively possess 11.85% of the $1.68 trillion digital currency economy. In addition, these prominent trading platforms control 7.83% of the total bitcoin supply, underscoring their significant market influence.
 
Binance and Coinbase’s Market Grip
 
Binance and Coinbase rank as the world’s leading crypto exchanges in terms of their daily trading volumes and the cryptocurrency reserves they manage. In the most recent 24-hour period on Saturday, Binance led with a substantial $15.87 billion in trading activity, while Coinbase, securing its position as the weekend’s second-largest exchange, saw $2.91 billion in trades.
 
Onchain data sourced from Arkham Intelligence further reveals that th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Will Make Workers More Effective But Adapting to Its Rapid Spread Is ‘Scary’: Sam Altman]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212793</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212793/sam-altman-openai-bill-gates-microsoft"/>
        <updated>2024-01-13T20:35:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI CEO Sam Altman sat down with Bill Gates to explore the positive potential and threats of artificial intelligence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Takes A Hit As It’s Dropped From Hong Kong’s Top 5 Crypto Index]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fe3b1c34</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/xrp-hong-kong-crypto-index/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-13T20:05:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XRP has taken a significant hit in its Hong Kong Virtual Asset Consortium (HKVAC) has announced the official delisting of the token, from the top five global large cryptocurrency index. 
 
HKVAC Delists XRP And Adds Solana
 
The Hong Kong Virtual Asset Rating Agency (HKVAC) has made the decision to remove XRP from its previous ranking in the top 5 largest cryptocurrency index list. This adjustment mirrors the altcoin’s decline from the top-performing cryptocurrencies with the largest market capitalization globally. 
 
 
Adding to the setback, HKVAC has disclosed it will be replacing XRP’s position with Solana (SOL). The Hong Kong-based consortium has stated a reorganization of its index effective by January 19, 2024. 
 
Earlier in December 2023, Solana overtook XRP to become the fifth-larg…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$311 Million in NFT Sales Amidst Fluctuating Blockchain and Collection Performances]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fe230e59</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/311-million-in-nft-sales-amidst-fluctuating-blockchain-and-collection-performances/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-13T18:33:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the last week, the non-fungible token (NFT) market experienced unremarkable sales, totaling $311.31 million. This figure represents a slight uptick of just 0.05% from the previous week. Despite this, Bitcoin NFT sales have consistently outperformed other blockchain networks since November 2023. However, it’s noteworthy that NFT sales on the Bitcoin blockchain have decreased by 19.12% compared to the previous week.
 
Weekly NFT Sales Reach $311 Million With Bitcoin Leading, Ethereum and Polygon See Impressive Growth
 
Data from cryptoslam.io over the past seven days shows that NFT sales reached $311.31 million. However, there was a significant decrease in market participation: the number of NFT buyers fell by 69.40%, and the number of sellers declined by 68.09% during the same period.
 
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Across-the-Board Crypto Stock Declines Erode Earlier Profit Streaks]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fe15b657</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/across-the-board-crypto-stock-declines-erode-earlier-profit-streaks/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-13T16:42:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Although spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds saw substantial trading activity on Thursday and Friday, publicly-listed crypto companies faced a different fate, with several equities experiencing significant losses when the market closed on Friday. For instance, Marathon Digital Holdings’ shares plummeted by over 15%, while Coinbase Global’s stock registered a loss of more than 7% during trading sessions before the weekend.
 
Extensive Range of Publicly-Listed Crypto Firms Grapple With Share Declines
 
The 11 spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) have collectively achieved $7.65 billion in trading volume since their listing. However, despite the strong trading activity, bitcoin’s spot market value experienced a 7% decline against the U.S. dollar during Friday’s trading sessions.
 
Additio…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brace For Impact: MicroStrategy’s Michael Saylor Is Selling Shares To Buy More Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fe114521</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/microstrategy-saylor-buy-bitcoin/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-13T16:09:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy’s co-founder Micheal Saylor looks to be building a ‘Bitcoin Strategy’ of his own. This can deduced from a recent report, which shows that he has begun to sell off some of his company’s stocks in a bid to acquire more of the flagship cryptocurrency. 
 
Saylor Sells MicroStrategy Shares
 
According to a Bloomberg report, Michael Saylor sold between 3,882 and 5,000 MicroStrategy shares on certain days leading up to the SEC’s approval of the Spot Bitcoin ETFs. These sales are reported to have earned the company’s co-founder over $20 million in total. This is said to be the first time that he has sold shares in nearly 12 years. 
 
 
Saylor will be using some of the profits made from these sales to invest in Bitcoin. Bitcoinist had previously reported Saylor’s plan to sell up to 31…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Play Super Nintendo and Other Classic Games on Bitcoin—Here’s How]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212729</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212729/you-can-play-super-nintendo-classic-games-bitcoin-heres-how"/>
        <updated>2024-01-13T16:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks to Ordinals, you can find working video games inscribed on the Bitcoin blockchain. Here’s how to play them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GBTC’s Closing NAV Discount and Steep Fees Trigger Outflows, ETF Analyst Expects ‘More Over Time’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fe1a8416</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/gbtcs-closing-nav-discount-and-steep-fees-trigger-outflows-etf-analyst-expects-more-over-time/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-13T14:41:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week, the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) greenlit the debut of 11 diverse spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs), which, in their initial two days on the market, experienced a substantial $7.65 billion in trading volume. Concurrently, while a host of new entrants enjoyed strong inflows, Grayscale’s GBTC encountered notable outflows, coinciding with the fund’s discount to net asset value reaching its lowest point since February 2021. 
 
Reduced NAV Discount Prompts GBTC Outflows
 
On Saturday, Eric Balchunas, the senior ETF analyst for Bloomberg, shared insights on the “nine newborn” spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs), which have impressively gathered $1.4 billion in cash. Balchunas observed that this surge in capital markedly outstrips the $579 million outflow…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nike Will 'Go Way Deeper' Into Video Game Fashion Amid NFT Push]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212723</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212723/nike-will-go-way-deeper-video-game-fashion-amid-nft-push"/>
        <updated>2024-01-13T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nike says it will continue to expand into video game wearables through its .Swoosh platform, but it's unclear if there will be more NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETFs Under Fire As Renowned Investor Slams Them As ‘Useless’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fe0099e8</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-etfs-investor-slams-them-as-useless/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-13T13:39:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a move that sent ripples through the Bitcoin community, renowned investor and Shark Tank personality Kevin O’Leary doused the flames of hype surrounding the recent approval of Spot Bitcoin ETFs, labeling them “practically useless” for institutional investors.
 
But amidst his skepticism, O’Leary offered a ray of sunshine for Bitcoin’s long-term prospects, predicting a significant price surge by 2030.
 
O’Leary: ETFs Fee Concerns, Predicts Shakeout
 
O’Leary’s main gripe with Spot ETFs? Fees. He argues that the charges levied by issuers, even with temporary waivers, render them an unattractive proposition for sophisticated investors who can simply hold Bitcoin directly.
 
 
 
Kevin O’Leary on Bitcoin ETF  pic.twitter.com/p0avcOEV7N
 
— Altcoin Daily (@AltcoinDailyio) January 12, 2024
 

…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Near Foundation Cuts Staff by 40%, CEO Says Organization Is in Good Financial Health]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fe0e1bb8</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/near-foundation-cuts-staff-by-40-ceo-says-organization-is-in-good-financial-health/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-13T12:42:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NEAR Foundation recently said it has let go of 35 workers as part of a realignment exercise that sees it “focus on a narrower and higher-impact set of activities.” The foundation’s CEO insisted that the job cuts did not in any way indicate that his organization was facing financial challenges.
 
The NEAR Foundation’s Record-Breaking Year
 
The NEAR Foundation announced on Jan. 11 that it had cut its staff by approximately 40% as part of a realignment process that will see it “focus on a narrower and higher-impact set of activities.” Illia Polosukhin, the CEO of the Swiss-based nonprofit foundation, has however pledged to help the 35 employees find other opportunities in the Web3 industry.
 
According to his letter addressed to the NEAR community, the job cuts are coming off the back of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Senators Demand Investigation Into Hack Of SEC’s X Account – Details]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fe0a8fb2</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/us-senators-demand-investigation-into-hack-of-secs-x-account-details/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-13T11:57:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US Senator and Chairman of the Senate Finance Committee, Ron Wyden, has requested an official investigation into the recent hack of the X account of the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). The letter is co-written by prominent crypto advocate Cynthia Lummis and will also seek to begin a probe into the SEC’s failure to employ the best cybersecurity measures to protect its digital presence.
 
 
SEC X Account Hack Draws Criticisms From US Senators
 
On January 9, the X account of the SEC made a surprise announcement confirming the approval of Bitcoin spot ETF trading in the US. This statement was quickly countered by the SEC’s Chairman Gary Gensler, who stated the commission’s X handle had been compromised and the ETF-related announcement was false. 
 
Although the SEC eventually app…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Semilore Faleti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Partners With Yellow Card to Expand Access to Its Products in 20 African Countries]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fff7fb26</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/coinbase-partners-with-yellow-card-to-expand-access-to-its-products-in-20-african-countries/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-13T11:01:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The leading crypto exchange Coinbase has said it will expand access to its products to 20 African countries. Coinbase also claimed that its partnership arrangement with the Africa-focused crypto exchange Yellow Card can help increase financial freedom in countries where it is lacking.
 
Increasing Financial Freedom
 
On Jan. 11, 2024, Coinbase, the U.S. cryptocurrency exchange, announced that it will expand access to its products to 20 African countries. According to a statement by Coinbase, users from the selected African countries will be able to “purchase USDC directly in our [Coinbase] Wallet app starting in February” through its partnership with the Africa-focused stablecoin platform Yellow Card.
 
As part of the arrangement, Yellow Card users will be able to acquire the stablecoin US…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Starkware CEO Uri Kolodny Steps Down Due to Family Health Issues]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74ffffb835</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/starkware-ceo-uri-kolodny-steps-down-due-to-family-health-issues/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-13T09:40:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starkware faces a leadership transition as CEO Uri Kolodny resigns over pressing family health issues. While stepping down, Kolodny leaves the company in the hands of co-founder and friend Eli Ben-Sasson.
 
Starkware Sees CEO Change as Uri Kolodny Resigns, Citing Family Health
 
Uri Kolodny, CEO of Starkware, announced his resignation from the company’s top position due to pressing family health concerns. Kolodny, who co-founded the Ethereum scaling and privacy technology firm in 2008 with Eli Ben-Sasson, made the announcement via X.
 
In the announcement post, Kolodny expressed both pride in Starkware’s achievements and sorrow at stepping back from day-to-day involvement. “I am so very proud of what we’ve built. First and foremost: the people who have joined us in building Starkware and S…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Sencil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s Why Bitcoin Price Fell To Below $42,000 Following ETF Approval: Asset Manager]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74ffe4856f</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/why-bitcoin-price-fell-to-below-42000-etf-approval/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-13T08:48:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bitcoin price has been experiencing significant downward pressure since the Securities and Exchange Commission approved the trading of spot exchange-traded funds in the United States. The premier cryptocurrency fell below $42,000 on Friday, January 12, reflecting a decline of 7% in the past 24 hours.
 
The underwhelming performance of the Bitcoin price since BTC spot ETFs commenced trading has been a major source of concern for investors and crypto enthusiasts. Anthony Scaramucci, founder of SkyBridge Capital, has weighed in with the possible reasons for the struggling price of the flagship cryptocurrency after such positive development.
 
Why Bitcoin Price Fell Below The $42,000 Mark
 
In a recent interview with Bloomberg, Scaramucci gave his opinion on why the Bitcoin price has been …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Opeyemi Sule</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Venezuelan Petro Reportedly on the Brink of Liquidation]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74ffe0052b</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/venezuelan-petro-reportedly-on-the-brink-of-liquidation/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-13T08:10:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to local sources, one of the first state-backed cryptocurrency assets, the Venezuelan Petro, would be facing an imminent liquidation. Asonacrip, a national cryptocurrency association, reported having information about the upcoming liquidation process, including the automatic exchange of the Petro balance to bolivares, the Venezuelan fiat currency.
Venezuelan Petro to Be Liquidated
The life of the Venezuelan petro, one of the first state-backed cryptocurrencies, might be ending soon. According to reports from Asonacrip, a Venezuelan cryptocurrency group, the government would be preparing to liquidate all the petros in circulation, automatically exchanging them for bolivares, the Venezuelan fiat currency.
The information coincides with the liquidation of other crypto assets held by…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Argentina Registers First Bitcoin Settled Lease Agreement]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74ffef9fd8</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/argentina-registers-first-bitcoin-settled-lease-agreement/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-13T06:41:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Argentina has registered one of its first lease agreements denominated in bitcoin after the application of the emergency executive order issued by President Javier Milei, which opened the door for this kind of settlement. The agreement stipulates that the tenant must pay the $100 USDT worth of bitcoin to the property’s landlord each month.
Argentina Starts Implementing Bitcoin-Settled Lease Agreements
Argentina has reached a milestone in crypto adoption, registering one of the first contracts involving bitcoin payments. According to La Capital, a local Argentine news outlet, the first Bitcoin-settled lease agreement was recently signed in Rosario City.
The agreement stipulates that the tenant will pay the equivalent of $100 USDT in Bitcoin to the landlord each month, having selected Fiwind…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Chair Gensler’s Approval Of Bitcoin ETFs Met With Criticism And Contradictions]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74ffeaa1d4</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/sec-chair-bitcoin-etfs-criticism-and-contradictions/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-13T06:05:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Chair Gary Gensler’s recent approval of Bitcoin ETFs has stirred up controversy as he simultaneously voiced criticism and unfounded claims against Bitcoin and the broader crypto industry.
 
 In a CNBC interview, Gensler made statements that raised eyebrows among industry participants.
 
Bitcoin ETFs Approval Fails To Shift Genler’s Stance On Crypto
 
While acknowledging the approval of the ETFs, Gensler emphasized that the SEC does not endorse or approve Bitcoin itself. The SEC chair referred to Bitcoin as a “speculative and volatile asset”, highlighting its alleged use for illicit activities and money laundering. 
 
Gensler dismissed the notion that Bitcoin can serve as a store of value or a widely accepted payment method, implying that its prim…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Chair Gary Gensler Recaps Takeover of Agency's Twitter Account]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212765</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212765/sec-chair-gary-gensler-addresses-cyberattack-on-agencys-twitter-account"/>
        <updated>2024-01-13T00:49:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The agency head gave an update on the investigation into a cyberattack that falsely announced Bitcoin ETF approvals earlier this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop Bails on Crypto Gaming, Killing NFT Marketplace]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212761</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212761/gamestop-bails-on-crypto-gaming-killing-nft-marketplace"/>
        <updated>2024-01-13T00:21:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The news comes four months after the storied video game retailer axed its NFT wallet, with GameStop set to exit the space entirely.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Is ’Bigger Than Any Government’: BlackRock CEO Larry Fink]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212727</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212727/bitcoin-bigger-than-any-government-blackrock-ceo-larry-fink"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T23:16:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a Fox Business interview, the former Bitcoin skeptic defended the cryptocurrency as a shield against government manipulation and economic instability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Super Mario AI Hologram Is Creeping People Out in Vegas]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212708</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212708/super-mario-ai-hologram-creeping-people-out-vegas"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T21:21:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The unauthorized AI hologram of gaming icon Super Mario becomes a viral sensation at CES, dubbed an "abomination" by one visitor.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Game Over: More Than 30% of Crypto Games Have Been Discontinued]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212689</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212689/game-over-more-than-30-percent-crypto-games-discontinued"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T19:39:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New research documents a slew of inactive crypto and NFT games that have been abandoned or otherwise inactive for months.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gary Gensler Remains Cagey on Ethereum, Punts on Potential ETF]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212681</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212681/gary-gensler-remains-cagey-ethereum-punts-potential-etf"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T18:45:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On a CNBC segment this morning, the SEC chair also remained vague about Ethereum's status as a security following Bitcoin ETF approvals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Game 'Nyan Heroes' Hits Epic Store Ahead of Airdrop]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212680</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212680/solana-game-nyan-heroes-hits-epic-store-ahead-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T18:17:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nyan Heroes pairs cats and crypto in a Fortnite-like battle royale shooter on Solana, with big moves apparently ahead in 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Plunges on Day Two of ETF Mania as Liquidations Soar]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212671</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212671/bitcoin-plunges-day-two-etf-mania-liquidations-soar"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T17:16:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bitcoin ETF buzz calmed Friday as the leading cryptocurrency dipped down near $43,000. Are traders selling the news after the frenzy?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Genesis Pays $8 Million and Forfeits BitLicense to Settle New York Charges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212656</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212656/genesis-pays-8-million-and-forfeits-bitlicense-to-settle-new-york-charges"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T16:27:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Genesis Trading has had its BitLicense since 2018.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Rallies as BlackRock Boss Eyes ETH ETF After Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212662</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212662/ethereum-rallies-blackrock-boss-eyes-eth-etf-after-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T16:17:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Analysts think an ETH ETF is now a slam dunk, sending Ethereum pumping 18% in the last week amid the Bitcoin ETF rollout in the U.S.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinShares Acquires Valkyrie Funds—And the BRRR Bitcoin ETF With It]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212627</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212627/coinshares-acquires-valkyrie-funds-brrr-bitcoin-etf"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T15:38:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The acquisition includes the Valkyrie Bitcoin Fund, which trades under the BRRR ticker on Nasdaq.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taproot Wizards Launch Quantum Cats Collection As Bitcoin Inscriptions]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212594</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212594/taproot-wizards-launch-quantum-cats-bitcoin-ordinals-collection"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T15:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 3,333-image images on the Bitcoin blockchain cost $66,000 to create.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taki Brings Play-to-Earn Mobile Games to Polygon After Merger, Acquisitions]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212607</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212607/taki-brings-play-earn-mobile-games-polygon-after-merger-acquisitions"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T13:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After launching a social app on Solana, Taki Games has merged with Unite, has a new CEO, and is launching Polygon mobile games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terra Co-Founder Do Kwon Requests SEC Trial Delay So He Can Attend]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212616</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212616/terras-do-kwon-requests-sec-trial-delay-so-he-can-attend"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T13:14:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lawyers for Kwon said that an adjournment to mid-March "would provide a realistic possibility" for him to attend.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elizabeth Warren: SEC 'Wrong on the Law' Over Bitcoin ETF Approval]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212614</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212614/elizabeth-warren-sec-wrong-on-the-law-over-bitcoin-etf-approval"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T10:48:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Senator claimed that the SEC had let crypto "burrow even deeper into our financial system," and pressed for AML rules.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generative Art Across Mediums: Artists Discuss the Evolving Space]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/GK3aN0zo/generative-art-across-mediums-artists-discuss-the-evolving-space</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/GK3aN0zo/generative-art-across-mediums-artists-discuss-the-evolving-space"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T02:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this panel discussion from Rug Radio's R Haus at Art Basel Miami 2023, Sofia Garcia, Ismail Tazi, Emily Edelman, and Aleksandra Art discuss the expanding generative art space—and why "generative" doesn't necessarily have to mean digital.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI-Backed 1X Wants to Put a Humanoid Robot to Work in Your Home]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212584</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212584/household-robots-1x-neo-eve-himanoid-biped"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T01:45:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The robotics company raised $100 million to build NEO, its second bipedal robot design that can perform domestic tasks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These Are All the Bitcoin ETFs That Are Now Trading in the US]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=62912</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/62912/high-profile-bitcoin-etf-applications"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T23:44:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spot Bitcoin ETFs are finally trading in the United States following SEC approval. Here are all the Bitcoin ETFs you can invest in today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves,Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nintendo Switch 2 Preview: Everything You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197793</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197793/nintendo-switch-2-rumors-leaks-latest-news"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T23:15:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATED: More and more signs are pointing to a release window for the Nintendo Switch 2. Here's the latest about Nintendo's next console.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Gas Hero' NFTs Top Charts—But the 'Stepn' Maker's Game Is Blocked in the US]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212500</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212500/gas-hero-nfts-top-charts-but-stepn-maker-game-blocked-us"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T22:36:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gas Hero, the latest NFT game from Find Satoshi Lab, is blocking players in 16 regions around the world, including the United States.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETFs Start With a Bang: $4.5 Billion on Day One of Trading]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212570</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212570/bitcoin-etf-4-billion-day-one-trading"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T22:19:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock stole the show, but Grayscale may have been the biggest winner. The crypto-native fund enjoyed its best day of trading ever.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Axie Infinity' Caps SLP Token Supply—Can It Revitalize the Play-to-Earn Game?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212564</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212564/axie-infinity-caps-slp-token-supply-revitalize-play-earn-game"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T21:56:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Axie Infinity's SLP or Smooth Love Potion token is getting a rework, including a capped supply and a "stability fund" to support it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pocket AI Gadget R1 Sells Out, Despite Social Media Snark]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212540</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212540/r1-rabbit-tech-pocket-ai-companion-ces"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T21:11:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CES is all about AI this year, and a new device sold 10,000 units in one day—even though it was unclear what you were buying.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Buy a Bitcoin ETF]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212493</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212493/how-to-buy-bitcoin-etf"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T20:43:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What are Bitcoin ETFs? How do they differ from stocks and how can you buy one? Here’s everything you need to know.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETFs Notch $1.9B in Trading Volume—But Merrill Lynch, Vanguard Won’t List]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212523</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212523/bitcoin-etfs-notch-1-9b-in-trading-volume-merrill-lynch-vanguard-wont-list"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T19:48:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The newly approved Bitcoin ETFs reached $1.9 billion worth of volume by midday, with BlackRock and Fidelity leading the pack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Did You Forget to Pay Crypto Taxes? IRS Is Letting You Off the Hook—Kinda]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212324</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212324/crypto-taxes-irs-waives-penalties"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T19:30:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The IRS is waiving penalties on unpaid taxes, crypto and otherwise, on 2020 and 2021 returns. Taxpayers have until March to make good.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETFs Are Here—When Ethereum ETF?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212478</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212478/bitcoin-etfs-are-here-when-ethereum-etf"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T17:23:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After the historic approval of a spot Bitcoin ETF on Wednesday, analysts say a spot ETH ETF could be imminent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Nears $49,000 for First Time Since 2021 as ETFs Start Trading]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212479</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212479/bitcoin-nears-49k-first-time-since-2021-etfs-start-trading"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T16:12:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The spike comes as spot Bitcoin ETFs launch on Wall Street for the first time ever, following Wednesday's long-awaited SEC approval.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Got a Solana Saga Before They Sold Out? Here Are All the Airdrops You Can Claim]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210634</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210634/solana-saga-airdrops-tokens-nfts-you-can-claim"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T16:06:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATED: Solana Saga owners keep racking in the perks, including valuable Saga Monkes NFTs and SAMO tokens. Here's everything you can claim.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fortnite Players Can Still Claim Part of a $245 Million Settlement—Here's Who Is Eligible]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197988</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197988/how-to-get-a-refund-for-fortnite-from-epic-games"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T15:34:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATED: Epic Games is paying out nearly a quarter of a billion dollars in refunds to Fortnite players, and the deadline for filing claims has now been extended.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitfinity Aims to Enhance Bitcoin Ordinals With An Ethereum Virtual Machine On ICP]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212411</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212411/bitfinity-aims-to-enhance-bitcoin-ordinals-with-ethereum-virtual-machine-integration-on-icp"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitfinity unveils a plan to integrate EVM with the Bitcoin blockchain, targeting DeFi services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The AI Coin to Rule Them All with Mike Grantis]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rkYpU8TJ/the-ai-coin-to-rule-them-all-with-mike-grantis</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rkYpU8TJ/the-ai-coin-to-rule-them-all-with-mike-grantis"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T18:46:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reza is joined by Mike Grantis from Contango Digital to discuss
- The AI coin to rule them all
- The Solana Ecosystem 
- What's next for Solana airdrops]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conversation With Snowfro: Bringing 'Chromie Squiggle' #8107 to the Physical Space]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DcrU04gG/conversation-with-snowfro-bringing-chromie-squiggle-8107-to-the-physical-space</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DcrU04gG/conversation-with-snowfro-bringing-chromie-squiggle-8107-to-the-physical-space"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Art Blocks founder and CEO and "Chromie Squiggle" project creator Erick "snowfro" Calderon spoke with Benny Redbeard Gross at Rug Radio's R Haus event at Art Basel 2023, to discuss how and why "Chromie Squiggle" NFT #8107 was given a special edition print run in collaboration with Avant Arte.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don't Underestimate Mobile Gaming: Qualcomm's Matthew Grossman]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/34Oil4Qu/dont-underestimate-mobile-gaming-qualcomms-matthew-grossman</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/34Oil4Qu/dont-underestimate-mobile-gaming-qualcomms-matthew-grossman"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Qualcomm product marketing manager Matthew Grossman tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin why mobile esports is exploding in popularity around the world—and dispels some of the misconceptions around mobile gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF: This Is the 'Calm Before the Storm', Says ETF Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/VOX04ytt/bitcoin-etf-this-is-the-calm-before-the-storm-says-etf-analyst</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/VOX04ytt/bitcoin-etf-this-is-the-calm-before-the-storm-says-etf-analyst"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T20:20:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bloomberg Senior ETF Analyst Eric Balchunas joins Farokh Sarmad, Michael Anderson, and Ovie Faruq on the FOMO Hour to share the latest intel on the looming approval for a spot Bitcoin ETF, what might happen when the very different worlds of TradFi and crypto collide, and his insights on “Genslish,” the unique and strategic language of SEC chair Gary Gensler.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Losing 1500 BTC on Mt Gox and the Problem with Women in Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/EfNuNu8a/losing-1500-btc-on-mt-gox-and-the-problem-with-women-in-web3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/EfNuNu8a/losing-1500-btc-on-mt-gox-and-the-problem-with-women-in-web3"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T19:02:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week our host is joined by Brooke Lacey! 

They discuss:  
- Making and losing generational wealth
- Trauma Bond
- Women in Web3
- The Problem with WAGMI]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ESL Faceit Group Exploring Blockchain 'Opportunistically,' Says Exec]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/yvrs4lBx/esl-faceit-group-exploring-blockchain-opportunistically-says-exec</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/yvrs4lBx/esl-faceit-group-exploring-blockchain-opportunistically-says-exec"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T02:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Braithwaite—ESL Faceit Group's VP of Game Ecosystems, Mobile, and Snapdragon Pro Series—shares the esports firm's approach to blockchain technology with GG's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bryan Johnson Explains His Quest for Immortality and Why He Started with the Penis]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tAwP55g9/bryan-johnson-explains-his-quest-for-immortality-and-why-he-started-with-the-penis</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tAwP55g9/bryan-johnson-explains-his-quest-for-immortality-and-why-he-started-with-the-penis"/>
        <updated>2023-12-24T19:38:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Billionaire biohacker Bryan Johnson shared with Decrypt's Jason Nelson why he began his longevity quest and how technology has shaped the endeavor. Johnson also discusses some of his controversial experiments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wildcard's Plans for 2024 with Founders Paul and Katy Bettner]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/TI3aFBhO/wildcards-plans-for-2024-with-founders-paul-and-katy-bettner</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/TI3aFBhO/wildcards-plans-for-2024-with-founders-paul-and-katy-bettner"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T21:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wildcard developers Paul and Katy Bettner tell Decrypt's Kate Irwin about why they see their game as a "Web3 game," not a crypto game, and share why they've stuck with their initial vision despite the challenging broader market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt and Rug Radio Merge to Create Global Web3 Publishing Company]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/VTEBYFD8/decrypt-and-rug-radio-merge-to-create-global-web3-publishing-company</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/VTEBYFD8/decrypt-and-rug-radio-merge-to-create-global-web3-publishing-company"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T17:04:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt and Rug Radio have announced their intent to merge, creating the world’s biggest decentralized publishing company. Codenamed [REDACTED], the alliance is aimed at revolutionizing tech-media, bringing together the forces of content creation and consumption.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>