<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-09-13T17:16:02.378Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-09-13T17:16:02.378Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether Hires PayPal Government Affairs Ace as U.S. Scrutiny Unresolved]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74530bae18</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/09/13/tether-hires-paypal-government-affairs-ace-as-us-scrutiny-unresolved/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T17:13:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tether hired a government-affairs veteran from PayPal and Chainalysis, Jesse Spiro, to head its own shop as the issuer of the leading {{USDT}} stablecoin has long been under a cloud of reported U.S. investigations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin’s World ID gets bridge to Solana via Wormhole]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900350/Worldcoins-World-ID-gets-bridge-to-Solana-via-Wormhole</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900350/Worldcoins-World-ID-gets-bridge-to-Solana-via-Wormhole"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T17:09:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wormhole was one of 17 projects to receive a Worldcoin Wave 1 Community Grant.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Floki and GoodEgg Become Meme Favorites As GEGG Develops A.I Dating Platform Using Cryptocurrency]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e745cf4c213</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/floki-and-goodegg-become-meme-favorites-as-gegg-develops-a-i-dating-platform-using-cryptocurrency/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T17:05:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the world of cryptocurrencies, where innovation meets humor, two memecoins have captured the attention of investors and enthusiasts alike: Floki (FLOKI) and GoodEgg (GEGG). While Floki (FLOKI) has already made a name for itself as a fan favorite in the meme coin space, GoodEgg (GEGG) is quickly rising through the ranks, thanks to its development of a groundbreaking A.I-powered dating platform that utilizes cryptocurrency. These two coins are now in the spotlight as potential meme coin giants, each with unique strengths and appeal to different sections of the crypto community.
 
The Rise of Floki (FLOKI)
 
Floki (FLOKI), inspired by Elon Musk’s Shiba Inu dog named Floki, has been one of the most well-known meme coins in the cryptocurrency space. From its humble beginnings, it has built a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Market In Jeopardy? Rising Stablecoins Dominance Signals Instability]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e745cf4c212</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/stablecoins-dominance-signals-crypto-instability/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T17:05:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The general cryptocurrency market has been quite unpleasant as major crypto assets have seen extended negative trends, fueling uncertainty within the sector. With the recent upsurge in the stablecoins dominance, which is considered a negative sign for cryptocurrencies, the broader ecosystem could be poised for additional pessimistic behavior.
 
Stablecoin Dominance Growth Poses Risk To Cryptocurrencies
 
Recent reports from Alphractal, an advanced platform for investment data analysis, show that the dominance of stablecoins is increasing rapidly amidst price fluctuations. Historically, a drop in stablecoin dominance is a bullish indication for cryptocurrencies, as observed from late 2022 to early 2024, while an increase in dominance is a definite signal of a bearish trend.
 
 
As market vo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Godspower Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum and Bitcoin Investors Add Future A.I Dating Cryptocurrency To Future Investment Portfolios, Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e745cf4c211</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-and-bitcoin-investors-add-future-a-i-dating-cryptocurrency-to-future-investment-portfolios-heres-why/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T17:05:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the cryptocurrency market continues to evolve, a new contender is emerging that has caught the attention of Ethereum (ETH) and Bitcoin (BTC) investors—GoodEgg (GEGG), a revolutionary AI-driven dating platform that promises to integrate artificial intelligence with blockchain technology for a game-changing experience. Both ETH and BTC investors, known for seeking strategic, long-term opportunities, are diversifying their portfolios by adding GoodEgg (GEGG), a project set to reshape online dating.
 
GoodEgg (GEGG) — A Game-Changer in AI and Blockchain 
The GoodEgg (GEGG) platform combines the power of artificial intelligence with the security of blockchain to create a next-level dating experience. By using advanced AI algorithms, GoodEgg (GEGG) matches users more efficiently while ensurin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top AI Cryptocurrencies: Artificial Superintelligence Alliance (FET), GoodEgg (GEGG) & Decide A.I (DCD)]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e745cf4c210</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/top-ai-cryptocurrencies-artificial-superintelligence-alliance-fet-goodegg-gegg-decide-a-i-dcd/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T17:05:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AI cryptocurrency space is heating up, and three key players are emerging as frontrunners: Artificial Superintelligence Alliance (FET), GoodEgg (GEGG), and Decide A.I (DCD). These projects are not just making waves in the blockchain and AI integration scene but are also gaining the attention of major investors. From pioneering AI applications to decentralized finance solutions, these tokens are showing major growth potential, attracting both retail investors and whales alike.
 
GoodEgg (GEGG) — The Best of AI Dating 
GoodEgg (GEGG) has quickly gained traction in the world of AI-driven cryptocurrencies, with its innovative concept of integrating AI with online dating. The project focuses on providing a secure, decentralized platform for users to meet and connect, utilizing advanced AI a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New A.I Dating Platform (GEGG) Challenges Artificial Superintelligence Alliance (FET) With New Online Dating Platform]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e745cf4c20f</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/new-a-i-dating-platform-gegg-challenges-artificial-superintelligence-alliance-fet-with-new-online-dating-platform/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T17:05:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The intersection of artificial intelligence and blockchain technology is rapidly evolving, with platforms like Artificial Superintelligence Alliance (FET) and GoodEgg (GEGG) emerging as major players in their respective niches. While FET focuses on decentralized AI infrastructure, GoodEgg (GEGG) has introduced a new AI-driven dating platform designed to disrupt the social space with innovative algorithms and blockchain-backed privacy features.
 
This emerging platform, GoodEgg, is making waves, challenging even the biggest AI projects like FET. The dynamic between these two platforms, although fundamentally different in application, showcases the growing potential for AI in diverse sectors.
 
FET Sets New Standards in AI with Unstoppable Growth” 
The Artificial Superintelligence Alliance (…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is HBAR's $0.50 Goal Still in Play After BlackRock Drama?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900346/Is-HBARs-050-Goal-Still-in-Play-After-BlackRock-Drama</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900346/Is-HBARs-050-Goal-Still-in-Play-After-BlackRock-Drama"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T17:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A bumpy road ahead for HBAR: can Hedera Hashgraph overcome the reputational hit after the BlackRock scandal?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Floki and GoodEgg Become Meme Favorites As GEGG Develops A.I Dating Platform Using Cryptocurrency]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900335/Floki-and-GoodEgg-Become-Meme-Favorites-As-GEGG-Develops-AI-Dating-Platform-Using-Cryptocurrency</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900335/Floki-and-GoodEgg-Become-Meme-Favorites-As-GEGG-Develops-AI-Dating-Platform-Using-Cryptocurrency"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T17:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the world of cryptocurrencies, where innovation meets humor, two memecoins have captured the attention of investors and enthusiasts alike: Floki (FLOKI) and GoodEgg (GEGG). While Floki (FLOKI) has already made a name for itself as a fan favorite in the meme coin space, GoodEgg (GEGG) is...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Market In Jeopardy? Rising Stablecoins Dominance Signals Instability]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900333/Crypto-Market-In-Jeopardy-Rising-Stablecoins-Dominance-Signals-Instability</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900333/Crypto-Market-In-Jeopardy-Rising-Stablecoins-Dominance-Signals-Instability"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T17:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The general cryptocurrency market has been quite unpleasant as major crypto assets have seen extended negative trends, fueling uncertainty within the sector. With the recent upsurge in the stablecoins dominance, which is considered a negative sign for cryptocurrencies, the broader ecosystem...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum and Bitcoin Investors Add Future A.I Dating Cryptocurrency To Future Investment Portfolios, Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900332/Ethereum-and-Bitcoin-Investors-Add-Future-AI-Dating-Cryptocurrency-To-Future-Investment-Portfolios-Heres-Why</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900332/Ethereum-and-Bitcoin-Investors-Add-Future-AI-Dating-Cryptocurrency-To-Future-Investment-Portfolios-Heres-Why"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T17:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the cryptocurrency market continues to evolve, a new contender is emerging that has caught the attention of Ethereum (ETH) and Bitcoin (BTC) investors—GoodEgg (GEGG), a revolutionary AI-driven dating platform that promises to integrate artificial intelligence with blockchain technology for a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial Superintelligence Alliance (FET) vs New A.I Dating Platform (GEGG): FET Investors Add GoodEgg To A.I Portfolio]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900322/Artificial-Superintelligence-Alliance-FET-vs-New-AI-Dating-Platform-GEGG-FET-Investors-Add-GoodEgg-To-AI-Portfolio</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900322/Artificial-Superintelligence-Alliance-FET-vs-New-AI-Dating-Platform-GEGG-FET-Investors-Add-GoodEgg-To-AI-Portfolio"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T17:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The intersection of artificial intelligence and blockchain technology continues to expand, with platforms like the Artificial Superintelligence Alliance (FET) and GoodEgg (GEGG) taking the lead. While the Artificial Superintelligence Alliance (FET) has been instrumental in shaping decentralized...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top AI Cryptocurrencies: Artificial Superintelligence Alliance (FET), GoodEgg (GEGG) & Decide A.I (DCD)]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900331/Top-AI-Cryptocurrencies-Artificial-Superintelligence-Alliance-FET-GoodEgg-GEGG-Decide-AI-DCD</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900331/Top-AI-Cryptocurrencies-Artificial-Superintelligence-Alliance-FET-GoodEgg-GEGG-Decide-AI-DCD"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T17:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AI cryptocurrency space is heating up, and three key players are emerging as frontrunners: Artificial Superintelligence Alliance (FET), GoodEgg (GEGG), and Decide A.I (DCD). These projects are not just making waves in the blockchain and AI integration scene but are also gaining the attention...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New A.I Dating Platform (GEGG) Challenges Artificial Superintelligence Alliance (FET) With New Online Dating Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900330/New-AI-Dating-Platform-GEGG-Challenges-Artificial-Superintelligence-Alliance-FET-With-New-Online-Dating-Platform</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900330/New-AI-Dating-Platform-GEGG-Challenges-Artificial-Superintelligence-Alliance-FET-With-New-Online-Dating-Platform"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T17:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The intersection of artificial intelligence and blockchain technology is rapidly evolving, with platforms like Artificial Superintelligence Alliance (FET) and GoodEgg (GEGG) emerging as major players in their respective niches. While FET focuses on decentralized AI infrastructure, GoodEgg (GEGG)...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Exchange CEX.IO Resumes UK Operations Amid Regulatory Changes]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900310/Crypto-Exchange-CEXIO-Resumes-UK-Operations-Amid-Regulatory-Changes</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900310/Crypto-Exchange-CEXIO-Resumes-UK-Operations-Amid-Regulatory-Changes"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T17:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency exchange CEX.IO has officially recommenced its services in the UK, following a compliance overhaul to meet the Financial Conduct Authority’s (FCA) new regulations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC Strikes Again! New Tokens Targeted in the Binance Lawsuit: AXS, Filecoin, Cosmos and More]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900305/The-SEC-Strikes-Again-New-Tokens-Targeted-in-the-Binance-Lawsuit-AXS-Filecoin-Cosmos-and-More</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900305/The-SEC-Strikes-Again-New-Tokens-Targeted-in-the-Binance-Lawsuit-AXS-Filecoin-Cosmos-and-More"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T16:59:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR The SEC expands its lawsuit against Binance, now classifying tokens such as Axie Infinity (AXS), Filecoin (FIL), and Cosmos (ATOM) as unregistered securities. Binance and its subsidiary BAM Trading are accused of promoting these tokens as investments without complying with the necessary...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arthur Hayes Believes Bitcoin Could Have Great Week, Could Be Good For SUI & Altcoins]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900334/Arthur-Hayes-Believes-Bitcoin-Could-Have-Great-Week-Could-Be-Good-For-SUI-Altcoins</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900334/Arthur-Hayes-Believes-Bitcoin-Could-Have-Great-Week-Could-Be-Good-For-SUI-Altcoins"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T16:58:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arthur Hayes, co-founder of BitMEX, insists that Bitcoin (BTC) will have a strong week because of potential market shifts, which might benefit altcoins like Sui (SUI). On the other hand, a decentralized FX trading DeFi platform with advanced features and investor rewards has become an attractive...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Industry leaders a16z, OpenSea pledge $6 million to shield NFT artists from legal threats]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900304/Industry-leaders-a16z-OpenSea-pledge-6-million-to-shield-NFT-artists-from-legal-threats</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900304/Industry-leaders-a16z-OpenSea-pledge-6-million-to-shield-NFT-artists-from-legal-threats"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T16:57:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Stand With Crypto Alliance, a Coinbase-backed non-profit organization, is leading efforts to establish the Creator Defense Fund initiative that has raised $6 million from venture capital firm Andreessen Horowitz (a16z) and NFT marketplace OpenSea. According to a Sept. 13 press release, a16z...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Asset Management Giant Grayscale Launches New XRP Trust After Axing Product in 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900307/Crypto-Asset-Management-Giant-Grayscale-Launches-New-XRP-Trust-After-Axing-Product-in-2021</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900307/Crypto-Asset-Management-Giant-Grayscale-Launches-New-XRP-Trust-After-Axing-Product-in-2021"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T16:55:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto asset management giant Grayscale launched a new XRP Trust after axing a similar product in 2021. The new trust is solely invested in XRP and offers investors a chance at exposure to “a protocol with an important real-world use case,” says Rayhaneh Sharif-Askary, Grayscale’s head of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether Hires PayPal Government Affairs Ace as U.S. Scrutiny Unresolved]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900342/Tether-Hires-PayPal-Government-Affairs-Ace-as-US-Scrutiny-Unresolved</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900342/Tether-Hires-PayPal-Government-Affairs-Ace-as-US-Scrutiny-Unresolved"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T16:55:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tether hired a government-affairs veteran from PayPal and Chainalysis, Jesse Spiro, to head its own shop as the issuer of the leading {{USDT}} stablecoin has long been under a cloud of reported U.S. investigations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin price eyes $60K reclaim as gold hits fresh all-time high]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900301/Bitcoin-price-eyes-60K-reclaim-as-gold-hits-fresh-all-time-high</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900301/Bitcoin-price-eyes-60K-reclaim-as-gold-hits-fresh-all-time-high"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T16:52:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin joins gold in rising as markets see a bigger chance of a 0.5% interest rate cut.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Price Explosion to $40 is “Definitely a Possibility” for These Reasons]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900308/XRP-Price-Explosion-to-40-is-Definitely-a-Possibility-for-These-Reasons</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900308/XRP-Price-Explosion-to-40-is-Definitely-a-Possibility-for-These-Reasons"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T16:48:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to popular crypto analyst Steph is Crypto, XRP could be on the verge of an extraordinary rally, potentially soaring over 7,400% from its current price.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Flappy Bird revival is hiding crypto plans]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900272/The-Flappy-Bird-revival-is-hiding-crypto-plans</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900272/The-Flappy-Bird-revival-is-hiding-crypto-plans"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T16:46:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Flappy Bird revival appears to be a crypto project with its own token and creative chief boasting a history with NFTs projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana’s Liquid Staking Market Could Skyrocket to $10 Billion — Could Memecoins Be the Key?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900263/Solanas-Liquid-Staking-Market-Could-Skyrocket-to-10-Billion-Could-Memecoins-Be-the-Key</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900263/Solanas-Liquid-Staking-Market-Could-Skyrocket-to-10-Billion-Could-Memecoins-Be-the-Key"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T16:45:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR Solana is adopting a liquid staking model that improves on traditional staking, offering greater flexibility and liquidity. Despite a staking ratio of 68%, only 6.5% of SOL is liquidly staked, suggesting significant growth potential. Bybit launches its own liquid staking product, bbSOL, to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether taps Jesse Spyro as head of government affairs]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900265/Tether-taps-Jesse-Spyro-as-head-of-government-affairs</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900265/Tether-taps-Jesse-Spyro-as-head-of-government-affairs"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T16:43:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tether brought Jesse Spyro onboard as its head of government affairs. The issuer of USDT fights for its reputation, while facing limitations in the Euro Area and accusations of uses to breach Iranian, Chinese and Russian sanctions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Teases Dogecoin as Payment Option on X After Brazil’s Platform Restrictions]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900276/Elon-Musk-Teases-Dogecoin-as-Payment-Option-on-X-After-Brazils-Platform-Restrictions</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900276/Elon-Musk-Teases-Dogecoin-as-Payment-Option-on-X-After-Brazils-Platform-Restrictions"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T16:42:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk, CEO of X, has sparked renewed interest in Dogecoin after hinting at its potential use as a payment option on his social media platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin and Ethereum Fee Drop: The Perfect Time for Cost-Effective Transactions]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e745cf0f5ec</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-and-ethereum-fee-drop-the-perfect-time-for-cost-effective-transactions/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T16:32:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Although both bitcoin and ethereum have been cruising at lower prices compared to earlier this year, there’s been a silver lining: transaction fees on these leading blockchains have significantly decreased. With costs now sitting at notable lows, it could be the perfect moment to fine-tune transaction expenses for certain activities or even gather unspent transaction […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Are Today’s ‘Rocky Rabbit’ Enigma and SuperSet Daily Combo Solutions]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=245981</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/here-are-todays-rocky-rabbit-enigma-superset-daily-combo-solutions"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T16:15:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can earn millions of free in-game coins in the Telegram game Rocky Rabbit. Here are the solutions for Friday, September 13.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quant (QNT) Price Prediction For 2024,2025 and 2026 Can It Out Perform Mpeppe (MPEPE)’s Gambling Token Experts Take a Look]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e745cfd2493</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/quant-qnt-price-prediction-for-20242025-and-2026-can-it-out-perform-mpeppe-mpepes-gambling-token-experts-take-a-look/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T16:06:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quant (QNT) has established itself as a powerful player in the world of blockchain technology, particularly due to its focus on interoperability between different networks. As investors look ahead to 2024, 2025, and 2026, many are optimistic about Quant (QNT)’s long-term potential. With its steady growth and strong market position, experts predict that Quant (QNT) could continue to rise, making it a popular choice for traders seeking stability and profits over time.
 
Mpeppe (MPEPE)’s Gambling Token: A New Frontier in Meme Coins and Online Gambling 
Mpeppe (MPEPE) is a rising star in the world of meme cryptocurrencies, and its integration into online gambling platforms adds a layer of excitement and speculation. Meme coins like Mpeppe (MPEPE) have made waves in the crypto space by leveragi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quant (QNT) Investors Maximize Their Bullish Gains and Purchase New Gambling Coin Currently At $0.0021]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e745cfd2492</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/quant-qnt-investors-maximize-their-bullish-gains-and-purchase-new-gambling-coin-currently-at-0-0021/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T16:06:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quant (QNT) investors are looking for new opportunities to maximize their bullish gains. One of the most promising investments gaining attention is Mpeppe (MPEPE), a new gambling coin currently priced at $0.0021. With its innovative use of blockchain technology and rising popularity in the online gambling space, Mpeppe (MPEPE) is becoming an attractive option for Quant (QNT) holders eager to diversify their portfolios.
 
Mpeppe (MPEPE)’s Appeal: The Power of Blockchain in Online Casinos
 
Mpeppe (MPEPE) has quickly gained traction due to its integration of blockchain technology in online gambling. The decentralized nature of cryptocurrencies like Mpeppe (MPEPE) offers players increased security and privacy, making it a natural fit for the online casino world. Quant (QNT) investors, known f…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uniswap (UNI) Investors Join New Gambling ICO Tipped To Explode Before Its Uniswap (UNI) Launch]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e745cfd2490</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/uniswap-uni-investors-join-new-gambling-ico-tipped-to-explode-before-its-uniswap-uni-launch/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T16:06:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Uniswap (UNI) investors are always on the lookout for the next big opportunity. Recently, many of these investors have turned their attention to the upcoming Mpeppe (MPEPE) gambling ICO, which is being touted as a project with massive growth potential. Tipped to explode before its official Uniswap (UNI) launch, Mpeppe (MPEPE) is drawing in crypto enthusiasts eager to capitalize on the growing intersection between cryptocurrency and online gambling.
 
The Cryptocurrency Revolution in Online Gambling 
Cryptocurrencies like Mpeppe (MPEPE) have revolutionized the online gambling industry by offering enhanced security, privacy, and transparency. As decentralized payment methods become more accepted in online casinos, the gambling community has embraced the advantages of using digital assets. Un…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[As Quant (QNT) Dips Slightly Community Sentiment Is Still Strong Crypto Experts See Mpeppe (MPEPE) As a Big Player]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e745cfd248e</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/as-quant-qnt-dips-slightly-community-sentiment-is-still-strong-crypto-experts-see-mpeppe-mpepe-as-a-big-player/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T16:06:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite a slight dip in Quant (QNT)’s price, the community remains steadfast in its belief in the long-term potential of the project. Known for its robust blockchain platform and innovative interoperability solutions, Quant (QNT) continues to maintain a strong presence in the crypto space. However, as the market adjusts, crypto experts are shifting some of their attention toward Mpeppe (MPEPE), which is emerging as a potential powerhouse in the world of decentralized finance (DeFi) and meme coins.
 
Mpeppe (MPEPE)’s Role in Decentralized Finance: A Game Changer 
Mpeppe (MPEPE) is making waves by offering functionality beyond the typical meme coin. With its ability to facilitate financial services and transactions within DeFi protocols, Mpeppe (MPEPE) is creating new opportunities for users…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB) Whale Allocates 5% Of Their Holding To Rising Crypto Star Mpeppe (MPEPE) Predicted to 150x]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e745cfd248d</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-shib-whale-allocates-5-of-their-holding-to-rising-crypto-star-mpeppe-mpepe-predicted-to-150x/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T16:06:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a bold move that has caught the attention of the crypto world, a prominent Shiba Inu (SHIB) whale has allocated 5% of their holdings to the rising crypto star, Mpeppe (MPEPE). As the market landscape continues to evolve, seasoned investors are increasingly looking beyond traditional meme coins like Shiba Inu (SHIB) and exploring new opportunities with innovative projects like Mpeppe (MPEPE). This shift signals a growing confidence in Mpeppe (MPEPE)’s potential to deliver significant returns.
 
Mpeppe (MPEPE): A Standout Project In The Meme Coin Space 
Mpeppe (MPEPE) has quickly emerged as a standout project in the cryptocurrency space, combining the viral appeal of meme coins with the transformative power of blockchain technology. While Shiba Inu (SHIB) has made headlines in the past, M…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong SFC Seeks Industry Feedback on New Licensing Rules for OTC Crypto Services]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e745cfd9795</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/hong-kong-sfc-seeks-industry-feedback-on-new-licensing-rules-for-otc-crypto-services/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T16:03:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong’s Securities and Futures Commission (SFC) is actively seeking input from industry participants on proposed new licensing regulations for over-the-counter (OTC) cryptocurrency services. The initiative aims to establish a comprehensive framework that mandates licensing and adherence to anti-money laundering (AML) and counter-terrorist financing regulations. This move, which includes joint supervision by the SFC and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Reiterates Binance’s Illegal Operations, Highlights ‘Lack of Disclosure’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e745cfd9f26</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com/cryptocurrency/sec-reiterates-binances-illegal-operations-highlights-lack-of-disclosure/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T16:02:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC)  
has expanded its lawsuit against Binance. The updated legal filings now include  
a wider range of tokens, with Axie Infinity among those listed as securities.
In the latest update to the SEC v. Binance lawsuit, the  
regulator has accused Binance and its US affiliate, BAM Trading, of enabling  
the trade of tokens now deemed unregistered securities. The SEC alleges that  
Binance actively promotes these newly classified securities tokens to  
customers, emphasizing their potential returns.
SEC Expands Binance Lawsuit
The SEC stated: “Binance and BAM Trading fill these markets  
with information republishing and amplifying the issuer and promoter statements  
and activity promoting [tokens] as an investment.”
The amendment to the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tareq Sikder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DAOs Need a Vibe Check]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e745cfe3b1b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/opinion/2024/09/13/daos-need-a-vibe-check/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T15:57:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recent token heist at Compound DAO revealed the weakness of current DAO governance voting. There is a better way, say Andrés Fábrega, Jay Yu, Amy Zhao, and Ari Juels.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrés  Fábrega, Jay  Yu, Amy  Zhao, Ari  Juels</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Latin American Crypto Exchange Ripio Unveils DeFi Credit Card With Visa]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e745cf8007a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2024/09/13/latin-american-crypto-exchange-ripio-unveils-defi-credit-card-with-visa/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T15:47:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The product will allow users to access up to 30% of blocked assets in a liquidity pool.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrés Engler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Exec In Limbo: US Ramps Up Pressure On Nigeria To Free Gambaryan]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e745cf985c5</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/binance-exec-in-limbo-us-ramps-up-pressure-on-nigeria-to-free-gambaryan/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T15:37:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US government is intensifying its attempts to secure the release of Tigran Gambaryan, a Binance executive imprisoned in Nigeria since February 2024.
 
 
According to reports, Gambaryan’s health has gotten much worse while he is in detention, which is why US officials are pushing for his release for humanitarian reasons.
 
Gambaryan faces significant money laundering and tax evasion charges in Nigeria. Visiting Nigeria for Binance operations meetings in February 2024 led to his arrest.
 
With high-level talks between American diplomats and Nigerian officials, this crisis has become a focal point in US-Nigeria ties.
 
Rising Diplomatic Pressure
 
Antony Blinken, the US Secretary of State, personally became involved in the matter and openly expressed worries to his Nigerian counterpart. U…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Government Intensifies Pressure on Nigeria to Free Detained Binance Exec: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249331</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249331/us-officials-pressure-nigeria-free-detained-binance-exec"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T15:29:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Officials have reportedly stepped up attempts to advocate for the release of Binance executive Tigran Gambaryan from Nigerian prison.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consumer Watchdog Calls Tether a 'Disaster for Consumers Waiting to Happen']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249323</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249323/consumer-watchdog-calls-tether-a-disaster-for-consumers-waiting-to-happen"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T15:10:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Tether has many of the same issues that FTX and Celsius had before their collapse," the watchdog wrote on its letter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FLOKI Investors Dive Into New Memecoin Priced $0.00021 Rivalling FLOKI’s Previous Success]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e745ce6683e</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/floki-investors-dive-into-new-memecoin-priced-0-00021-rivalling-flokis-previous-success/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T15:08:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the world of memecoins, Floki (FLOKI) has been a significant player, capturing the hearts of investors with its Viking-inspired branding and rapid growth. However, a new contender, GoodEgg (GEGG), is set to rival Floki (FLOKI)’s success with its fresh A.I-powered dating platform and a price of just $0.00021 in its presale. Investors who saw massive returns with Floki (FLOKI) are now eyeing GoodEgg (GEGG), hoping to replicate those gains as GEGG makes waves in the memecoin market.
 
Why FLOKI Holders Are Turning to GoodEgg (GEGG) 
Floki (FLOKI) investors are no strangers to success. The memecoin made headlines with its impressive market performance, driven by a passionate community and high-profile partnerships. However, with the GoodEgg (GEGG) presale gaining traction and raising $250k …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Price Prediction: More Gains To Made In New SOL Rival GoodEgg (GEGG)]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e745ce66839</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/solana-price-prediction-more-gains-to-made-in-new-sol-rival-goodegg-gegg/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T15:08:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana (SOL) has been a powerhouse in the cryptocurrency world, often regarded as a leading competitor to Ethereum due to its fast transaction speeds and low fees. However, in recent news, the Solana ecosystem faces challenges as selling pressure looms due to developments involving the FTX/Alameda exchange. At the same time, investors are increasingly turning their attention to GoodEgg (GEGG), an emerging AI-based dating platform in the crypto space, as it positions itself to rival Solana (SOL) in 2024 and beyond.
 
Solana’s Selling Pressure: A Warning for Traders 
Solana (SOL), currently trading at around $134.80, has recently faced potential selling pressure due to a large unstaking event linked to the now-bankrupt FTX exchange. A crypto wallet, associated with the bankrupt FTX and Alame…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 Reasons Solana Holders Are Entering New A.I Dating Presale, SOL Price Prediction For September]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e745ce66831</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/3-reasons-solana-holders-are-entering-new-a-i-dating-presale-sol-price-prediction-for-september/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T15:08:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana (SOL) has seen significant growth in its ecosystem, and now, investors are looking for the next big thing. Recently, many Solana (SOL) holders have been turning their attention to GoodEgg (GEGG), a future A.I dating cryptocurrency that promises massive returns. But why are Solana (SOL) holders entering the presale of this new crypto platform, and what can we expect from Solana in the upcoming months?
 
Here are three key reasons why Solana (SOL) investors are getting involved in the GoodEgg (GEGG) presale:
 
 
 
 Solana’s Growing Ecosystem and DeFi Success 
 
 
The Solana (SOL) ecosystem has been experiencing remarkable growth, especially within decentralized exchanges (DEX). According to Tristan Frizza, Founder of Zeta Markets, Solana (SOL) has reached $1.811 billion in DEX trading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy Just Bought Another $1.1 Billion Worth of Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249319</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249319/microstrategy-just-bought-another-1-1-billion-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T14:54:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Saylor's software firm MicroStrategy now holds over $14 billion worth of Bitcoin after four years of buying up BTC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will McCurdy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken Pushes for Jury Trial in SEC Lawsuit, Rails Against 'Crypto Asset Securities' Claims]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249313</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249313/kraken-pushes-for-jury-trial-in-sec-lawsuit-rails-against-crypto-asset-securities-claims"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T14:30:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken accused the SEC of blocking efforts to register or cooperate, saying they were "stonewalled" by inconsistent rulings and guidance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vismaya V</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Money, Get Away: Fake Celebrity Meme Coin Linked to Pink Floyd and Neymar Is 'Saddest Launch' Ever]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249290</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249290/money-get-away-fake-celebrity-meme-coin-linked-to-pink-floyd-and-neymar-is-saddest-launch-ever"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T13:45:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["The celebrity meta is officially dead," Bubblemaps CEO says after celeb-pushed token fails to break $20,000 market cap.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Are Today’s ‘X Empire’ Elon Musk Game Daily Combo and Riddle]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241078</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/todays-musk-empire-stock-exchange-daily-combo"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T13:15:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking for the X Empire daily combo and riddle solution for Friday, September 13? Here are the latest boosts for the Telegram game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Are Today's ‘Hamster Kombat’ Daily Combo and Cipher Code]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=239305</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/todays-hamster-kombat-daily-combo-cipher-code"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T13:05:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking for the daily combo and cipher code for Friday, September 13? Here’s what you need to make bank in Telegram game Hamster Kombat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Ethereum Founder Vitalik Buterin Defines 'Stage 1+' Layer-2 Networks]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249281</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249281/how-ethereum-founder-vitalik-buterin-defines-stage-1-layer-2-networks"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T12:43:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“It doesn't matter if I invested, or if you're my friend; stage 1 or bust,” he said in a recent tweet. Here's what that means.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will McCurdy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Stagnates as Analysts Forecast Potential Bottom For Ethereum Before End of Year]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249278</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249278/bitcoin-stagnates-as-analysts-forecast-potential-bottom-for-ethereum-before-end-of-year"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T10:11:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Traders should monitor medium-term reversal indicators such as RSI and Stochastics," to catch signs of assets being oversold, said 10X Research.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI Launches New ‘01’ Model That Outperforms ChatGPT-4o]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249227</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249227/openai-launches-new-01-model-that-outperforms-chatgpt-4o"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T01:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AI developer said it is “resetting the counter” for its product names as its latest set of models excel across its tests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bill to Fight AI Deepfakes Reaches US House as Entertainment Industry Cheers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249254</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249254/entertainment-industry-celebrates-as-no-fakes-act-moves-to-congress"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T00:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With backing from both parties, the legislation follows the intrduction of its counterpart in the U.S. Senate earlier this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Hamster Kombat’ and ‘Catizen’ Telegram Token Demand Could Disrupt TON, Devs Warn]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249203</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249203/hamster-kombat-catizen-token-airdrops-ton-issues"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T23:01:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Airdrop season on The Open Network is nearly here, and developers admit that demand could get the better of the Telegram-linked network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Napolitano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adobe Pushes Into Generative Video With Firefly Amid AI Controversy]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249181</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249181/adobe-pushes-into-generative-video-with-firefly-amid-ai-controversy"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T22:43:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adobe’s Firefly Video Model, set for release in beta later this year, introduces new generative AI capabilities to its Premiere Pro video suite.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Magic Muffins’ Game Launches on Telegram to Take on ‘Hamster Kombat’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249215</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249215/magic-muffins-game-telegram-take-on-hamster-kombat"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T22:15:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earn Alliance’s Telegram game Magic Muffins delivers a tap-based combat experience that’s tied to the platform’s upcoming ALLY token launch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kalshi's US Election Prediction Markets Go Live as CFTC Seeks Appeal]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249204</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249204/kalshi-us-election-prediction-markets-go-live-cftc-seeks-appeal"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T21:38:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Legal and regulated U.S. prediction markets platform Kalshi has launched its first election pools after the court win over the CFTC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Napolitano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Dollar Is Taking Over the World Thanks to Stablecoins: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249197</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249197/stablecoins-drive-us-dollar-dominance-globally"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T21:16:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Survey data shows that stablecoins are inciting net flows into dollar instruments where U.S. dollar banking is unavailable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Wrapped Bitcoin Sparks Pushback from Justin Sun]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249189</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249189/coinbase-wrapped-bitcoin-sparks-pushback-from-justin-sun"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T20:31:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The TRON founder's connection to  WBTC has driven interest in alternatives, and Sun is not a fan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Hamster Kombat’ Will Give Out Billions of Tokens via Binance in Telegram Game Airdrop]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249171</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249171/hamster-kombat-give-out-billions-tokens-binance-telegram-game-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T18:54:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance users will be able to earn a share of 3 billion HMSTR in the lead-up to Hamster Kombat’s token launch on TON.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana’s Pump.Fun Has Launched Millions of Tokens—Fewer Than 100 Are Worth Much at All]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249107</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249107/fewer-than-100-pump-fun-tokens-above-1m-market-cap-amid-meme-coin-lull"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T17:55:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pump.fun is “stale,” traders believe, as the protocol fails to keep more than 100 tokens above a $1 million market cap.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fuse Plugs Solana Token Into Energy Distribution DePIN Play]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=248985</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/248985/fuse-plugs-solana-token-energy-distribution-depin-play"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T17:32:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With a new $12 million fundraising round, the renewable energy company aims to reward customers for supporting the power grid.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[European Central Bank Drops Interest Rates Again as Bitcoin, Stocks Bounce Back]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249154</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249154/european-central-bank-drops-interest-rates-again-bitcoin-up"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T16:58:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Fed is likely to drop rates next, potentially setting up Bitcoin for another "Uptober" after a shaky start to September.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 198 - THE GREAT APE HEIST!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/RJ6YcMxP/fomo-hour-198-the-great-ape-heist</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/RJ6YcMxP/fomo-hour-198-the-great-ape-heist"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T16:28:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto rises with stocks after CPI falls again. Bitfinex BTC longs continue to grow. SUI again leads L1s, up 18%. FTX estate unstakes $24m SOL, still has $943m. Binance introduces SOL liquid staking. SWIFT introduces infrastructure for RWA transfers. Pendle launches Bitcoin yield pools. UK makes crypto legal property. India leads crypto adoption for second year. Vitalik won’t advertise L2s with multi-sig security. Based rollups seen as alternative future for ETH. Blockchain music start up raises $50m. Ford & Toyota file blockchain patents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale Debuts XRP Trust Following Bitcoin and Ethereum ETF Launches]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249124</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249124/grayscale-debuts-xrp-trust-bitcoin-ethereum-etfs"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T16:12:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto asset manager Grayscale launched the XRP Trust, a new product giving investors exposure to the Ripple-aligned asset.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Eve Frontier’ Survival Game Is Being Built on Ethereum, CCP Reveals]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249126</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249126/eve-frontier-survival-game-ethereum-ccp-reveals"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T15:57:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eve Online maker CCP Games has rebranded Project Awakening, which is being built on Ethereum layer-2 network Redstone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Will Hit New High Price If Trump or Harris Wins, Says Analyst—But Bettors Favor Kamala]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249073</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249073/bitcoin-hit-new-high-price-trump-or-harris-wins-bettors-favor-kamala"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T14:07:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kamala Harris has pulled ahead of Donald Trump on Polymarket, but Standard Chartered sees a new Bitcoin peak if either candidate wins the election.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gary Gensler Under Fire for Alleged Political Favoritism in SEC Appointments]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249095</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249095/gary-gensler-under-fire-for-alleged-political-favoritism-in-sec-appointments"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T13:47:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["The SEC appears to be unlawfully considering an applicant’s political ideology when hiring bureaucrats," the lawmakers wrote.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vismaya V</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[eToro Will Only Offer Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Bitcoin Cash in US After Settling SEC Charges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249074</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249074/etoro-only-offer-bitcoin-ethereum-bitcoin-cash-us-settling-sec-charges"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T13:19:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC announced that eToro has settled securities charges, and will pay a penalty alongside curtailing offered crypto assets in the U.S.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward,André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gameloft Reveals 'Claynosaurz' Mobile Game Based on Solana NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249031</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249031/gameloft-claynosaurz-mobile-game-solana-nfts"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T13:01:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana NFT collection Claynosaurz is expanding into gaming via a team-up with mobile giant Gameloft. Here's what to expect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erika Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood Is Well Positioned as Investors Increasingly Prefer Crypto, Says Bernstein]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249053</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249053/robinhood-is-well-positioned-as-investors-increasingly-prefer-crypto-says-bernstein"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T12:37:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The way younger investors prefer to invest will "determine what the financial platforms of the future look like,” analysts write.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Launches Wrapped Bitcoin Token Following BitGo WBTC Controversy]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=248997</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/248997/coinbase-launches-wrapped-bitcoin-token-following-bitgo-wbtc-controversy"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T11:01:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The leading exchange puts forward cbBTC as a formidable new option in the DeFi space.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fomo Hour 197 - Debate Disaster]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rMxl1cgJ/fomo-hour-197-debate-disaster</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rMxl1cgJ/fomo-hour-197-debate-disaster"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T19:15:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto falls slightly after Presidential debate. Exchanges see highest BTC outflow since May. Be wary of Yen move for BTC: Hayes. SOL active addresses hit ATH. At least 5 massive SOL announcements coming: Mert. Binomial to introduce restaking on BNB. Indonesian exchange hacked for $22m. Atomic Wallet wins lawsuit over $100m hack. Lawyers argue Ellison shouldn’t go to jail. ENS integrated with Venmo & PayPal. Galaxy & State Street launch 3 crypto ETFs. Standard Chartered begins UAE crypto custody. AAVE leads resurgence in DeFi coins.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 196 - THE INFLOWS RETURN!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/e9F8zYRp/fomo-hour-196-the-inflows-return</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/e9F8zYRp/fomo-hour-196-the-inflows-return"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T22:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETFs: +$29m, ETH ETFs: -$5m. BTC rallies, ETF has first inflow in 9 trading days. BTC may have put in first higher low in 6 months. Saylor predicts $13m price for BTC. Wealth advisors quickly adopting BTC: BitWise CEO. Binance among few firms to get Indonesia license. Spot trading on CEXs up 30% in August. SEC made $4.68bn from crypto firms in 2023. $5.6bn lost to scams in 2023. XRP security status may be unchallenged in appeal. EtherFi announces credit card on Scroll. Base has more DEX users than other L2s combined. Tether & Tron create taskforce against crime. TIA still only making $585 in daily fees. WLD investigated by Singapore police.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 195 - CAN WE GET A BOUNCE?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/m7JRnQJc/fomo-hour-195-can-we-get-a-bounce</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/m7JRnQJc/fomo-hour-195-can-we-get-a-bounce"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T22:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC: 55.3k (+2%), ETH: 2320 (+1%), SOL: 130 (0%). Top Gainers: FTM, TAO, BTT, AAVE, TON, ATOM. Crypto mini-bounce continues, BTC reclaims $55k. BTC RSI hits lowest level since July 2021. Bitfinex longs continue to grow aggressively. BTC hashrate hits another ATH. BTC could hit $90k on Trump election: Bernstein. BlackRock settles intraday BTC trades off-chain. Spot BTC ETFs have been a failure: Bianco. Power giant Tepco explores Bitcoin mining. ETH Foundation & Vitalik continue to sell ETH. Farcaster DAU’s down 95%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Presenting MYRIAD, a prediction market and digital media engagement ecosystem]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/Rwj71okY/presenting-myriad-a-prediction-market-and-digital-media-engagement-ecosystem</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/Rwj71okY/presenting-myriad-a-prediction-market-and-digital-media-engagement-ecosystem"/>
        <updated>2024-09-09T14:28:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Media company DASTAN, the parent company of Decrypt and Rug Radio, is embarking on the next stage of its evolution with the launch of MYRIAD, a prediction market and engagement ecosystem that aims to “transform the digital media landscape.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 194 - ARE NFTS BACK?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5oNbWn5H/fomo-hour-194-are-nfts-back</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5oNbWn5H/fomo-hour-194-are-nfts-back"/>
        <updated>2024-09-07T12:02:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto weak after continued ETF outflows. Durov breaks silence, TON bounces 3%. Telegram will start moderating private chats. Hayes & Brandt flip bearish on BTC. Coinbase shares hit 7 month lows. 90% of crypto firm applications rejected in UK. Japan’s 3 largest banks to trial stablecoins. Trump promises again to embrace crypto. INJ launches BlackRock BUIDL index. DWF to launch synthetic stablecoin. Vitalik to donate all L2 tokens to charity. Most VCs in crypto ‘will disappear’.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Researcher Explains Meme Coin Mania]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tC2Oz5H9/crypto-researcher-explains-meme-coin-mania</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tC2Oz5H9/crypto-researcher-explains-meme-coin-mania"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T18:59:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Head of Research at CoinMarketCap, Alice Liu, breaks down the highs and lows of meme coin mania in 2024. We’ve seen meme coins like Dogwifhat (WIF) soar to huge market caps and we’ve seen political meme coins crash as the candidate drops out (BODEN). Liu explains the data behind all of this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 193 - NVIDIA DROPS-OFF]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LxNEmmjX/fomo-hour-193-nvidia-drops-off</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LxNEmmjX/fomo-hour-193-nvidia-drops-off"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T17:05:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto falls on macro wobble, Yen fears. OI wiped in BTC drop to $56k, funding negative. Altcoins down 13% YTD, stablecoin supply up 30%. BTC mining profitability at record low: JP Morgan. FBI says North Korea targeting BTC ETF issuers. Trump family to launch DeFi project on ETH. Trump project linked to AVAX’s Dough Finance. Trump family members hacked during launch. AI coins underperform after Nvidia investigation. MATIC upgrade to POL begins. TON falls as Telegram faces issues in many countries. VC funding & BTC correlation breaks down. We have entered crypto’s ‘corporate phase’. Gensler will leave regardless of election: Ripple CEO. Harris campaign has asked Coinbase for advice. Penpie DeFi project hacked for $27m. Galois Capital settles with SEC over FTX custody.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 192 - WTF IS ETHERVISTA]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/xOt72jL2/fomo-hour-192-wtf-is-ethervista</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/xOt72jL2/fomo-hour-192-wtf-is-ethervista"/>
        <updated>2024-09-03T19:24:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OI continues to rise as BTC stabilises. BTC still best performing assets class this year. FTX to distribute $16bn to creditors starting in Q4. Qatar introduces regulatory framework for crypto. ETH L1s fees down 90%, L2 activity ATH. Base hits 14m monthly users, many may be Sybil. ETH is in death spiral: Krueger. SOL to see significant unlocks in Q1. Japan considers dropping crypto tax to 20%. Rate cuts won’t help BTC: Hayes. BTC should double after rate cuts: Tapiero. Mr 100 linked back to Upbit wallet. WazirX hacker moves funds to Tornado. SUI to launch handheld gaming device. Sony & PYTH announce collaboration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Millionaire Explains How Neiro United Meme Coins]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LjhyvMyI/dogecoin-millionaire-explains-how-neiro-united-meme-coins</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LjhyvMyI/dogecoin-millionaire-explains-how-neiro-united-meme-coins"/>
        <updated>2024-08-31T13:16:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kabosu, the dog many know as Doge and the mascot of Dogecoin, sadly passed away earlier this year. Its owner later adopted another Shiba Inu called Neiro which caused a long blockchain civil war with multiple tokens battling it out for liquidity. Now a month later SlumDOGE, the man who became a millionaire off Dogecoin (but never sold), explains why Neiro is a moment for the dog coin community to unite.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 191 - CRYPTO STABLE]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/VM5OAovR/fomo-hour-191-crypto-stable</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/VM5OAovR/fomo-hour-191-crypto-stable"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T17:27:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETFs: -$72m, ETH ETFs: -$2m. BTC weekly volatility returns to multi-year lows. BlackRock BTC ETF sees first outflow in months. ETH dominance hits 4-year low. Vitalik linked wallet sells $2m ETH. Bukele talks up BTC impact in Time interview. CBoE files for ETH & BTC ETF options. Elon & Tesla win DOGE manipulation lawsuit. Macron denies inviting Durov to France. Trump promises to make US the ‘crypto capital’. Trump advertises Liberty Financial DeFi project. DeFi mindshare continues to grow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 190 - OPENSEA VS SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/g3scPNlK/fomo-hour-190-opensea-vs-sec</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/g3scPNlK/fomo-hour-190-opensea-vs-sec"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T16:17:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC: 59.7k (0%), ETH: 2545 (0%), SOL: 146 (-1%). Top Gainers: HNT, IMX, ICP, ADA, KCS. BTC ETFs: -$105m, ETH ETFs: +$6m. Bitcoin in tight liquidation range, ETH outperforms. ETH ETF sees first in flow in 10 days. Funding rates all turn negative. Mr 100 buys 500 BTC in dip. France formally charges Durov, can’t leave country. TON jumps 6% after Durov release. TON faces another outage related to DOGS. AI coins fall after Nvidia earnings. Crypto payments about to soar: Armstrong. Binance denies freezing Palestinian accounts. CryptoCom & Standard Chartered partner.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 189 - TRUMP LAUNCHES MORE NFTS]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/xUt5dSH4/fomo-hour-189-trump-launches-more-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/xUt5dSH4/fomo-hour-189-trump-launches-more-nfts"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T20:05:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETFs: -$127m, ETH ETFs: -$3m. BTC hits $58k after ETF outflows, then bounces. BTC sees largest exchange outflow in a year. Divergence between BTC & stocks grows. TON stops producing blocks briefly, price bounces. TON outage linked to DOGS launch. Maker DAO rebrands as Sky. USDS upgrade from DAI will have freezing function. Robinhood readds SOL support. SEC charges 2 brothers with $60m crypto scam. Nasdaq pitches options on BTC ETFs. Full-time open source devs under 8k in crypto. Crypto owners more likely to be ‘psychopaths’.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 188 - TON CONTINUES TO FALL]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/UhURASRQ/fomo-hour-188-ton-continues-to-fall</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/UhURASRQ/fomo-hour-188-ton-continues-to-fall"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T16:36:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock ETF sees biggest inflow in 35 days. BTC ETFs have 12 straight days of inflows. ETH ETFs have 8 straight days of outflows. ETH/BTC ratio continues to hit new lows. Russia to start using crypto for trade this week. Stablecoin TVL hits ATH of $168bn. Durov faces several serious charges in France. Telegram also under investigation in India. TRX flips TON, enters top 10 crypto coins. Crypto is the currency of AI: Naval. 84k new crypto millionaires created this year. SEC lawsuit against Kraken to proceed to trial. Aave proposes integration with BlackRock BUIDL. Celsius has repaid $2.5bn in assets so far.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 187 - AI TOKENS LEADING]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/M7IhK60K/fomo-hour-187-ai-tokens-leading</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/M7IhK60K/fomo-hour-187-ai-tokens-leading"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T16:11:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI tokens lead ahead of Nvidia earnings. Crypto funds saw $533m inflows last week. BTC ‘bull market’ back on in IFP index. BTC close to ‘parabolic zone’ soon. Many coins ‘flipping back to bullish’ indicators. Open Interest begins to creep back up again. Binance Labs to focus on AI investments. 51 L2s now built on OP stack alone. Some exchanges rejected for Hong Kong license. Vitalik questions DeFi yields in crypto. New malware steals crypto on MacOS. Avalanche Discord hacked after Polygon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Meme Coin That Became a REAL Religion!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/szDuQcIw/the-meme-coin-that-became-a-real-religion</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/szDuQcIw/the-meme-coin-that-became-a-real-religion"/>
        <updated>2024-08-24T17:42:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pastor Kelby created a meme coin on Pumpdotfun which has since registered a church and developed its own religious theories and philosophies. Twice a day Kelby heads a sermon on Twitter where he spreads lessons from books that have personally helped him achieve happiness.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 186 - AVAX LEADS PUMP]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JRqyT8vz/fomo-hour-186-avax-leads-pump</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JRqyT8vz/fomo-hour-186-avax-leads-pump"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T17:14:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETFs: +$65m, ETH ETFs: -$1m. Crypto stays range-bound ahead of Powell speech. Russia plans stablecoins of BRICS countries. El Salvador buys 162 BTC with daily buys. AVAX up 15% as Grayscale launches trust. Tron removes 12k BTC from USDD reserves. Trump promotes crypto DeFi project. Crypto half of corporate political donations. Tether abandons plan to launch its own blockchain. Sony backed L2 set to launch in weeks. Babylon launches BTC staking. CZ leaves prison for ‘halfway house’. PayPal & Anchorage partner for bank crypto rewards. Bitcoin mining market worth $74bn: JP Morgan. Bitfarms buys Stronghold in ‘strategic defence’.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 185 - KAMALA 'SUPPORTS' CRYPTO?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/u48y6NBU/fomo-hour-185-kamala-supports-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/u48y6NBU/fomo-hour-185-kamala-supports-crypto"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T17:14:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETFs: +$40m, ETH ETFs: -$18m. BTC breaks channel, ripe for ‘short squeeze’. BTC OI rises $1.3bn post Fed minutes. Kamala ‘supports crypto policies’ says advisor. Vitalik ‘bull posts’ ETH. Story Protocol raises $80m for L1. WazirX halts open orders after problems with Rupee. Coinbase & Ripple lead political donations. Salame claims government reneged on plea deal. EigenLayer team claimed coins despite being in US.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 184 - PUNKS ARE FLYING!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ILpzl0Wk/fomo-hour-184-punks-are-flying</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ILpzl0Wk/fomo-hour-184-punks-are-flying"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T17:21:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETFs: +$88m, ETH ETFs: -$7m. BTC funding negative in ‘short squeeze’ setup. BTC dominance up 18% in 2 years. TRX leads L1s as memecoin activity soars. Chance of SOL ETF is zero in 2024: Bloomberg. Another SOL ETF approved in Brazil. Binance & CZ face new class action lawsuit. Tether to launch UAE-Dirham stablecoin. Mt Gox moves $700m in BTC. CRV founder faces backlash on DAO proposal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 183 - WE ARE NOW SHITCOINING ON TRON]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/GMxAt3Zm/fomo-hour-183-we-are-now-shitcoining-on-tron</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/GMxAt3Zm/fomo-hour-183-we-are-now-shitcoining-on-tron"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T17:54:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto follows stocks higher, BTC rallies to $61k. SOL funds saw largest weekly outflow ever. Tether mints another $1bn on Tron. SEC blocked SOL ETF from CBoE. China classifies crypto for money laundering. DNC platform doesn’t mention crypto. Rumours Gensler may be Treasury Secretary pick. Chrome extension ‘Bull Checker’ leads to exploits. Genesis-linked wallet hacked for $238m. ADA drops out of the top 10 coins.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>