<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-07-24T12:31:53.084Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-07-24T12:31:53.084Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Burry just became a crypto investor thanks to this stock position]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19720310/Michael-Burry-just-became-a-crypto-investor-thanks-to-this-stock-position</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19720310/Michael-Burry-just-became-a-crypto-investor-thanks-to-this-stock-position"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T12:25:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While China has for years had a fraught relationship with cryptocurrencies, more recent news from the nation – and particularly … Continue reading]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kamala Harris 'In Talks' to Speak at Bitcoin Conference: CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241357</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241357/kamala-harris-in-talks-to-speak-at-bitcoin-conference-ceo"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T12:23:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Magazine CEO David Bailey claimed that Harris' campaign is currently "making up their minds" on a Bitcoin Conference appearance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Riot Platforms’ Acquisition of Block Mining Makes Sense, JPMorgan Says]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7473061870</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/07/24/riot-platforms-acquisition-of-block-mining-makes-sense-jpmorgan-says/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T12:19:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Riot will have the second-largest capacity among U.S. listed bitcoin miners following the acquisition, and the deal serves as the latest evaluation of underdeveloped power assets, the report said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Canny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pros and Cons of Investing in Stock Market ETFs]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19720272/Pros-and-Cons-of-Investing-in-Stock-Market-ETFs</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19720272/Pros-and-Cons-of-Investing-in-Stock-Market-ETFs"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T12:19:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Weighing your options: The pros and cons of investing in stock market ETFs Investing in the stock market can be a daunting task, especially for those who are new to the world of finance. One investment vehicle that has gained significant popularity over the years is the Exchange-Traded Fund...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ferrari To Accept Bitcoin and Crypto Payments In Europe]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74730647d3</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/ferrari-to-accept-bitcoin-and-crypto-payments-in-europe"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T12:18:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Luxury sports car manufacturer Ferrari announced it will expand the ability to pay with Bitcoin and crypto to its European dealerships starting this month. The move comes after Ferrari first began accepting Bitcoin and crypto payments at its US dealers last year.

JUST IN: Luxury Cars Manufacturer Ferrari to accept #Bitcoin and crypto payments in Europe. pic.twitter.com/PxT7Z7OwbP
— Bitcoin Magazine (@BitcoinMagazine) July 24, 2024
  
  
  
Ferrari said the rollout to Europe will occur by the end of July, enabling customers to purchase new vehicles using Bitcoin and crypto. The company plans to expand the Bitcoin payment option to dealers worldwide by the end of 2024, where legally permitted.
Ferrari continues its partnership with leading Bitcoin payments processor BitPay to process the payments. When a purchase is made in Bitcoin, BitPay instantly converts it to traditional fiat currency for Ferrari's dealers to remove exposure to Bitcoin and crypto volatility.
The ability to pay with Bitcoin and other crypto caters to Ferrari's tech-savvy customer base with sizeable Bitcoin wealth. It also taps into growing mainstream adoption, as more major companies accept Bitcoin payments including Microsoft, AT&T, and travel site Expedia.
Ferrari said accepting Bitcoin and crypto provides customers with additional flexibility and convenience in purchasing the company's luxury vehicles. The automaker saw strong demand after enabling Bitcoin payments in the US last year.
As luxury and high-end brands adopt Bitcoin payments, it helps legitimize the asset class as a currency and not just an investment. The ability of consumers to spend Bitcoin at more retailers was also cited as a factor in the recent Bitcoin market rally.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vivek Sen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ProtonMail Maker Proton Is Launching Its Own Bitcoin Wallet]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74730647ca</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/protonmail-maker-proton-is-launching-its-own-bitcoin-wallet"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T12:18:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Proton, the Swiss technology company that creates privacy-preserving online tools like ProtonMail and ProtonVPN, is launching Proton Wallet, a self-custody Bitcoin wallet.
This new product will be integrated with ProtonMail and will enable users to send bitcoin as easily as sending an email.
“Bitcoin’s value to society has been hindered by the difficulty of transacting and security concerns, and we designed Proton Wallet to specifically address both,” said Andy Yen, founder and CEO of Proton in a press release shared with Bitcoin Magazine. “Proton Wallet’s ability to support Bitcoin via email now makes Bitcoin transactions as easy to use as PayPal, while preserving the decentralized and non-custodial nature of Bitcoin.”
Proton Wallet is the latest in its suite of end-to-end encrypted tools…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Frank Corva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fetch.ai (FET) Traders Turn Bullish as ASI Phase 2 Nears]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19720288/Fetchai-FET-Traders-Turn-Bullish-as-ASI-Phase-2-Nears</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19720288/Fetchai-FET-Traders-Turn-Bullish-as-ASI-Phase-2-Nears"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T12:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now regarded as Artificial Superintelligence Alliance (ASI), Fetch.ai (FET) completed the first phase of the merger with Ocean Protocol (OCEAN) and SingularityNET (AGIX) on July 22. The competition means that the project is 50% done with the integration that will see FET, OCEAN, and AGIX come...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Ethereum ETFs Hold $10.24B in Reserves Following $106M in Inflows]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7473071160</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/us-ethereum-etfs-hold-10-24b-in-reserves-following-106m-in-inflows/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T12:14:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Based on the recent data, the nine newly introduced ethereum exchange-traded funds (ETFs) saw $106.78 million in inflows on Tuesday. Blackrock took the lead with $266.55 million in trading volume throughout the day. Blackrock Dominates Inflows as Nearly Half a Billion Exits ETHE The newly introduced ethereum ETFs performed admirably on Tuesday, registering their first […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin investment fund opens doors to EU citizenship]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19720248/Bitcoin-investment-fund-opens-doors-to-EU-citizenship</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19720248/Bitcoin-investment-fund-opens-doors-to-EU-citizenship"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T12:13:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new fund offers a way to gain citizenship in Portugal by indirectly investing over $500,000 into Bitcoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cross-Chain Service DeBridge to Issue Governance Token, Completes Activity Snapshot]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7473075a03</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/07/24/cross-chain-service-debridge-to-issue-governance-token-completes-activity-snapshot/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T12:12:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cross-chain service is popularly used to transfer funds between Ethereum, Base and Solana blockchains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AgriDex Settles First Agricultural Trade on Solana Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74730759f4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/07/24/agridex-settles-first-agricultural-trade-on-solana-blockchain/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T12:12:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AgriDex, a Solana-based marketplace aiming to bring the global agricultural market on-chain by tokenizing various crops has settled its first agricultural trade on the Solana blockchain, it told CoinDesk on Wednesday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amitoj Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Mover Americas: Bitcoin Regains $66,000, but Mt. Gox Selling Pressure Persists]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74730759ef</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/07/24/first-mover-americas-bitcoin-regains-66000-but-mt-gox-selling-pressure-persists/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T12:12:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest price moves in bitcoin (BTC) and crypto markets in context for July 24, 2024. First Mover is CoinDesk’s daily newsletter that contextualizes the latest actions in the crypto markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley, Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Altcoin Move Is Loading | What Am I Buying Here And Why?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19720289/Altcoin-Move-Is-Loading-What-Am-I-Buying-Here-And-Why</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19720289/Altcoin-Move-Is-Loading-What-Am-I-Buying-Here-And-Why"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T12:10:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#bitcoin #crypto #altcoins Consider dropping a like if you enjoyed the video and say hello to Russ! 👍A free trade of 500 USDT on ByBit as mentioned: https://partner.bybit.com/b/ddash500To get access to free Russ's Alerts on Telegram, sign up for the DashReport 💹➡️...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KnowBe4 recruited fake North Korean AI tech professional]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19720228/KnowBe4-recruited-fake-North-Korean-AI-tech-professional</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19720228/KnowBe4-recruited-fake-North-Korean-AI-tech-professional"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T12:10:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KnowBe4 hired a fake IT worker as a software engineer for its artificial intelligence (AI) team. The security training firm KnowBe4 realized its oversight after the new hire began using his company-issued computer with wrongful intentions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Panda World Price Prediction – Is $PADW a Good Investment?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19720219/Panda-World-Price-Prediction-Is-PADW-a-Good-Investment</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19720219/Panda-World-Price-Prediction-Is-PADW-a-Good-Investment"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T12:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Panda World offers a turn-based RPG where players can embark on quests, collect cards, and build teams to progress through various stages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nigeria to train 1,000 youths on AI, blockchain every year]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19720226/Nigeria-to-train-1000-youths-on-AI-blockchain-every-year</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19720226/Nigeria-to-train-1000-youths-on-AI-blockchain-every-year"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T12:06:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Nigerian government has launched an annual training program for 1,000 citizens in AI and blockchain to position Nigeria ahead of global economies and foster innovation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum ETFs Shine On Day 1 With $107M Net Inflows — But What About The Bitcoin ETFs?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19720273/Ethereum-ETFs-Shine-On-Day-1-With-107M-Net-Inflows-But-What-About-The-Bitcoin-ETFs</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19720273/Ethereum-ETFs-Shine-On-Day-1-With-107M-Net-Inflows-But-What-About-The-Bitcoin-ETFs"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T12:04:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The much-anticipated launch of Ethereum ETFs in the U.S. saw a promising start, attracting a combined net inflow of nearly $107 million on their first day. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin Hails Groundbreaking Research Paper on Ethereum Block-Building Auctions]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19720213/Vitalik-Buterin-Hails-Groundbreaking-Research-Paper-on-Ethereum-Block-Building-Auctions</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19720213/Vitalik-Buterin-Hails-Groundbreaking-Research-Paper-on-Ethereum-Block-Building-Auctions"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T12:04:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR Vitalik Buterin praises the Correlation Between Builders’ Market Share and Profitability: The research paper explores factors that impact builders’ success in securing blocks and maximizing earnings. A positive correlation exists between builders’ market share and profitability....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Riot Platforms’ Acquisition of Block Mining Makes Sense, JPMorgan Says]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19720247/Riot-Platforms-Acquisition-of-Block-Mining-Makes-Sense-JPMorgan-Says</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19720247/Riot-Platforms-Acquisition-of-Block-Mining-Makes-Sense-JPMorgan-Says"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T12:03:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Riot will have the second-largest capacity among U.S. listed bitcoin miners following the acquisition, and the deal serves as the latest evaluation of underdeveloped power assets, the report said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Performing Stocks of the Day: MMTC, Avanti Feeds and Many More]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19720209/Best-Performing-Stocks-of-the-Day-MMTC-Avanti-Feeds-and-Many-More</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19720209/Best-Performing-Stocks-of-the-Day-MMTC-Avanti-Feeds-and-Many-More"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T12:02:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore the best performing stocks of July 24, 2024: best picks in the stock market The stock market is a dynamic arena where fortunes can be made or lost within hours. Every day, certain stocks outperform the rest, capturing the attention of investors and analysts alike. Understanding the best...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana (SOL) Price Prepares to Retest All-time High Fueled by Rising Institutional Demand]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19720212/Solana-SOL-Price-Prepares-to-Retest-All-time-High-Fueled-by-Rising-Institutional-Demand</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19720212/Solana-SOL-Price-Prepares-to-Retest-All-time-High-Fueled-by-Rising-Institutional-Demand"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T12:02:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinspeaker Solana (SOL) Price Prepares to Retest All-time High Fueled by Rising Institutional Demand The rising adoption of Web 3.0 projects and meme coins on the Solana ecosystem has helped bolster the SOL’s bullish outlook. Solana (SOL) Price Prepares to Retest All-time High Fueled by Rising...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alkimiya launches Bitcoin blockspace markets protocol to tackle fee volatility]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19720201/Alkimiya-launches-Bitcoin-blockspace-markets-protocol-to-tackle-fee-volatility</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19720201/Alkimiya-launches-Bitcoin-blockspace-markets-protocol-to-tackle-fee-volatility"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T12:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alkimiya, a blockspace markets protocol, has introduced a new tool that enables users to trade Bitcoin transaction fees directly. This move comes as Bitcoin transaction fees continue to exhibit high volatility, with fees known to fluctuate between 20 to 500 times their value within a single...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PEPE price prediction: Why a 30% upswing could be on its way]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19720196/PEPE-price-prediction-Why-a-30-upswing-could-be-on-its-way</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19720196/PEPE-price-prediction-Why-a-30-upswing-could-be-on-its-way"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T12:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PEPE broke above a bullish pattern, hinting at a 30% price increase in the coming days.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Privacy Email Firm Proton Launches Self-Custody Bitcoin Wallet]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19720271/Privacy-Email-Firm-Proton-Launches-Self-Custody-Bitcoin-Wallet</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19720271/Privacy-Email-Firm-Proton-Launches-Self-Custody-Bitcoin-Wallet"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T12:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Privacy and security email firm Proton has unveiled the Proton Wallet, a self-custody Bitcoin-only wallet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin Launches Token Unlocking Program]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19720163/Worldcoin-Launches-Token-Unlocking-Program</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19720163/Worldcoin-Launches-Token-Unlocking-Program"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T12:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin (WLD) is set to launch a significant token unlocking program on July 24 that will gradually unlock 2.38 billion WLDs worth approximately $5.54 billion over the next four years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cross-Chain Service DeBridge to Issue Governance Token, Completes Activity Snapshot]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19720221/Cross-Chain-Service-DeBridge-to-Issue-Governance-Token-Completes-Activity-Snapshot</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19720221/Cross-Chain-Service-DeBridge-to-Issue-Governance-Token-Completes-Activity-Snapshot"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cross-chain service is popularly used to transfer funds between Ethereum, Base and Solana blockchains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AgriDex Settles First Agricultural Trade on Solana Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19720216/AgriDex-Settles-First-Agricultural-Trade-on-Solana-Blockchain</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19720216/AgriDex-Settles-First-Agricultural-Trade-on-Solana-Blockchain"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AgriDex, a Solana-based marketplace aiming to bring the global agricultural market on-chain by tokenizing various crops has settled its first agricultural trade on the Solana blockchain, it told CoinDesk on Wednesday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP’s Path Forward: RealUSD Launch, SEC Hearing, and Potential Market Impact]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19720300/XRPs-Path-Forward-RealUSD-Launch-SEC-Hearing-and-Potential-Market-Impact</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19720300/XRPs-Path-Forward-RealUSD-Launch-SEC-Hearing-and-Potential-Market-Impact"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XRP fell 1.66% on Tuesday, July 23, after a 1.76% gain the previous day, closing at $0.5983. This drop aligns with a broader market downturn, where the total crypto market cap fell 1.50% to $2.351 trillion. Speculation about a potential settlement in the ongoing legal battle between the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Is The Top Choice For Criminal Activity, Europol Report Shows]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74730d70a5</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-the-top-choice-of-criminals-europol-report/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T11:36:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest research from Europol called the Europol Internet Organized Crime Threat Assessment makes it clear how thieves’ use of Bitcoin is changing. The report talks about the use of stablecoins like Tether (USDT) and Bitcoin for illegal activities, and how Monero is becoming more popular for private transfers, among other key findings.
 
 
Bitcoin: The Cybercrime Kingpin?
 
The Europol study highlights how improbable it is that Bitcoin’s significance in cybercrime will change very soon. The proven popularity of Bitcoin and the wide range of exchanges and services supporting it make it a constant tool for crooks.
 
Law enforcement departments are not, however, sitting about. By employing blacklisting features in stablecoins, authorities have been able to freeze dubious money, therefore d…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South African Startup Neonomad to Launch Rand-Backed Stablecoin]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74730fa7a0</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/south-african-startup-neonomad-to-launch-rand-backed-stablecoin/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T11:23:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neonomad, the South African hybrid exchange platform, is set to launch Zarcoin, a stablecoin tied to the South African Rand. This innovative stablecoin epitomizes the seamless integration of regulatory safety with decentralized efficiency. Neonomad’s platform will also facilitate multiple offerings, including in the decentralized finance space. Banking South Africa’s Unbanked South African fintech startup Neonomad, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ether's BTC-Denominated Price Flirts With 9-Year-Long Trendline Support: Technical Analysis]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74730fb60e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/07/24/ethers-btc-denominated-price-flirts-with-9-year-long-trendline-support-technical-analysis/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T11:23:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The trendline connecting 2016 and 2017 lows has consistently offered support since January.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2025 EU Crypto Landscape: MiCAR, TRF, and DORA Explained]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74730b16e9</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/2025-eu-crypto-landscape-micar-trf-and-dora-explained/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T11:03:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the European Union strides towards comprehensive crypto regulation, MiCAR stands out as a cornerstone of this new landscape. However, the true impact of MiCAR, alongside other critical regulations like the Transfer of Funds Regulation (TRF) and the Digital Operational Resilience Act (DORA), will only begin to unfold in 2025. To delve deeper into these […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ferrari to Extend Cryptocurrency Payments to Europe: Reuters]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e747cf72caf</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2024/07/24/ferrari-to-extend-cryptocurrency-payments-to-europe-reuters/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T10:39:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company also plans to extend the service to other markets by the end of the year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto-Friendly Revolut Targets $45 Billion Valuation in Upcoming Share Sale]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e747cf1e5fe</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/crypto-friendly-revolut-targets-45-billion-valuation-in-upcoming-share-sale/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T10:22:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Revolut, the crypto-friendly digital bank, is reportedly planning to sell $500 million of employee shares, targeting a staggering valuation of $45 billion. This move is seen as a significant step towards a potential Initial Public Offering (IPO). Revolut’s progressive approach to cryptocurrencies, combined with its innovative banking solutions, continues to disrupt the financial sector, underscoring […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Dips Below $66,000 After Mt. Gox Shifts $2.8 Billion BTC to a New Wallet]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241331</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241331/bitcoin-dips-below-66000-after-mt-gox-shifts-2-5-billion-btc-to-a-new-wallet"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T10:13:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin briefly sank below $66,000 on Wednesday after Mt. Gox shifted $2.8 billion worth of BTC, including $25 million sent to Bitstamp.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Resilience: Investors Showing Reduced Willingness To Sell BTC – Analyst]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e747cfc4e7f</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/investors-showing-reduced-desire-to-sell-bitcoin/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T10:08:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following the renewed optimism around Bitcoin, the largest cryptocurrency asset, Axel Adler Jr, a research and data analyst at CryptoQuant, has spotted a noticeable drop in the willingness of investors to sell their BTC holdings. This pattern shows that there is a rising confidence in the prospect of additional gains in the flagship crypto asset as the market as a whole experiences a significant recovery.
 
Waning Bitcoin Selling Pressure From Investors
 
The CryptoQuant’s analyst, Axel Adler Jr, highlighted the positive development in his latest sentiment research. His analysis underscores a change in outlook where holders are constantly choosing to keep their BTC holdings rather than sell them, despite recent market rallies.
 
 
According to the expert, Bitcoin has become a major investm…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Godspower Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unbound Fund Offers a New Path to EU Citizenship With Bitcoin Investment]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e747cf861f6</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/unbound-fund-offers-a-new-path-to-eu-citizenship-with-bitcoin-investment/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T09:43:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unbound Fund has announced a new opportunity for individuals to acquire Portuguese/EU citizenship by indirectly holding bitcoin worth about $542,000 (€500,000). The fund is said to be the first of its kind to be eligible for the Golden Visa, providing exposure to bitcoin. Unbound Fund’s features include 100% passive bitcoin holding, investment in Blackrock ETFs […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Price Flat the Day After for Spot ETFs Debut in US]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241350</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241350/ethereum-price-flat-the-day-after-for-spot-etfs-debut-in-us"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T09:40:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Consensys CEO Joe Lubin, who's also an Ethereum co-founder, said it's "important that more individuals and organizations are able to own Ethereum."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETFs Break Inflow Streak as Traders Look to Trump’s Nashville Appearance for Volatility]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e747cfa7b06</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/07/24/bitcoin-etfs-break-inflow-streak-as-traders-look-to-trumps-nashville-appearance-for-volatility/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T09:30:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitwise’s BITB led with $70 million in net outflows, followed by Ark’s ARKB at $52 million and Grayscale’s GBTC at $27 million.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iris Energy Is Positioned to Become One of the Biggest Listed Bitcoin Miners: Canaccord]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e747ce777ff</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/07/24/iris-energy-is-positioned-to-become-one-of-the-biggest-listed-bitcoin-miners-canaccord/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T08:59:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The broker raised its price target for the shares to $15 from $12 and reiterated its buy rating.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Canny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Conference Lineup: Kamala Harris In Talks To Follow Trump, Kennedy Jr.]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e747ce2963a</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-conference-kamala-harris-in-talks/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T08:39:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US Vice President Kamala Harris is reportedly in discussions to join the speaker lineup at the upcoming Bitcoin conference, adding to the roster that already includes leading US presidential candidate Donald Trump and candidate Robert F. Kennedy Jr. The conference, set to take place in Nashville from July 25-27, is anticipated to be a blockbuster event.
 
All 3 Presidential Candidates Could Woo Bitcoin Voters
 
David Bailey, CEO of Bitcoin Magazine and the conference organizer, announced the potential addition via X, stating, “We’re in talks with Kamala Harris’ campaign for her to speak at the conference. Would be very savvy of her to reset the democrat positioning on the fastest growing voter block in the country. They’re making up their minds today.”
 
The potential participation of Harr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Exchange Bybit Targets Institutional Traders with 2 New Features]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e747ce32d2d</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com/cryptocurrency/exchange/crypto-exchange-bybit-targets-institutional-traders-with-2-new-features/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T08:35:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bybit, the  
world's second-largest cryptocurrency exchange by trading volume, has unveiled  
two new initiatives aimed at enhancing liquidity and facilitating large-scale  
transactions in the crypto market.
On  
Wednesday, the platform introduced both a liquidity matching program for spot  
markets and zero commissions for block trading.
Bybit Launches Spot  
Liquidity Pairing
The company  
announced the launch of its Spot Liquidity Pairing Program, designed to connect  
market makers with projects seeking improved liquidity, a persistent issue in  
the cryptocurrency.
As part of  
this program, Bybit will highlight "Premium" liquidity providers on  
its recommendation list to projects. For July, seven market makers have been  
recognized in this category, including Amber Group, Auros, C…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Damian Chmiel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mt. Gox Moves $3B Bitcoin to New Wallet, $130M to Bitstamp Exchange]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e747ce3438e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2024/07/24/mt-gox-moves-3b-bitcoin-to-new-wallet-130m-to-bitstamp-exchange/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T08:35:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The defunct exchange has moved billions of dollars worth of bitcoin over two days.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miner Riot Scoops Small Kentucky Rival for $92 Million as Sector Sags]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241329</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241329/bitcoin-miner-riot-scoops-small-kentucky-rival-for-92-million-as-sector-sags"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T07:13:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The terms of the deal included $18.5 million in cash and $74 million in Riot common stock, the company said Tuesday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Sinclair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum ETFs Hit $107 Million Inflows on Debut: 'Very Solid First Day']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241326</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241326/ethereum-etfs-top-107-million-debut-very-solid-first-day"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T05:44:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Total inflows from eight competitors have dragged the performance of ETH ETFs into positive territory despite Grayscale's sag.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Sinclair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Touts Tesla's AI Edge During Q2 Earnings Call]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241323</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241323/elon-musk-tesla-ai-robotics-q2-earnings-call"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T03:06:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Tesla CEO highlighted links between the automaker and xAI, as well as its progress in robotics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Says SEC is Refusing to Cough Up Documents Critical for its Defense]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241308</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241308/coinbase-sec-refusing-documents-critical-defense"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T01:05:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase has filed a motion to compel the SEC to produce documents deemed critical to its defense against the regulator.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Sainsbury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Are Today’s ‘Musk Empire’ Stock Exchange Daily Combo and Riddle]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241078</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/todays-musk-empire-stock-exchange-daily-combo"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T00:40:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking for the Musk Empire daily combo and riddle solution for Tuesday, July 23? Here are the latest boosts for the Telegram crypto game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken Returns Bitcoin to Customers of Mt. Gox 10 Years After Hack]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241306</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241306/kraken-returns-bitcoin-customers-mt-gox-hack"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T00:20:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It marks one of the last remaining chapters to be concluded in the Mt. Gox saga, which has taken years to resolve.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Sinclair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Launches Llama 3.1 as Mark Zuckerberg Pushes Open-Source AI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241302</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241302/meta-launches-llama-3-1-as-mark-zuckerberg-pushes-open-source-ai"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T23:50:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meta's latest AI model, released for free on Tuesday, can challenge the capabilities of OpenAI’s ChatGPT.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 164 - ETH ETF DAY!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Qn97IvaR/fomo-hour-164-eth-etf-day</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Qn97IvaR/fomo-hour-164-eth-etf-day"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T22:48:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETF Flows: +$534m. ETH outperforms slightly as 9 ETFs set to launch. Grayscale moves $1bn ETH to Coinbase for outflows. Biggest BlackRock ETF inflow day in 4 months. Mt Gox moves $2.8bn BTC for distributions. US government moves $4m BTC to Coinbase. Bedford FC buys $4.5m BTC. Hamilton Lane launches private credit fund on SOL. CNBC discusses BTC reserve currency rumour. Polymarket sets another trading record. BlockFi administrator submits plan to repay customers. WLD denies insider trading and manipulation claims. India keeps high crypto taxes unchanged. Gate exchange exits Japan. Marathon Digital fined $138m for breaching NDA. HyperLend launches lending on HyperLiquid.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Citi Boosts Coinbase Stock Price Target, Rates COIN a ‘Buy’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241284</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241284/coinbase-coin-stock-price-target-citi-research-buy"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T22:40:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Citing a Supreme Court ruling, the firm notes that the Securities and Exchange Commission could have its authority diminished.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Took Over the Las Vegas Sphere—Where’s Dogwifhat?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241285</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241285/bitcoin-took-over-las-vegas-sphere-wheres-dogwifhat"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T22:17:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dogwifhat raised $700,000 to get on the Sphere back in March, but Bitcoin has beaten the dog to punch via Crypto.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum ETFs Hit $1 Billion in Day One Trading Volume as ETH Price Sits Still]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241281</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241281/ethereum-etf-1-billion-first-day-eth-price-flat"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T21:34:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was a successful launch for the new funds—but the price of Ethereum held flat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple's Foldable iPhone Rumored to Be Coming in 2026—Late to the Party?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241252</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241252/apple-foldable-iphone-report-years-of-rumors"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T21:03:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new report revives years of speculation over an iPhone with a folding screen, long after competitors have been in the space.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Are Today's ‘Hamster Kombat’ Daily Combo and Cipher Code]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=239305</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/todays-hamster-kombat-daily-combo-cipher-code"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T19:55:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking for the daily combo and cipher code for Tuesday, July 23? Here’s what you need to make bank in Telegram game Hamster Kombat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can Grayscale's Ethereum Mini Trust Prevent a GBTC Redemptions Rerun?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241243</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241243/can-grayscale-ethereum-mini-trust-prevent-gbtc-redemptions-rerun"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T19:09:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Tuesday’s launch of spot Ethereum ETFs, the crypto market is braced for potential outflows from Grayscale's Ethereum Trust.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These Are All the Ethereum ETFs Now Trading in the US]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230228</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230228/ethereum-etfs-approved-us"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T18:19:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many major investment firms have dropped spot Ethereum ETFs in the U.S. which are now trading on American stock exchanges. Here's the running list.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mark Cuban Says Kamala Harris’ Camp Reached Out With 'Multiple Questions' About Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241214</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241214/mark-cuban-says-kamala-harris-far-more-open-crypto-biden"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T18:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Less than two days into the VP's presidential campaign, advisors to Kamala Harris are apparently weighing how to approach crypto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Denies Considering Bitcoin Skeptic Jamie Dimon or BlackRock's Fink for Treasury]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241234</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241234/trump-denies-considering-bitcoin-skeptic-dimon-blackrock-fink-treasury"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T16:50:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin-bullish BlackRock CEO Larry Fink is not on Trump’s radar for a Treasury pick, the President has clarified.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pudgy Penguins Firm Raises $11 Million for Ethereum Layer-2 Push]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241125</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241125/pudgy-penguins-igloo-raises-11-million-ethereum-layer-2"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T15:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Igloo, Inc. just raised fresh funding to pursue its crypto tech ambitions following the Pudgy Penguins firm’s acquisition of Frame in June.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Still 'Most Abused' Crypto Asset Among Criminals, Says Europol]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241208</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241208/bitcoin-most-abused-crypto-among-criminals-europol"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T15:12:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The report's authors shared concerns that the approval of spot Bitcoin ETFs could create new opportunities for scammers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Joe Biden Is Dead' Meme Coins Are Spreading as Quickly as the Wild Rumors]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241198</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241198/joe-biden-is-dead-meme-coins-wild-rumors"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T13:47:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a rumor that Joe Biden was “unlikely to survive the night” after his COVID-19 diagnosis, crypto degens have launched corresponding meme coins.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SingularityNET Puts $53 Million Toward an AI ‘Supercomputer’ and New Data Centers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241118</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241118/singularitynet-53-million-ai-supercomputer-data-centers"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The funding will help build modular hubs to support artificial general intelligence (AGI) research.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Investors Hold Strong as BlackRock's IBIT Pulls in $526 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241163</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241163/bitcoin-investors-hold-strong-as-blackrocks-ibit-pulls-in-526-million"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T12:34:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock's iShares Bitcoin Trust reported inflows of $526.7 million in investor funds on July 22, the highest single-day tally since March.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Price Climbs to $3,500 Ahead of Spot ETF Trading in US]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241162</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241162/ethereum-price-climbs-to-3500-ahead-of-spot-etf-trading-in-us"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T11:34:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["When you give investors the choice to buy Bitcoin or Ethereum, they end up buying both," said Bitwise CIO Matt Hougan, looking ahead to the ETFs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[English Football Club Owned by Bitcoiner Adds $4.5 Million Bitcoin to Its Treasury]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241141</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241141/english-football-club-owned-by-bitcoiner-adds-4-5-million-bitcoin-to-its-treasury"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T10:55:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The exact purchase price was a very meme-friendly $4,500,420.69.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Minsberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Could Fortnite Use Blockchain? ‘Perhaps Someday,’ Says Epic CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241111</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241111/fortnite-blockchain-perhaps-someday-says-epic-ceo"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T10:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fortnite may utilize blockchain in the future but it will not use crypto or offer NFT trading, Epic Games CEO Tim Sweeney said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Mostly Unbothered as Mt. Gox Moves $2.8 Billion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241134</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241134/bitcoin-price-unbothered-mt-gox-btc-billions"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T09:51:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's signs investors have been buying the dip, said analysts, but Bitcoin traders are still in for a "news driven and volatility filled week."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mika Shares How to Sell Crypto Using Kraken Wallet]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/6e7AC9Po/mika-shares-how-to-sell-crypto-using-kraken-wallet</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/6e7AC9Po/mika-shares-how-to-sell-crypto-using-kraken-wallet"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T09:07:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rug Radio creator Mika guides you through the process of selling crypto and transferring it back to your bank account.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gate.io to Shift Japanese Customers to Compliant Crypto Exchanges as it Exits Market]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241132</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241132/gate-io-japanese-compliant-crypto-exchanges-exits-market"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T07:12:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gate.io will cease accepting new account registrations from Japanese residents and will begin a phased termination of services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Sinclair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polymarket Punter's Profits Surge to Top Spot After Biden Bows Out, Endorses Harris]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241123</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241123/polymarket-punters-profits-surge-to-top-spot-after-biden-bows-out-endorses-harris"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T05:39:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Polymarket trader has been rewarded for taking a punt following President Joe Biden's endorsement of Kamala Harris on Sunday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Sinclair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale Shifts $1 Billion in Ethereum to Coinbase Ahead of US ETF Trading Debut]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241104</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241104/grayscale-shifts-1-billion-in-ethereum-to-coinbase-ahead-of-us-etf-trading-debut"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T01:06:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale's transaction of $1 billion to Coinbase Prime has fuelled speculation, though others see it as business as usual.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Sainsbury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum ETFs Finally Start Trading Tomorrow—Here’s What to Expect]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241084</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241084/ethereum-etf-what-to-expect-analysts"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T23:52:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While some see ETH hitting an all-time high, the immediate aftermath of the launch could be “underwhelming,” analysts say.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[And the Winner Is: We Got AI Models to Predict the Next President]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=240990</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/240990/ask-ai-donald-trump-kamala-harris"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T23:37:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT, Grok, Claude AI, and Venice AI gave their takes on who would win in a hypothetical head-to-head matchup.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram Hits 950 Million Users Amid Crypto Gaming Boom]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241063</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241063/telegram-hits-950-million-users-crypto-gaming-boom"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T22:50:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Multi-faceted messaging app Telegram is seeing unprecedented popularity as it becomes the platform of choice for crypto gamers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Kawailani Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 163 - JOEVER FOR BYEDEN]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/0GxuImTw/fomo-hour-163-joever-for-byeden</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/0GxuImTw/fomo-hour-163-joever-for-byeden"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T16:26:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto dips then bounces on Biden-Harris switch. SOL again leads, DEX volume eclipses ETH + BNB. Biden news had led to $67m liquidations. Democrats have chance to ‘regain crypto vote’. Mt Gox transfers to Bitstamp expected soon. Crypto sees $3.2bn fund inflows in 3 weeks. China company Boyaa buys $100m BTC. Polymarket saw $80m bets on Biden withdrawal. Polymarket 2024 volumes hit $500m. Elon appearance at Bitcoin Nashville rumoured. Combined SOL, BTC & ETH ETF coming: Geraci. Call skew heads to 2024 extremes in bullish sign. Plan B points to bullish setup in S2F model. Coinbase premium moves back to positive. Gensler likely resigns next year: 10x. Germany already lost $124m profit selling.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's the Meta? Do Crypto Degens Care About Being Scammed?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/nNFxaZd6/whats-the-meta-do-crypto-degens-care-about-being-scammed</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/nNFxaZd6/whats-the-meta-do-crypto-degens-care-about-being-scammed"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T15:25:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What's the Meta? With the rise of Pumpdotfun and rug pulls becoming a daily occurrence, why do crypto degens keep investing? Do these investors enjoy being scammed? It appears that people very often invest in meme coins that are very obviously going to rug pull. Once it happens, they just laugh it off on Twitter, is being scammed fun?!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 162 - SOLANA LEADS THE CHARGE!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/695Aw43b/fomo-hour-162-solana-leads-the-charge</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/695Aw43b/fomo-hour-162-solana-leads-the-charge"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T21:28:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETF Inflows: +$85m. SOL leads majors ahead of ETH ETF. Rumours Trump may want BTC in strategic reserve. Trump BTC round-table tickets going for $845k. Polymarket hits volume record of $20m. ETH ETFs will get steady capital: Binance CEO. Winklevii donate $1m to try and unseat Warren. Tornado sees $1.9bn volume resurgence. New overlay attacks growing in crypto. Messari co-founder faces backlash on views. Raydium integrates with Moonpay. Tencent leads investment round in Chainbase. ZA Bank partners with stablecoin issuers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 161 - THE BIG WIF COMEBACK?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/wDunKbUD/fomo-hour-161-the-big-wif-comeback</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/wDunKbUD/fomo-hour-161-the-big-wif-comeback"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T17:02:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETF Inflows: +$53m. Crypto remains stable despite macro sell-off. ETH ETF providers undercut each other on fees. Grayscale keeps 2.5% high fee, launches mini-fund. Grayscale launches ‘Decentralised AI Fund’. Dimon may be ‘changing tune’ on Bitcoin. Many alts now bounced 50-90% from lows. Vote implies 55% of Mt. Gox depositors won’t sell. BlockFi to make creditor distributions this month. WazirX exchanges sees $230m suspected breach. Vitalik warns against voting ‘pro-crypto’. Vitalik & Autism Capital trade barbs. Bitcoin Magazine to hold pro-Trump fundraiser. State Street explore blockchain payments. UPbit sees 44% monthly drop in volume.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 160 - CHATTING TO ROBINHOOD!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mwCkRYNA/fomo-hour-160-chatting-to-robinhood</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mwCkRYNA/fomo-hour-160-chatting-to-robinhood"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T17:30:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETF Inflows: +$423m. Crypto pushes higher, biggest ETF inflow in 6 weeks. Mt. Gox FUD ‘overestimated’ as whales accumulate. Kraken to begin Mt. Gox repayments in 7-14d. ETH spot ETFs will push ETH to $5k: Bitwise. SOL ETF will be next: Bloomberg. XRP up 35% this week ahead of potential settlement. Aethir reports $36m H1 customer revenue. Craig Wright now under threat of perjury & forgery. FTX & CFTC in $12.7bn settlement. WLD up 40% after delaying unlock schedule. Helio announces instant crypto fiat commerce. Phantom pauses cross-chain swaps amid exploit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 159 - MEMECOINS GO MAD!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ynyia4ZI/fomo-hour-159-memecoins-go-mad</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ynyia4ZI/fomo-hour-159-memecoins-go-mad"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T09:15:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETF Inflows: +$301m. BTC dips from $65k as $6bn moves from Mt. Gox. Coinbase & MicroStrategy surge with BTC. Genesis sells another $38m BTC. ETH ETF timeline delayed until July 23rd. Trump chooses crypto friendly Vance as VP. Old clip shows Vance bashing Gensler on crypto. Bitcoin is good during debasement: Larry Fink. Michael Dell calls Fink video ‘fascinating’. Fear & Greed index shifts to Greed. Tether mints $1bn USDT on Tron. Stripe expands crypto integration to the EU.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 158 - A WILD WEEKEND FOR BITCOIN]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BcG2gbdq/fomo-hour-158-a-wild-weekend-for-bitcoin</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BcG2gbdq/fomo-hour-158-a-wild-weekend-for-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T17:58:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trump response optimism takes BTC to $63K. Bitcoin whales accumulate most since April 2023. Trump still set to talk at Bitcoin Nashville. ETH ETF approval this week: Geraci. XRP vs SEC press conference rumoured on 18th. Crypto funds saw $1.44B inflows last week. Rumours China is to ‘unban BTC’ in Q4. S. Korea may delay crypto taxes until 2028. Russia to allow crypto trading on stock exchange. All altcoin categories outperform BTC over 7d. BitConnect infamous promoter convicted. Scroll becomes 8th L2 with TVL over $1bn. ETHFI Season 2 claims available this week. Base hits record 1m UserOps in a week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zoltan Istvan on AI and Human Immortality]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/4BsXkpuA/zoltan-istvan-on-ai-and-human-immortality</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/4BsXkpuA/zoltan-istvan-on-ai-and-human-immortality"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T21:02:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Transhumanist Party founder Zoltan Istvan chats with Decrypt's Emerging Technology report Jason Nelson about his journey with transhumanism, running for office, and why he fears AI is outpacing life science and poses a threat to the quest for immortality.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 157 - ROLLBIT FRIDAY!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/COVjTRpj/fomo-hour-157-rollbit-friday</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/COVjTRpj/fomo-hour-157-rollbit-friday"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T16:14:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The German state sells $2bn+ BTC and has under $300m left. BTC ETF sees $800M of inflows, Mr 100 keeps buying. SOL ETF deadline set for 2025, election could be key. SOL stablecoin TVL soars on Tether & PYUSD growth. Firedancer sees the first accepted block on SOL testnet. ETH ETFs finally expected next week. Monthly active crypto addresses top 100m. Trump to speak at Bitcoin Nashville conference. Golman Sachs to launch 3 tokenization projects. Short squeeze in altcoins sees TIA rise 80% from lows. MOG leads top memes coins, BONK flips WIF. Farming interest shifts to Berachain & Monad.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's the Meta? Meet the Solana Dev Who Suffered Third Degree Burns to Pump a Token]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OgJCZDWk/whats-the-meta-meet-the-solana-dev-who-suffered-third-degree-burns-to-pump-a-token</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OgJCZDWk/whats-the-meta-meet-the-solana-dev-who-suffered-third-degree-burns-to-pump-a-token"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T12:08:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Mikol: the Dare dev that doused himself in isopropyl alcohol and had fireworks shot at him. He instantly went up in flames and was rushed to hospital, where it became apparent he suffered third degree burns.

In this episode, Mikol reflects on the biggest night of his life, details his injuries, and the grueling recovery process he’s still in. Despite the traumatic incident, Mikol isn’t done with the project. Instead, he’s planning to build a decentralized app where community members can take on dares in exchange for DARE tokens.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 156 - ETH ON THE RISE!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/soJHVe7R/fomo-hour-156-eth-on-the-rise</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/soJHVe7R/fomo-hour-156-eth-on-the-rise"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T17:34:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETF Flows: +$147m. ETH outperforms with ETF optimism. Germany government moves 2375 BTC again. Tether mints another $250m USDT on SOL. Trump to speak at Bitcoin Nashville. Goldman Sachs to launch 3 tokenisation projects. Realised losses similar to COVID period. Staked ETH nears ATH. CEX stablecoin volume hits 7-month low. CFTC says 70-80% of crypto not securities. Base hardfork improves compression 20-30%. BitMEX pleads guilty to AML violation. APTOS & SEI see weak attendance at ETHcc event.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 155 - ETFs SAVE THE DAY]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MLhJXkd3/fomo-hour-155-etfs-save-the-day</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MLhJXkd3/fomo-hour-155-etfs-save-the-day"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T17:38:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETF Flows: $216m. $654m of inflows into ETFs over 3 days. BTC transaction fees hit 4-year low. German state moves $300m BTC, holdings $1bn. SOL flips ETH for 7d DEX volumes. SOL Firedancer sees first accepted block on testnet. Tether mints another $250m USDT on SOL. Crypto monthly active addresses tops 100m. Biden crypto veto now expected to be upheld. Tech coalition urges Biden to back crypto. People face security threats at ETHCC. DBS sees 300% growth in crypto trading. PYUSD now 7th largest stable coin. China may have already sold BTC holdings. Elliptic exposes $11bn USDT scam network. StanChart in talks to buy Howard’s crypto fund. Polychain accuses former employee of side deals. SEI leads altcoins as it launches v2 mainnet beta. TIA rises 80% from lows on short squeeze. TON to release L2 based on Polygon’s tech stack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 154 - THE CELEBS ARE BACK...]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/D9FImiB3/fomo-hour-154-the-celebs-are-back</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/D9FImiB3/fomo-hour-154-the-celebs-are-back"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T18:15:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETF Flows: +$295m. ETF inflows fight German selling, BTC unchanged. German government sells $900m BTC, moves more. Rate of sales implies German supply sold this week. ETH ETFs set to launch next week. Election may affect SOL ETF decision March 2025. Raydium beats ETH for 24hr fees. BTC ‘power law’ points to 300% gain by 2025. BTC in 80 day post-halving re-accumulation phase. BlackRock treasury fund hits $500m. Republicans release pro-crypto policy. Senate urges blockchain tests for national security. Drop in BTC mining difficulty ‘comparable to FTX’. MetaMask introduces delegation toolkit. 25 major projects to launch tokens in H2 2025.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 153 - A WEAK WEEKEND]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5YSiCw7F/fomo-hour-153-a-weak-weekend</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5YSiCw7F/fomo-hour-153-a-weak-weekend"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T23:04:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC sinks 5% then bounces back to unchanged. $58-60k the main area for ‘shorts to defend’. Crypto funds saw $441m inflows last week. German government transfers 1000 BTC to sell. Crypto sentiment at lowest in over a year. ETH spot premium hits local highs. Japanese firm Metaplanet buys $2.5m BTC. Expect more miners merging: TeraWulf CEO. SOL Firedancer bug bounty goes live. GLM transfers $117m of ETH treasury to exchanges. 98% of coins have topped this cycle: Kang. ETH ETF should come in next 2 weeks: Geraci. Crypto progress disheartening: Copeland.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 152 - JOINED BY DEEZE!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/oLurNfIh/fomo-hour-152-joined-by-deeze</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/oLurNfIh/fomo-hour-152-joined-by-deeze"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T18:57:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC hits $54k, set for worst week in over year. Mt. Gox begins to move BTC & make distributions. German government continues to sell holdings. Worst day for BTC liquidations since FTX. Justin Sun says he is willing to buy German BTC. German MP calls on it to stop selling BTC. $52k super-trend support line eyed for BTC. Funding rates turn extremely negative across majors. Only 6 mining machines profitable below $56k. Coinbase spot buyers emerge to counter drop. Total3 hits RSI lows only hit 4 times in last 4 years. Fear & Greed index hits lowest since Jan 2023. Capo remains bullish. Real selling begins at $38k: Schiff. Coinbase continue to fight for Gensler’s emails. Circle mints $250m USDC on SOL. Symbiotic hits $1bn TVL. Taiwan Mobile may open crypto exchange. Unisat completes funding round with Binance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 151 - BTC TAPS THE 60K LINE]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/HP5x5DDr/fomo-hour-151-btc-taps-the-60k-line</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/HP5x5DDr/fomo-hour-151-btc-taps-the-60k-line"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T18:27:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETF Flows: -$14m. BTC drops to $60k, CME gap filed again. $1bn shorts liquidated if we rally to $62.6k. Pump(.)fun surpasses ETH for revenue. ETH will outperform BTC after ETF launch: K33. ETH ETF may be delayed even further. BTC heading to $150k: Fundstrat. Chainlink & Fidelity partner for fund data on-chain. USDC protects the dollar: Circle ad. Robinhood considers crypto futures in US & EU. Another BTC miner looks to IPO in US. Vitalik bullish on prediction markets. Sentient Labs raises $85m for AI on SOL. Mantra to tokenise $500m of real estate. TAO falls 15% after security breach. Crypto scams & hacks hit $572m in Q2.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 150 - BILLY TO A BILLY?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/lyMeJEHY/fomo-hour-150-billy-to-a-billy</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/lyMeJEHY/fomo-hour-150-billy-to-a-billy"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T15:58:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETF inflows hit highest in a month. ETH ETF inflows to hit $5bn in 6 months: Gemini. ETH public funds see largest outflow since 2022. SOL hits new ATH for monthly economic value. Sellers starting to look exhausted: Crypto Quant. Silvergate sued by SEC, settles for $63m. Circle gets stablecoin license for USDC in EU. US DoJ ironically chooses Coinbase for custody. Bitcoin miner aims for $16bn IPO. Bitfarms increases BTC mining amid takeover attempt. DOT has 2 year runway amid large burn. DOT ecosystem builders turn against team. PENDLE TVL falls $3bn as restaking rewards end. PayPal stablecoin goes live on Jupiter. At least $600m altcoin unlocks this month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 149 - LUCA NETZ LIVE!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/VwszUB8K/fomo-hour-149-luca-netz-live</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/VwszUB8K/fomo-hour-149-luca-netz-live"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T07:39:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC bounces back above $61k after nosedive. SOL leads majors, BTC dominance falls. BTC RSI hit 18, largest net selling day in over a year. $174m ETF outflow led by GBTC. German government sells $24m more more BTC. Mt Gox info probably ‘leaked to insiders’. Mr 100 buys dip for first time in 34 days. SOL leads Moonpay transactions for 5th week. Trump may speak at Bitcoin Nashville. Biden rehires crypto advisor. Crypto & AI complement each other: Balaji. Bitcoin will protect AI’s wealth: Pomp. Tether stops minting on Algorand & EOS. Jupiter launches v3 swaps. ETH Foundation mailing list gets leaked. Jump CEO resigns after CFTC investigation. 54% of Japanese institutional investors want BTC. Strike launches in UK. MiCA approved EUR stablecoins coming in 6 days.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>