<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-06-01T13:15:56.733Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-06-01T13:15:56.733Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bybit Affiliate Withdraws Hong Kong VASP Application Months After Regulator Issued License Warning]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741e2526b3</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bybit-affiliate-withdraws-hong-kong-vasp-application-months-after-regulator-issued-license-warning/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T13:12:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Singaporean crypto exchange Bybit’s affiliate Spark Fintech Limited, has abandoned its pursuit of an operating license in Hong Kong. The affiliate withdrew its virtual asset trading platform application on May 31, exactly four months after submitting it. The decision followed the Hong Kong regulator’s classification of Bybit as an unlicensed entity, accompanied by threats […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana price prediction: Will SOL break out to hit $500 this cycle?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19546332/Solana-price-prediction-Will-SOL-break-out-to-hit-500-this-cycle</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19546332/Solana-price-prediction-Will-SOL-break-out-to-hit-500-this-cycle"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T13:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The token's momentum is slowing down. However, this analysis suggests that it may only be for a short time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Nasdaq's record, Salesforce stock's bad day, GameStop spikes again: Markets news roundup]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19546318/The-Nasdaqs-record-Salesforce-stocks-bad-day-GameStop-spikes-again-Markets-news-roundup</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19546318/The-Nasdaqs-record-Salesforce-stocks-bad-day-GameStop-spikes-again-Markets-news-roundup"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A man in Europe recently recovered nearly $3 million in Bitcoin after thinking his password was lost forever.Read more...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MotoGP’s Gresini racing goes crypto with new fan sponsorship program]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19546334/MotoGPs-Gresini-racing-goes-crypto-with-new-fan-sponsorship-program</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19546334/MotoGPs-Gresini-racing-goes-crypto-with-new-fan-sponsorship-program"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MotoGP race team Gresini Racing is embracing elements of decentralized ownership through a new program allowing fans to purchase personal team sponsorship packages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Scammers Target Canadians on Dating Apps, Leading to Huge Financial Losses]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19546292/Crypto-Scammers-Target-Canadians-on-Dating-Apps-Leading-to-Huge-Financial-Losses</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19546292/Crypto-Scammers-Target-Canadians-on-Dating-Apps-Leading-to-Huge-Financial-Losses"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T12:38:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This summer, crypto scammers are aggressively targeting Canadians on dating apps and websites. Unfortunately, many...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Veteran trader predicts Bitcoin could soon match 100 ounces of Gold]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19546271/Veteran-trader-predicts-Bitcoin-could-soon-match-100-ounces-of-Gold</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19546271/Veteran-trader-predicts-Bitcoin-could-soon-match-100-ounces-of-Gold"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T12:27:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Veteran trader Peter Brandt forecasts a major surge in Bitcoin’s (BTC) value compared to gold (XAU), predicting BTC could reach … Continue reading]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Challenges SEC’s Rulemaking Process, Argues for Clear Regulations on Digital Assets]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741e22bb3b</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/coinbase-challenges-secs-rulemaking-process-argues-for-clear-regulations-on-digital-assets/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T12:22:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase, Inc. has escalated its dispute with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) by filing a reply brief in the Third Circuit Court of Appeals, arguing the necessity of clear rulemaking for the digital asset industry. The case underscores the ongoing tensions between regulators and the digital asset sector over compliance and operational standards. Coinbase […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 signs that Ethereum price will finally break $4K in June]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19546264/3-signs-that-Ethereum-price-will-finally-break-4K-in-June</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19546264/3-signs-that-Ethereum-price-will-finally-break-4K-in-June"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T12:21:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anticipation of potential Ether ETF approvals in June is pivotal in driving ETH's price above $4,000, with whales accumulating and rising holding sentiment furthering the bullish outlook.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crucial SHIB Rewards Warning Issued to Shiba Inu Community]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19546262/Crucial-SHIB-Rewards-Warning-Issued-to-Shiba-Inu-Community</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19546262/Crucial-SHIB-Rewards-Warning-Issued-to-Shiba-Inu-Community"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T12:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SHIB, LEASH, BONE, Sheboshis holders get crucial warning]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Privacy as a human right in crypto: An uncompromising stand]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19546250/Privacy-as-a-human-right-in-crypto-An-uncompromising-stand</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19546250/Privacy-as-a-human-right-in-crypto-An-uncompromising-stand"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T12:14:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The following is a guest post by Felix Mohr, Co-founder at MohrWolfe. In an age where our digital footprints are scattered across the expanse of the internet like breadcrumbs, the concept of privacy has become as elusive as it is precious. As we navigate the aftermath of COVID-19—a time that has...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Solana Memecoin Devil Biden (DEVBIDEN) to Explode 14,000% in 48 Hours – Should You Buy It?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19546236/New-Solana-Memecoin-Devil-Biden-DEVBIDEN-to-Explode-14000-in-48-Hours-Should-You-Buy-It</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19546236/New-Solana-Memecoin-Devil-Biden-DEVBIDEN-to-Explode-14000-in-48-Hours-Should-You-Buy-It"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T12:03:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Devil Biden (DEVBIDEN), a new Solana memecoin that was launched this week, is poised to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$2.5 Billion In Bitcoin Flows Out Of Centralized Exchanges – Time To Buy?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19546222/25-Billion-In-Bitcoin-Flows-Out-Of-Centralized-Exchanges-Time-To-Buy</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19546222/25-Billion-In-Bitcoin-Flows-Out-Of-Centralized-Exchanges-Time-To-Buy"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T12:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Investor confidence appears to be on the rise in the crypto market lately, and Bitcoin has been a major beneficiary of this positive trend. Consequently, there has been a continuous accumulation of BTC amongst large-scale investors despite its somewhat frustrating price action. The premier...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 9 best gadgets right now]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19546223/The-9-best-gadgets-right-now</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19546223/The-9-best-gadgets-right-now"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May was a loaded month with Apple and Google both releasing products. Project Astra was definitely the most interesting thing we saw at an otherwise boring Google I/O. Apple also dropped its latest iPad Pros with the all-new M4 chip and OLED displays, a 13-inch iPad Air for the first time, and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Biden steps back, vetoes crypto bill after Trump conviction]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19546210/Joe-Biden-steps-back-vetoes-crypto-bill-after-Trump-conviction</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19546210/Joe-Biden-steps-back-vetoes-crypto-bill-after-Trump-conviction"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T11:46:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After not using this same power last week, Joe Biden surprised the cryptocurrency market by vetoing a crypto-related bill. This … Continue reading]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No New Retail Investors Are Joining the Crypto Market, Says Top Trader – Here’s What He Thinks Could Change That]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19546212/No-New-Retail-Investors-Are-Joining-the-Crypto-Market-Says-Top-Trader-Heres-What-He-Thinks-Could-Change-That</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19546212/No-New-Retail-Investors-Are-Joining-the-Crypto-Market-Says-Top-Trader-Heres-What-He-Thinks-Could-Change-That"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T11:45:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A closely followed trader is claiming that no new retail investors are joining the crypto market, but he believes one event could attract the newbies. Pseudonymous trader The Flow Horse tells his 217,800 followers on the social media platform X that it will likely take Bitcoin (BTC) hitting six...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin price explosion: Chart patterns identify explosive BTC levels to watch]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19546194/Bitcoin-price-explosion-Chart-patterns-identify-explosive-BTC-levels-to-watch</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19546194/Bitcoin-price-explosion-Chart-patterns-identify-explosive-BTC-levels-to-watch"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T11:32:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) continues to cling to the $67,000 mark, with bears and bulls failing to push the maiden cryptocurrency’s price … Continue reading]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uniswap Foundation postpones vote on incentives]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19546185/Uniswap-Foundation-postpones-vote-on-incentives</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19546185/Uniswap-Foundation-postpones-vote-on-incentives"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T11:30:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Users imply that the unnamed VC firm’s actions had revealed its significant influence, which could be seen as a mistake, undermining the decentralized values.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong’s Crypto Crackdown? 11 Exchanges Get Nod, But Big Names Skip Out]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19546199/Hong-Kongs-Crypto-Crackdown-11-Exchanges-Get-Nod-But-Big-Names-Skip-Out</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19546199/Hong-Kongs-Crypto-Crackdown-11-Exchanges-Get-Nod-But-Big-Names-Skip-Out"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T11:20:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong’s Securities and Futures Commission (SFC) has announced that 11 virtual asset trading platforms (VATPs) are poised to receive official licenses, a year after the city introduced new regulations to foster a thriving crypto industry. Prominent platforms such as Crypto.com and Bullish,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report Shows No Evidence of Special Treatment for BTC Ponzi Scheme Mastermind in Brazilian Jail]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741e299cb8</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/report-shows-no-evidence-of-special-treatment-for-btc-ponzi-scheme-mastermind-in-brazilian-jail/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T11:20:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Brazilian State Attorney General has dismissed allegations that Johann Steynberg, the late mastermind of a South African bitcoin ponzi scheme, was granted irregular access to a computer and the internet while in prison. Acting public prosecutor Lauro Machado Nogueira recently released a report stating that evidence from prison authorities contradicted these claims. Additionally, Steynberg, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Sentiment Turns Bearish Again – Here’s What Happened The Last Time]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741e2b5a22</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-sentiment-turns-very-bearish-what-happened/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T11:05:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin was one of the best-performing assets in the crypto market in the past month, outshining blue-chip cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin. According to data from CoinGecko, the meme coin’s price rose by more than 26%, while BTC increased in value by approximately 19% in May.
 
However, the latest on-chain data shows that investors have still not become bullish about DOGE despite its positive price performance. The question here is – how will the unwavering bearish sentiment impact the price of Dogecoin? 
 
How Will The Bearish Sentiment Benefit Dogecoin Price?
 
In a recent post on the X platform, prominent crypto pundit Ali Martinez revealed that market sentiment for Dogecoin is currently bearish. This on-chain revelation is based on the weighted sentiment metric, which tracks the overall…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Opeyemi Sule</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Sentiment Turns Bearish Again – Here’s What Happened The Last Time]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19546137/Dogecoin-Sentiment-Turns-Bearish-Again-Heres-What-Happened-The-Last-Time</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19546137/Dogecoin-Sentiment-Turns-Bearish-Again-Heres-What-Happened-The-Last-Time"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T11:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin was one of the best-performing assets in the crypto market in the past month, outshining blue-chip cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin. According to data from CoinGecko, the meme coin’s price rose by more than 26%, while BTC increased in value by approximately 19% in May. However, the latest...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto community divided as Biden vetoes repeal of SEC’s SAB 121]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19546134/Crypto-community-divided-as-Biden-vetoes-repeal-of-SECs-SAB-121</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19546134/Crypto-community-divided-as-Biden-vetoes-repeal-of-SECs-SAB-121"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T11:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here's how the crypto community reacted to Biden's SAB 121 repeal veto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB) May Break Major Record This Month, Here's Reason]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19546120/Shiba-Inu-SHIB-May-Break-Major-Record-This-Month-Heres-Reason</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19546120/Shiba-Inu-SHIB-May-Break-Major-Record-This-Month-Heres-Reason"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T10:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu has major hurdle ahead in June to surmount]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global Crypto Craze, 562 Million Embrace Digital Currency]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19546107/Global-Crypto-Craze-562-Million-Embrace-Digital-Currency</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19546107/Global-Crypto-Craze-562-Million-Embrace-Digital-Currency"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T10:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new report out today shows a sharp increase in the adoption rate of digital currencies across the globe. It is now interesting to note that 562 million people own and use digital currencies which is higher as compared to the previous year's data which is 420 million in 2023. This means that...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin Officially Launches in Colombia]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741e10360b</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/worldcoin-officially-launches-in-colombia/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T10:21:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin, the iris-scanning biometric proof-of-personhood project, announced on Thursday the launch of its operations in Colombia. Via social media, the project reported that eye-scanning operations were already available in Bogota and Medellin, for World ID users. Currently, only ten locations with orbs (iris scanning machines) are available, six in Bogota and four in Medellin. Nonetheless, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Presidential Veto Alert: Biden Blocks SAB 121 Overturn]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741e1cde8a</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/us-president-joe-biden-vetoes-overturn-of-sab-121/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T09:36:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US President Joe Biden has vetoed congressional resolution H.J. Res.109, which seeks to repeal the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Staff Accounting Bulletin (SAB) No.121, a controversial guidance measure that is widely viewed as anti-crypto. Interestingly, Biden’s action comes amidst rumors that the incumbent government was posturing to gain the favor of crypto voters in the coming US general elections. 
 
 
SAB 121 Repeal To Jeopardize Investors’ Interest, Biden Says
 
On March 31, 2022, the SEC introduced SAB 121 which directed all financial institutions that custody cryptocurrencies for clients to consolidate these assets on their balance sheet thus precluding these firms from safeguarding such digital assets. 
 
SAB 121 received much criticism for its perceived anti-crypto …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Semilore Faleti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Turkey Detains 127 Crypto Ponzi Scheme Co-Conspirators, Seizes Assets Worth Over $31 Million]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741e1bc016</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/turkey-detains-127-crypto-ponzi-scheme-co-conspirators-seizes-assets-worth-over-31-million/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T08:29:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to Turkish authorities, the country’s law enforcement agencies have disrupted a criminal syndicate that lured unsuspecting residents into investing in a Ponzi scheme disguised as a cryptocurrency investment. The syndicate is reported to have swindled $1 billion from investors who were deceived by the scammers’ promise of high profits and zero risks. During the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Changing Of The Guard? NYSE President Acknowledges Bitcoin’s Staying Power]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741e0d4447</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/nyse-president-acknowledges-bitcoins-staying-power/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T06:52:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The long-awaited arrival of spot Bitcoin ETFs in January 2024 has proven to be a watershed moment for the cryptocurrency market. Industry figures like Lynn Martin, president of the New York Stock Exchange Group, are crediting these exchange-traded funds with a surge in liquidity and mainstream adoption of cryptocurrencies.
 
 
NYSE Boss Highlights Success Of Bitcoin
 
In an interview at Consensus 2024, Martin pointed to the “more than six years of conversations” with the SEC regarding Bitcoin ETFs. She went on to emphasize “‘the success of Bitcoin ETFs’ and the liquidity they’ve brought is ‘undeniable.'” This newfound liquidity is believed to be a key factor behind the recent price appreciation in the crypto market, with the total market capitalization surpassing $1 trillion for the first …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether Makes Major Move Into Bitcoin Mining With $100 Million Investment In This Firm]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741ff436e2</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/tether-makes-major-move-into-bitcoin-mining/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T05:38:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a significant development, Tether, the issuer of the widely used stablecoin USDT, has acquired a $100 million stake in Bitdeer Technologies Group, a US-listed Bitcoin miner owned by Chinese billionaire Jihan Wu. 
 
Notably, the deal includes an option for Tether to purchase an additional $50 million shares within a year, strengthening its position in the Bitcoin mining sector.
 
Tether’s Multi-Million Dollar Stake In Bitdeer
 
According to Bloomberg, the subscription agreement between Tether and Bitdeer involved a private placement of 18.6 million Class A ordinary shares, generating $100 million in gross proceeds. 
 
Additionally, a warrant allows Tether to acquire up to five million additional shares at $10 per share. The private placement concluded on Thursday, with Cantor Fitzgerald …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Issues Investor Alert Highlighting 5 Common Crypto Scams]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741ff4729c</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/sec-issues-investor-alert-highlighting-5-common-crypto-scams/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T05:36:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC’s Office of Investor Education and Advocacy has issued an alert, highlighting five common crypto scams investors should watch out for to avoid losing money. The SEC warns that fraudsters exploit cryptocurrency popularity with sophisticated techniques, making fund recovery difficult. For example, “Fraudsters may conduct pump-and-dump schemes with crypto assets, including so-called ‘memecoins’ that […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin & Shiba Inu: How The Memecoins Stack Against Top Coins In Daily Users]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741ffcc2d0</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-shiba-inu-memecoins-top-coins-daily-users/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s how Dogecoin (DOGE) and Shiba Inu (SHIB) compare against the top coins in the cryptocurrency sector in terms of the “active addresses.”
 
Dogecoin & Shiba Inu Compared Against The Others In Active User Count
 
In a new post on X, the market intelligence platform IntoTheBlock shared an infographic that reveals where the various top cryptocurrencies in the market currently stand based on the daily number of active addresses.
 
An address is said to be “active” when it gets involved in some sort of transaction activity. The receiver and the sender in a transfer become active for the moment of the transaction.
 
 
The unique number of active addresses may be considered the same as the daily number of users on the network. As such, the metric’s value can tell us whether the blockchain is…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Survey: 77% Believe Presidential Candidates Should Be Informed on AI and Crypto]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741fff6b59</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/survey-77-believe-presidential-candidates-should-be-informed-on-ai-and-crypto/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T03:25:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Grayscale-Harris Poll survey, conducted in April-May 2024, reveals crucial insights into American likely voters’ views on cryptocurrency and its potential impact on the upcoming presidential election. The survey, involving over 2,000 adults, highlights key trends such as high interest in crypto among young, minority, male, and Democratic voters. Significant findings include 97% of likely […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Files New Document Claiming SEC’s Actions Aimed At Crushing Crypto]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741ff96141</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/coinbase-claim-secs-actions-aimed-crushing-crypto/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T03:01:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent filing, US-based cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase has made sharp accusations against the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and its chairman, Gary Gensler, claiming their actions aim to stifle the cryptocurrency sector. 
 
The filing comes amid an ongoing legal battle between Coinbase and the SEC, which alleges that the exchange engaged in unregistered sales of what the regulator calls “securities.”
 
Coinbase Challenges SEC’s ‘Inconsistent Legal Claims’ 
 
Coinbase’s Friday filing highlights the SEC’s increasing enforcement actions in recent months, suggesting a deliberate effort to undermine the digital asset industry. 
 
The exchange accuses the SEC of advancing “inconsistent and unsupportable” legal claims and of perpetuating an oppressive campaign against the indu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Could Bitcoin Replace Gold For National Reserves? Expert Weighs In]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741fe59772</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/could-bitcoin-replace-gold-for-national-reserves/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T02:09:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gabor Gurbacs, a strategic advisor at Tether, the issuer of USDT, recently spotlighted Bitcoin’s potential in “revolutionizing” how central banks handle and secure national reserves, using India’s logistical challenges with gold as a prime example.
 
A Digital Solution For Traditional Gold Logistics
 
India’s decision to relocate a significant portion of its gold reserves from the UK back to domestic vaults has reignited discussions about the logistical challenges of physical gold. A report from the Economic Times particularly noted:
 

India’s central bank has moved around a 100 tonnes, or 1 lakh kilograms of gold from the United Kingdom back to its vaults in India, and intends to move more in coming months.
 
Leveraging this scenario, Gurbacs suggested that cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI Board Defends CEO Sam Altman Amid ‘Toxic Culture’ Claims]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233372</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233372/openai-toxic-culture-former-current-board-members-argue"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T01:53:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former OpenAI board members claimed there was “psychological abuse,” but their replacements say Altman was “consistently collegial.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global Crypto Ownership Reaches 562 Million: 6.8% of World Population Now Own and Use Digital Currencies]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741fe1522e</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/global-crypto-ownership-reaches-562-million-6-8-of-world-population-now-own-and-use-digital-currencies/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T01:24:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new report reveals that 562 million people globally now own digital currencies, an increase from 420 million in 2023, making up 6.8% of the world’s population. Asia is at the forefront of this growth, with North America close behind. Overall, cryptocurrency adoption is rising worldwide, with notable increases seen across all continents. ‘562 Million […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Japanese Exchange DMM Bitcoin Falls Victim To $305 Million Hack]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741fe290e1</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dmm-bitcoin-falls-victim-to-305-million-hack/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T01:08:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DMM Bitcoin, one of Japan’s largest cryptocurrency exchanges, recently suffered a major setback when it reported a loss of 48 billion yen ($305 million) in Bitcoin (BTC) due to a security breach. 
 
The incident, discovered on May 31, 2024, revealed the illegal leakage of BTC from a DMM Bitcoin wallet. As a result, several services have been temporarily suspended to address the situation and protect customer assets. 
 
Unauthorized Access Incident Hits DMM Bitcoin
 
According to local media reports, on May 31, DMM Bitcoin detected an unauthorized access incident resulting in the illegal leakage of 4,502.9 BTC, equivalent to approximately 48.2 billion yen. The exchange then took measures to prevent further unauthorized outflows. 
 
 
In response to the security breach, DMM Bitcoin suspended…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Estonian Nationals Extradited to US for $575M Crypto Fraud]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741fec9794</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/estonian-nationals-extradited-to-us-for-575m-crypto-fraud/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T00:43:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two Estonian nationals have been extradited from Estonia to the U.S. to face charges for their roles in “a massive multi-faceted cryptocurrency Ponzi scheme,” according to an announcement by the U.S. Department of Justice (DOJ). Sergei Potapenko and Ivan Turõgin are accused of operating a $575 million Ponzi scheme involving the fraudulent cryptocurrency mining service […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Price Prediction: Machine Learning Algorithm Reveals Where Price Will Be In June]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741fefb48d</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/xrp-price-prediction-june/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T00:07:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XRP is among the altcoins that continue to command a large following even after putting on a poor performance for the last few years. At the same time, expectations for the altcoin have fluctuated between bullish and bearish, especially in the long term. However, in the short term at least, the machine learning algorithm at CoinCodex predicts some level of bullishness for XRP.
 
XRP To Jump 20% In June
 
As the month of May draws to an end and June swims into view, there are varying expectations for the crypto market and where it could go from here. For XRP, the CoinCodex machine learning algorithm predicts that the month of June will be bullish for it.
 
The one-month prediction timeframe on the website shows that the price would rise as high as $0.627709, and from the current price of XR…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[President Biden Vetoes SEC SAB 121 Repeal Resolution]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741fe80b3d</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/president-biden-vetoes-sec-sab-121-repeal-resolution/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T00:04:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. President Joe Biden issued a veto against H.J.Res. 109, a resolution that would disapprove of the Securities and Exchange Commission’s (SEC) Staff Accounting Bulletin No. 121 (SAB 121). In its veto document, Bides states that the approval of this Republican-led resolution would “inappropriately constrain the SEC’s ability to set forth appropriate guardrails and address […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. President Biden Vetoes Resolution Overturning SEC Guidance]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741fea6d13</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/05/31/us-president-biden-vetoes-resolution-overturning-sec-guidance/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T23:38:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S President Joe Biden signed a veto of a House Joint Resolution that would have repealed the Securities and Exchange Commission's (SEC) Staff Accounting Bulletin 121.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[President Biden Vetoes Pro-Crypto Resolution, Defends SEC's Judgement]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233358</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233358/biden-veto-sab-121-resolution"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T23:30:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The White House said the bipartisan-passed bill would “jeopardize the well-being of consumers and investors.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Kawailani Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin Explains Why ‘Big Blockers’ Lost the Bitcoin Scaling Wars]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233339</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233339/vitalik-buterin-on-why-big-blockers-lost-the-bitcoin-scaling-wars"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T22:01:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum’s creator says the best way to prevent future disputes will require new technologies like ZK-SNARKs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Franklin Templeton Reveals Ethereum ETF Fee]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233336</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233336/franklin-templeton-reveals-ethereum-etf-fee"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T21:14:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The global asset manager will charge investors 0.19%, in line with the low fees in the competitive spot Bitcoin ETF race.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Caitlyn Jenner Releasing a Meme Coin Is Riskier Than Kim Kardashian Shilling Ethereum Max, Legal Experts Say]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233315</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233315/caitlyn-jenner-meme-coin-risk-kim-kardashian-ethereum-max"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T20:34:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week wasn’t the first time a Kardashian-linked token turned heads in crypto, but the stakes could be higher this time around.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Runes Are Back? Meme Coin Surge Pushes Market Cap Over $2 Billion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233318</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233318/bitcoin-runes-back-meme-coin-surge-2-billion"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T19:44:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the last week, the value of assets on the Runes protocol for Bitcoin meme coins has doubled—and DOG is leading the charge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Should Join UK in ‘Blockchain Sandbox’ Free of Regulatory Meddling, SEC Commissioner Says]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233170</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233170/blockchain-regulatory-sandbox-us-uk-hester-peirce-unikely"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T19:14:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Commissioner Hester Peirce says a safe space for blockchain experimentation could foster better crypto regulations—but experts doubt it will happen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Ethereum Meme Coin Price Hits New High After Post-Verdict Dip]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233310</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233310/trump-ethereum-meme-coin-price-new-high"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T18:52:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Donald Trump-themed MAGA meme coin surged late Thursday after a short-lived crash prompted by his “hush money” trial verdict.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Bitcoin Game Boy’ Gets a Runes Makeover—Here’s How to Win One]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233296</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233296/bitcoin-game-boy-runes-makeover-giveaway"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T17:52:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The BitBoy One is a Bitcoin-centric gaming handheld, and a new limited-edition Runes model gives it a sleek overhaul.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Next Notcoin? Telegram-Based Game ‘Hamster Kombat’ to Launch Token on TON]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233287</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233287/next-notcoin-telegram-game-hamster-kombat-open-network-token"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T17:10:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hamster Kombat, another tap-to-earn game akin to Notcoin—and based around a hamster CEO—is launching a token on The Open Network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI, Meta Disclose Their AI Tools Were Used for Political Disinformation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233249</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233249/openai-meta-disclose-ai-tools-political-disinformation"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T16:01:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AI giants both revealed this week how their tools have been enlisted in China, Israel, Russia, and Iran to spread political disinformation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Accuses SEC of 'Purposeful Effort to Destroy' Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233279</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233279/coinbase-accuses-sec-purposeful-effort-destroy-crypto"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T15:44:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a legal filing on Friday, America's leading crypto exchange accused the SEC of trying to snuff out crypto by refusing to make new rules.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Japanese Exchange DMM Bitcoin Hacked for $308 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233283</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233283/japanese-exchange-dmm-bitcoin-hacked-308-million"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T15:26:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The exploit against Japanese exchange DMM Bitcoin is one of the largest to hit the crypto industry in years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Week in Polkadot: JAM Upgrade Passes in Near-Unanimous Vote]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233042</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233042/the-week-in-polkadot-jam-upgrade-passes-in-near-unanimous-vote"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T15:07:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Polkadot community has spoken, with the network's proposed JAM upgrade getting an almost unanimous vote of approval.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will McCurdy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ZK Trademark Fight: Competitors Demand Matter Labs Withdraw Application]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233226</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233226/zk-trademark-fight-competitors-demand-matter-labs-withdraw-application"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T15:06:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matter Labs, developer of zkSync technology, has faced criticism for its attempt to register the term "ZK" as a trademark.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arbitrum Is About to Unlock $250 Million in Funds for Ethereum Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233082</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233082/arbitrum-unlock-250-million-funds-ethereum-games"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T14:53:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arbitrum holders are strongly supporting a program that’s devised to boost gaming on Ethereum layer-2 network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No, JasmyCoin Does Not Have a Partnership With Apple—But Its Token Is Still Pumping]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233229</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233229/no-jasmycoin-does-not-have-a-partnership-with-apple-but-its-token-is-still-pumping"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T12:04:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After Apple announced it’ll be integrating Japan’s My Number feature into its iPhones, investors believed JasmyCoin was part of the deal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terra Coins LUNA and LUNC Rise After Do Kwon SEC Settlement]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233218</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233218/terra-luna-lunc-rise-do-kwon-sec-settlement"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T10:16:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terra founder Do Kwon and Terraform Labs reached a tentative settlement with the SEC in their civil fraud case Thursday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trial Begins for $575 Million HashFlare Crypto Mining Fraud Defendants]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233217</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233217/trial-begins-for-575-million-hashflare-crypto-mining-fraud-defendants"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T10:01:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two men linked to $575 Million HashFlare crypto mining fraud had their first court appearance yesterday in Seattle.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robert F. Kennedy Jr. ‘Delighted’ Trump Is Now Pro Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233155</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233155/robert-f-kennedy-jr-delighted-trump-is-now-pro-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T23:29:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“I’m not a fan of Trump’s,” Kennedy noted after the Trump trial verdict was announced, but said blockchain can defend Americans against “dystopian” AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Kawailani Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Still Favored by Crypto Bettors to Win Election, Despite Guilty Verdict]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233148</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233148/trump-verdict-election-win-odds-polymarket"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T22:51:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People putting money on Trump's political future on Polymarket don't seem to think much has changed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Kawailani Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TON Market Cap Plunges by Billions After Fixing Inflated Supply Data]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233113</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233113/ton-market-cap-plunges-billions-fixing-inflated-supply-data"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T22:21:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The market capitalization of Toncoin (TON) dropped by billions of dollars after The Open Network updated its circulating supply data.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Meme Coins Plunge After He's Found Guilty on 34 Felony Charges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233146</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233146/trump-meme-coins-plunge-after-hes-found-guilty-on-34-felony-charges"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T21:53:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MAGA (TRUMP) and other tokens inspired by Donald Trump are down bad after the former U.S. president's "hush money" trial ended.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 127 - CELEB COINS CRASH!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mGbE2GHV/fomo-hour-127-celeb-coins-crash</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mGbE2GHV/fomo-hour-127-celeb-coins-crash"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T20:28:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NYSE to launch BTC options. CME has ‘no plans’ to offer SOL futures. Stablecoin market cap rises to 2 year high. Inflation below 3.3% ‘means BTC ATH’. Crypto market cap heading to $200T: Yat Siu. Gemini recovers $2.2bn for Earn users. PayPal stablecoin will offer ‘confidential transfers’. Mastercard launches Crypto Credential pilot on BTC. Layer Zero launches on SOL. L2s are cultural extensions of ETH: Vitalik. FTX’s Salame says he will share story. SEI announces 27m SEI airdrop. ASI merger complete, to launch June 13th.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Enthusiasts Are ‘Not Psychopaths’, New Research Concludes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233091</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233091/bitcoin-investors-not-psychopaths-canadian-research-preview"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T19:58:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A forthcoming study of 500 Canadian Bitcoin investors found them to be financially literate and emotionally stable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Caitlyn Jenner Solana Meme Coin Crashes After Launching Ethereum Token to Support Trump]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233084</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233084/caitlyn-jenner-solana-meme-coin-crashes-ethereum-donald-trump"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T19:36:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new Caitlyn Jenner token on Ethereum takes a fee to support Donald Trump's presidential ambitions—but the Solana coin has plummeted.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Superfan Elon Musk Says He ‘Never Discussed Crypto With Trump’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233063</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233063/elon-musk-donald-trump-crypto"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T18:28:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amid the former president’s pivot to embrace cryptocurrency, the Tesla CEO denies a report that they’ve talked about crypto policy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Final Fantasy’ Maker Square Enix Moves to Arbitrum for Ethereum Game NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233069</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233069/symbiogenesis-square-enix-arbitrum-ethereum-game-nfts"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T17:41:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Square Enix is jumping to Ethereum layer-2 Arbitrum for the next NFT character mint for its Symbiogenesis blockchain game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Pay? Every Good Thing About OpenAI's GPT-4o Is Now Free]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233032</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233032/why-pay-every-good-thing-about-gpt-4o-free"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T17:20:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT Plus and Free are now equally capable. Does it make any sense for you to keep a paid subscription?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Startup Babylon Raises $70 Million to Bring BTC Staking to Ethereum and Solana]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233029</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233029/bitcoin-startup-babylon-raises-70-million-btc-staking-ethereum-solana"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T16:44:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Babylon, a startup working to enable native Bitcoin staking on chains like Ethereum and Solana, just raised $70 million towards that goal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do Kwon and Terraform Labs Settle With SEC Over LUNA, TerraUSD Fraud Charges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233039</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233039/do-kwon-terraform-labs-settle-sec-luna-terrausd-fraud"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T16:11:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The startup behind the collapsed LUNA and TerraUSD coins is settling with the SEC over fraud charges, a court filing revealed Thursday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward,Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Meme Coins Surge as DOG's 85% Jump Calms Fears That 'Runes Are Dead']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233027</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233027/bitcoin-meme-coins-surge-calms-fears-runes-dead"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T15:42:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As some Bitcoin-based meme coins glitter with gains, a dog-themed token pushes back on claims that Runes hype has faded.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pudgy Penguins Mobile Game Coming to Mythos Chain on Polkadot]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233026</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233026/pudgy-penguins-mobile-game-polkadot-mythos-chain"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T15:16:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NFL Rivals and Blankos Block Party creator Mythical Games is developing the Pudgy Penguins mobile game to launch in 2025.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chainlink and Circle Want to Help Institutions Use Stablecoins and DeFi]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233024</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233024/chainlink-circle-institutions-defi-stablecoins"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T15:05:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The partnership is aimed at "moving the industry forward and growing the adoption of tokenized assets," a Chainlink exec told Decrypt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ali Shutler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum DeFi Projects Still Favorite Target for Hackers, But Stolen Funds Down 28% in May: Immunefi]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233016</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233016/ethereum-defi-projects-still-favorite-target-for-hackers-but-stolen-funds-down-28-in-may-immunefi"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T13:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Investors have lost $473 million since the beginning of the year to hacks and frauds, a decrease of 20% from last year during the same period.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarang Khaitan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 126 - MEMECOIN MADNESS!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/eA3xqKLr/fomo-hour-126-memecoin-madness</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/eA3xqKLr/fomo-hour-126-memecoin-madness"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T21:30:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock ETF flips Grayscale in size. BTC ETFs see 11 straight days of inflows. ZKasino gives 72hours for ETH withdrawals. ENS to migrate to L2. ADA drops out of top 10 coins. Salame sentenced to 7.5 years in jail. Riot Platforms attempts takeover of Bitfarms. Ripple donates $25m to Fairshake PAC. Pump(.)fun launches live streaming. Iggy Azelea MOTHER coin leads celeb tokens. Beeple Everyday features many coins. Runes bounce, DOG hits $560m. PEPE active wallets double during rally. Cristiano Ronaldo launches 4th NFT. Friend Tech announces club wars.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum DN-404 Tokens Are a Sensation in Asia. Are They the West’s Next Big Trend?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/drcV3Zte/ethereum-dn-404-tokens-are-a-sensation-in-asia-are-they-the-wests-next-big-trend</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/drcV3Zte/ethereum-dn-404-tokens-are-a-sensation-in-asia-are-they-the-wests-next-big-trend"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T19:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz and Rug Radio creator Pukerainbow sat down for a conversation with some of the biggest adopters involved in Ethereum’s newest trend: dividing NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Buying Crypto Simplified with Mika]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/Z9rxTcnJ/buying-crypto-simplified-with-mika</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/Z9rxTcnJ/buying-crypto-simplified-with-mika"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T16:54:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the first part of our series turning crypto beginners into crypto pros, Rug Radio creator Mika guides you through the process of purchasing cryptocurrency using crypto exchange Kraken.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 125 - ETH NEARS 4K]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BrgFfEe8/fomo-hour-125-eth-nears-4k</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BrgFfEe8/fomo-hour-125-eth-nears-4k"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T17:40:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH leads rally on continued bullish ETF sentiment. Previous anti-crypto Trump comments highlighted. Wave of influencers and celebrities hacked, release coins. Phantom becomes no.1 finance app in the US. Argentina & El Salvador hold talks on BTC adoption. LINK to have large announcement on May 30th. PEPE, MOG, TURBO, TRUMP hit ATHs in ETH memes. MOG up 60%, mentioned in Beeple Everyday. Caitlyn Jenner hacker releases JENNER coin. Garga outlines future plans for BAYC. Friend Tech founder offers $200k to migrate off Base.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 124 - THE ETH ETF IS APPROVED!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5ELzjWt4/fomo-hour-124-the-eth-etf-is-approved</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5ELzjWt4/fomo-hour-124-the-eth-etf-is-approved"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T18:43:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH ETFs get approved 19b-4 forms. ETFs won’t trade until July or August: Galaxy. ETF means many coins not securities: Coinbase CLO. Coinbase relists XRP in US. SOL ETF coming: Scaramucci. US House passes vote to ban CBDC. Building a pro-crypto army in congress: Sen. Lummis. Polymarket backlash over if ETH ETF truly approved. Expect ETH ETFs to be 10-15% of BTC: Bloomberg. BTC ETFs see $1.75bn inflows over 9 days. BTC to $150k in 2024 is base case: Tom Lee. ETH co-founder moves $37m ETH to exchanges. Grayscale launches trusts for STX & NEAR. Coinbase loses against SEC on DOGE sweepstakes. ALGO ad attacks BTC, SOL, ETH. Phantom now no.2 finance App on Google Play.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 123 - ETHEREUM KEEPS GOING!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JE3lB00G/fomo-hour-123-ethereum-keeps-going</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JE3lB00G/fomo-hour-123-ethereum-keeps-going"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T15:43:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH soars, ETF S1 approvals expected in hours. US house greenlights FIT21 bill with broad support. Gensler says SEC already has rules for crypto. Hong Kong set to allow ETH staking for ETFs. ETH OI continues to soar. SOL mentioned as next ETF candidate on CNBC. SOL ETF will take years: Bloomberg. MetaMask plans BTC integration. Fed says only 7% of Americans own crypto. SBF heads to a new prison. Hong Kong orders WLD shutdown. TON added to Binance ahead of potential listing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 122 - ETH ETF MOVES CLOSER!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/FlTuDkm9/fomo-hour-122-eth-etf-moves-closer</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/FlTuDkm9/fomo-hour-122-eth-etf-moves-closer"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T16:33:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH ETFs move closer to approval, drop staking. Blackrock ETF see biggest inflow in 6 weeks. Grayscale ETH discount narrows under 10%. BTC & ETH heading for ATH: StanChart. Banana zone squared coming for ETH: Raoul Pal. Trump accepts crypto donations including DOGE. Pelosi mulls support of crypto bill. Farcaster raises $150M, DEGEN up 20%. Coinbase to launch gold & oil futures trading. Uniswap ‘ready to fight’ against SEC. Vitalik proposes solutions to MEV problems. Phantom may soon support email sign-up. Jupiter announces initiative to tokenise RWAs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 121 - ETHEREUM GOD CANDLES!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/EE1S4Hf4/fomo-hour-121-ethereum-god-candles</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/EE1S4Hf4/fomo-hour-121-ethereum-god-candles"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T16:17:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH ETF suddenly seems likely, flurry of amendments. ETH biggest daily gain ever, gains SOL market cap. ETF approval shifted due to political pressure. ETF approval may come as soon as tomorrow. Squeeze liquidates $230M of shorts. ETH OI hits record of $14B on exchanges. BTC nears ATH amid 6th straight day of ETF inflows. SOL flips ETH in Google search trends. House Democrats will not whip against crypto bills. Anti-crypto FDIC chair Gruenberg to step-down. Grayscale CEO steps down, ETHE discount narrows. Genesis settles for $2B with creditors. Binance to focus launchpad on higher float projects. SEI v2 launch coming next week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Do A Little With Chikai]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BGCnTbKb/we-do-a-little-with-chikai</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BGCnTbKb/we-do-a-little-with-chikai"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T18:21:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week’s episode, we sit down with our good friend and one of the biggest supporters of the pod, Chikai Ohazama. Chikai is the co-founder of Keyhole which was acquired by Google and became Google Earth. He is one of the most caring art collectors in our space, as well as an extremely talented AI artist.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 120 - SOLANA LEADS THE CHARGE]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/7jrsiszc/fomo-hour-120-solana-leads-the-charge</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/7jrsiszc/fomo-hour-120-solana-leads-the-charge"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T18:08:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SOL again leads majors, DEX volume dwarfs others. BTC whales buys $106M in 24hrs. ETH ETF decision on Thursday or Friday. 5 of 7 onchain indicators ‘point to bull-run’. ETH ETF may be rejected due to weak link to futures. AI coins in focus ahead of Nvidia earnings. Cobie inks new article on low float, high FDV coins. ETH foundation staff reveal links to EigenLayer. 12 L2 & L3s controlled by single multisig. Layer Zero pauses sybil rewards. Aevo to airdrop pre-launch tokens on platform. FTM to migrate one-to-one to Sonic S coin. UK judge rules Craig Wright is not Satoshi.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 119 - GOOD MORNING BULLS!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ikMRioZH/fomo-hour-119-good-morning-bulls</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ikMRioZH/fomo-hour-119-good-morning-bulls"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T11:02:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SOL leads majors higher again, BTC stable. ETFs see $257M inflow, volumes hit 2 month high. 414 holders of BlackRock ETF ‘blows away record’. SOL continues to be fastest blockage despite usage. Pump. fun exploited for $1.9M by ex-employee. LINK up 20% after partnership with top banks. Senate also repeals SEC crypto rule. US Senator uses laser eyes PFP. Tether mints another $1B USDT. Bitcoin production costs now $45K: JP Morgan. Pink Drainer retires after stealing $85m assets. PancakeSwap to reimburse fees on Uniswap. TON & Tether partnership on payment solution. Trabucco writes character defence of Ryan Salame.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 118 - ARE THE ETFS BACK?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/KJXI4MVU/fomo-hour-118-are-the-etfs-back</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/KJXI4MVU/fomo-hour-118-are-the-etfs-back"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T11:02:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin has best day in 2 months after dovish CPI. ETFs see $300M inflow, highest in weeks. ETH continues to underperform ahead of ETF ruling. Millennium buys $2B of BTC ETF. CME group to launch BTC spot trading. Fed’s Kashkari compares BTC to beanie babies. Tate says he will buy $100M BTC. El Salvador now owns 5750 BTC. Binance creates ‘antidote’ to address poisoning. Tornado Cash developer appeals conviction. China busts $1.9B USDT banking racket. MEV bot operators charged with fraud by DoJ. Swiss to adopt global crypto tax rules. FTX repayments create ‘bullish overhang’ for crypto. SEI up 30% after proposing v2 upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 117 - BITCOIN GAINS ON CPI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JMdi3Lp7/fomo-hour-117-bitcoin-gains-on-cpi</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JMdi3Lp7/fomo-hour-117-bitcoin-gains-on-cpi"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T11:02:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC bounces driven by spot buying. US ETF sees $100M+ inflow for first time in weeks. State of Wisconsin buys $170M of BTC ETF. Vanguard appoints Bitcoin friendly CEO. Coinbase sees billions of BTC leave exchange. BTC to consolidate between $55-75K: Novogratz. SOL beats ETH TEV for first time ever. ETH may be labelled a security by SEC next week. AI & memes the only two positive sectors this week. Crypto hostility led by TradFi: Lubin. Tornado Cash developer guilty of money laundering. Circle shifts legal hope to US ahead of IPO. Cypher developer gambled $300K of customer funds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 116 - ROARING KITTY RETURNS!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cXfQ3AJh/fomo-hour-116-roaring-kitty-returns</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cXfQ3AJh/fomo-hour-116-roaring-kitty-returns"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T11:02:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto falls, stays in range ahead of CPI tomorrow. US ETFs see small net inflow led by Fidelity HK ETFs wipe 2 weeks of inflows in a single day. Bracebridge bought $363m of BTC ETFs. Coinbase has system wide outage. Poloniex hacker sends funds to Tornado Cash. Brazil biggest in LATAM for crypto trading. Biden removes China BTC miner near military base. CertiK patches $5m flaw in Aptos bridge. LayerZero sees 100k bot accounts self-report. DYDX CEO set to leave. Tate sells $500k BTC to buy GME.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Do A Little With  Roger Dickerman]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/F6mt1fXu/we-do-a-little-with-roger-dickerman</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/F6mt1fXu/we-do-a-little-with-roger-dickerman"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T14:38:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week’s episode, we sit down with our good friend and founder of the 24 Hours of Art, Roger Dickerman. We dive into Roger’s background in trading and fitness, his love of art, founding Artifex and 24 Hours of Art, the power of routines, and so much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Do A Little With Funghi]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9USXAFZb/we-do-a-little-with-funghi</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9USXAFZb/we-do-a-little-with-funghi"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T13:44:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week’s episode, we sit down with our good friend and co-founder of Shillr, Funghibull. Funghi is one of our favorite collectors, builders and overall people in the space. 

We dive into Funghi’s background playing rugby, going to medical school in Scotland, 10 gram mushroom trips, finding punks, forming Shillr, and so much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mika Breaks Down Solana Congestion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/5lkvPCM1/mika-breaks-down-solana-congestion</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/5lkvPCM1/mika-breaks-down-solana-congestion"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T10:12:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rug Radio Creator and crypto influencer Mika explains what happened during Solana's Q1 2024 network congestion through Kraken's Learn Center.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mika Explains the Bitcoin Halving]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/f9rUBkUS/mika-explains-the-bitcoin-halving</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/f9rUBkUS/mika-explains-the-bitcoin-halving"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T10:08:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rug Radio Creator and crypto influencer Mika explains the recent Bitcoin halving and how you can build your understanding through Kraken's Learn Center.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Neighbor Alice Season 1 Beta Goes Live]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/sGfYcHuB/my-neighbor-alice-season-1-beta-goes-live</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/sGfYcHuB/my-neighbor-alice-season-1-beta-goes-live"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T09:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rug Radio Creator Orangie plays the new season of multiplayer builder-game My Neighbor Alice and tries out all its features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>