<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-12-09T04:18:02.564Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-12-09T04:18:02.564Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ASCAP Advocates for Strengthened Rights of Publicity Amidst AI Copyright Debate]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19096957/ASCAP-Advocates-for-Strengthened-Rights-of-Publicity-Amidst-AI-Copyright-Debate</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19096957/ASCAP-Advocates-for-Strengthened-Rights-of-Publicity-Amidst-AI-Copyright-Debate"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T03:50:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The American Society of Composers, Authors and Publishers (ASCAP) has doubled down on its support for direct licensing and the expansion of the right of publicity in response to the Copyright Office’s call for comments on artificial intelligence (AI). Breaking away from the ongoing debate...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EU Legislators Seal the Deal on AI Act]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19096944/EU-Legislators-Seal-the-Deal-on-AI-Act</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19096944/EU-Legislators-Seal-the-Deal-on-AI-Act"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T03:24:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a pivotal development, European Union lawmakers in Brussels have achieved a significant breakthrough by reaching a “provisional agreement” on the long-anticipated Artificial Intelligence Act (AI Act). This landmark legislation is poised to establish a comprehensive set of rules that will...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Controversial Role of AI in Detecting Student Suicide Risks]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19096927/The-Controversial-Role-of-AI-in-Detecting-Student-Suicide-Risks</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19096927/The-Controversial-Role-of-AI-in-Detecting-Student-Suicide-Risks"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T03:03:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the ever-evolving landscape of education, schools find themselves at the crossroads of a critical decision: Should they leverage Artificial Intelligence (AI) surveillance tools to detect student suicide risks?  As concerns about the mental health of students intensify, the use of online...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Bill Introduced In Congress Targets Crypto’s Suspected Involvement In Financing Terrorism]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748b3f2005</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bill-congress-targets-crypto-involvement-terrorism/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T03:02:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In response to the Hamas attacks on Israel in October, a group of bipartisan US senators has introduced the Terrorism Financing Prevention Act. The legislation aims to tighten regulatory actions against terror groups by countering the use of cryptocurrency for funding purposes. 
 
Led by Senators Mitt Romney, Mark Warner, Mike Rounds, and Jack Reed, the bill seeks to expand sanctions on foreign parties that facilitate financial transactions with terrorists, including the designation of all US-designated Foreign Terrorist Organizations (FTOs), such as Hamas.
 
Sanctions For Foreign Banks And Crypto Transactions?  
 
As announced by the US Senator for Utah state, Mitt Romney, the Terrorism Financing Prevention Act addresses the emerging threat of digital assets and their potential role in fi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Bill Introduced In Congress Targets Crypto’s Suspected Involvement In Financing Terrorism]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19096908/New-Bill-Introduced-In-Congress-Targets-Cryptos-Suspected-Involvement-In-Financing-Terrorism</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19096908/New-Bill-Introduced-In-Congress-Targets-Cryptos-Suspected-Involvement-In-Financing-Terrorism"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T03:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In response to the Hamas attacks on Israel in October, a group of bipartisan US senators has introduced the Terrorism Financing Prevention Act. The legislation aims to tighten regulatory actions against terror groups by countering the use of cryptocurrency for funding purposes. Led by Senators...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Senator Calls for Light Crypto Regulation That Doesn’t Kill Innovation and Drive Companies Offshore]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748b39765a</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/us-senator-calls-for-light-crypto-regulation-that-doesnt-kill-innovation-and-drive-companies-offshore/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T02:32:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A U.S. senator says Congress needs to regulate the crypto industry “with a light touch that doesn’t kill innovation in the U.S.” Noting that crypto “has the potential to disrupt much of the traditional banking model,” he stressed that crypto regulation needs to be appropriate to avoid driving companies offshore.
 
‘We Need to Regulate With a Light Touch’
 
Senator Bill Hagerty (R-TN), a member of the U.S. Senate Banking and Foreign Relations Committees and former U.S. Ambassador to Japan, addressed JPMorgan CEO Jamie Dimon’s controversial remarks about bitcoin and cryptocurrency during an interview with Bloomberg and in a post on social media platform X on Thursday.
 
Commenting on Dimon’s statement made during a Senate hearing that he would close down crypto and bitcoin if he were the gov…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Rockets Up 14%, But Watch Out For Whale Selling]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748b3b0d9c</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/solana-rockets-up-14-watch-out-for-whale-selling/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T02:10:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana (SOL) has seen a rally of over 14% over the past day, but exchange deposits from the whales could be a worrying sign for these gains.
 
Solana Has Observed A Fresh Rally During The Past Day
 
While Bitcoin has gone stale in the last few days, some altcoins have taken the front seat as they have registered some sharp bullish momentum. Among these decoupled assets is also Solana, which has really blasted off in the past day.
 
During the last 24 hours, SOL has observed a rally of more than 14%, reaching the $73 level for the first time since early May, as the chart below shows.
 

 
 
SOL’s performance during the past day has been the second strongest among the top 30 cryptocurrencies by market cap, with only Cardano (ADA) coming up with better returns.
 
The coin has also notably out…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Rockets Up 14%, But Watch Out For Whale Selling]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19096883/Solana-Rockets-Up-14-But-Watch-Out-For-Whale-Selling</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19096883/Solana-Rockets-Up-14-But-Watch-Out-For-Whale-Selling"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T02:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana (SOL) has seen a rally of over 14% over the past day, but exchange deposits from the whales could be a worrying sign for these gains. Solana Has Observed A Fresh Rally During The Past Day While Bitcoin has gone stale in the last few days, some altcoins have taken the front seat as […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unconfiscatable 2023 | Bitcoin Conference Livestream | Day 2 - Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19096688/Unconfiscatable-2023-Bitcoin-Conference-Livestream-Day-2-Part-2</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19096688/Unconfiscatable-2023-Bitcoin-Conference-Livestream-Day-2-Part-2"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T01:55:09.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Undressing: Deepfake Nude Services Skyrocket in Popularity]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209181</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209181/ai-undressing-deepfake-nude-services-skyrocket-in-popularity"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T01:12:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Analytics firm Graphika says the amount of non-consensual intimate imagery online has grown 2,408% since January.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Undressing: Deepfake Nude Services Skyrocket in Popularity]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19096844/AI-Undressing-Deepfake-Nude-Services-Skyrocket-in-Popularity</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19096844/AI-Undressing-Deepfake-Nude-Services-Skyrocket-in-Popularity"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T01:12:33.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether Joins El Salvador’s “Freedom Visa” Program, Requires $1M Bitcoin Investment]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748b27db46</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/tether-el-salvador-visa-program-1m-bitcoin/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T01:08:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[El Salvador, along with the largest stablecoin issuer in the world, Tether, has introduced a new citizenship-by-investment program, the “Adopting El Salvador Freedom Visa Program,” aimed at attracting 1,000 individuals willing to make a significant investment in the country using Bitcoin or USDT. 
 
Successful applicants will receive a residency visa, a pathway to citizenship, and the opportunity to become integral contributors to El Salvador’s “socio-economic transformation.”
 
Tether Selected As Technology Provider For El Salvador 
 
In collaboration with Tether, the government of El Salvador announced the program’s launch. It aims to create an environment where individuals can actively shape the nation’s future by catalyzing economic expansion and driving transformative societal change.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ANALYSIS: Bloomberg Predicts $500k Bitcoin!? | EP 884]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19096014/ANALYSIS-Bloomberg-Predicts-500k-Bitcoin-EP-884</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19096014/ANALYSIS-Bloomberg-Predicts-500k-Bitcoin-EP-884"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T01:07:23.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Criminal Drains 95 Year-Old Woman’s Bank of America Account – Now Bank Wants $4,237 in Overdraft Fees]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19096836/Criminal-Drains-95-Year-Old-Womans-Bank-of-America-Account-Now-Bank-Wants-4237-in-Overdraft-Fees</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19096836/Criminal-Drains-95-Year-Old-Womans-Bank-of-America-Account-Now-Bank-Wants-4237-in-Overdraft-Fees"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T01:04:37.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[India’s crypto regulations delayed until 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19096834/Indias-crypto-regulations-delayed-until-2025</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19096834/Indias-crypto-regulations-delayed-until-2025"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T01:02:12.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top-100 Web3 Altcoin Surges by 67% This Week Amid Wallet Update, New Partnership and Token Relisting]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19096826/Top-100-Web3-Altcoin-Surges-by-67-This-Week-Amid-Wallet-Update-New-Partnership-and-Token-Relisting</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19096826/Top-100-Web3-Altcoin-Surges-by-67-This-Week-Amid-Wallet-Update-New-Partnership-and-Token-Relisting"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T01:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sound money is WINNING in Argentina #bitcoin #crypto #shorts]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19096835/Sound-money-is-WINNING-in-Argentina-bitcoin-crypto-shorts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19096835/Sound-money-is-WINNING-in-Argentina-bitcoin-crypto-shorts"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T01:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin will follow dollarization. Then the rest of the world will slowly follow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Developers are HYPED about this HUGE Upgrade!! #solana #SOL #crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19096843/Solana-Developers-are-HYPED-about-this-HUGE-Upgrade-solana-SOL-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19096843/Solana-Developers-are-HYPED-about-this-HUGE-Upgrade-solana-SOL-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T01:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Almost every developer I interviewed at the Solana Hacker House are excited about the Runtime v2 and Firedancer upgrades coming for the Solana network. They are going to make transactions even faster and cheaper. Will Solana really become an Ethereum killer?Full video at Solana Hacker House...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Exchange Binance Drops Abu Dhabi License Application as Global Needs Shift]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748b22a8b6</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/crypto-exchange-binance-drops-abu-dhabi-license-application-as-global-needs-shift/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T00:34:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto exchange Binance has withdrawn its application for a license in Abu Dhabi. “When assessing our global licensing needs, we decided this application was not necessary,” a Binance spokesperson stated, adding that the company plans to continue to work with regulators “to provide world-class services and offerings in the Middle East and beyond.”
 
Binance Says ‘This Application Was Not Necessary’
 
Cryptocurrency exchange Binance has reportedly withdrawn its application with Abu Dhabi’s financial regulator. A spokesperson for Binance said on Thursday:
 

When assessing our global licensing needs, we decided this application was not necessary.
 
According to Binance’s website, Abu Dhabi-based Binance (AD) Ltd. received conditional financial services permission from the Financial Services …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside SEC’s closed-door Bitcoin ETF meeting with Fidelity]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19096910/Inside-SECs-closed-door-Bitcoin-ETF-meeting-with-Fidelity</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19096910/Inside-SECs-closed-door-Bitcoin-ETF-meeting-with-Fidelity"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T00:23:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) recently convened a discreet meeting with Fidelity Investments to get into the technicalities of the Spot Bitcoin ETF application. This clandestine gathering shed light on Fidelity’s approach, featuring a comprehensive presentation on “Bitcoin...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iran and Russia are secretly plotting against U.S. and its dollar]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19096911/Iran-and-Russia-are-secretly-plotting-against-US-and-its-dollar</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19096911/Iran-and-Russia-are-secretly-plotting-against-US-and-its-dollar"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T00:14:52.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2024 U.S. defense bill drops crypto rules from legislation]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19096800/2024-US-defense-bill-drops-crypto-rules-from-legislation</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19096800/2024-US-defense-bill-drops-crypto-rules-from-legislation"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T00:10:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lawmakers have removed crypto provisions from the 2024 National Defense Authorization Act as it heads to a final vote. The 2024 National Defense Authorization Act heads to near-certain approval without new rules on cryptocurrencies after negotiators stripped the crypto language to ease passage...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin bulls are betting everything on Wall Street – The reality?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19096912/Bitcoin-bulls-are-betting-everything-on-Wall-Street-The-reality</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19096912/Bitcoin-bulls-are-betting-everything-on-Wall-Street-The-reality"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T00:05:33.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitget Booms in November, Spot Trading Jumps 82%]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19096802/Bitget-Booms-in-November-Spot-Trading-Jumps-82</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19096802/Bitget-Booms-in-November-Spot-Trading-Jumps-82"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T00:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitget saw significant growth amid a mix of factors, including market recovery, expanded offerings and a shifting regulatory landscape.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Regulatory Failures: FCA’s Slow Enforcement And Staffing Woes Draw Criticism]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748b2d1d6b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/uks-fca-criticized-for-slow-crypto-enforcement/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T00:04:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The UK’s Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) is facing criticism from the country’s National Audit Office (NAO) for its sluggish approach to enforcing crypto laws and a shortage of staff with expertise in cryptocurrencies. 
 
In a recent report published by the NAO, an independent entity responsible for scrutinizing public spending, it highlighted the potential impact of crypto-assets as an area of uncertainty that could hinder the FCA’s regulatory effectiveness.
 
While the FCA mandated compliance with anti-money laundering regulations for digital asset firms in January 2020 and began engaging with unregistered firms, it did not initiate enforcement actions against illegal operators of crypto ATMs until February 2023. The report raises concerns about the FCA’s ability to address risks effec…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Provisions Dropped From 2023 U.S. Defense Bill]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748b2d6db4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/12/08/crypto-provisions-dropped-from-2023-us-defense-bill/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T00:01:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The military-linked bill is viewed as must-pass legislation, so lawmakers sometimes try to tack on other things to get them passed, too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don't Miss These 3 Bull Run Altcoin Gems]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19096798/Dont-Miss-These-3-Bull-Run-Altcoin-Gems</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19096798/Dont-Miss-These-3-Bull-Run-Altcoin-Gems"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T00:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Regulatory Failures: FCA’s Slow Enforcement And Staffing Woes Draw Criticism]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19096799/Crypto-Regulatory-Failures-FCAs-Slow-Enforcement-And-Staffing-Woes-Draw-Criticism</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19096799/Crypto-Regulatory-Failures-FCAs-Slow-Enforcement-And-Staffing-Woes-Draw-Criticism"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T00:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Open Interest Climbs To 6-Month High, 100% Rally Incoming?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748b2aaf04</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-open-interest-6-month/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T23:03:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Dogecoin open interest has been on a steady climb lately and on the 10-year anniversary of the meme coin, the open interest broke a new 6-month high. Open futures interest rose to $625 million on Wednesday, December 6, showing just how much interest the meme coin has been seeing lately.
 
Dogecoin Open Interest At New 6-Month High
 
Dogecoin’s open interest saw a considerable spike between the months of October and December after the price began a steady climb. This took the open interest from around $240 million in August to as high as $625 million by early December.
 
 
As Bitcoinist previously reported, this steady increase in the open interest could signal a price rally is coming. It actually means more investors are betting on the price of the digital asset, and while it could go …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Best Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thirdweb Begins Mitigation of Vulnerability Affecting Thousands of Smart Contracts]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748b153a87</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/thirdweb-begins-mitigation-of-vulnerability-affecting-thousands-of-smart-contracts/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T22:36:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thirdweb, a Web3 development framework provider, has announced that it has started mitigating a vulnerability that could potentially affect thousands of smart contracts across several networks. The vulnerability, uncovered in November, impacts various pre-built smart contracts that the framework provides for rapidly deploying applications using an undisclosed open-source library.
Thirdweb Mitigates Critical Vulnerability Across Dozens of EVM Networks
Thirdweb, a Web3 development framework provider, is mitigating the impact of a recently discovered vulnerability in its smart contracts suite. The organization stated that in the last 48 hours, more than 8,000 contracts had been mitigated to contain the impact of this vulnerability, and it is working to extend these actions.
While the organiza…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kazakhstan’s Crypto Purge: More Than 900 Exchanges Axed In 2023]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748b106099</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/kazakhstans-crypto-purge-more-900-exchanges-axed/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T22:04:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kazakhstan’s Financial Monitoring Agency (FMA) has taken a firm stance against unlicensed crypto exchanges. Throughout 2023, the FMA has actively shut down access to nearly a thousand crypto exchanges operating without appropriate licensing.
 
Crackdown On Unlicensed Crypto Exchanges
 
The actions by the FMA were disclosed in a press release published on the Kazakh government’s website. The agency’s chairman, Ruslan Ostroumov, emphasized during a meeting of the Eurasian Group on Combating Money Laundering in China, noting:
 

This year, 980 illegal cryptocurrency exchange platforms have been blocked in the country. Nine investigations have been launched into illegal exchange transactions worth $36.7 million and laundering of criminal proceeds. Preventive measures are being taken.
 
 
Kazak…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SOL Surges 13% as Solana NFTs Overtake Ethereum, BONK Up 26%]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209160</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209160/sol-surges-13-solana-nfts-overtake-ethereum-bonk-up-26"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T21:22:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana’s resurgence isn’t slowing, with SOL and Solana-based tokens still rising and NFT sales volume ruling the wider market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Buys Back 700 Million XRP: Researcher Explains Why]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748b1ea54e</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ripple-buys-back-700-million-xrp/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T21:03:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In recent days and weeks, there has been much speculation as to whether the XRP price is being manipulated and what forces could be behind it. Now, renowned XRP community member Mr. Huber (@Leerzeit) has made an interesting discovery. According to him, it seems like Ripple has bought back 700 million tokens in an effort to stabilize the XRP price.
 
Huber, who is recognized for his insights within the XRP community, first shared crucial data indicating Ripple’s recent activity in the XRP market. He presented a chart comparing the XRP price with the total market capitalization of the cryptocurrency market, emphasizing a noticeable pattern.
 
“Check this out: XRP has lost literally all the extra gains it has made against the general crypto market since the ruling and legal clarity. All of it…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Venezuelan Attorney General Alleges Exxonmobil Financed Opposition to Essequibo’s Ballot With Cryptocurrency]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748b197c79</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/venezuelan-attorney-general-alleges-exxonmobil-financed-opposition-to-essequibos-ballot-with-cryptocurrency/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T20:36:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tarek William Saab, the Venezuelan attorney general, stated that Exxonmobil, a U.S.-based oil and gas company, used intermediaries and cryptocurrency to finance actions against the ballot where Venezuelans were consulted about their position on the ongoing Essequibo claim. Fourteen arrest warrants were issued for individuals who allegedly conspired against the country.
Exxonmobil Used Cryptocurrency in Conspiracy to Fuel Opposition to Venezuela’s Essequibo Claim
The Venezuelan government uncovered a plot that involves money laundering, cryptocurrency, and a conspiracy to influence the recent ballot to define Venezuela’s actions regarding the Essequibo claim. Tarek William Saab, the Venezuelan attorney general, stated that Exxonmobil, one of the biggest oil and gas companies, had used natio…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jito's Token Launch Pushed Competitor Marinade's MNDE to All-Time Highs]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748b19c5ca</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/12/08/jitos-token-launch-pushed-competitor-marinades-mnde-to-all-time-highs/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T20:34:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marinade's market cap is dwarfed by Jito, though, despite being a bigger crypto ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano Jumps 20% as Analyst Eyes Bitcoin Pullback to $40K to 'Fill CME Gap']]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748b19c5c1</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/12/08/cardano-jumps-20-as-analyst-eyes-bitcoin-pullback-to-40k-to-fill-cme-gap/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T20:34:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Market observers "underappreciate" future inflows from institutional investors to bitcoin, asset 21.co CEO said in a CoinDesk TV interview.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avail Hopes to Sell Hollywood on Using AI to Sort Through Scripts]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209135</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209135/ai-to-sort-summarize-movie-tv-scripts-avail"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T20:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The film and TV script summary platform says it can save time and effort with minimal AI hallucinations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI's Potential in Business Breakthroughs Is Overhyped, Says OpenAI COO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209143</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209143/ais-potential-in-business-breakthroughs-is-overhyped-says-openai-coo"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T20:10:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI won’t make you a millionaire, says Brad Lightcap, Sam Altman’s right hand man, calling the tech more of a “sidekick.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Price Pump: Why This Crypto Analyst Believes It’s Now Or Never]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748b051520</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/xrp-price-pump-now-or-never/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T20:03:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Popular Bitcoin and crypto analyst Muro has joined the XRP bandwagon, predicting a ‘now or never’ moment to go long on the XRP price. The crypto has had a flurry of activities over the past few months, with various predictions coming on the crypto’s direction before the end of 2023 and in 2024. However, it had gone unnoticed by Muro until the last week of November when he noted a price breakout.
 
Technicals Signal A Breakout
 
The XRP price appears to be on the verge of exploding from a technical standpoint. Crypto analyst Muro initially made his stance on XRP known in a social media post on November 23, when the crypto broke above the $0.6 region after days of consolidation. 
 
 
According to him, XRP’s breakout resembled that of ETH and SOL and is ready to continue on this movement with…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Says 'Not Your Keys, Not Your Wallet' in Butchered Attempt at Bitcoin Mantra]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209133</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209133/elon-musk-says-not-keys-not-wallet-butchered-bitcoin-mantra"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T19:47:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[World's richest man and alleged crypto fan Elon Musk took a swing at the classic Bitcoin "not your keys" mantra—and whiffed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Got $1 Million in Bitcoin or Tether? El Salvador Will Give You a 'Freedom Visa']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209122</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209122/el-salvador-passport-cough-up-1m-bitcoin-tether"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T19:06:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[El Salvador has announced a new “freedom visa” for rich people who want to live in the Central American nation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Swan Soars In Bitcoin Space: Onboarding Institutions With $200 Million Deployed]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748b03b841</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/swan-soars-in-bitcoin-space-onboarding-institutions-with-200-million-deployed/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T19:04:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a year of turmoil in the Bitcoin and crypto sector, Swan has been one of the companies injecting capital into the nascent industry. Despite the sector’s struggles, including high-profile setbacks faced by Sam Bankman-Fried and Changpeng Zhao, Bitcoin has thrived, culminating in a remarkable rally to close the year.
 
 
A report from Fortune Magazine highlights Swan’s investment and why they could be poised to yield positive results as the market turns bullish.
 
 
Swan Expands Offerings with Bitcoin-Backed Lending Amid Industry Turbulence
 
Swan, a Bitcoin-centric financial firm, announced an expansion into institutional services such as Bitcoin-backed lending and a substantial $40 million fundraising in 2023.
 
Founded in 2019 by Cory Klippsten, Swan started as a straightforward Bitcoi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reynaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Prime Is Giving Out Free Items for NFT Game ‘Champions Ascension’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209121</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209121/amazon-prime-giving-out-free-items-nft-game-champions-ascension"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T18:57:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Got an Amazon Prime membership? You’ll be able to grab in-game items for NFT actioner Champions Ascension on PC for weeks to come.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[El Salvador Introduces Exclusive Citizenship Through $1 Million Crypto Investment]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748b0edeef</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/el-salvador-introduces-exclusive-citizenship-through-1-million-crypto-investment/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T18:37:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[El Salvador has unveiled a new citizenship investment program, the “Freedom Visa,” open to a limited number of applicants. By investing $1 million in bitcoin or tether, participants can secure Salvadoran citizenship.
 
El Salvador’s Bold Bid: Citizenship for Crypto Millionaires
 

 
In a newly announced move, El Salvador, recognized for granting bitcoin (BTC) legal tender status in 2021, has now launched the “Adopting El Salvador Freedom Visa” program. With an annual cap of 1,000 participants, this initiative aims to draw high-net-worth individuals, offering them residency and eventual citizenship in return for their investment, mirroring several Visa schemes in a wide array of nations.
 

 

 

 
The program’s framework requires a $1 million investment in BTC or USDT, with successful appl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Digital Asset Brokerage Firm Nonco Raises $10M Seed Funding Led by Valor Capital, Hack VC]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748b08b119</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/12/08/digital-asset-brokerage-firm-nonco-raises-10m-seed-funding-led-by-valor-capital-hack-vc/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T18:23:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The firm says it has already seen $6 billion in volume in the Latin American region since its debut in April.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin HODLing: A Third Of The Supply Now Unmoved Since 5+ Years]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748b0b49ed</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-hodling-third-supply-unmoved-since-5-years/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T18:02:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data shows about a third of the total circulating Bitcoin supply hasn’t seen any movement on the blockchain since over five years ago.
 
Bitcoin Supply Grows More Dormant As HODLing Continues
 
In a new post on X, analyst James V. Straten shared a chart showing how the Bitcoin supply held by the different long-term holder segments has changed over the asset’s history.
 
The “long-term holders” (LTHs) refer to those investors who have been holding onto their coins since at least 155 days ago. The holders who own coins with an age less than this threshold are known as the “short-term holders” (STHs).
 
 
Statistically, the longer a holder keeps their coins dormant, the less likely they become to move them at any point. Due to this reason, the LTHs are the more resolute group of the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Layer-2 Starknet Reveals STRK Token Airdrop]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209109</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209109/ethereum-layer-2-starknet-reveals-strk-token-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T18:01:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starknet, an Ethereum scaling network, is readying 1.8 billion STRK tokens between the airdrop and rebates, plus incentives for DeFi users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Dogecoin? The Original Meme Coin Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=5678</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/dogecoin-crypto-cryptocurrency-guide-how-to-buy-doge"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T17:50:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin is a peer-to-peer cryptocurrency based on a popular Internet meme. The token started off as a joke, but it's become a serious proposition.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward,Stephen Graves,Wendy Clack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defending The Undefendable: The Censoring Miner]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7494f6fe2b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/markets/defending-the-undefendable-the-censoring-miner"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T17:34:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What do prostitutes, blackmailers, slumlords, and Bitcoin miners who censor transactions all have in common? What if I told you that they are modern-day heroes of the free market economy, bravely providing their economic services despite facing universal scorn and outlawry? These individuals are unquestionably heroes, forged by the unjust treatment at the hands of society and of the state apparatus. If you don’t like the idea of them being heroes, then the only way to deprive them of this stature is to remove the shackles that misguided people have placed upon them. This rogue’s gallery of scapegoats is worthy of our vindication.
Defending the Undefendable is a 1976 book written by the renowned Austrian school economist and anarcho-capitalist theorist Walter Block. Defending the Undefendab…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Matulef</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Animoca Brands Boosts 'Mocaverse' Funding to $31.88 Million With Dapper, Polygon Onboard]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209096</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209096/animoca-brands-boosts-mocaverse-funding-31-88-million-dapper-polygon-onboard"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T17:27:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum NFT-based digital identity and loyalty platform Mocaverse will connect metaverse game worlds, apps, and other Web3 projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HODL: VanEck Bitcoin ETF Uses Laser-Eyed Lingo for Ticker]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209094</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209094/hodl-vaneck-bitcoin-etf-uses-laser-eyed-lingo-for-ticker"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T17:26:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fund manager is one of the biggest contenders in the spot Bitcoin ETF race.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Novel Wallet Is a Book That Hides Your Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209113</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209113/novel-wallet-is-a-book-that-hides-your-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T17:16:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This low-tech tome puts every possible passphrase word in print, providing a creative way to safely store your seed phrase.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Withdraws Abu Dhabi Investment Fund Licence Application]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209069</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209069/binance-withdraws-abu-dhabi-investment-fund-licence-application"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T12:30:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The license, which Binance voluntarily canceled, would have permitted the exchange to manage a collective investment fund in the country.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elizabeth Warren: Update Bank Secrecy Act to Address Crypto 'Threat']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209068</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209068/elizabeth-warren-update-bank-secrecy-act-to-address-crypto-threat"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T11:02:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Senator linked crypto to terrorist financing, drug trafficking, and North Korea's nuclear weapons programme.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Judge Bans Changpeng ‘CZ’ Zhao from Leaving the Country]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209060</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209060/us-judge-bans-changpeng-cz-zhao-from-leaving-the-country"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T02:51:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["The defendant has enormous wealth and property abroad," wrote Judge Richard Jones, "and no ties to the United States."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Early Bitcoin Ordinals Art Sells for Record $450,000]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209032</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209032/early-bitcoin-ordinals-art-sells-for-record-450000"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T02:21:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Honey Badger inscription number eight, created on Jan. 15, sold on Magic Eden on Thursday for 10.4 BTC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft May Be Working On an AI Edition of Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209025</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209025/microsoft-ai-windows-2024-germanium-copilot"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T02:06:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 Windows release is rumored to have AI in everything from its graphical user interface to its command line.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jito Airdrop Hands Out $225 Million to Solana Users]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209010</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209010/jito-airdrop-hands-out-225-million-solana-users"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T23:22:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana DeFi users are celebrating after Jito launched JTO, with 90 million tokens up for grabs for eligible users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INTERVIEW: Ember Sword CEO Says NFT Games Are More 'Transparent']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/M9OHCVpA/interview-ember-sword-ceo-says-nft-games-are-more-transparent</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/M9OHCVpA/interview-ember-sword-ceo-says-nft-games-are-more-transparent"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T21:58:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ember Sword CEO Mark Laursen shares why some big game studios "irk" him—and why he got into game development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Unveils Open-Source Path for AI Development on Its Silicon Chips]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209003</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209003/apple-ai-ml-development-mlx-silicon"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T21:07:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MLX speeds AI development on Apple hardware, connecting its users with the broader AI development community on other platforms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What the Bitcoin Halving Means for Investors]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208164</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208164/bitcoin-halving-what-it-means-investors"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T19:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The next Bitcoin halving takes place in April—but this time is different, insiders say. Here's what retail investors should know.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reebok Follows Nike Into Digital Fashion and Gaming, With an AI Twist]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208993</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208993/reebok-follows-nike-into-digital-wearables-gaming-with-ai-twist"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T19:31:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Footwear brand Reebok will debut an on-chain gaming experience next year that it promises will be “mind-bending.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meme Coins Dogecoin, SHIB Slip—But Solana's BONK Continues to Soar]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208973</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208973/meme-coin-dogecoin-shib-solana-bonk"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T18:38:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bullish traders are once again eyeing up risky assets for quick gains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ronin and Beam Gaming Tokens Surge, Outpacing Bitcoin and Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208986</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208986/ronin-beam-gaming-tokens-surge-outpacing-bitcoin-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T18:16:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gaming tokens remain hot, with RON and BEAM the biggest winners this week with huge double-digit weekly percentage jumps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gamers Can Now Livestream to Twitter via Streamlabs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208972</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208972/gamers-can-now-livestream-twitter-streamlabs"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T17:01:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Streamlabs’ new X feature allows gamers to go live on Twitter from a phone or computer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Montenegro Set to Extradite Terra Co-Founder Do Kwon to US: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208983</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208983/montenegro-extradite-terra-co-founder-do-kwon-us"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T17:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Terraform Labs co-founder has been caught in a jurisdictional tug-of-war between the U.S. and his native South Korea.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These Are the High-Profile Spot Bitcoin ETF Applications Currently in Play]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=62912</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/62912/high-profile-bitcoin-etf-applications"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T15:06:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. SEC has dragged its heels on approval of a Bitcoin spot ETF—but analysts are optimistic that there's light at the end of the tunnel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Auction House Sotheby's Announces First Sale of Bitcoin Ordinals Collection]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208961</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208961/auction-house-sothebys-announces-first-sale-of-bitcoin-ordinals-collection"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T13:22:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The sale marks the first occasion on which works from the BitcoinShrooms collection will be made available to the public, Sotheby's said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood Crypto Launches in EU With 'Crypto Back' Bitcoin Rewards Program]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208954</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208954/robinhood-crypto-launches-in-eu-with-crypto-back-bitcoin-rewards-program"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T10:06:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood Crypto's EU users will receive a percentage of trading volume back in Bitcoin, as well as Bitcoin rewards for referrals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rising Bitcoin Fees Prompt Renewed Battle Over Ordinals, BRC-20 Tokens]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208945</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208945/rising-bitcoin-fees-prompt-renewed-battle-over-ordinals-brc-20-tokens"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T02:01:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While some call for purging the NFT-like inscriptions, others say they are good for the network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t ‘AI Wash’ Investment Pitches: SEC Chair Gary Gensler]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208944</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208944/dont-ai-wash-investment-pitches-sec-chair-gary-gensler"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T01:33:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While excited by AI technology, Gensler highlighted its potential biases and conflicts of interest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Adds AI Across Its Apps, Launches Standalone Image Generator]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208935</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208935/meta-adds-ai-across-its-apps-launches-standalone-image-generator"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T01:02:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Facebook, Instagram, Messenger, and WhatsApp get new AI features, and the Meta Imagine tool lets users create AI art.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Set to List Jito Following Airdrop of Solana Token]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208923</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208923/coinbase-set-list-jito-following-airdrop-solana-token"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T00:07:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase has announced it will list Solana-based DeFi project Jito's token on its platform following the JTO airdrop Thursday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Merit Circle Brings Immutable zkEVM Into Beam Crypto Gaming Ecosystem]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208912</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208912/merit-circle-brings-immutable-zkevm-into-beam-crypto-gaming-ecosystem"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T23:31:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Merit Circle’s Beam tech is expanding beyond Avalanche to the Immutable zkEVM as a part of the DAO's "chain agnostic" approach.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Stock Short Sellers Have Lost $2.6 Billion Since Bitcoin Bull Run Began]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208921</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208921/crypto-stock-short-sellers-lost-2-6-billion-since-bitcoin-bull-run-began"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T23:07:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Short sellers are playing with fire and getting burned as Bitcoin's boom boosts crypto stocks. Experts say it's about to get worse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To AI: Best AI Tools for Image Generation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208752</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208752/which-ai-art-generator-should-you-use-comparison-dalle-midjourney-stable-diffusion-sdxl-adobe-firefly-amazon-titan-leonardo"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T22:05:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Which AI image generator fits your needs? From Dall-E and MidJourney to Stable Diffusion, we've got a comprehensive guide to help you choose.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Buy BTC': Viral Leaked GTA 6 Game Trailer Shills Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208899</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208899/buy-btc-viral-leaked-gta-6-game-trailer-shills-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T21:20:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The much-anticipated Grand Theft Auto 6 trailer came with a Bitcoin-buying plug, thanks to an anonymous leaker.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Director Jordan Bayne on the State of Film3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZLoEDkL9/director-jordan-bayne-on-the-state-of-film3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZLoEDkL9/director-jordan-bayne-on-the-state-of-film3"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T00:11:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the 2023 Film3 Summit, Jordan Bayne—director and founder of The Squad—spoke with Decrypt's Sander Lutz about how the Film3 world has progressed over the last year and what decentralized technologies can offer to creators that want to buck the Hollywood system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Questions With SCENE: Phil Mohun]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TwOjXfOR/5-questions-with-scene-phil-mohun</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TwOjXfOR/5-questions-with-scene-phil-mohun"/>
        <updated>2023-12-01T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bright Moments co-founder Phil Mohun joins 5 Questions With SCENE to recount some favorite moments from the road, including negotiating with Patagonian gauchos, falling in love with Tokyo, and gaining a newfound appreciation for shrooms chocolate bars.

Shot and edited by Vincent Roazzi Jr.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are NFTs Ever Coming Back?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qLmFpNKE/are-nfts-ever-coming-back</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qLmFpNKE/are-nfts-ever-coming-back"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T18:38:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this weeks episode we sit down with Cashtro from Arcade.xyz to discuss NFTs, shitcoins, what collections have held onto their floor prices, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Summit: Will Web3 Gaming Ever be Mainstream?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OvVWhGbW/web-summit-will-web3-gaming-ever-be-mainstream</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OvVWhGbW/web-summit-will-web3-gaming-ever-be-mainstream"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T19:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animoca Brands CEO Robby Yung, EndeavorXR CEO Amy Peck and Gamee co-founder CEO Bozena Rezab joined Decrypt's Stephen Graves on stage at Web Summit to talk about the future of Web3 gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Allie Eve Knox on Spankchain and the life of a Crypto Financial Dominatrix]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/16rVeg6o/allie-eve-knox-on-spankchain-and-the-life-of-a-crypto-financial-dominatrix</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/16rVeg6o/allie-eve-knox-on-spankchain-and-the-life-of-a-crypto-financial-dominatrix"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T21:20:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the first IRL episode of This Time Will Be Different!

In this week's episode, our host, Reza Jafery, is joined by Allie Eve Knox, the Spankchain Chief of Staff and FinDomme. 

They discuss
- How to sell feet pics
- If crypto is really as permissionless as it seems
- the intersections between crypto and sex work]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Questions With SCENE: Jeff Davis]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PChJu1R8/5-questions-with-scene-jeff-davis</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PChJu1R8/5-questions-with-scene-jeff-davis"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artist Jeff Davis joins 5 Questions with SCENE to answer burning questions about his artistic practice, the path that brought him to Art Blocks, and his quietly sophisticated DJ abilities.

Video shot and edited by Vincent Roazzi Jr.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Heatbit Founder Alex Busarov on the Bitcoin Miner That Heats Your Home]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DJuHqcGT/heatbit-founder-alex-busarov-on-the-bitcoin-miner-that-heats-your-home</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DJuHqcGT/heatbit-founder-alex-busarov-on-the-bitcoin-miner-that-heats-your-home"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T18:12:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt joined Heatbit founder Alex Busarov at Web Summit for a walkthrough of the firm's flagship product, a Bitcoin miner that acts as a domestic space heater—aimed at the casual user.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nym CEO Harry Halpin on Privacy, Decentralized VPNs and Tornado Cash]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/aLTtY2aq/nym-ceo-harry-halpin-on-privacy-decentralized-vpns-and-tornado-cash</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/aLTtY2aq/nym-ceo-harry-halpin-on-privacy-decentralized-vpns-and-tornado-cash"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T18:08:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The founder of privacy-preserving mixnet Nym sat down with Decrypt at Web Summit to talk about its new decentralized VPN, the Web3 privacy landscape and why "devs should be defended" in the wake of the Tornado Cash crackdown.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pat Felder - The worst is over [Macro Deep Dive Episode]]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MdcKPVo0/pat-felder-the-worst-is-over-macro-deep-dive-episode</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MdcKPVo0/pat-felder-the-worst-is-over-macro-deep-dive-episode"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T17:10:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the first Markets Edition of This Time Will Be Different! In this episode we dive into the current macroeconomic conditions around crypto and look at the data behind the price action. 


Reza sits down with Pat Felder, founder of Prismatic Capital to discuss the current macro environment, and to answer the question on everyone's mind-- is the bear market really over?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Sandbox Co-Founder Sebastien Borget: 'We're Already Integrating AI']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/HlARjhG1/the-sandbox-co-founder-sebastien-borget-were-already-integrating-ai</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/HlARjhG1/the-sandbox-co-founder-sebastien-borget-were-already-integrating-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T16:09:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt sat down with The Sandbox co-founder Sebastien Borget at Web Summit to talk about AI, the open metaverse and the creative challenges of interoperability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dacoco CEO Saro McKenna: How Alien Worlds is Creating an AI-Powered 'Lore DAO' with Kevin J Anderson]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QrQTrsjH/dacoco-ceo-saro-mckenna-how-alien-worlds-is-creating-an-ai-powered-lore-dao-with-kevin-j-anderson</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QrQTrsjH/dacoco-ceo-saro-mckenna-how-alien-worlds-is-creating-an-ai-powered-lore-dao-with-kevin-j-anderson"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T16:06:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt joined Dacoco CEO Sarojini McKenna at Web Summit 2023 to talk about Alien Worlds' new Lore DAO and its AI-powered collaboration with sci-fi author Kevin J Anderson.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avalon's Jeffrey Butler on Designing a Metaverse MMO That Lets Players Co-Create]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XDz9vsvT/avalons-jeffrey-butler-on-designing-a-metaverse-mmo-that-lets-players-co-create</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XDz9vsvT/avalons-jeffrey-butler-on-designing-a-metaverse-mmo-that-lets-players-co-create"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T00:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avalon Chief Product Officer Jeffrey Butler speaks with Decrypt reporter Jason Nelson and details his studio's new MMO game with interoperable assets—and how it will enable players to create and monetize their own content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Gen Z Is Different: OTK Chief Strategy Officer Talks Creator Economy Shift and Rise of Kick]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PieshbpH/how-gen-z-is-different-otk-chief-strategy-officer-talks-creator-economy-shift-and-rise-of-kick</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PieshbpH/how-gen-z-is-different-otk-chief-strategy-officer-talks-creator-economy-shift-and-rise-of-kick"/>
        <updated>2023-11-10T18:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One True King, an esports and gaming lifestyle brand and media company, was founded by creators like Asmongold and Mizkif. OTK's Chief Strategy Officer Zachary Diaz, who previously worked at TikTok and Twitch, shares with Decrypt's Kate Irwin about how the creator economy is changing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moisés Zamora on Videomart and Bucking the Hollywood System]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kyjQCle8/moises-zamora-on-videomart-and-bucking-the-hollywood-system</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kyjQCle8/moises-zamora-on-videomart-and-bucking-the-hollywood-system"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T17:11:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Selena: The Series" creator and co-showrunner Moisés Zamora joins Decrypt's Sander Lutz at the Film3 Summit 2023 to discuss why the Hollywood system is broken and why he founded the Videomart NFT digital film marketplace to give creators more power.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>