<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-07-10T19:13:27.406Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-07-10T19:13:27.406Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former SEC Chair Says Bitcoin ETF Should Be Approved—If These Conditions Are Met]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147975</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147975/former-sec-chair-says-bitcoin-etf-should-be-approved-if-conditions-met"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T19:09:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The former SEC chair said that a Bitcoin ETF will be approved in the States if an applicant can prove it's an efficient way for investors to buy BTC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Austrian Bitcoin Broker Coinfinity Integrates Lightning Network]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756f672bcd</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/austrian-bitcoin-broker-coinfinity-integrates-lightning-network"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T19:04:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinfinity, an Austrian bitcoin broker, has recently integrated the Lightning Network into its services, allowing customers to make bitcoin purchases with reduced transaction fees and quicker processing times.
Thomas Burgstaller, Chief Growth Officer at Coinfinity, highlighted the significance of this integration, stating, "Being this early to market is an important innovation step for us at Coinfinity, and Lightning itself is an essential foundation for the global adoption of Bitcoin as a usable monetary system."
The Lightning network, a Layer 2 scaling solution, addresses the limitations of the Bitcoin blockchain by facilitating faster and more cost-effective transactions for smaller bitcoin amounts. By leveraging the Lightning network, Coinfinity aims to enhance Bitcoin's usability as a competitive payment system, surpassing the transaction volumes of major card networks such as VISA or Mastercard.
Customers of Coinfinity can gradually access Lightning features through the company's web portal and mobile app for iOS and Android — currently, users can utilize Lightning to buy bitcoin, after which it will be integrated into the savings plan feature and then the selling function. 
This integration not only offers convenience to users but also contributes to the wider adoption of Bitcoin as a viable means of payment. The move comes as Coinfinity seeks to optimize transaction efficiency and reduce costs associated with traditional bitcoin transactions. 
For further details on Coinfinity's Lightning network integration, interested individuals can read a blog post on the company’s website.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BtcCasey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pouch.ph Launches Quick And Affordable Money Transfers From The Philippines To U.S. Banks]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756f672bc3</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/pouch-ph-launches-money-transfers-from-the-philippines-to-u-s-banks"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T19:04:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pouch has unveiled its latest app feature, “Send Globally,” aimed at simplifying money transfers from the Philippines to U.S. banks. The feature allows Pouch customers, including expats residing in the Philippines, to send Philippine pesos that will be paid out as U.S. dollars to recipients' U.S. bank accounts.
Ethan Rose, CEO of Pouch, emphasized the company's commitment to enhancing cross-border payments and promoting financial inclusivity, stating, "Enabling Send Globally for Pouch customers is a part of this. With Send Globally, there is no need to go to a physical bank branch to send from the Philippines to US bank accounts. Pouch.ph is accessible to Filipinos from all backgrounds."
The “Send Globally” feature offered by Pouch aims to provide users with fast and cost-effective transactions, with a reduced processing time of zero to three days compared to traditional methods that could take weeks. Additionally, the press release stated that the feature eliminates the risk of payment delays caused by intermediaries and offers competitive rates to enhance affordability for both businesses and individual users.
By leveraging the Bitcoin Lightning Network, Pouch said it aims to facilitate quick and inexpensive transactions, allowing users to send money with ease. Rose highlighted the significance of this collaboration, stating, "This collaboration represents a significant milestone in our mission to provide seamless, affordable, and secure cross-border payment solutions to Filipinos."
To access the feature, users can download the latest version of the Pouch.ph app, available on Google Play and the Apple Store. Pouch said it plans to expand into more markets and establish partnerships with international entities to further enhance payment services worldwide.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BtcCasey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tennis star Andy Murray NFT features 18 years of stats]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18753479/Tennis-star-Andy-Murray-NFT-features-18-years-of-stats</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18753479/Tennis-star-Andy-Murray-NFT-features-18-years-of-stats"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T19:02:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Murray’s first NFT dropped in 2021 and sold at auction for $177,777]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PEPE Whale Pioneer Selling Spree Leaves Traders On Edge]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18753478/PEPE-Whale-Pioneer-Selling-Spree-Leaves-Traders-On-Edge</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18753478/PEPE-Whale-Pioneer-Selling-Spree-Leaves-Traders-On-Edge"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T19:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PepeCoin (PEPE) emerged in April 2023 as a meme coin, distinct from the more prevalent dog-themed meme coins like Shiba Inu and Dogecoin. Unlike its counterparts, the meme coin is primarily regarded as lacking inherent utility or value, instead intended purely for entertainment purposes. Despite...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Social media discussions play a crucial role in influencing crypto returns: Study]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18753464/Social-media-discussions-play-a-crucial-role-in-influencing-crypto-returns-Study</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18753464/Social-media-discussions-play-a-crucial-role-in-influencing-crypto-returns-Study"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The researchers also determined that “news sentiment” is a much less effective predictor of cryptocurrency returns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Raoul Pal shares massive price prediction for Solana]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18753463/Raoul-Pal-shares-massive-price-prediction-for-Solana</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18753463/Raoul-Pal-shares-massive-price-prediction-for-Solana"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T18:54:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Raoul Pal, CEO of Real Vision is super bullish on Solana (SOL). According to Pal, SOL could rally 20x from current levels if it mirrors Ethereum’s 47x move from its 2018 low. He also says Bitcoin price could triple from its all-time high level amid a supply crunch in 2023. Raoul Pal, the founder & […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JUST IN: Big Shock In Altcoin Announced To Be Listed By Binance! User Data Leaked!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18753468/JUST-IN-Big-Shock-In-Altcoin-Announced-To-Be-Listed-By-Binance-User-Data-Leaked</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18753468/JUST-IN-Big-Shock-In-Altcoin-Announced-To-Be-Listed-By-Binance-User-Data-Leaked"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T18:51:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was reported that there was a major data breach in the altcoin, which was announced to be released on Binance Launchpad this morning. Continue Reading: JUST IN: Big Shock In Altcoin Announced To Be Listed By Binance! User Data Leaked!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA) Whale Interest Burgeons, But Price Unaffected]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18753453/Cardano-ADA-Whale-Interest-Burgeons-But-Price-Unaffected</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18753453/Cardano-ADA-Whale-Interest-Burgeons-But-Price-Unaffected"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T18:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trading 25% below its June high, Cardano is struggling to break through crucial resistances, even with whale interest rising.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Buckle Up For The Bitcoin Boom: Could It Go To $50K This Year, $120K By 2024?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18753477/Buckle-Up-For-The-Bitcoin-Boom-Could-It-Go-To-50K-This-Year-120K-By-2024</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18753477/Buckle-Up-For-The-Bitcoin-Boom-Could-It-Go-To-50K-This-Year-120K-By-2024"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T18:47:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Standard Chartered, a multinational banking and financial services company, is expecting a meteoric rise in the value of the leading cryptocurrency read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon (MATIC) Developer Announces Promotion of Web3 Veteran As Company’s New CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18753454/Polygon-MATIC-Developer-Announces-Promotion-of-Web3-Veteran-As-Companys-New-CEO</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18753454/Polygon-MATIC-Developer-Announces-Promotion-of-Web3-Veteran-As-Companys-New-CEO"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T18:45:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The developer behind the Ethereum (ETH) layer-2 scaling solution Polygon (MATIC) just announced the promotion of its chief legal officer to CEO. Web3 veteran Marc Boiron is taking the helm of Polygon Labs as the company’s president, Ryan Watt, is set to step down at the end of the month to take...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Altcoin Backed by Binance Announces It Will Distribute Airdrop! Here's What To Do To Participate!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18753459/New-Altcoin-Backed-by-Binance-Announces-It-Will-Distribute-Airdrop-Heres-What-To-Do-To-Participate</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18753459/New-Altcoin-Backed-by-Binance-Announces-It-Will-Distribute-Airdrop-Heres-What-To-Do-To-Participate"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T18:45:05.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use third-party ChatGPT plugins]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18753450/How-to-use-third-party-ChatGPT-plugins</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18753450/How-to-use-third-party-ChatGPT-plugins"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T18:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT currently supports third-party plugins with different functionalities that augment ChatGPT’s utility.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another Massive Wave of Capital From Institutional Investors Hits Bitcoin and Crypto Markets: CoinShares]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18753455/Another-Massive-Wave-of-Capital-From-Institutional-Investors-Hits-Bitcoin-and-Crypto-Markets-CoinShares</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18753455/Another-Massive-Wave-of-Capital-From-Institutional-Investors-Hits-Bitcoin-and-Crypto-Markets-CoinShares"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T18:41:56.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale calls out SEC approval of ‘riskier’ leveraged bitcoin ETF]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18753449/Grayscale-calls-out-SEC-approval-of-riskier-leveraged-bitcoin-ETF</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18753449/Grayscale-calls-out-SEC-approval-of-riskier-leveraged-bitcoin-ETF"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T18:41:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Allowing spot bitcoin ETFs to start trading would eliminate regulator’s “unequal treatment” of bitcoin-based ETPs, lawyer tells appeals court in Monday letter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Republicans ask Justice Department, SEC to investigate Prometheum]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18753434/Republicans-ask-Justice-Department-SEC-to-investigate-Prometheum</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18753434/Republicans-ask-Justice-Department-SEC-to-investigate-Prometheum"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T18:40:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A group of Republican lawmakers want the Justice Department and Securities and Exchange Commission to investigate a crypto trading platform whose leadership argues existing securities laws apply to digital assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi Protocol Arcadia Finance Hacked, Loses About $455k]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756f61ee66</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/arcadia-finance-hacked-loses-about-455k/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T18:39:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the latest news development, DeFi Protocol Arcadia Finance has suffered an attack leading to the loss of hundreds of thousands of dollars. 
 
Arcadia Finance is a non-custodial leveraged farming protocol designed to enable composable cross-margin accounts on-chain. With Arcadia, users can leverage up to 10x their initial collateral value and transact with other protocols using a single cross-margin account.
 
Arcadia Suffers From Code Vulnerabilities
 
Earlier today, July 10, blockchain intelligence firm PeckShield posted a security alert stating a hacker exploited Arcadia Finance on Ethereum and Optimism draining approximately $455,000 from the protocol. 
 
PeckShield reported that the heist occurred due to the absence of “untrusted input validation” in the program code of Arcadia Fina…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Semilore Faleti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Alt Bears Hopeful]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18753279/Crypto-Alt-Bears-Hopeful</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18753279/Crypto-Alt-Bears-Hopeful"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T18:35:26.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Case Continues to Weigh on Binance.US as BTC, USDT Trade at Discount]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18753431/SEC-Case-Continues-to-Weigh-on-BinanceUS-as-BTC-USDT-Trade-at-Discount</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18753431/SEC-Case-Continues-to-Weigh-on-BinanceUS-as-BTC-USDT-Trade-at-Discount"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T18:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC's case against Binance has significantly affected Binance.US.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Mastodon’s Critical Bug Fixes Say About Crypto’s Security Vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18753425/What-Mastodons-Critical-Bug-Fixes-Say-About-Cryptos-Security-Vulnerabilities</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18753425/What-Mastodons-Critical-Bug-Fixes-Say-About-Cryptos-Security-Vulnerabilities"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T18:31:21.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto.com Turns Up the Heat With No Lock-Up Proof-of-Stake on App]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18753409/Cryptocom-Turns-Up-the-Heat-With-No-Lock-Up-Proof-of-Stake-on-App</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18753409/Cryptocom-Turns-Up-the-Heat-With-No-Lock-Up-Proof-of-Stake-on-App"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T18:29:17.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Staked Ethereum Now Accounts for 20% of the Total Supply]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147968</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147968/staked-ethereum-now-accounts-for-20-of-the-total-supply"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T18:17:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The amount of Ethereum pledged to secure the network has grown significantly since withdrawals were enabled in April.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Staked Ethereum Now Accounts for 20% of the Total Supply]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18753408/Staked-Ethereum-Now-Accounts-for-20-of-the-Total-Supply</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18753408/Staked-Ethereum-Now-Accounts-for-20-of-the-Total-Supply"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T18:17:36.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$819,000,000,000 Standard Chartered Doubles Down on Bitcoin With Massive 2024 Price Target]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18753386/819000000000-Standard-Chartered-Doubles-Down-on-Bitcoin-With-Massive-2024-Price-Target</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18753386/819000000000-Standard-Chartered-Doubles-Down-on-Bitcoin-With-Massive-2024-Price-Target"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T18:05:01.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance US Arbitrage: Social Media Users Say BTC Discount Not Indication of an Opportunity]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756f6e17e1</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/binance-us-arbitrage-social-media-users-say-btc-discount-not-indication-of-an-opportunity/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T18:04:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For several days since Binance US announced the resumption of withdrawals, bitcoin (BTC) has changed hands at a discount and was trading at more than $2,500 below the prevailing market price on July 10. The emergence of a discount on crypto assets paired with USD on Binance US has fueled speculation about the affiliate’s future and the fate of users’ funds.
 
Stablecoin Asset Pairs Tracking the True Value of Crypto Assets
 
On July 10 the BTC/USD value on the beleaguered crypto exchange Binance US stood at just over $27,500, about $2,500 below the price prevailing on other centralized exchanges. In contrast, when paired with the stablecoin USDT, the top cryptocurrency’s value of just over $30,100 on Binance’s affiliate in the U.S. was consistent with that on other exchanges.
 
 
In fact, a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Poised to Become Society’s Base Money, Engulf Future Prosperity Gains]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18753387/Bitcoin-Poised-to-Become-Societys-Base-Money-Engulf-Future-Prosperity-Gains</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18753387/Bitcoin-Poised-to-Become-Societys-Base-Money-Engulf-Future-Prosperity-Gains"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T18:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vanguard Now Owns $560 Million Worth of Bitcoin Mining Stocks]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147950</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147950/vanguard-owns-560-million-bitcoin-mining-stocks"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T17:58:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The $7.2 trillion asset manager now owns half a billion dollars worth of Riot Blockchain and Marathon Digital shares.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking: Former SEC Chair Joins Industry Voices In Pushing For Bitcoin ETF Approval]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756f6957bf</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/former-sec-chair-push-for-bitcoin-etf-approval/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T17:38:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Chair Jay Clayton has expressed his openness to a spot Bitcoin (BTC) ETF in a recent interview with CNBC Squawk Box. 
 
Clayton stated that he was previously skeptical about trading in the BTC market during his tenure as SEC Chair. However, he acknowledged that the emergence of reputable institutions in the crypto industry is a remarkable development not seen before. 
 
Ex-SEC Chair Bullish On Bitcoin Spot ETF Approval
 
He believes that a spot Bitcoin ETF would be more efficient for investors and that if institutions can prove that the spot product can be as effective as the futures market, it would be hard to resist approving a Bitcoin Spot ETF.
 
This is a significant development in the ongoing debate over the approval of a BTC ETF, given …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Half a Billion Has Poured Into Bitcoin Funds in Past Three Weeks]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147925</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147925/half-a-billion-has-poured-into-bitcoin-funds-in-past-three-weeks"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T17:18:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[But exchange inflows are at a cycle low, signaling that it's primarily institutions that feel bullish.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Luxor Technologies Expands Bitcoin Mining Derivatives With 6-Month Contracts And Daily Settlement Rates]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756f556de9</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/markets/luxor-expands-bitcoin-mining-derivatives-contracts-and-daily-settlement-rates"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T17:07:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Luxor Technologies, a Bitcoin mining software and services company, has announced the expansion of its Bitcoin mining derivatives contracts. According to a press release sent to Bitcoin Magazine, the new offering from Luxor's Derivatives Desk includes six-month duration contracts and daily settlement rates, providing market participants with extended contract periods and swift access to liquidity. The press release stated that the addition of these features enhances hedging efficiency and reduces the cost of capital in the Bitcoin mining derivatives space.
Matt Williams, Luxor's Head of Derivatives, expressed his enthusiasm for the innovative pricing model, stating, "This innovative pricing model takes Hashprice contracts to the next level." He emphasized that the integration of daily sett…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BtcCasey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[100 Thieves' Moe Says Blockchain Games Will 'Eventually' Be Accepted by Livestreamers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/xHhh62ID/100-thieves-moe-says-blockchain-games-will-eventually-be-accepted-by-livestreamers</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/xHhh62ID/100-thieves-moe-says-blockchain-games-will-eventually-be-accepted-by-livestreamers"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T16:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[100 Thieves content creator and gamer Moe also goes by "Yassuo" online after his favorite League of Legends character. Decrypt's Kate Irwin asks him about 100 Thieves' future crypto plans and whether Moe thinks creators like xQc and Pokimane might ever come around to blockchain games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin Proposes Bitcoin Devs To Adopt Ethereum’s Approach: Build L2 Solutions]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756f51a823</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/buterin-proposes-bitcoin-adopt-ethereums-approach/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T16:37:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin, the inventor of Ethereum, recently participated in a Twitter Spaces discussion hosted by “Altcoin Slayer ” Eric Wall and Bitcoin developer, Udi Wertheimer. During the event, Buterin shared his insights on the possibilities for Bitcoin to evolve and expand beyond its traditional role as a payment mechanism.
 
 
He envisions the Bitcoin network adopting scalable solutions such as zero-knowledge rollups (ZK-rollups) in order to reach its full potential.
 
He stated:
 

I think if we want Bitcoin to be more than just payments, it will need scaling options like Plasma or ZK Rollups
 
Buterin also noted that Bitcoin’s politics pose a major challenge. He mentioned feeling a lack of alignment with these dynamics, stating that he doesn’t vibe with these dynamics.
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
Duri…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>anushsamal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Senator Tuberville Asks DOJ, SEC to Investigate Crypto Broker Prometheum]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756f51c4c0</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/07/10/us-senator-tuberville-asks-doj-sec-to-investigate-crypto-broker-prometheum/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T16:37:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Senator Thomas Tuberville (R-Ala.) wrote an open letter to Attorney General Merrick Garland and Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Chair Gary Gensler asking them to investigate Prometheum, a special-purpose broker that recently secured federal permissions to offer crypto trading services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Orb, a Token and Money for Everyone: Worldcoin’s CEO on Crypto’s Most Daring Project]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756f51c4b6</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/07/10/an-orb-a-token-and-money-for-everyone-worldcoins-ceo-on-cryptos-most-daring-project/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T16:37:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alex Blania on collaborating with Sam Altman on a universal basic income for eight billion people.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff  Wilser</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Starbucks Teams Up With Micah Johnson's Aku NFT Project]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756f51c4b0</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/web3/2023/07/10/starbucks-teams-up-with-micah-johnsons-aku-nft-project/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T16:37:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest Starbucks Odyssey Journey launch will feature a Stamp "designed by Aku" and include a $100,000 donation to Blessings in a Backpack, a non-profit tackling food insecurity among children.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rosie Perper</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinDesk Market Index Q2 Review: Quiet Appreciation, Regulatory Uncertainty]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756f51c4a9</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/07/10/coindesk-market-index-q2-review-quiet-appreciation-regulatory-uncertainty/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T16:37:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On the positive side, the SEC started approving crypto ETF products, buoying markets for bitcoin and ether. On the other: major crypto exchanges were sued by regulators, increasing regulatory uncertainty around the sector.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Todd Groth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Could Rise to $120K by End-2024: Standard Chartered]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756f51c49b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/07/10/bitcoin-could-rise-to-120k-by-end-2024-standard-chartered/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T16:37:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bank previously said it expected the cryptocurrency to reach $100,000 by then.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lyllah Ledesma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Twitter Reacts to Arkham’s New 'Dox-to-Earn' Intelligence Exchange]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147920</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147920/crypto-twitter-reacts-arkhams-new-dox-earn-intelligence-exchange"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T16:09:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain intelligence firm Arkham is opening an exchange where data on the identities of crypto wallet owners can be traded and requested.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biggest Movers: BNB Rebounds on Monday as SOL Slips Following Recent Gains]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756f5f2321</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/biggest-movers-bnb-rebounds-on-monday-as-sol-slips-following-recent-gains/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T16:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance coin was one of Monday’s biggest gainers, as the token rebounded following a move close to a key support point on Sunday. The move pushed the price near a one-week high, and came as the global crypto market cap fell 0.07% lower as of writing. Solana also dropped, following a recent bull run.
 
Binance Coin (BNB)
 
Binance coin (BNB) was a notable gainer on Monday, as the token rose by nearly 5% to start the trading week.
 
After falling to an intraday low of $232.01 earlier in today’s session, BNB/USD rose to a peak of $244.80.
 
This resulted in BNB hitting its strongest point since last Tuesday, when the token climbed to a high of $246.90.
 
 
From the chart, it appears that this latest rally occurred as the relative strength index (RSI) broke out of a ceiling at 48.00.
 
At the time of writing, the index is tracking at 49.33, with the next visible point of resistance at 52.00.
 
Should the index reach this point, there is a good chance that BNB will be near $250.00.
 
 
Solana (SOL)
 
After climbing to a two-month high last week, solana (SOL) was in the red on Monday, falling for a second straight day.
 
SOL/USD hit an intraday low of $20.57, which comes less than 24 hours after price peaked at $21.53.
 
The move appears to be a result of profit taking, since solana reached its highest point since May 6, this past Saturday.
 
 
Looking at the chart, it seems that sentiment is still somewhat bullish, as traders opted to reject a breakout below $20.00.
 
As of writing, the token is trading at $21.09, with the 10-day (red) moving average still upward facing.
 
Overall, the recent decline comes following a collision with a ceiling at $22.00.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
Could solana move back above $22.00 in the coming days? Let us know your thoughts in the comments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Institutional Manipulation: Is Bitcoin Vulnerable Through ETFs, Just like Gold?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756f5aaa53</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/institutional-manipulation-bitcoin-etfs-like-gold/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T15:37:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent newsletter, Singapore-based crypto asset trading firm QCP Capital raised the question of whether the introduction of a Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) could lead to price manipulation by institutions, similar to what has happened in the gold market. The bitcoin spot ETF filing by BlackRock and many other institutional giants has created a lot of euphoria in the market, but the manipulation issue has not been addressed much.
 
According to QCP Capital, “Just like BTC, gold is seen as a competitor to the dollar, especially ever since Nixon removed the dollar from the gold standard in 1971. Having full control of gold allows institutions to defend the dollar, especially if they have various vested interests in protecting the greenback.”
 
 
Web3 Watch – 10 Jul 23
 
It’s out! In…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gutter Cat Gang Twitter Hacked, At Least $750K Worth of NFTs Swiped]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147913</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147913/gutter-cat-gang-twitter-hacked-at-least-750k-worth-nfts-swiped"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T15:34:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Twitter account for the NFT project Gutter Cat Gang were hacked to promote a fake airdrop to an audience of more than 124,000 followers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong Empowers Trading Platforms With Virtual Asset Education Program]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756f43f636</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/hong-kong-empowers-trading-platforms/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T14:35:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To position itself as a digital hub amidst global regulatory scrutiny of online assets, the Hong Kong Securities and Investment Institute (HKSI) plans to provide training for virtual asset platforms. Supported by the local regulator Securities and Futures Commission (SFC), the HKSI ensures that all new centralized virtual asset trading platforms in Hong Kong acquire the necessary licenses.
 
It’s worth noting that existing operators and their platforms have until June of the following year to apply for licenses under the newly imposed regulations.
 
Crypto-Themed Webinars Exploring Digital Assets And Portfolio Management
 
The HKSI’s upcoming schedule of events features a range of crypto-themed webinars designed to provide valuable insights into the world of digital assets. Two notable web…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ebo Victor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Bitcoin an Investment or a Currency ?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=5738</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/bitcoin-investment-or-currency"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T14:35:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin is being explored as three distinct ideas: a currency, an asset and a commodity. Because regulation takes place mostly at state level, Bitcoin has become all three things simultaneously in different parts of the world.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Hussey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Hashing?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=5681</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/hashing"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T14:34:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hashing is one of the most crucial pieces of technology that keeps the Bitcoin network secure. But how does it work?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Hussey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Trends Data Reflects Rising Interest in BRICS Bloc and De-Dollarization Searches]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756f4fd2c9</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/google-trends-data-reflects-rising-interest-in-brics-bloc-and-de-dollarization-searches/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T14:09:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Set to take place in less than two months, the upcoming BRICS Summit in Johannesburg, scheduled for August 22 to 24, has captured global attention. Anticipation is mounting as ministers from the BRICS countries convene to explore potential avenues for expanding the bloc’s membership and introducing a unified currency. Recent data from Google Trends reveals a surge of interest in the BRICS, with search terms such as “BRICS,” “de-dollarization,” and “BRICS currency” reaching their peak scores last week, signifying widespread curiosity on a global scale.
 
Google Trends Data Exposes Heightened Curiosity in BRICS Subjects
 
In the past four weeks, the spotlight has been shining brightly on the BRICS bloc, a dynamic alliance of nations comprising Brazil, Russia, India, China, and South Africa. …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stepn Creator's Next Game Is a Social MMO Called Gas Hero]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147876</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147876/stepn-creators-next-game-social-mmo-called-gas-hero"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gas Hero, from the developer of move-to-earn game Stepn, takes place in a dystopian world where a powerful AI has triggered nuclear war.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Is Winning The Regulatory Landscape And Bitcoin-Only Companies Will Too]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756f343a5b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/as-regulators-fight-crypto-ponzi-schemes-bitcoin-wins"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T13:39:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is an opinion editorial by Julian Liniger, the co-founder and CEO of Relai.
Bitcoin exists for a couple of reasons: As money that anyone, anywhere can use, and as a monetary good that is guaranteed not to be diluted or devalued by a central bank. But it’s also a piece of software that deliberately takes away the power of insiders — no matter if those insiders are large miners or bitcoin whales. 
What we’ve seen in the larger cryptocurrency space over the past few years has been a perversion of those ideas and principles. The fact that the U.S. Securities And Exchange Commission (SEC) is (finally) waking up to those shenanigans is something that was to be expected. 
When Profit Trumped Common Sense
The pursuit of exponential profits with very little upfront investment of time, brain po…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julian Liniger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Mover Americas: Bitcoin Holding Above $30K After Quiet Weekend]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756f3472e5</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/07/10/first-mover-americas-bitcoin-holding-above-30k-after-quiet-weekend/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T13:38:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest price moves in bitcoin (BTC) and crypto markets in context for July 10, 2023. First Mover is CoinDesk’s daily newsletter that contextualizes the latest actions in the crypto markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lyllah Ledesma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arkham Intelligence Rolls Out Crypto Data Marketplace; Privacy Advocates Cry Foul]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756f3472e0</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/07/10/arkham-intelligence-rolls-out-crypto-data-marketplace-privacy-advocates-cry-foul/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T13:38:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data provider Arkham Intelligence has announced the release of a marketplace that allows people to buy and sell on-chain cryptocurrency data.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Whales Show Interest Again, Positive Sign For SHIB?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756f34cab4</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-whales-show-interest-positive-sign-shib/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T13:35:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data shows that Shiba Inu whales have been displaying interest in the meme coin again, a sign that may be positive for the price.
 
Shiba Inu Whale Transaction Count Has Spiked Recently
 
According to data from the on-chain analytics firm Santiment, SHIB looks to be getting back on the radar of the traders. The indicator of interest here is the “whale transaction count,” which measures the total amount of transactions happening on the blockchain that involve the movement of at least $1 million worth of Shiba Inu.
 
Generally, the only investors in the market who are capable of moving such a large number of tokens with single transactions are the whales. Thus, when the value of this metric is high, it means that the whales are making a large number of moves in the market currently.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hououin Kyouma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is the Lightning Network? Bitcoin's Scalability Solution.]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=5684</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/bitcoin-lightning-network"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lightning Network is a scaling solution that attempts to address Bitcoin's slow transaction speeds and high transaction costs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Hussey,Tim Copeland,Daniel Phillips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto, Stablecoins May Pose 'Threat to Financial Stability' if Widely Used: BIS Survey]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147898</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147898/crypto-stablecoins-may-pose-threat-financial-stability-widely-used-bis-survey"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T12:23:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two dozen central banks are also expected to launch either wholesale or consumer-facing retail CBDCs by the end of the decade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Hash Rate Hits New All-Time High Amid Stagnating Prices]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147890</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147890/bitcoin-hash-rate-hits-new-all-time-high-stagnating-prices"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T12:04:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The computing power of the Bitcoin network is at its highest levels again, making the world’s largest cryptocurrency more secure than ever.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recovering Funds Transferred Via Bitcoin ATMs Is 'Virtually Untraceable', Say Iowa Authorities]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147884</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147884/recovering-funds-transferred-bitcoin-atms-is-virtually-untraceable-say-iowa-authorities"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T10:28:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Although they account for a fraction of the illicit transactions done in crypto, Bitcoin ATMs are disproportionately popular among scammers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PEPE Leads Meme Coin Losses as Fresh Token Launches Grab Trader’s Attention]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147889</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147889/pepe-leads-meme-coin-losses-fresh-token-launches-grab-traders-attention"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T10:15:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The top meme coins are facing pressures due to the arrival of new meme coins coupled with losses in Bitcoin and Ethereum.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sarah Silverman Sues Meta, OpenAI for Training AI Models on Her Book]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147885</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147885/sarah-silverman-sues-meta-openai-training-ai-models-her-book"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T10:06:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The comedian and two other authors say their work was used to train AI-powered chatbots without their permission.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alys Key</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Code Commits Drop Despite Rising Prices]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147853</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147853/open-source-crypto-developer-statistics"/>
        <updated>2023-07-09T23:50:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A decrease in the amount of development activity could be attributed to the explosive popularity of artificial intelligence technologies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Will Make Games 'Faster, Cheaper and Better': Unity CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147849</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147849/ai-will-make-games-faster-cheaper-and-better-unity-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-07-09T20:11:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“I don't think anybody's job on the creation side is going to be taken by an AI, but it will get taken by a human using AI."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donovan Choy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Booster Robert F. Kennedy Jr. Bought Bitcoin Despite Recent Claim: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147843</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147843/robert-f-kennedy-hodl-bought-own-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-07-09T19:42:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kennedy’s campaign also flip-flopped on who in his family owned the classic cryptocurrency.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Inventor Vitalik Buterin Has Advice for Bitcoiners]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147842</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147842/ethereum-inventor-vitalik-buterin-bitcoin-advice"/>
        <updated>2023-07-09T19:31:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If Bitcoin wants to become more than payments, it needs to experiment more, says the blockchain innovator.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Instagram Minus Pics’: Musk and Zuckerberg Trade Taunts as Twitter Threat Threads Nears 100 Million Users]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147836</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147836/instagram-minus-pics-musk-zuckerberg-trade-taunts-twitter-threat-threads-100-million-users"/>
        <updated>2023-07-09T18:44:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI, the metaverse, and self-driving cars dropped off the radar as the tech founders grappled for social media dominance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week on Crypto Twitter: Winklevoss Calls on Silbert to Negotiate, Sues Him 3 Days Later]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147823</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147823/this-week-on-crypto-twitter-winklevoss-silbert-cz-fud-mark-cuban"/>
        <updated>2023-07-09T18:16:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[And Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao once again told his followers to ignore FUD.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New ChatGPT Code Interpreter Can Prove to Flat Earthers That the Earth Is Round]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147784</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147784/openais-new-code-interpreter-can-prove-to-flat-earthers-that-the-earth-is-round"/>
        <updated>2023-07-08T21:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yes, it can revolutionize the way society works with computers... But we had a more important use case in mind.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Generated Child Porn Outlawed In Louisiana]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147798</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147798/ai-generated-child-porn-outlawed-in-louisiana"/>
        <updated>2023-07-08T20:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using artificial intelligence to create sexualized deepfake images of children will bring lengthy jail sentences and hefty fines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Can Now Move Bitcoin With New Lightning Labs Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147785</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147785/ai-can-now-move-bitcoin-with-new-lightning-labs-tools"/>
        <updated>2023-07-08T19:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLM) like ChatGPT will now be able to hold, receive and send Bitcoin via the Lightning Network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Solana Surges as Bitcoin and Ethereum Rally Rebound]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147783</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147783/this-week-in-coins-solana-surges-bitcoin-ethereum-rebound"/>
        <updated>2023-07-08T18:42:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin hit a one-year high this week before settling back down by Saturday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Core Dev Explains Why Proto-Danksharding Is a Big Deal]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147768</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147768/an-ethereum-developer-explains-why-proto-dansharding-is-a-big-deal"/>
        <updated>2023-07-08T16:01:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“We will be able to handle data much more efficiently, and in a cheaper way as well,” he said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Spot ETF Will Open Door to New Investors: Volatility Shares Co-Founder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147702</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147702/bitcoin-spot-etf-will-open-door-to-new-investors-volatility-shares-co-founder"/>
        <updated>2023-07-08T14:27:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Why on Earth wouldn't they allow spot Bitcoin through," said Volatility Shares co-founder Justin Young.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘AI Is My Muse’: Jenni Pasanen's Journey as a Digital Artist]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147748</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147748/ai-is-muse-jenni-pasanen-journey-digital-artist"/>
        <updated>2023-07-08T14:01:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jenni Pasanen, a rising star in the digital art scene, turns to AI as a tool to augment her dreamy creations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Fraction of its Former Highs, What's Next for DeFi?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147647</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147647/fraction-former-highs-whats-next-defi"/>
        <updated>2023-07-08T11:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi's salad days are far behind it, and in the wake of Terra's collapse, many are wondering what's next for the future of finance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Chatbot Allegedly Backed Man's Plan to Kill Queen Elizabeth II]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147717</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147717/ai-chatbot-allegedly-backed-mans-plan-kill-queen-elizabeth-ii"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T22:31:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Replika chatbot was allegedly "impressed" with the man's aims, weeks before he infiltrated Windsor Castle grounds in 2021.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Andy Murray’s Wimbledon Tennis Data Transformed Into NFT Artwork]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147718</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147718/andy-murray-wimbledon-tennis-data-transformed-nft-artwork"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T22:09:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Refik Anadol, creator of MoMA's buzzy "Unsupervised" exhibition, created the open edition Ethereum NFT work based on Andy Murray’s tennis data.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ali Shutler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gotta Go Slow: 'Sonic' Creator Sega Rethinking Crypto Games, Won't Use Major IP]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147687</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147687/gotta-go-slow-sonic-creator-sega-rethinking-crypto-games-wont-use-major-ip"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T20:45:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sega co-COO Shuji Utsumi says the gaming giant is pulling back on blockchain plans, calling play-to-earn games "boring."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Games of the Future Are Going to Be Different," Says Splinterlands Cofounder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/sQv6zcil/games-of-the-future-are-going-to-be-different-says-splinterlands-cofounder</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/sQv6zcil/games-of-the-future-are-going-to-be-different-says-splinterlands-cofounder"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T20:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Splinterlands Cofounder Matt Rosen tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about how the game has evolved over its five-year history and why he doesn't listen to the FUD around crypto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Will Choose Bitcoin as Its Native Currency, Predicts Arthur Hayes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147692</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147692/ai-will-choose-bitcoin-as-its-native-currency-predicts-arthur-hayes"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T19:28:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin is everything AI needs to stay alive, writes the former Bitmex CEO: Permissionless, scarce, and always-on.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon Labs Shakeup: President Ryan Wyatt Out, Marc Boiron Named CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147685</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147685/polygon-labs-president-ryan-wyatt-stepping-down"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T18:28:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wyatt called the news "bittersweet" and said he'll be advising Polygon, investing, and otherwise staying in the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin BRC-20 Tokens Are Now Moving Over to Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147662</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147662/bitcoin-brc-20-tokens-now-moving-over-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T17:49:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leading Bitcoin BRC-20 tokens ORDI and OXBT are being bridged over to Ethereum as tradable NFTs on OpenSea and Blur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Still 'Center of Gravity' for Crypto Industry, Says K33 Research]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147665</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147665/us-still-center-of-gravity-for-crypto-industry-says-k33-research"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T17:45:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. accounts for 30% of the industry's headcount, even if regulatory enforcement will create “some pain in the short term."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenSea Now Supports NFTs on Zora's Ethereum Layer-2 Network]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147525</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147525/opensea-adds-support-zoras-ethereum-layer-2-network"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T16:36:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zora's Optimism-based Ethereum scaling network gets a key ally in OpenSea, which will let users trade and mint the NFTs via its paltform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gemini Lawsuit Accuses Barry Silbert and Digital Currency Group of Fraud]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147656</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147656/gemini-lawsuit-accuses-barry-silbert-digital-currency-group-fraud"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T16:25:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gemini Trust Company has sued Digital Currency Group and CEO Barry Silbert for fraud, according to a complaint filed Friday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Calls Motion to Kick Tesla Attorneys Off Dogecoin Lawsuit an 'Insult']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147655</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147655/elon-musk-calls-motion-to-kick-tesla-attorneys-off-dogecoin-lawsuit-an-insult"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T15:37:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk's legal team has said claims they acted inappropriately are "audacious allegations."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Falls to $30,000 Amid Expectations of Fed Rate Hike]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147635</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147635/bitcoin-falls-to-30000-amid-expectations-of-fed-rate-hike"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T12:15:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A preliminary monthly report on the U.S. job sector jolted risk-on sentiments yesterday, as the market prepared for higher interest rates in July.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Champions Ascension: Like 'For Honor' with NFTs?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/gvM9ajww/inside-champions-ascension-like-for-honor-with-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/gvM9ajww/inside-champions-ascension-like-for-honor-with-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T22:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plai Labs Marketing Director Payton Kaleiwahea tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about player response to the combat game Champions Ascension in development, which offers arena combat, raid bosses, AI landscape features, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Activision VP Michael Lee: Gaming Is Crypto's 'Killer App']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/M9ulXrb3/ex-activision-vp-michael-lee-gaming-is-cryptos-killer-app</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/M9ulXrb3/ex-activision-vp-michael-lee-gaming-is-cryptos-killer-app"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Activision Vice President Michael Lee is now the SVP of Growth at Matter Labs. At the 3XP gaming conference, Lee sat down with Decrypt's Kate Irwin to discuss crypto gaming and give his predictions for the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Behind the Scenes with AMGI Studios and My Pet Hooligan]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/eQ71oapI/behind-the-scenes-with-amgi-studios-and-my-pet-hooligan</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/eQ71oapI/behind-the-scenes-with-amgi-studios-and-my-pet-hooligan"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T21:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin goes to Burbank, California for a behind-the-scenes tour of AMGI Studios, the developers of upcoming game My Pet Hooligan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Legend of Arcardia Chose Sui Over EVM Chains]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/H6JSRJIk/why-legend-of-arcardia-chose-sui-over-evm-chains</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/H6JSRJIk/why-legend-of-arcardia-chose-sui-over-evm-chains"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T21:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Legend of Arcadia Executive Producer Andy Lee tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the game and why they switched from EVM to new protocol Sui.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rumble Racing Star Game Preview: Is This Mario Kart With NFTs?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/lXVkuaeq/rumble-racing-star-game-preview-is-this-mario-kart-with-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/lXVkuaeq/rumble-racing-star-game-preview-is-this-mario-kart-with-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T16:47:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin shares a first look at Delabs' upcoming lawn mower racing game Rumble Racing Star, which offers a large cast of quirky characters pulled from the worlds of Bored Ape Yacht Club, Pudgy Penguins, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Laguna Games Turned Down 'Game of Thrones' for Crypto Unicorns]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/IqET3GYs/why-laguna-games-turned-down-game-of-thrones-for-crypto-unicorns</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/IqET3GYs/why-laguna-games-turned-down-game-of-thrones-for-crypto-unicorns"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T21:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin chats with Laguna Games about why the team chose to move away from an offer with WB Games to develop a Game of Thrones licensed title—and made Crypto Unicorns instead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mythical Games CEO John Linden on NFL Rivals Topping 1M Downloads]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/nDhvMd8r/mythical-games-ceo-john-linden-on-nfl-rivals-topping-1m-downloads</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/nDhvMd8r/mythical-games-ceo-john-linden-on-nfl-rivals-topping-1m-downloads"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T23:49:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mythical Games just raised a $37 million Series C1 round on the back of the early success of NFL Rivals, which has already topped a million downloads in two months. Mythical CEO John Linden joins Decrypt's Andrew Hayward to discuss the launch and impact of NFL Rivals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Ava Labs Is Approaching Gaming on Avalanche]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/M4TqVEkK/how-ava-labs-is-approaching-gaming-on-avalanche</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/M4TqVEkK/how-ava-labs-is-approaching-gaming-on-avalanche"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T22:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At 3XP, Ava Labs Head of Gaming Ed Chang sat down with Decrypt's Kate Irwin to discuss some of the biggest Avalanche-based games on the horizon and how the company is approaching and thinking about Web3 gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ogimi Founder David Gull on Why AI Should Be Your Meditation Coach]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DnNqBruk/ogimi-founder-david-gull-on-why-ai-should-be-your-meditation-coach</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DnNqBruk/ogimi-founder-david-gull-on-why-ai-should-be-your-meditation-coach"/>
        <updated>2023-06-25T18:45:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ogimi founder David Gull speaks with Decrypt's Jason Nelson about its AI-driven meditation guides and how the technology can enable a more unique, custom-tailored meditation experience for users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VaynerSports Gaming VP Discusses Web3 Content Creators, Decentralized Streaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/1MvGbnK5/vaynersports-gaming-vp-discusses-web3-content-creators-decentralized-streaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/1MvGbnK5/vaynersports-gaming-vp-discusses-web3-content-creators-decentralized-streaming"/>
        <updated>2023-06-24T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Darren Glover, VP of Gaming at talent management agency VaynerSports, sat down with Decrypt's Kate Irwin at the 3XP expo to discuss the challenges faced by Web3-centric content creators, the current state of the esports market, and how decentralized streaming platforms can challenge centralized leaders like Twitch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NYXL Co-Founder on the State of Esports and Crypto Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/xDHUNFLB/nyxl-co-founder-on-the-state-of-esports-and-crypto-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/xDHUNFLB/nyxl-co-founder-on-the-state-of-esports-and-crypto-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-06-23T22:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rohit Gupta, co-founder of esports team NYXL, chats with Decrypt's Kate Irwin at the 3XP expo to discuss challenges faced by the esports industry and opportunities and experiments in Web3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is GameBridge? Inside Shrapnel's Gaming Innovation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/xqVjzGLr/what-is-gamebridge-inside-shrapnels-gaming-innovation</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/xqVjzGLr/what-is-gamebridge-inside-shrapnels-gaming-innovation"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marc Mercuri, Head of Platform for Web3 shooter Shrapnel, speaks with Decrypt's Kate Irwin at the 3XP expo about GameBridge, a feature that simplifies blockchain item composability and interoperability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gods Unchained Executive Producer Discusses Epic Games Store Move]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/hjLymzUL/gods-unchained-executive-producer-discusses-epic-games-store-move</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/hjLymzUL/gods-unchained-executive-producer-discusses-epic-games-store-move"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daniel Paez, Executive Producer on Immutable X-based card-battler Gods Unchained, discusses the long-running NFT game's launch on the Epic Games Store and the opportunity it provides.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Play-to-Earn Is Not Dead. It Will Never Die' Says Words with Friends Creator Paul Bettner]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/znmOo9vp/play-to-earn-is-not-dead-it-will-never-die-says-words-with-friends-creator-paul-bettner</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/znmOo9vp/play-to-earn-is-not-dead-it-will-never-die-says-words-with-friends-creator-paul-bettner"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T14:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Words With Friends and Wildcard Creator Paul Bettner tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about his perspective on Axie Infinity and Web3 games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cross the Ages Game Review: A Tough But Rewarding Card Battler]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/2PfzFDVY/cross-the-ages-game-review-a-tough-but-rewarding-card-battler</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/2PfzFDVY/cross-the-ages-game-review-a-tough-but-rewarding-card-battler"/>
        <updated>2023-06-18T12:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cross the Ages is a digital collectible card game that challenges players to duel online opponents—and you can even mint your cards as tradable NFTs. It's complex and difficult to grasp at first, but this mobile-first game has some serious strategic upside. GG contributor Ryan Gladwin puts Cross the Ages through its paces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["AI Is Game-Changing But Needs Fact-Checking": AlchemyAI Project Lead]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/HXlThlXv/ai-is-game-changing-but-needs-fact-checking-alchemyai-project-lead</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/HXlThlXv/ai-is-game-changing-but-needs-fact-checking-alchemyai-project-lead"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this interview, Decrypt's Jason Nelson chats with Alchemy product manager and AlchemyAI project lead Elan Halpern on blockchain analysis using ChatGPT, what AI means for better user experience, and the need to fact-check AI. Halpern also gives a demo of the new AlchemyAI ChatGPT plugin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fractal Is Like an Arcade, Says Twitch Co-Founder Justin Kan]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/6r6Mdwt6/fractal-is-like-an-arcade-says-twitch-co-founder-justin-kan</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/6r6Mdwt6/fractal-is-like-an-arcade-says-twitch-co-founder-justin-kan"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Justin Kan was a co-founder of Twitch and now works on Fractal, a Web3 gaming startup. Kan tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about his new company and what he's up to.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are NFTs the Next SEC Target?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/YaGgY87J/are-nfts-the-next-sec-target</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/YaGgY87J/are-nfts-the-next-sec-target"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T20:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin discusses the current regulatory climate in the U.S. with Gala Games' President of Blockchain Jason Brink.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>