<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-10-18T04:23:16.403Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-10-18T04:23:16.403Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC targets Ripple’s XRP sales on exchanges, distributions of XRP to employees in new filing]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20040450/SEC-targets-Ripples-XRP-sales-on-exchanges-distributions-of-XRP-to-employees-in-new-filing</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20040450/SEC-targets-Ripples-XRP-sales-on-exchanges-distributions-of-XRP-to-employees-in-new-filing"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T04:18:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC is appealing the July 2023 ruling that determined Ripple's XRP sales on digital asset platforms, executives' sales, and other distributions of XRP did not constitute investment contracts, according to a new filing shared by attorney James Filan."Whether the district court erroneously...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PayPal’s PYUSD Market Cap Plummets by $400 Billion Amid Yield Declines]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20040440/PayPals-PYUSD-Market-Cap-Plummets-by-400-Billion-Amid-Yield-Declines</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20040440/PayPals-PYUSD-Market-Cap-Plummets-by-400-Billion-Amid-Yield-Declines"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T04:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PayPal’s stablecoin, PYUSD, has experienced a dramatic decline in market capitalization over the past six weeks, going from over $1 billion to around $610 billion at the time of writing. Once a top four stablecoin, PYUSD’s value has plummeted from its August peak, suggesting a significant loss...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Price Set To Resume Upside: Is Momentum Building?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20040432/XRP-Price-Set-To-Resume-Upside-Is-Momentum-Building</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20040432/XRP-Price-Set-To-Resume-Upside-Is-Momentum-Building"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T04:08:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XRP price is holding gains above the $0.5450 zone. The price seems to be eyeing more gains above the $0.5550 and $0.5650 levels in the near term. XRP price is consolidating above the $0.5400 zone. The price is now trading above $0.5420 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. There is a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nansen Integrates With Solana To Offer Advanced Token And Wallet Trading Tools]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e744654716e</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/nansen-integrates-with-solana-to-offer-advanced-token-and-wallet-trading-tools/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T04:07:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nansen revealed its new blockchain analytics platform for Solana. The integration aims to provide Web3 investors with the network’s detailed on-chain data and offer better tools for blockchain analytics.
 
 
Nansen Launches New Platform
 
On Thursday, blockchain analytics firm Nansen announced the launch of its new platform for Solana. The platform is set to offer “advanced tools” to monitor token balances, track wallet movements, and analyze Solana’s Decentralized Finance (DeFi) and Non-Fungible Token (NFT) ecosystem.
 
According to the announcement, the new platform seeks to provide “actionable insights across Solana’s Blockchain” by addressing the Web3 analytics sector’s gaps, aiming to provide better tools for the network and fill the breach that makes real-time balance tracking and fo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rubmar Garcia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin Rebrands as “World” and Launches World Chain]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20040439/Worldcoin-Rebrands-as-World-and-Launches-World-Chain</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20040439/Worldcoin-Rebrands-as-World-and-Launches-World-Chain"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T04:06:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin (WLD), a digital identity project that utilizes iris scanning, has announced its rebranding to “World.” This change is part of a broader trend, as many projects have recently undergone rebranding for various reasons. World Continues Its Development Amid Controversy At a recent event...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Venmo US Users Now Support Crypto Purchases Through MoonPay]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20040268/Venmo-US-Users-Now-Support-Crypto-Purchases-Through-MoonPay</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20040268/Venmo-US-Users-Now-Support-Crypto-Purchases-Through-MoonPay"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T03:59:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With MoonPay integration, 60 million Venmo US users can now purchase cryptocurrencies directly using their balance, bank transfers, or debit cards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pierre Ferragu Notes The Disconnect Between Media And Crypto-Based Polymarket On Trump-Harris Election Outcome: 'I Love The Dissonance']]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20040430/Pierre-Ferragu-Notes-The-Disconnect-Between-Media-And-Crypto-Based-Polymarket-On-Trump-Harris-Election-Outcome-I-Love-The-Dissonance</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20040430/Pierre-Ferragu-Notes-The-Disconnect-Between-Media-And-Crypto-Based-Polymarket-On-Trump-Harris-Election-Outcome-I-Love-The-Dissonance"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T03:54:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pierre Ferragu, an analyst at New Street Research, recently expressed his views on the disconnect between prediction markets and the press regarding the 2024 U.S. presidential elections read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP is back above $0.55 with uncertainty over SEC appeal in lawsuit against Ripple]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20040265/XRP-is-back-above-055-with-uncertainty-over-SEC-appeal-in-lawsuit-against-Ripple</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20040265/XRP-is-back-above-055-with-uncertainty-over-SEC-appeal-in-lawsuit-against-Ripple"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T03:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple (XRP) gains on Thursday as traders digest the uncertainty in the Securities & Exchange Commission’s (SEC) appeal in the lawsuit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Power of Stablecoins – Boosting E-Commerce Payments and Opening Doors for Retailers in Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20040248/The-Power-of-Stablecoins-Boosting-E-Commerce-Payments-and-Opening-Doors-for-Retailers-in-Crypto</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20040248/The-Power-of-Stablecoins-Boosting-E-Commerce-Payments-and-Opening-Doors-for-Retailers-in-Crypto"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T03:40:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoins are already becoming a mainstream digital tool for everyday use. Now, both companies and regular users utilize them for payments. In Singapore, for example, the stablecoin payment value reached $1 billion a few weeks ago, once again proving that they are becoming a key solution for...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Bitcoin Whale Wallets Surge Amid Growing Investor Confidence]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20040249/New-Bitcoin-Whale-Wallets-Surge-Amid-Growing-Investor-Confidence</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20040249/New-Bitcoin-Whale-Wallets-Surge-Amid-Growing-Investor-Confidence"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T03:39:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Investor confidence in Bitcoin is rising, as shown by a surge in new whale wallets and increased active addresses, signaling potential market growth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paypal Expands Crypto Reach: 60 Million Venmo Users Now Linked to Moonpay]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7446571c3f</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/paypal-expands-crypto-reach-60-million-venmo-users-now-linked-to-moonpay/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T03:38:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Venmo’s 60 million users can now fund transactions on the Moonpay platform, thanks to a new integration announced by Paypal. U.S. users can use Venmo balances, linked bank accounts, or cards to buy and sell cryptocurrencies through Moonpay, expanding payment flexibility. However, this option is unavailable in New York and Texas, continuing Paypal’s push into […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CFTC says court ‘erred at every turn’ in allowing Kalshi’s election markets]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20040240/CFTC-says-court-erred-at-every-turn-in-allowing-Kalshis-election-markets</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20040240/CFTC-says-court-erred-at-every-turn-in-allowing-Kalshis-election-markets"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T03:32:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CFTC says a federal court judge “mistakenly erred” when it allowed betting market Kalshi to list event contracts for the 2024 US elections.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Graph Price Prediction 2024, 2025 – 2030: Will GRT Price Rally To $1?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20040453/The-Graph-Price-Prediction-2024-2025-2030-Will-GRT-Price-Rally-To-1</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20040453/The-Graph-Price-Prediction-2024-2025-2030-Will-GRT-Price-Rally-To-1"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T03:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Story Highlights The live price of The Graph crypto is . The Graph price is expected to go as high as $0.58 by the end of 2024. GRT price with a potential surge could reach a maximum of $1.286 by the end of 2030. After an impressive 233% annual return in 2023, GRT maintains its …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple News : SEC Appeals XRP Lawsuit Close to Deadline!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20040216/Ripple-News-SEC-Appeals-XRP-Lawsuit-Close-to-Deadline</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20040216/Ripple-News-SEC-Appeals-XRP-Lawsuit-Close-to-Deadline"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T03:23:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission has submitted Form-C with detailed appeal on October 17. Social media was filled with speculations if the SEC has missed the deadline. We unveiled in yesterday’s news that it was not the case. As the appeal is now officially submitted, what does it...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Muted, Dogecoin Rallies As Market Maintains 'Greed' Sentiment: Analyst Predicts New Peak For King Crypto As US Elections And Potential Fed Rate Cut Looms]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20040242/Bitcoin-Ethereum-Muted-Dogecoin-Rallies-As-Market-Maintains-Greed-Sentiment-Analyst-Predicts-New-Peak-For-King-Crypto-As-US-Elections-And-Potential-Fed-Rate-Cut-Looms</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20040242/Bitcoin-Ethereum-Muted-Dogecoin-Rallies-As-Market-Maintains-Greed-Sentiment-Analyst-Predicts-New-Peak-For-King-Crypto-As-US-Elections-And-Potential-Fed-Rate-Cut-Looms"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T03:18:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin and Ethereum continued trading flat even as equities notched fresh record highs. However, Dogecoin moved higher on Thursday. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US has 26M strong ‘crypto voting bloc’ ahead of elections — Survey]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20040212/US-has-26M-strong-crypto-voting-bloc-ahead-of-elections-Survey</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20040212/US-has-26M-strong-crypto-voting-bloc-ahead-of-elections-Survey"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T03:17:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One in seven, or 16%, of respondents in a survey by The Digital Chamber said they'd vote for the most pro-crypto candidate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Touts 'DOGE' Agency While Endorsing Trump During Pennsylvania Town Hall — Dogecoin Goes Soaring Over 8%]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20040219/Elon-Musk-Touts-DOGE-Agency-While-Endorsing-Trump-During-Pennsylvania-Town-Hall-Dogecoin-Goes-Soaring-Over-8</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20040219/Elon-Musk-Touts-DOGE-Agency-While-Endorsing-Trump-During-Pennsylvania-Town-Hall-Dogecoin-Goes-Soaring-Over-8"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T03:10:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk, CEO of Tesla Inc. and owner of social media platform X, threw his support behind former President Donald Trump during a campaign town hall on Thursday while floating the idea of a new government agency named after a cryptocurrency meme. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global Adoption Of Stablecoins Leaves US In The Dust—Report]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7446523578</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/global-adoption-of-stablecoins-leaves-us-in-the-dust-report/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T03:05:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US-based consumers’ adoption of stablecoins is facing a slowdown in 2024 even when there is increasing activity in Bitcoin that rose in popularity following the launch of the spot Bitcoin exchange-traded funds.
 
 
The graph below shows a decline in transactions by US-regulated platforms in just under a year. This can be attributed to the growing problem of US-based stablecoins in terms of regulation and adoption within the country.
 
This indicates that the stablecoins of emerging markets with bases outside the US are experiencing higher implementation. As stablecoins see increased use globally, this type of digital asset is being used to carry value and conduct cheap transactions in every nook and corner of the world.
 

 
 
Global Demand For US Dollar-Backed Assets
 
As countries ai…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tron Revenue Up 170% In 1 Year, TRX To Print New All-Time Highs?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7446523575</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/tron-revenue-up-trx-to-print-new-all-time-highs/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T03:05:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tron is already one of the top performers in the top 10, looking at its impressive growth over the last ten months. The smart contracts platform dominates USDT transfers while also making inroads into meme coins and snapping market share from Solana.
 
Tron Revenue Up 170% Year-On-Year
 
Recent data shows that the resurgence of Tron and its emergence as a leader in USDT transfers, even surpassing Ethereum and its broad ecosystem, has pushed revenue by 170% in the past year alone.
 
 
According to Lookonchain data, the network’s revenue rose to $7.28 million as of mid-October, expanding from $2.69 million registered over the same time last year.
 
 
Like Ethereum and other public ledgers, Tron relies on the 27 Super Validators to process transactions and secure the network. Every transactio…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dalmas Ngetich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Final Verdict on Do Kwon Extradition to Be Released This Weekend]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20040196/Final-Verdict-on-Do-Kwon-Extradition-to-Be-Released-This-Weekend</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20040196/Final-Verdict-on-Do-Kwon-Extradition-to-Be-Released-This-Weekend"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T03:04:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Montenegro’s Minister of Justice, Bojan Božović, announced that a decision on Do Kwon extradition will be finalized and signed by the end of the week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin: 2 factors that can propel BTC beyond $67K]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20040114/Bitcoin-2-factors-that-can-propel-BTC-beyond-67K</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20040114/Bitcoin-2-factors-that-can-propel-BTC-beyond-67K"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T03:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Spot ETF cost an average of $57K which is crucial for current bull rally.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Positioned for More Upside: Can It Keep Climbing?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20040060/Bitcoin-Price-Positioned-for-More-Upside-Can-It-Keep-Climbing</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20040060/Bitcoin-Price-Positioned-for-More-Upside-Can-It-Keep-Climbing"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T02:44:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin price holding gains above the $67,000 resistance zone. BTC is now consolidating and aiming for more gains above the $68,350 resistance. Bitcoin remained stable and extended gains above the $67,500 zone. The price is trading above $67,400 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There is...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Goes Mainstream: Blackrock Boosts North America’s $1.3T Inflows]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74465c9b46</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/crypto-goes-mainstream-blackrock-boosts-north-americas-1-3t-inflows/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T02:37:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency is increasingly integrated into the mainstream as North America continues to lead the global crypto market, receiving $1.3 trillion in onchain value between July 2023 and June 2024, according to Chainalysis. Institutional giants like Goldman Sachs and Blackrock are now taking serious positions in the crypto space, with U.S. bitcoin exchange-traded products (ETPs) driving […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morgan Stanley Bitcoin ETF Holdings Reached $272 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20040046/Morgan-Stanley-Bitcoin-ETF-Holdings-Reached-272-Million</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20040046/Morgan-Stanley-Bitcoin-ETF-Holdings-Reached-272-Million"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T02:34:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Morgan Stanley Bitcoin ETF holdings have reached $272.1 million, representing 0.02% of its $1.2 trillion in assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Files Last-Minute Appeal in Ripple Case—Why the XRP Army is Outraged]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287069</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287069/sec-files-last-minute-appeal-in-ripple-case-why-xrp-army-outraged"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T02:15:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While the SEC isn't contesting the ruling that XRP sales to retail investors aren't securities, it is instead focusing on other key aspects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Sinclair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Files Last-Minute Appeal in Ripple Case—Why the XRP Army is Outraged]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20040024/SEC-Files-Last-Minute-Appeal-in-Ripple-CaseWhy-the-XRP-Army-is-Outraged</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20040024/SEC-Files-Last-Minute-Appeal-in-Ripple-CaseWhy-the-XRP-Army-is-Outraged"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T02:15:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While the SEC isn't contesting the ruling that XRP sales to retail investors aren't securities, it is instead focusing on other key aspects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JPMorgan: We Are Bullish on Digital Assets Into 2025]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e744659c52f</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/jpmorgan-we-are-bullish-on-digital-assets-into-2025/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T01:38:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Global investment bank JPMorgan is bullish on cryptocurrency into 2025, driven by regulatory shifts and geopolitical tensions. Analysts suggest a Donald Trump re-election as the U.S. president could propel BTC higher, reinforcing the “debasement trade” as investors seek refuge in digital assets. With major liquidations behind and institutional support increasing, JPMorgan sees strong momentum for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Price To $10: Similar Patterns That Led To Previous Parabolic Breakout Have Reappeared]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e744645041b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-price-to-10-breakout/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T01:01:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Dogecoin price is once again gearing up for a significant move to the upside. In a recent price analysis of current price movement and previous price action, an analyst suggested Dogecoin is on track to repeat another parabolic run, potentially sending its price skyrocketing to $10.
 
Dogecoin Price Exhibiting Parabolic Pattern
 
Recent Dogecoin price movements have put the meme coin back in the spotlight, with a noticeable breakout over the past few days. The meme coin’s price increased to hit $0.129, its highest price point so far in October. This rally has allowed Dogecoin to outpace many other large market cap cryptocurrencies in both daily and weekly performance.
 
 
According to a price analysis posted on social media platform X, Dima James Potts noted that this recent breakout r…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Is Today’s 'Major' Telegram Game Puzzle Durov Combo]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286896</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/here-is-todays-major-telegram-puzzle-durov-combo"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T00:43:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking to complete Major’s daily Pavel Durov puzzle on Telegram? Here’s the solution for Thursday, October 17.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arthur Hayes Predicts Bitcoin Boom Amid Middle East Tensions and Inflation]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e744646d24e</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/arthur-hayes-predicts-bitcoin-boom-amid-middle-east-tensions-and-inflation/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T00:38:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Bitmex CEO Arthur Hayes sees a bitcoin bull market on the horizon, driven by soaring energy prices and rampant inflation as Middle East tensions escalate. He argues that rising costs will send BTC’s value surging in fiat terms, with newly printed dollars flooding the market. But while bitcoin’s future looks bright, Hayes warns investors […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Surge In Bitcoin Activity: Whales Transactions Hit New Highs, Is A Bull Run Brewing?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e744647992e</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-whales-transactions-hit-new-highs/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T00:30:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin is witnessing a surge in network activity as large investor transactions, also known as whales, have skyrocketed significantly to new highs in light of recent broader market confidence. In comparison to the trading volume in the past few days, the growth is notable as the crypto asset’s price has started to recover from its lows.
 
Bitcoin Whales Transactions At A Record Level
 
According to market intelligence and on-chain data platform, Santiment, Bitcoin whale transactions have increased sharply in the last day to new highs, suggesting a rise in activity from large holders. Specifically, the surge marks its highest level in over 10 weeks.
 
 
Data from Santiment reported that the network saw about 11,697 whale transactions exceeding $100,000, a level not seen since Japan’s stock…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Godspower Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Officially Appeals XRP Ruling — Will the Court Reverse Ripple’s Win?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7446434cd3</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/sec-officially-appeals-xrp-ruling-will-the-court-reverse-ripples-win/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T23:47:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has officially appealed the XRP ruling by Judge Analisa Torres, reigniting the legal battle over whether XRP sales on crypto exchanges qualify as securities. The regulator challenges key aspects of the court decision, including rulings that cleared Ripple executives and non-cash XRP distributions. The outcome could have a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin Rebrands as World, Launches New Eyeball Scanning Orb]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287051</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287051/worldcoin-rebrands-as-world-launches-new-retina-scanning-orb"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T23:30:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[World's redesigned Orb has 30% fewer parts and triple the production capacity of its predecessor, powered by NVIDIA’s Jetson.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu DAO And Foundation Are ‘Coming Soon’: What To Expect]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74464d00ab</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-dao-foundation-coming-soon/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T23:28:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu is on the cusp of a significant transformation. Lucie (@LucieSHIB), the marketing lead for Shiba Inu, announced via X on October 17 that the Shiba Inu Decentralized Autonomous Organization (DAO) and the Shib Doggy DAO Foundation are “coming soon,” signaling a pivotal shift toward decentralization and community governance.
 
“The time is almost here. As we approach the 2024/2025 launch, the Shib ecosystem is on the verge of a transformative shift that will put power into the hands of real holders,” Lucie stated. She emphasized that the upcoming DAO and Foundation are designed to exclude “trolls” and “FUD-spreaders” who do not hold tokens but may attempt to influence the project’s direction negatively.
 
Why A Shiba Inu DAO And Foundation?
 
The Shib Doggy DAO Foundation aims to le…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Team Postpones ShibaCon Conference With Less Than A Month To Go, What Happened?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74464d00a9</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-shibacon-conference/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T23:28:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To the surprise of various community members, the Shiba Inu team has announced the postponement of the highly anticipated ShibaCon conference. Originally, scheduled to take place on November 9, the Shiba Inu team has decided to reschedule the ShibaCon conference till further notice, leaving many in the community wondering what prompted the sudden change. 
 
ShibaCon Conference Delayed
 
On October 14, the Shiba Inu team released a statement via its official SHIB social media account on X (formerly Twitter). According to the team, the ShibaCon conference, which was scheduled to take place in Bangkok, Thailand, four days after the US Presidential elections on November 5, has been indefinitely postponed. 
 
 
The news which was dropped just three weeks before the conference has left many in t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Researchers Hacked AI Robots Into Breaking Traffic Laws—And Worse]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286994</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286994/how-researchers-hacked-ai-robots-into-breaking-traffic-laws-and-worse"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T23:14:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers showed vulnerabilities in AI-powered robots being exploited to perform dangerous tasks, including detonating bombs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Adoption Reaches Critical Low in El Salvador Despite Government Push]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74464f374e</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-adoption-reaches-critical-low-in-el-salvador-despite-government-push/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T23:05:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new survey has found that bitcoin usage has dropped to critical levels in El Salvador, with less than 10% of its citizens using it to make transactions. The numbers are surprising to analysts, given the push that President Nayib Bukele has made for bitcoin in the country since its adoption as legal tender in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Worldcoin Built an Ethereum Network Specifically for Humans]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286983</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286983/world-chain-launches-mainnet-world-coin"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T22:34:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[World, previously called Worldcoin, has debuted an Ethereum layer-2 chain with an aim to onboard real humans—not bots.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Napolitano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken Unveils a New Wrapped Bitcoin Product—Here’s What It Means for Defi]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7446341cef</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/kraken-unveils-a-new-wrapped-bitcoin-product-heres-what-it-means-for-defi/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T22:17:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken has launched KBTC, a wrapped bitcoin product fully backed 1:1 by bitcoin and compatible with multiple networks. KBTC aims to expand bitcoin’s use beyond its native chain and into decentralized finance (defi) ecosystems. Kraken Introduces KBTC to Enhance Bitcoin’s Utility Across Networks Kraken’s KBTC is an ERC20 token that allows bitcoin (BTC) to interact […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Bulls Have Reason to Worry If L2s Remain Dominant, Says VanEck Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286970</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286970/ethereum-price-target-plunge-vaneck-analyst"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T22:16:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum's "changing fundamentals" and growing embrace of layer-2 networks could massively impact ETH's future price, a VanEck analyst said Thursday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk-Themed ‘X Empire’ Ends Telegram Gameplay Ahead of Airdrop]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286977</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286977/x-empire-ends-telegram-gameplay-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T21:12:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tap-to-earn game X Empire is gearing up for next week’s X token launch and airdrop on The Open Network (TON).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Big Role Ethena’s USDE Could Play in Hyperliquid’s Upcoming Mainnet]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e744633a81c</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/the-big-role-ethenas-usde-could-play-in-hyperliquids-upcoming-mainnet/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T21:06:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethena has proposed integrating its liquidity and hedging engine into Hyperliquid, a layer one (L1) blockchain set to launch its EVM mainnet. The proposal includes adding USDE, Ethena’s stablecoin, within the Hyperliquid ecosystem upon mainnet launch. Ethena Eyes Hyperliquid’s Rapid Growth for Next Phase of USDE Expansion The proposal outlines a cautious approach to integrating […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USDT Popularity Soars As Tether Adds Over 36 Million Users in Q3 2024]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74463c4588</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/usdt-popularity-up-as-tether-adds-36m-users-in-q3/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T21:01:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tether’s USDT, the largest crypto stablecoin, recently celebrated its 10th year in the industry. The company’s growth has been impressive, thanks to its steady user base, holdings that include $97 billion in US government bonds, and its plans to partner with US law enforcement agencies to strengthen its brand.
 
 
Now, the team behind Tether can find another reason to celebrate: data suggest that Tether’s USDT user growth recorded its best quarter in Q3 by adding 36.25 million new users. The company added that its quarterly user data has increased by 9% on average over the last 12 months, giving it enough cushion as it expands its use cases and applications.
 
 
On-Chain Tether USDT Users Drive Growth
 
In a post at Tether.io, the company boasts of an increasing adoption of its stablecoin,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Targets 100,000 TPS On L1 And L2 With Buterin’s ‘The Surge’ Plan]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74463c4587</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-100000-tps-l1-l2-buterin-the-surge/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T21:01:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a new blog post titled “Possible futures for the Ethereum protocol, part 2: The Surge,” Ethereum co-founder Vitalik Buterin outlined an ambitious roadmap aiming to scale Ethereum’s transaction processing capacity to over 100,000 transactions per second (TPS) across Layer 1 (L1) and Layer 2 (L2) solutions. This initiative, known as “The Surge,” seeks to enhance scalability while preserving decentralization and security.
 
Buterin began by reflecting on Ethereum’s initial scaling strategies, which involved sharding and Layer 2 protocols like state channels and Plasma. At the beginning, Ethereum had two scaling strategies in its roadmap, he wrote, pointing to a 2015 paper that discussed sharding—a method where each node only needs to verify and store a fraction of the transactions. This ap…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PayPal's Venmo Can Now Be Used to Buy Bitcoin and Ethereum via MoonPay]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286969</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286969/paypal-venmo-buy-crypto-moonpay"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T20:52:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PayPal's Venmo can now be used by U.S. customers to top up and make crypto purchases on MoonPay, according to a Thursday announcement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QCP Capital Reports Bitcoin Lifted by Spot Demand—What Analysts Are Watching Next]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7446399047</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/qcp-capital-reports-bitcoin-lifted-by-spot-demand-what-analysts-are-watching-next/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T20:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) enjoyed a 2.20% boost driven by rising spot demand, briefly touching $68,000 before settling at $67,000, according to Singapore-based digital asset trading firm QCP Capital. The firm highlighted strong options activity and inflows into exchange-traded funds (ETFs), with analysts pointing to a growing wave of optimism in the market. Bitcoin Inches Toward Record […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Venture Investment Falls 20% in Q3, AI Startups Defy Trend]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74463986ab</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com/cryptocurrency/crypto-venture-investment-falls-20-in-q3-ai-startups-defy-trend/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T20:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Venture capital investment in the crypto sector declined in the third quarter of 2024, following a persistent  
downtrend that began earlier this year. However, while overall numbers were  
down, early-stage startups in AI and blockchain infrastructure obtained most of the investments.
According to a report by Galaxy, the total venture capital investment in crypto  
and blockchain-focused startups reached $2.4 billion in Q3 2024, a 20% decline  
from the previous quarter. Similarly, the number of deals fell by 17%,  
with 478 deals completed.
Venture Capital Investments
This dip in activity is partly due to the ongoing  
sluggishness in the broader crypto market, which has been stuck in a  
"barbell" situation, Bitcoin on one end and meme coins on the other,  
but little interest from inst…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Staked Ether Is Creating a Benchmark for the Crypto Economy, Says ARK Invest]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e744620c5ab</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/10/17/staked-ether-is-creating-a-benchmark-for-the-crypto-economy-says-ark-invest/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T19:15:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The growing use of stETH in DeFi protocols means the asset is slowly taking the role of the fed funds rate in the crypto ecosystem, says ARK Invest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Carreras</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETFs Race Past $20 Billion Milestone in Just 10 Months]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286948</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286948/bitcoin-etf-20-billion-milestone-inflows-blackrock"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T19:06:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Approved in January, Bitcoin exchange-traded funds have experienced trading activity like no other ETF product.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Galaxis Teams Up With TV Show ‘Killer Whales’ to ‘Empower Creators’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285090</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285090/galaxis-teams-up-with-tv-show-killer-whales-to-empower-creators"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T19:05:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The partnership will see Galaxis showcased throughout the reality show, as well as “actively supporting” the Web3 projects featured.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wrapped Bitcoin Wars Ramp Up as Kraken Reveals kBTC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286934</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286934/wrapped-bitcoin-wars-kraken-kbtc"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T17:58:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto exchange Kraken has unveiled a new wrapped Bitcoin product dubbed kBTC, joining a growing battle with Coinbase, 21.co, and BitGo.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Presidential Election Tops $2 Billion in Betting Volume on Polymarket]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286923</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286923/us-presidential-election-2-billion-volume-polymarket"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T17:46:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trump is currently leading the Polymarket betting pool on the winner of the U.S. election, which has topped $2 billion in total volume.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Napolitano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Majors Fall 1 to 2%, A New Tiger takes to the Charts, Van Eck teases Big Web3 Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/a6Tm7OGW/majors-fall-1-to-2-a-new-tiger-takes-to-the-charts-van-eck-teases-big-web3-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/a6Tm7OGW/majors-fall-1-to-2-a-new-tiger-takes-to-the-charts-van-eck-teases-big-web3-gaming"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T17:42:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lucky GOAT memecoin trader turned $5,000 into $1.5M during GOAT's run to $300M. A new memecoin based on Disney Park's new baby tiger "Bakso" was a top mover on Wednesday, running to $10M (now $6M). Crypto majors fall 1-2%, memes red across board. a16z calls 2024 crypto's biggest year yet in "State of Crypto" report. Vitalik publishes part 2 of blog outlining ETH's future. Van Eck teases big bet on Parallel and web3 gaming. Huge day for digital art with 4 marquee mints seeing success.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Gnosis Pay Isn’t Just Another Crypto Card]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=283801</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/283801/why-gnosis-pay-isnt-just-another-crypto-card"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T17:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The self-custodial crypto debit card is a step towards ‘banking 3.0,’ combining legacy payments infrastructure with Web3 innovation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meme Coins Blast Past Bitcoin Gains as Crypto Market Gets Frothy Again]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286859</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286859/meme-coins-blast-past-bitcoin-gains"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T16:52:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's been a good week for Bitcoin—but meme coins like TURBO and BRETT are really riding the "Uptober" rocket ship to the moon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FBI Arrests Suspect in SEC Twitter Hack That Pumped Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286910</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286910/fbi-arrest-sec-twitter-hack-bitcoin-etfs"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T15:53:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Remember when the SEC's Twitter account was hacked to prematurely share that Bitcoin ETFs were approved? The FBI has arrested a suspect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward,Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Is Today’s 'Captain Tsubasa: Rivals' Telegram Game Daily Combo]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=250928</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/captain-tsubasa-rivals-telegram-game-daily-combo"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T14:30:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anime soccer game Captain Tsubasa: Rivals gives out 5 million free daily balls ahead of the TON token airdrop. Here’s the combo for Thursday, October 17.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FLOKI’s Valhalla Welcomes Hafthor Björnsson, "The Mountain" from Game of Thrones, as Official Ambassador]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286885</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286885/flokis-valhalla-welcomes-hafthor-bjornsson-the-mountain-from-game-of-thrones-as-official-ambassador"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T14:27:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Miami, Florida, 17th October 2024, GamingWire]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GamingWire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Are Today’s ‘X Empire’ Elon Musk Game Daily Combo and Rebus Solution]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241078</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/todays-musk-empire-stock-exchange-daily-combo"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T14:25:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking for the X Empire daily combo and rebus solution for Thursday, October 17? Here are the latest boosts for the Telegram game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Game 'Moonray' Coming to PS5—Without Crypto Features]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286878</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286878/ethereum-game-moonray-ps5-console"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T14:01:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Moonray will expand from PC to PlayStation 5 in 2025, but the PS5 version of the Ethereum-based game won't launch with crypto features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Exchange Reserves Reach a 2-Year Low, But Analysts Disagree on Why]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286858</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286858/bitcoin-exchange-reserves-2-year-low"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T13:05:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Low Bitcoin exchange reserves is good, right? "The common interpretation of this trend needs a more nuanced approach," a Hyblock exec said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hamster Kombat Season 2 Teaser]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/qcvjjJxN/hamster-kombat-season-2-teaser</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/qcvjjJxN/hamster-kombat-season-2-teaser"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T12:03:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here's a first look at Season 2 of Telegram tap-to-earn game Hamster Kombat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WazirX to List Its 240,000 Wallets and Balances as Part of Debt Restructuring]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286841</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286841/wazirx-240000-wallet-addresses-debt-restructuring"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T12:02:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Transparency starts with showing you everything, even if that means sharing what might seem like overwhelming data,” WazirX noted.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vismaya V</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Beat Up Old Honda Just Hit Every Crypto Hot Spot in Europe—Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286679</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286679/meme-machine-honda-crypto-europe"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T12:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A banged up Honda Civic called The Meme Machine traveled across Europe this summer, becoming emblematic of crypto in 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Hamster Kombat’ Telegram Game Overhaul Revealed for Season 2]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286808</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286808/hamster-kombat-season-2-developing-games"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T12:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a very meta shift, the next season of Telegram game Hamster Kombat will be all about developing and publishing games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Is Today’s 'Tomarket' Telegram Game Daily Combo]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286780</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/here-is-todays-tomarket-telegram-game-daily-combo"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T11:40:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram game Tomarket is handing out free tomatoes and bonus items ahead of the airdrop. Here’s the combo for Thursday, October 17.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Market Dominance Reaches 3-Year High—What's That Mean?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286838</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286838/bitcoin-market-dominance-3-year-high"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T11:38:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“The price is climbing toward the midpoint of this range, but it has not yet established a decisive breakout," one analyst told Decrypt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Price Charts Return to Google Search]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286836</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286836/bitcoin-ethereum-price-charts-return-to-google-search"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T09:50:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The search giant explained that it had temporarily removed some crypto price charts due to “inaccurate data.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitfinex Hacker Deserves 5-Year Sentence for Laundering $8 Billion in Stolen Bitcoin: DOJ]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286829</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286829/bitfinex-hacker-ilya-lichtenstein-5-year-sentence"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T09:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The DOJ recommendations on sentencing are the preamble to the judge’s final ruling. The pair are due to be sentenced in November.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin Lays Out Grand Vision for Ethereum Layer-2s With ‘The Surge’ Roadmap]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286826</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286826/vitalik-buterin-lays-out-grand-vision-ethereum-layer-2s-the-surge-roadmap"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T06:09:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While Buterin didn’t give an exact date for when The Surge would be fully implemented, he did call for sustained progress for Ethereum.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vismaya V</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Euroclear Enters Asia with Stake in Singapore’s Blockchain Infrastructure Firm Marketnode]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286823</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286823/euroclear-enters-asia-stake-singapores-blockchain-infrastructure-firm-marketnode"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T05:34:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Euroclear has made its first Asian investment, acquiring a stake in blockchain-focused Marketnode, backed by Temasek, SGX Group, and HSBC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Sinclair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Set to Rise Beyond $70,000 in 'Coming Weeks,' Experts Say]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286814</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286814/bitcoin-rise-beyond-70000-coming-weeks-experts-say"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T04:45:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin's upward momentum remains robust, with market experts forecasting a rise beyond its March all-time high.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood Targets Seasoned Traders With Bitcoin Futures, New Desktop Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286802</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286802/robinhood-targets-seasoned-traders-with-bitcoin-futures-new-desktop-platform"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T00:04:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood told Decrypt on Wednesday its futures offerings via its trading app is expected in the “coming months.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Sinclair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miners Gain Record Hash Rate as JP Morgan Gives Nod to Sector Ahead of US Election]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286786</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286786/bitcoin-miners-gain-record-hash-rate-jp-morgan-gives-nod-sector-us-election"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T23:07:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The combined hash rate of U.S.-publicly listed bitcoin miners now accounts for a record 28.9% of the network, J.P. Morgan said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Meta Is Helping AI Models 'Think' Clearly Before Answering]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286731</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286731/meta-helping-ai-models-think"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T22:12:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meta researchers introduced TPO, a technique that teaches an AI model to essentially "think" about an answer before responding.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Weather Agency Turns to AI for More Accurate and Faster Hurricane Forecasts]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286788</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286788/us-weather-agency-turns-to-ai-for-more-accurate-and-faster-hurricane-forecasts"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T22:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The agency, which has been utilizing machine learning for years, is now leaning heavily on neural networks to boost prediction accuracy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Hits Miami, But XRP Army Appears MIA]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286730</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286730/ripple-miami-xrp-army"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T21:22:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Labs’ eighth annual Ripple Swell event featured panels and accoutrements intended for a white-collar crowd.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BTC hits $68K, Trump odds Continue to Rise, GOAT nears $300M]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/c88qN8eB/btc-hits-68k-trump-odds-continue-to-rise-goat-nears-300m</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/c88qN8eB/btc-hits-68k-trump-odds-continue-to-rise-goat-nears-300m"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T18:31:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC hits $68k as ETF inflows continue to soar. Open Interest at CME hits ATH, funding still low. Tesla moves $750m BTC to new wallet. Canary applies for Litcoin ETF, LTC up 8%. Grayscale asks SEC to convert altcoin fund to ETF. Kraken integrates with EigenLayer for restaking. ‘Network state’ Praxis raises $525m for new city. Trump project raises only $11m so far. a16z founders donate $2.5m to Trump PAC. TikTok accused of being crypto exchange in UK. Gotbit CEO arrested in Portugal. Perplexity AI launches finance platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ETF Inflows Soar, Kamala Courts Crypto, TURBO Nears $1BN!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zn2lboMV/etf-inflows-soar-kamala-courts-crypto-turbo-nears-1bn</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zn2lboMV/etf-inflows-soar-kamala-courts-crypto-turbo-nears-1bn"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T18:22:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETFs see $800m inflows in 2-days, huge volume. ETF inflows may be linked to Trump odds: CoinShares. Bitcoin will rival housing market as asset class: Fink. Vitalik proposes drop to 1ETH to become validator. Kamala reveals pro-crypto policies. Kamala mocked for linking crypto to race. Hyperliquid announces HYPE token coming. PUFFER airdrop claim goes live. Tether considering lending to commodities trader. Man takes $500m lost Bitcoin case to court. Google removes crypto prices from search. SUI Foundation denies $400m insider selling. UAE approves $AED stablecoin. Bitget wallet now only behind Binance for downloads.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BTC hits 2-week High, China Stocks Rally again, GOAT hits $120M]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/0V0rYhMX/btc-hits-2-week-high-china-stocks-rally-again-goat-hits-120m</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/0V0rYhMX/btc-hits-2-week-high-china-stocks-rally-again-goat-hits-120m"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T14:09:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC hits 2-week high as China stocks rise. SUI breaks into the top 15 coins. $1.3bn ETH might be sold from PlusToken scam. S. Korea may approve BTC & ETH ETFs this month. Australia launches first ETH ETF. Samara to buy BTC with $33m bond. Altcoins to see $500m unlocks this week. Vitalik writes blog on the future of ETH. Grayscale reveals 35 altcoins considered for funds. Ethena proposes SOL for USDe collateral. Only one Binance launchpad coin up this year. AVAX summit begins this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Falls Ahead of CPI, Stripe Reinstates Crypto, Fed Charges Market-makers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/aYgFvZqj/crypto-falls-ahead-of-cpi-stripe-reinstates-crypto-fed-charges-market-makers</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/aYgFvZqj/crypto-falls-ahead-of-cpi-stripe-reinstates-crypto-fed-charges-market-makers"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T07:29:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Majors drop despite stocks hitting ATHs. Stripe reinstates crypto payments. Crypto settlements near $20bn in 2024. S. Korea to review ban on BTC ETFs. US charges market makers for market manipulation. FBI created their own coin to ensnare targets. Vitalik ‘outside pick’ for Nobel Prize. Trump family token to built on Aave stack. $16m OP tokens allocated to superchain users. Wisdomtree debuts debit card for on-chain fund. 47% of hedge funds have crypto exposure. Argentina overtakes Brazil for crypto inflows. Tucker interviews Ryan Salame over FTX.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Todd ‘revealed’ as Satoshi, Google may be Broken-up, Murad’s Wallets Doxxed]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pLw8b2d2/todd-revealed-as-satoshi-google-may-be-broken-up-murads-wallets-doxxed</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pLw8b2d2/todd-revealed-as-satoshi-google-may-be-broken-up-murads-wallets-doxxed"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T07:29:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC will be range bound until election: Bernstein. TAO & memecoins dominate mindshare. Peter Todd ‘revealed’ as Satoshi by HBO. US government able to sell $4.4bn Silk Road BTC. Ireland unable to access $378m seized BTC. SOL could do 5x if Trump wins: StanChart. Coinbase integrates Taproot addresses for BTC. Canary Capital applies for XRP ETF. S. Korea to regulate stablecoin transfers. CryptoCom files countersuit against SEC. Babylon fills cap with 22k BTC. Scroll airdrop coming Oct 22nd. USDC goes live on SUI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bounces from $59K, Tesla unveils Robotaxis, Memecoins Outperform]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cyJj6tWj/bitcoin-bounces-from-59k-tesla-unveils-robotaxis-memecoins-outperform</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cyJj6tWj/bitcoin-bounces-from-59k-tesla-unveils-robotaxis-memecoins-outperform"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T07:29:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC briefly dips under $59k, $160m liquidations. Mt Gox extends repayment plan by 1 year. Uniswap plans L2 for DeFi. SEC sues crypto trading firm Cumberland. Binomial sues SEC over futures trading. SEC’s Uyeda criticises agency’s policy. Justin Sun named prime minister of Liberland. MicroStrategy wants to become BTC bank. Binance pre-market trading goes live. Nearly 50% of US investors want crypto ETFs. Whale phished for $35m crypto. Ethena invests $46m in RWA funds. Trump’s crypto project aims to raise $300m.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentraland Desktop Client Preview]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qqzvDcTC/decentraland-desktop-client-preview</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qqzvDcTC/decentraland-desktop-client-preview"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T15:53:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum metaverse game Decentraland has shared an exclusive look at the visual and performance upgrades coming via its new desktop client.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Trader Murad Mahmudov talks about the Supercycle and how he chooses Meme Coins.]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Hj3nDp7G/crypto-trader-murad-mahmudov-talks-about-the-supercycle-and-how-he-chooses-meme-coins</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Hj3nDp7G/crypto-trader-murad-mahmudov-talks-about-the-supercycle-and-how-he-chooses-meme-coins"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T21:47:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Trader Murad Mahmudov talks about the Supercycle and how he chooses Meme Coins. Crypto stable, had sold off after China stocks fall. Crypto adopted faster than other tech: BlackRock. Crypto adoption to hit 8% of world population. CryptoCom recieves Wells notice from SEC. HBO documentary on Satoshi airs tonight. FTX bankruptcy plan approved by judge. Scroll airdrop may be imminent. Jupiter goes live on mobile iOS. Phantom rolls out support for Base. AAVE launches GHO on Base. Gensler may be replaced by Robinhood CLO. 87% of new token launches on SOL. National Bank of Bahrain creates BTC fund. BedRock DeFi allows BTC staking on ARB.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Memecoins take off, funding stays low, China stocks keep on rising!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/703mAYhV/memecoins-take-off-funding-stays-low-china-stocks-keep-on-rising</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/703mAYhV/memecoins-take-off-funding-stays-low-china-stocks-keep-on-rising"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T08:27:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR EP213. Memecoins take off, funding stays low, China stocks keep on rising!
Many altcoins & memecoins soar despite stable BTC. Funding rates continue to be low or negative. Crypto funds saw $147m of outflows last week. BTC remains best performing major assets this year. SUI breaks into the top 20 coins again. TAO leads top 100 away from memes, sifu shorts. $100m bridge to SOL over the last 7 days. Metaplanet buys $6.7m more BTC. ETH proposal aims to improve throughput 50%. EIGEN, OP, APT lead token unlocks this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Walrus Protocol Unlocks New Applications for Decentralized Data Storage]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kwEYLYWj/how-walrus-protocol-unlocks-new-applications-for-decentralized-data-storage</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kwEYLYWj/how-walrus-protocol-unlocks-new-applications-for-decentralized-data-storage"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T11:19:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mysten Labs Chief Scientist George Danezis joined Decrypt to talk about its new decentralized storage protocol Walrus, which promises to unlock new applications such as AI and social media, thanks to its novel Red Stuff data encoding algorithm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Coinbase Sees Crypto as a Bipartisan, 'Purple' Political Issue]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/YR2YmmwR/why-coinbase-sees-crypto-as-a-bipartisan-purple-political-issue</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/YR2YmmwR/why-coinbase-sees-crypto-as-a-bipartisan-purple-political-issue"/>
        <updated>2024-10-05T22:18:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase VP of Corporate and Business Development, Shan Aggarwal, joined Decrypt's Sander Lutz and Liz Napolitano at Messari Mainnet 2024 to discuss the exchange's efforts to grow mainstream crypto adoption—and how the changing political conversation around digital assets is rapidly playing a major role in that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Is Playing Offense—Not Just Defense—Against Crypto Crime, Says Head of Financial Investigations]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DiJ8D2Qc/binance-is-playing-offensenot-just-defenseagainst-crypto-crime-says-head-of-financial-investigations</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DiJ8D2Qc/binance-is-playing-offensenot-just-defenseagainst-crypto-crime-says-head-of-financial-investigations"/>
        <updated>2024-10-05T01:58:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nils Anderson Röed, the exchange’s global head of financial investigations, sat down with Decrypt’s Sander Lutz at Messari Mainnet 2024 to discuss how Binance is proactively dismantling criminal networks around the world, the strategy with which the crypto exchange is approaching sensitive conflicts in the Middle East, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 212 - SEEDPHRASE TALKS ART!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PJfaJNkZ/fomo-hour-212-seedphrase-talks-art</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PJfaJNkZ/fomo-hour-212-seedphrase-talks-art"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T19:29:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Payrolls Higher than expected, Bitcoin reacts hard. Crypto sank early in the week as Middle East tensions spooked markets. Powell signals two more rate cuts this year. SUI leads L1s again, nears YTD high despite large unlock. Majority of FTX repayments still months away. EIGEN becomes non-transferable, hits $6bn FDV. SEC to appeal Ripple securities law ruling. Visa launches tokenization platform for banks. SWIFT plans digital asset trial in 2025. ByBit launched trading of global stock indices. SPX, GIGA & FWOG hit ATHs, most memes fall. XCOPY to release 250 piece collection on Shape. HBO documentary claims to have identified Satoshi.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Altcoins bleed, ByBit launches stock index trading, POCHITA soars]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kYjAt3nt/altcoins-bleed-bybit-launches-stock-index-trading-pochita-soars</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kYjAt3nt/altcoins-bleed-bybit-launches-stock-index-trading-pochita-soars"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T21:11:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Altcoins sink, BTC dominance nears cycle high. BTC in ‘three blind mice’ downtrend. Tron revenue hits record $577m in Q3. ByBit to launch trading of major stock indices. Franklin Templeton launch fund on APT. SWIFT banks to trial digital assets in 2025. Aerodrome hits $1bn TVL on Base. Cronje calls out Aerodrome for copyright. ETH ICO wallet sells $47m. SEC files appeal against Ripple ruling. EIGEN falls 20% on staking rewards FUD. FTX to auction off WLD position. Half of US voters think crypto ‘important’. North Korea ‘infiltrating’ crypto industry. Snowden challenged over SOL centralisation view. Top SEC official on crypto set to depart.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DACOM Summit: Fastex CLO Vardan Khachatryan on Crypto Compliance]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LGGnxkb6/dacom-summit-fastex-clo-vardan-khachatryan-on-crypto-compliance</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LGGnxkb6/dacom-summit-fastex-clo-vardan-khachatryan-on-crypto-compliance"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T14:32:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fastex Chief Legal Officer Vardan Khachatryan joined Rug Radio creator Mlow at DACOM Summit to discuss how the crypto exchange is advancing compliance, and the regulatory challenges that lie ahead for the sector.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 210 - MIDDLE EAST TENSIONS RISE]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Bcj37IF2/fomo-hour-210-middle-east-tensions-rise</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Bcj37IF2/fomo-hour-210-middle-east-tensions-rise"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T17:14:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto drops as Middle East tensions flare. $500m liquidations in drop. BTC ETFs see largest outflows in a month. Fidelity ETH ETF sees 2nd highest outflow ever. SUI hits 6-month highs, bridge goes live on mainnet. Hashdex set to launch XRP ETF. Wormhole leads altcoin gains after Upbit lists. BTC miners hit record low profits in September Crypto hackers stole $750m in Q3. Telegram has been disclosing IPs since 2018.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Arbitrum is Simplifying Web3 for Web2 Adopters]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Mm9OGAoG/how-arbitrum-is-simplifying-web3-for-web2-adopters</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Mm9OGAoG/how-arbitrum-is-simplifying-web3-for-web2-adopters"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T14:19:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arbitrum's Head of Korea, John Park, joined Rug Radio creator Pukerainbow at ArbiVerse to talk about the Ethereum layer-2's strategy in Asia, hackathons, and bringing enterprise clients to its ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rep. Tom Emmer Is Confident Crypto Laws Are Coming Soon—No Matter Who Wins the Election]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qWDybFgM/rep-tom-emmer-is-confident-crypto-laws-are-coming-soonno-matter-who-wins-the-election</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qWDybFgM/rep-tom-emmer-is-confident-crypto-laws-are-coming-soonno-matter-who-wins-the-election"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T20:37:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Republican Majority Whip Tom Emmer sat down with Decrypt’s Sander Lutz and Liz Napolitano to discuss the state of crypto legislation, Kamala Harris, Fairshake, and more at Messari Mainnet 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>