<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-11-27T23:15:53.996Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-11-27T23:15:53.996Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Burn Rate Explodes 499,416%, Can This Send SHIB To $0.1?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7493d56a06</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-burn-rate-499416-0-1/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T23:09:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Shiba Inu community burn has marked a rather historic moment with the amount of tokens that have been burned in the last day. According to data from the burn tracking website Shibburn, the initiative may have just set a new record after the burn rate jumped 499,416%.
 
Shiba Inu Burn Rate Sees Impressive Spike
 
The drastic increase in the Shiba Inu burn rate has shocked the community after hundreds of millions worth of tokens were taken out of circulation. Shibburn data puts the token burn figure for the last 24 hours at over 264.2 million, a notable jump from its previous day’s figures of 2.7 million.
 
 
Interestingly, the 2.7 million figure which was recorded on Sunday amounted to a 5,000% surge in burn rate, suggesting renewed interest. But nothing would prepare the community for …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Best Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Burn Rate Explodes 499,416%, Can This Send SHIB To $0.1?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19067389/Shiba-Inu-Burn-Rate-Explodes-499416-Can-This-Send-SHIB-To-01</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19067389/Shiba-Inu-Burn-Rate-Explodes-499416-Can-This-Send-SHIB-To-01"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T23:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Shiba Inu community burn has marked a rather historic moment with the amount of tokens that have been burned in the last day. According to data from the burn tracking website Shibburn, the initiative may have just set a new record after the burn rate jumped 499,416%. Shiba Inu Burn Rate Sees...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Standard Chartered to offer support for China’s digital yuan]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19067378/Standard-Chartered-to-offer-support-for-Chinas-digital-yuan</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19067378/Standard-Chartered-to-offer-support-for-Chinas-digital-yuan"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T23:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Standard Chartered Bank has announced its upcoming participation in China’s digital yuan, also known as digital renminbi (RMB), with the pilot project set to commence on Nov. 27. The bank said it will provide customers with digital yuan exchange, redemption, and other services. Additionally, the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum price falls as regulatory worries and pause in DApp use impact investor sentiment]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19067391/Ethereum-price-falls-as-regulatory-worries-and-pause-in-DApp-use-impact-investor-sentiment</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19067391/Ethereum-price-falls-as-regulatory-worries-and-pause-in-DApp-use-impact-investor-sentiment"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ether price struggles amid regulatory concerns and a drop in DApp usage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Where in the World Is Hex Founder Richard Heart?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207640</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207640/where-world-hex-founder-richard-heart"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T22:45:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC has been trying, and apparently failing, to hunt down controversial Hex founder Richard Heart for months.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Where in the World Is Hex Founder Richard Heart?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19067373/Where-in-the-World-Is-Hex-Founder-Richard-Heart</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19067373/Where-in-the-World-Is-Hex-Founder-Richard-Heart"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T22:45:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC has been trying, and apparently failing, to hunt down controversial Hex founder Richard Heart for months.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[With Just 0.0004% of Bitcoin’s Hashpower, Solo Miner’s 2 PH/S Effort Secures Block Reward]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7493d0b675</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/with-just-0-0004-of-bitcoins-hashpower-solo-miners-2-ph-s-effort-secures-block-reward/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T22:38:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On November 26, 2023, a stroke of remarkable luck befell a solo miner when they discovered block 818,588, verifying a total of 4,193 transactions. This achievement garnered the miner a total of 6.887 BTC, inclusive of the 6.25 BTC subsidy and transaction fees.
 
Solo Miner’s Slim Odds Pay Off: Claims Bitcoin Block Reward With Mere 2 PH/s Hashrate
 
Echoing a similar event from the end of October, this miner, also affiliated with Solo Ckpool, successfully mined the block. Ckpool is designed to support independent miners, allowing them to retain the entire block reward, unlike other pools where rewards are shared.
 
 
Con Kolivas, the developer overseeing Solo Ckpool, remarked that this was the 279th block successfully mined by the pool. He noted the rarity of such an event, stating, “A miner of this size would solve a block on average only once every 5 years,” underscoring the miner’s extraordinary luck in this instance.
 
 
For context, the Bitcoin network’s total hashpower stands at approximately 488 exahash per second (EH/s), or 488 quintillion hashes per second. In comparison, the solo miner’s contribution of 2 PH/s, or 2 quadrillion hashes, represents a mere 0.0004% of the network’s collective hashpower, highlighting the improbability of their success.
 
What do you think about the solo miner discovering a block with such a small amount of hashrate? Share your thoughts and opinions about this subject in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Inflows Smash 2-Year Milestone in ETF-Inspired Run]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19067357/Crypto-Inflows-Smash-2-Year-Milestone-in-ETF-Inspired-Run</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19067357/Crypto-Inflows-Smash-2-Year-Milestone-in-ETF-Inspired-Run"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T22:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Inflows to crypto funds hit a two-year high in spot ETF-inspired nine week run.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Altcoin Rally Cools as Massive $650M Worth of Token Unlocks Loom Over Crypto Market]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7493d141ef</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/11/27/altcoin-rally-cools-as-massive-650m-worth-of-token-unlocks-loom-over-crypto-market/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T22:34:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several major alternative cryptocurrencies including DYDX, Optimism (OP) and SUI dropped sharply as massive token unlocks weighed on prices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC says Changpeng Zhao committed an SBF-like fraud]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19067359/SEC-says-Changpeng-Zhao-committed-an-SBF-like-fraud</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19067359/SEC-says-Changpeng-Zhao-committed-an-SBF-like-fraud"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T22:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) is ramping up its scrutiny of Binance US, targeting Changpeng Zhao, the platform’s former CEO. This intensified investigation follows Zhao’s recent plea of guilt to charges brought by the Department of Justice (DOJ), a turn of events that’s shaken the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Risks of Stablecoins: Exploring The Bitcoin-Dollar With Mark Goodwin]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7493d1b734</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/videos/the-risks-of-stablecoins-exploring-the-bitcoin-dollar-with-mark-goodwin"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T22:30:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Stablecoins
Stablecoins are a type of cryptocurrency that aims to maintain a stable value by pegging it to another asset, such as a fiat currency, precious metal, or a basket of assets. Stablecoins have gained significant popularity in recent years due to their potential to address some of the limitations of traditional cryptocurrencies, such as Bitcoin. While Bitcoin is known for its price volatility, stablecoins provide a more price stable alternative, making them suitable for various use cases.
One of the most prominent ways stablecoins are marketed is in regards to their ability to act as a bridge between traditional finance and the digital asset space. By pegging their value to a stable asset, stablecoins provide a reliable medium of exchange and store of value. This sta…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ETF Launch Will Send Bitcoin Price to $1Million in a Week]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19067341/ETF-Launch-Will-Send-Bitcoin-Price-to-1Million-in-a-Week</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19067341/ETF-Launch-Will-Send-Bitcoin-Price-to-1Million-in-a-Week"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T22:17:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Could the launch of the Blackrock Spot Bitcoin ETF lead to a $1,000,000 Bitcoin price in just a few days? Samson Mow, the head of Jan3 bringing Bitcoin to nation-states, believes so and he's done the math!! See why Samson Mow and Robert Breedlove foresee HyperBitcoinization within the next 5-10...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance’s Ex-CEO Changpeng Zhao Restricted To US, Travel Ban Imposed]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7493dc21f6</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/former-binance-ceo-ordered-to-stay-in-us/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T22:09:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to a Reuters report, former Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao, commonly known as CZ, must remain in the United States for the time being, as stated by a federal judge on Monday. 
 
This decision comes after Zhao, the founder of the world’s largest cryptocurrency exchange, pleaded guilty to violating US anti-money laundering laws.
 
Binance Ex-CEO Denied UAE Return Amid Money Laundering Charges
 
The judge ruled that Zhao must stay in the US until the Seattle court determines whether he should remain in the country through his sentencing hearing in February or be allowed to return to the United Arab Emirates (UAE), where he holds citizenship.
 
Last week, Zhao resigned as CEO of Binance after admitting to willfully causing the exchange to fail in maintaining an effective anti-money laund…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Altcoin Rally Cools as Massive $650M Worth of Token Unlocks Loom Over Crypto Market]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19067335/Altcoin-Rally-Cools-as-Massive-650M-Worth-of-Token-Unlocks-Loom-Over-Crypto-Market</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19067335/Altcoin-Rally-Cools-as-Massive-650M-Worth-of-Token-Unlocks-Loom-Over-Crypto-Market"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T22:07:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several major alternative cryptocurrencies including DYDX, Optimism (OP) and SUI dropped sharply as massive token unlocks weighed on prices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cosmos co-founder splits ATOM after years of infighting]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19067334/Cosmos-co-founder-splits-ATOM-after-years-of-infighting</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19067334/Cosmos-co-founder-splits-ATOM-after-years-of-infighting"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T22:01:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Cloud joined more than 65 other operators in EigenLayer’s ‘Operator Working Group’ as the restaking protocol eyes a mainnet deployment for node operators in the first half of 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Watch Out! $105 Million in Token Unlocks THIS WEEK! #shorts]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19067321/Watch-Out-105-Million-in-Token-Unlocks-THIS-WEEK-shorts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19067321/Watch-Out-105-Million-in-Token-Unlocks-THIS-WEEK-shorts"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T22:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Watch Out! $105 Million in Token Unlocks THIS WEEK!Introducing the ALTCOINBUZZ ALPHA x DECUBATE Special Offer! Decubate Bronze+ Tier Members can now claim a full refund on your 1st month of Altcoin Buzz Alpha Membership!Eligibility✅ Submit your Bronze+ Member email ID to #Alpha channel in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bankless Co-Founders Propose Separation from BanklessDAO Amid Grant Controversy]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19067302/Bankless-Co-Founders-Propose-Separation-from-BanklessDAO-Amid-Grant-Controversy</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19067302/Bankless-Co-Founders-Propose-Separation-from-BanklessDAO-Amid-Grant-Controversy"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amidst the ongoing controversy surrounding cryptocurrency media outlet Bankless and its associated decentralized autonomous organization...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Enters New Era As CEO Richard Teng Prioritizes Transparency, Compliance]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19067323/Binance-Enters-New-Era-As-CEO-Richard-Teng-Prioritizes-Transparency-Compliance</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19067323/Binance-Enters-New-Era-As-CEO-Richard-Teng-Prioritizes-Transparency-Compliance"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T21:57:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With three decades of financial services and regulatory experience, the new CEO of Binance, Richard Teng, has made an initial statement as read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pudgy Penguins Release Exclusive Walmart 'Influencer Box' for Cyber Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207633</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207633/pudgy-penguins-release-exclusive-walmart-influencer-box-cyber-monday"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T21:46:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The prominent Ethereum NFT project continues pumping out plush toys, serving up a Cyber Monday exclusive via Walmart.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pudgy Penguins Release Exclusive Walmart 'Influencer Box' for Cyber Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19067287/Pudgy-Penguins-Release-Exclusive-Walmart-Influencer-Box-for-Cyber-Monday</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19067287/Pudgy-Penguins-Release-Exclusive-Walmart-Influencer-Box-for-Cyber-Monday"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T21:46:02.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Watch Out: South Korea’s Largest Cryptocurrency Exchange Experiences Unusual Volume Increases in 5 Altcoins!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19067292/Watch-Out-South-Koreas-Largest-Cryptocurrency-Exchange-Experiences-Unusual-Volume-Increases-in-5-Altcoins</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19067292/Watch-Out-South-Koreas-Largest-Cryptocurrency-Exchange-Experiences-Unusual-Volume-Increases-in-5-Altcoins"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T21:45:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some altcoins on Upbit, South Korea's largest cryptocurrency exchange, are experiencing unusual volume increases. Continue Reading: Watch Out: South Korea’s Largest Cryptocurrency Exchange Experiences Unusual Volume Increases in 5 Altcoins!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is CZ a Flight Risk? DOJ Says He Is]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19067290/Is-CZ-a-Flight-Risk-DOJ-Says-He-Is</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19067290/Is-CZ-a-Flight-Risk-DOJ-Says-He-Is"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T21:41:13.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong Regulators Speed up Crypto Products Approval Following JPEX Fiasco]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19067288/Hong-Kong-Regulators-Speed-up-Crypto-Products-Approval-Following-JPEX-Fiasco</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19067288/Hong-Kong-Regulators-Speed-up-Crypto-Products-Approval-Following-JPEX-Fiasco"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T21:41:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the JPEX saga over, there has been an increase in crypto products approvals by Hong Kong regulators, according to an OSL executive.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin traders’ bullish bias holds firm even as BTC price dips to $37K]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19067286/Bitcoin-traders-bullish-bias-holds-firm-even-as-BTC-price-dips-to-37K</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19067286/Bitcoin-traders-bullish-bias-holds-firm-even-as-BTC-price-dips-to-37K"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T21:40:36.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Binance CEO CZ Can’t Leave US Until Court Decides If He’s a Flight Risk]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207617</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207617/former-binance-ceo-cz-cant-leave-flight-risk"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T21:24:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prosecutors say CZ has ample means to flee, despite the hefty bond he’s placed. Now the Binance founder is stuck in the U.S. for now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Binance CEO CZ Can’t Leave US Until Court Decides If He’s a Flight Risk]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19067241/Former-Binance-CEO-CZ-Cant-Leave-US-Until-Court-Decides-If-Hes-a-Flight-Risk</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19067241/Former-Binance-CEO-CZ-Cant-Leave-US-Until-Court-Decides-If-Hes-a-Flight-Risk"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T21:24:39.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale Bitcoin Trust’s discount narrows to 8% amid growing ETF optimism]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19067240/Grayscale-Bitcoin-Trusts-discount-narrows-to-8-amid-growing-ETF-optimism</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19067240/Grayscale-Bitcoin-Trusts-discount-narrows-to-8-amid-growing-ETF-optimism"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T21:20:06.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Data Finds Defi - Not NFTs - Are Future Of Blockchain Investing]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19067254/New-Data-Finds-Defi-Not-NFTs-Are-Future-Of-Blockchain-Investing</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19067254/New-Data-Finds-Defi-Not-NFTs-Are-Future-Of-Blockchain-Investing"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T21:19:25.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Blade Runner' Director Ridley Scott Calls AI a 'Technical Hydrogen Bomb']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207618</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207618/blade-runner-director-ridley-scott-ai-technical-hydrogen-bomb"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T21:18:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leading directors, including Oppenheimer’s Christopher Nolan and Terminator’s James Cameron, speak out over AI's potentially catastrophic global impact.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Whale Inflow Activity On The Rise: Something To Watch For?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7493db2b15</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-whale-inflow-activity-rise-something-watch/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T21:06:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data shows the Bitcoin whale exchange inflow activity has been increasing recently, a sign that may not be positive for the price.
 
Bitcoin Exchange Whale Ratio Has Been Going Up Recently
 
As an analyst in a CryptoQuant Quicktake post pointed out, the exchange whale ratio has recently observed an uptrend. The “exchange whale ratio” refers to an indicator that keeps track of the ratio between the sum of the top 10 transfers to exchanges and the total exchange inflow.
 
The ten largest deposits to exchanges generally come from whale entities, so this ratio’s value can tell us about how the inflow activity of these humongous investors compares against that of the entire market.
 
 
When this metric is high, the whales comprise a significant part of the total exchange inflows. Since…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF Hope Pushes Crypto Fund Investments to $1.5 Billion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207610</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207610/bitcoin-etf-hope-pushes-crypto-fund-investments-to-1-5-billion"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T20:31:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The lingering prospect of new, regulator-approved Bitcoin ETFs continues to draw interest and cold hard cash.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Symbiogenesis' Launch Date Revealed as Square Enix Gives Out Free NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207608</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207608/symbiogenesis-launch-date-revealed-square-enix-gives-out-free-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T20:16:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Final Fantasy maker has set a date for Symbiogenesis, and is giving away NFTs for users who participate in the first auction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking Down the Bankless Backlash]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7493c21954</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/11/27/breaking-down-the-bankless-backlash/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T20:08:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Hoffman, cofounder, responds to criticism surrounding the media brand’s DAO. Should he have been more hands-on?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Kuhn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance’s CEO Sets Out Bold Vision: Revealing Future Plans Post-CZ’s Exit]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7493c2df5a</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/binance-roadmap-ceo-reveals-future-plans-after-czs/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T20:01:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent blog post, Richard Teng, the newly appointed CEO of Binance, shared his vision for the future of the crypto exchange following the departure of Changpeng Zhao (CZ). Teng expressed his commitment to maintaining Binance’s core principles while driving growth and innovation.
 
Binance CEO Stresses Collaboration With Regulators
 
Teng acknowledged Binance’s foundation and principles, emphasizing the importance of delivering “best-in-class products” that bring value to its more than 160 million users. Teng pledged to continue the company’s focus on product excellence and its mission to promote the “freedom of money.”
 
As for Binance’s historical compliance problems, Teng highlighted the “significant efforts” the company has made over the past two years to strengthen its compliance …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Is Dominating a Key Bitcoin ETF Service. Can Anyone Else Join the Race?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7493cc690d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/11/27/coinbase-is-dominating-a-key-bitcoin-etf-service-can-anyone-else-join-the-race/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T19:49:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The race to provide a key bit of infrastructure for bitcoin [BTC] ETFs – custody services – hasn't actually been much of a race so far. Crypto exchange Coinbase has dominated so far, winning the job from the majority of applications from the likes of BlackRock, WisdomTree and Valkyrie.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Founder CZ Stuck in U.S. for the Moment]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7493cd4db0</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/11/27/binance-founder-cz-stuck-in-us-for-the-moment/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T19:41:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A district judge ordered Changpeng "CZ" Zhao to stay in the U.S. until he could make a proper ruling on a U.S. Department of Justice motion to block him from returning to his home in the UAE.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Hovers Near Yearly High as Halving and ETF Loom]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207593</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207593/bitcoin-hovers-near-yearly-high-halving-etf"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T19:40:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin appears to be holding onto gains in an anticipation of big events next year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jito Reveals JTO Airdrop for Solana DeFi Users—Here's Who Can Claim]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207594</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207594/jito-reveals-jto-airdrop-solana-defi-users-heres-who-claim"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T19:37:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Solana DeFi platform Jito is giving 100 million JTO tokens to its community to facilitate collective governance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin User Alleges Hack Linked to Erroneous 83.65 BTC Fee Incident]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7493ce1250</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-user-alleges-hack-linked-to-erroneous-83-65-btc-fee-incident/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T19:35:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto community was initially baffled by the massive fee of 83.65 bitcoin, originally attributed to a costly mistake. However, recent revelations paint a darker picture. According to a social media account on X called “@83_5BTC,” hackers stole the funds from the unnamed individual and immediately swept the bitcoin to a different wallet. 
 
Alleged Hacking Incident Tied to Bitcoin’s Massive 83.65 Bitcoin Fee Error
 
The alleged victim, @83_5BTC, revealed that after transferring 139 BTC to a new cold wallet, the funds were immediately swept to another wallet by the attackers. The transaction split the sum, sending 55.77 BTC to the hackers’ wallet, while the rest, a staggering 83.65 BTC, was paid as a transaction fee. This incident surpasses the previous high-fee record of 19.8 BTC.
 
Mo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Flawless “Base-Building” Bitcoin Signal Says The Bottom Is In]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7493c91696</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/this-base-building-bitcoin-signal-bottom-is-in/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T19:10:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Bitcoin price approaches $40,000 per coin and higher, sidelined market participants and even crypto bears will at some point start to consider that the bottom is in.
 
A signal has since appeared that is currently flawless at picking out when BTCUSD has built a strong enough base. Each time after moving away from this so-called “base,” Bitcoin blasted off to a massive bull run. Let’s take a closer look.
 
Bitcoin Production Cost Gives BTC A Base For Liftoff
 
Bitcoin price is trading at $37,000 per coin, up more than double from lows set one year ago. Yet there are plenty of cryptocurrency investors who are fully expecting to see BTC at $10,000 or less in the near future.
 
At some point, these investors will be right, or have to change their stance. However, a fundamental signal has re…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tony &amp;quot;The Bull&amp;quot; Severino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Summit: Will Web3 Gaming Ever be Mainstream?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OvVWhGbW/web-summit-will-web3-gaming-ever-be-mainstream</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OvVWhGbW/web-summit-will-web3-gaming-ever-be-mainstream"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T19:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animoca Brands CEO Robby Yung, EndeavorXR CEO Amy Peck and Gamee co-founder CEO Bozena Rezab joined Decrypt's Stephen Graves on stage at Web Summit to talk about the future of Web3 gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lightning Is Doomed]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7493cab152</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/technical/lightning-is-doomed"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T18:59:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lightning is doomed. High fees from Ordinals have killed all hope of scaling Bitcoin non-custodially, there is no chance at all that people will be able to cost effectively open channels or enforce hung payments on-chain when necessary. It’s all over, pack it all up guys. Time to start shopping around and deciding whether Coinbase or Cashapp is a better platform for all of our Bitcoin needs now that we can’t afford to do it directly on-chain in a high fee environment.
It was fun while it lasted. We’ll always have the pixelated dick pics on the Lightning art site, the Lightning torch meme where everyone was scared to send it to people in countries the state told us is full of nothing but bad people, we’ll still have the zapping sats from custodial account to custodial account. Into the era …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shinobi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spot Bitcoin ETFs Have Almost $100M in AUM in Brazil, Led by Hashdex Offering]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7493cb4520</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/11/27/spot-bitcoin-etfs-have-almost-100m-in-aum-in-brazil-led-by-hashdex-offering/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T18:54:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pro-market digital assets regulation and growing interest from large institutions are among the factors of the success so far, said Hashdex's CEO.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lyllah Ledesma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Israel Intensifies Scrutiny Of TRON Transactions Amid Ongoing Militant Financing Battle]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7493b2848e</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/israel-intensifies-scrutiny-of-tron-transactions/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T18:01:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A report from news outlet Reuters indicates increasing oversight by Israeli authorities on transactions on TRON. The report comes amid backlash from the crypto community due to mainstream media outlets trying to link crypto to illegal activity.
 
 
 
Israel Intensifies Crackdown On TRON Wallets Linked to Militant Funding
 
According to Reuters, TRON is becoming a “key player” in the financing of Iran-backed militant groups, from Hamas to Hezbollah. Israel’s battle against funding sources takes a new turn, as per Reuters, after consulting with financial crime and blockchain experts and basing their investigation on data provided by Israel’s National Bureau for Counter Terror Financing (NBCTF).
 
TRON’s appeal over Bitcoin lies in its faster transaction speeds, lower costs, and greater stabi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reynaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CEO Richard Teng Says He's Committed to 'the Binance Way' After CZ's Guilty Plea]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207583</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207583/ceo-richard-teng-says-committed-binance-way-after-czs-guilty-plea"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T17:50:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After the leading exchange and founder Changpeng Zhao settled U.S. charges, Binance’s new CEO says the firm has “turned the page.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hounax Scandal: Hong Kong Police Probe $15 Million Crypto Fraud, Investors In Turmoil]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7493bafba0</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/hounax-scandal-hong-kong-police-probe-crypto-fraud/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T17:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong’s Securities and Futures Commission (SFC) has taken decisive action against what it suspects to be a fraudulent crypto asset trading platform. The SFC flagged the company at the center of these allegations, Hounax, earlier this month, marking a crucial step in the city’s ongoing efforts to combat crypto-related scams.
 
The case gained further momentum as the Hong Kong Police Force initiated an investigation following reports from numerous individuals who claimed significant financial losses.
 
News outlet, The South China Morning Post highlighted that the police, having received complaints from 131 victims, are now actively probing the alleged scam that purportedly swindled investors out of HK$120 million ($15.4 million).
 
 
Hounax’s Dubious Operations And Regulatory Oversight
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Funds Attract Largest Weekly Inflow in 2023 as Bitcoin 'Short-Sellers Capitulate': CoinShares]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7493a543ad</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/11/27/crypto-funds-attract-largest-weekly-inflow-in-2023-as-bitcoin-short-sellers-capitulate-coinshares/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T16:50:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto investment funds last week attracted their largest inflow this year, extending their strongest run since the 2021 bull market as anticipation for a spot bitcoin [BTC] exchange-traded fund (ETF) continued to entice investors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paradigm Says Blast Launch ‘Crossed Lines’ in Messaging and Execution, Pacman Defends Platform Amid Criticism]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7493a695c0</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/paradigm-says-blast-launch-crossed-lines-in-messaging-and-execution-pacman-defends-platform-amid-criticism/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T16:42:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amid the rapidly evolving landscape of Ethereum layer two (L2) solutions, Blast, a new entrant, has sparked a wave of discussions in the crypto community. Spearheaded by Pacman, known for his work on the non-fungible token (NFT) marketplace Blur, Blast has garnered both significant funding and scrutiny. Despite being a lead investor in the project, Paradigm’s head of research, Dan Robinson, highlighted issues with “the messaging and execution” of Blast’s launch strategy, while Pacman defends the platform’s mechanics and vision.
 
Paradigm Addresses Blast Launch
 
Dan Robinson of Paradigm, a key investor in the Ethereum L2 platform Blast, has recently discussed the project’s launch via the social media platform X. Robinson cited issues with the messaging and execution, particularly the deci…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Standard Chartered China Offering Exchange Services for Digital Yuan]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7493a2af7d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/11/27/standard-chartered-china-offering-exchange-services-for-digital-yuan/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T16:18:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bank will give customers access to the digital RBM's interconnection platform, offering recharge and redemption.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DEMAND Launches World’s First Stratum V2 Bitcoin Mining Pool]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7493ac72b3</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/demand-launches-worlds-first-stratum-v2-bitcoin-mining-pool"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T16:07:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin mining company DEMAND has announced today the world’s inaugural Stratum V2 mining pool, according to a press release sent to Bitcoin Magazine. This pool, built on the open-source Stratum Reference Implementation (SRI), aims to usher in a new era for mining by introducing enhanced security, flexibility, and performance.
The Stratum V2 protocol marks a significant leap forward from its predecessor, according to the release, offering a suite of improvements that not only elevate mining capabilities but also champion a more decentralized mining landscape.
Alejandro de la Torre, DEMAND’s co-founder and CEO, stated, “With Stratum V2 and our new solo mining pool, we aim to make home mining more attractive, which should in effect help decentralize the Bitcoin mining ecosystem and improve t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nik Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Magic Eden Launches Cross-Chain NFT and Crypto Wallet for Bitcoin, Ethereum, Solana, and Polygon]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207443</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207443/magic-eden-cross-chain-nft-wallet-bitcoin-ethereum-solana-polygon"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T15:22:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Magic Eden Wallet is now in closed beta and promises a range of features for NFT collectors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bybit Woos Holders of Rival Crypto Cards With Rewards Program]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203973</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203973/bybit-woos-holders-of-rival-crypto-cards-with-rewards-program"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T13:45:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto card holders are eligible for a limited-time rewards program with up to €25 in card bonuses on signing up for a Bybit Card.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terra Ecosystem's LUNA, LUNC Surge By Double-Digits]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207561</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207561/terra-ecosystems-luna-lunc-surge-by-double-digits"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T12:44:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terra ecosystem coins have spiked following the injection of $15 million into the network's DeFi ecosystem by Terraform Labs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ATOM Slips 4% as Founder Pushes for Cosmos Fork After Inflation Vote]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207559</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207559/atom-slips-4-as-founder-pushes-for-cosmos-fork-after-inflation-vote"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T11:12:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The passing of a proposal to slash inflation on Cosmos Hub’s ATOM token has seen Jae Kwon pushing to “coordinate a split.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Illuvium Preview: Everything You Need to Know About the NFT Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207455</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207455/illuvium-preview-everything-need-know-about-nft-games"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T20:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Illuvium is an NFT-powered sci-fi fantasy world with cards, creatures, and worlds to explore. Here's an introduction to its games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paradigm Says Ethereum Layer-2 Blast Launch 'Crossed Lines' as Users Lock Up $535 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207548</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207548/paradigm-says-ethereum-layer-2-blast-launch-crossed-lines-users-lock-up-535-million"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T18:44:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blast’s launch has been both controversial and highly popular, but investor Paradigm now says it doesn’t “endorse these kinds of tactics.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biggest Video Games Releasing in December 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207495</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207495/biggest-video-games-releasing-december-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T16:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Take flight in Ubisoft’s new open-world Avatar game, or dig into the hotly anticipated NFT games Symbiogenesis and Shrapnel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week on Crypto Twitter: Another One Bites the Dust]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207525</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207525/this-week-on-crypto-twitter-cz-blast"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T10:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twitter discourse was dominated by the shocking fall of Binance CEO CZ on Tuesday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Bitcoin Hits 18-Month High After Sleepy Week, Ethereum Rallies]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207488</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207488/this-week-in-coins-bitcoin-18-month-high-ethereum-rallies"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T16:57:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Things got exciting for Bitcoin at the end of the week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Auction House Christie's Embraced NFTs After Beeple's $69 Million Sale]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207461</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207461/how-auction-house-christies-embraced-nfts-after-beeple-69-million-sale"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T14:20:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The creators of Christie’s 3.0 reflect on the impact of their on-chain art marketplace one year out, and how the 257-year old auction house improbably became a tech thought leader.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Layer-2 Blast Has $400 Million Locked in Just 4 Days, Despite Concerns]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207489</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207489/ethereum-layer-2-blast-has-400-million-locked-in-just-4-days-despite-concerns"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T23:57:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Layer-2 network Blast isn’t live yet. That’s not stopping people from depositing vast sums of crypto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy Stock Hits Nearly Two-Year High]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207492</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207492/microstrategy-stock-hits-nearly-two-year-high"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T23:40:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The business intelligence firm is earning significant investor interest as its Bitcoin holdings turn a profit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Kawailani Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Role of AI on the Battlefield Debated as Putin Stakes New Policy Position]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207456</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207456/role-of-ai-on-the-battlefield-debated-as-putins-stakes-new-policy-position"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T22:33:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Netflix documentary highlights American companies like Shield AI adapting new tech for modern combat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EU's Anti-Bitcoin Central Bank Head Lagarde Admits Son Lost Big on Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207444</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207444/eu-anti-bitcoin-central-bank-head-admits-son-lost-big-on-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T20:12:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Christine Lagarde, the European Central Bank president, said she spent years trying to convince her 30-something son to stay away from crypto bets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Pseudonymous Longevity Guru Doxxed Himself—What's Next?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207395</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207395/agingdoc-david-barzilai-longevity-expert"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T19:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dr. David “Agingdoc” Barzilai said his “zany quirkiness” would have outed him eventually.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Holiday Gift Guide 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207338</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207338/crypto-holiday-gift-guide-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T18:41:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt rounds up the best holiday prezzies from the world of crypto and emerging tech, from stocking fillers to glamorous gifts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves,Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Q* and Q-Learning? OpenAI Could Have Imploded Over AI Fears]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207413</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207413/what-is-q-star-q-learning-agi-openai"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T18:15:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A technological milestone reportedly called Q* was concerning enough to spark a coup at the world’s leading AI company.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Axie Infinity Starts Giving NFT Owners Commercial Rights as Official Merch Drops]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207402</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207402/axie-infinity-starts-giving-nft-owners-commercial-rights-official-merch-drops"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T17:54:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sky Mavis has launched a merch store for its Axie Infinity game IP, and is also allowing a small portion of its NFTs to be used commercially by owners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inverse Cramer? Bitcoin Doomer Turns Bullish as Crypto Hits $38,000]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207391</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207391/inverse-cramer-bitcoin-doomer-turns-bullish-crypto-hits-38000"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T17:36:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Bitcoin continues to pump, CNBC host Jim Cramer has changed his tune about crypto once again. Some Bitcoiners joke that BTC is now doomed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Stock Hits 18-Month High Alongside Bitcoin and Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207390</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207390/coinbase-stock-hits-18-month-high-alongside-bitcoin-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T17:13:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase stock—which trades as COIN on the Nasdaq—hit an 18-month high on Friday. Bitcoin and Ethereum are also surging in price.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s When 'Final Fantasy' Maker Square Enix Is Dropping NFTs for its Ethereum Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207381</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207381/heres-when-final-fantasy-maker-square-enix-dropping-nfts-ethereum-game"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T16:29:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Symbiogenesis, an original Ethereum and Polygon game from Final Fantasy creator Square Enix, is set to launch in December.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Surges Above $38,000 as BTC and Ethereum Hit 18-Month Highs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207355</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207355/bitcoin-surges-above-38000-btc-ethereum-hit-18-month-highs"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T15:49:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin smashed through the $38,000 mark early Friday, while Ethereum pushed past $2,100—both hitting marks unseen since May 2022.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terra Co-Founder Do Kwon's Extradition Approved by Montenegro Court]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207337</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207337/terra-co-founder-do-kwons-extradition-approved-by-montenegro-court"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T11:10:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Terraform Labs founder will serve his four-month sentence in Montenegro for document forgery before a final decision on his extradition.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BLUR Up 30% Following Season 2 Airdrop, Binance Listing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207334</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207334/blur-up-30-following-season-2-airdrop-binance-listing"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T10:28:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The token of NFT marketplace Blur has surged following news of its listing on Binance and the completion of its Season 2 airdrop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Has Nayib Bukele’s Big Bitcoin Bet Borne Fruit?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207301</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207301/has-nayib-bukeles-big-bitcoin-bet-borne-fruit"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T22:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not yet, but according to the orange-pill ethos, he could still be vindicated someday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Turkey Day in Coins: BTC, ETH, and DOGE Sit Stuffed]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207307</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207307/this-turkey-day-in-coins-btc-eth-and-doge-sit-stuffed"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T21:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As if dosed with tryptophan, the entire crypto market has barely moved.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amid Mainstream Boom, AI Skeptics Say the Tech is Overhyped]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207306</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207306/amid-mainstream-boom-ai-skeptics-say-the-tech-is-over-hyped"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T20:45:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More than half of survey respondents said AI is "over-hyped," even as it's clearly impacted software development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Formula E: High Voltage Beginner's Guide—Get Started in the Play-to-Earn Racer]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206844</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/formula-e-high-voltage-beginners-guide-how-play"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T20:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Play-to-earn racing game Formula E: High Voltage pays you crypto tokens for successful finishes. Our guide will get you up to speed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Sender Overpays Record-Breaking $3 Million Transaction Fee]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207263</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207263/bitcoin-sender-overpays-record-breaking-3-million-transaction-fee"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T17:25:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Someone accidentally paid over $3 million in fees to send $2 million in BTC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Allie Eve Knox on Spankchain and the life of a Crypto Financial Dominatrix]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/16rVeg6o/allie-eve-knox-on-spankchain-and-the-life-of-a-crypto-financial-dominatrix</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/16rVeg6o/allie-eve-knox-on-spankchain-and-the-life-of-a-crypto-financial-dominatrix"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T21:20:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the first IRL episode of This Time Will Be Different!

In this week's episode, our host, Reza Jafery, is joined by Allie Eve Knox, the Spankchain Chief of Staff and FinDomme. 

They discuss
- How to sell feet pics
- If crypto is really as permissionless as it seems
- the intersections between crypto and sex work]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Questions With SCENE: Jeff Davis]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PChJu1R8/5-questions-with-scene-jeff-davis</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PChJu1R8/5-questions-with-scene-jeff-davis"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artist Jeff Davis joins 5 Questions with SCENE to answer burning questions about his artistic practice, the path that brought him to Art Blocks, and his quietly sophisticated DJ abilities.

Video shot and edited by Vincent Roazzi Jr.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Heatbit Founder Alex Busarov on the Bitcoin Miner That Heats Your Home]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DJuHqcGT/heatbit-founder-alex-busarov-on-the-bitcoin-miner-that-heats-your-home</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DJuHqcGT/heatbit-founder-alex-busarov-on-the-bitcoin-miner-that-heats-your-home"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T18:12:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt joined Heatbit founder Alex Busarov at Web Summit for a walkthrough of the firm's flagship product, a Bitcoin miner that acts as a domestic space heater—aimed at the casual user.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nym CEO Harry Halpin on Privacy, Decentralized VPNs and Tornado Cash]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/aLTtY2aq/nym-ceo-harry-halpin-on-privacy-decentralized-vpns-and-tornado-cash</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/aLTtY2aq/nym-ceo-harry-halpin-on-privacy-decentralized-vpns-and-tornado-cash"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T18:08:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The founder of privacy-preserving mixnet Nym sat down with Decrypt at Web Summit to talk about its new decentralized VPN, the Web3 privacy landscape and why "devs should be defended" in the wake of the Tornado Cash crackdown.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pat Felder - The worst is over [Macro Deep Dive Episode]]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MdcKPVo0/pat-felder-the-worst-is-over-macro-deep-dive-episode</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MdcKPVo0/pat-felder-the-worst-is-over-macro-deep-dive-episode"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T17:10:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the first Markets Edition of This Time Will Be Different! In this episode we dive into the current macroeconomic conditions around crypto and look at the data behind the price action. 


Reza sits down with Pat Felder, founder of Prismatic Capital to discuss the current macro environment, and to answer the question on everyone's mind-- is the bear market really over?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Sandbox Co-Founder Sebastien Borget: 'We're Already Integrating AI']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/HlARjhG1/the-sandbox-co-founder-sebastien-borget-were-already-integrating-ai</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/HlARjhG1/the-sandbox-co-founder-sebastien-borget-were-already-integrating-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T16:09:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt sat down with The Sandbox co-founder Sebastien Borget at Web Summit to talk about AI, the open metaverse and the creative challenges of interoperability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dacoco CEO Saro McKenna: How Alien Worlds is Creating an AI-Powered 'Lore DAO' with Kevin J Anderson]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QrQTrsjH/dacoco-ceo-saro-mckenna-how-alien-worlds-is-creating-an-ai-powered-lore-dao-with-kevin-j-anderson</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QrQTrsjH/dacoco-ceo-saro-mckenna-how-alien-worlds-is-creating-an-ai-powered-lore-dao-with-kevin-j-anderson"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T16:06:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt joined Dacoco CEO Sarojini McKenna at Web Summit 2023 to talk about Alien Worlds' new Lore DAO and its AI-powered collaboration with sci-fi author Kevin J Anderson.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avalon's Jeffrey Butler on Designing a Metaverse MMO That Lets Players Co-Create]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XDz9vsvT/avalons-jeffrey-butler-on-designing-a-metaverse-mmo-that-lets-players-co-create</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XDz9vsvT/avalons-jeffrey-butler-on-designing-a-metaverse-mmo-that-lets-players-co-create"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T00:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avalon Chief Product Officer Jeffrey Butler speaks with Decrypt reporter Jason Nelson and details his studio's new MMO game with interoperable assets—and how it will enable players to create and monetize their own content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Gen Z Is Different: OTK Chief Strategy Officer Talks Creator Economy Shift and Rise of Kick]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PieshbpH/how-gen-z-is-different-otk-chief-strategy-officer-talks-creator-economy-shift-and-rise-of-kick</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PieshbpH/how-gen-z-is-different-otk-chief-strategy-officer-talks-creator-economy-shift-and-rise-of-kick"/>
        <updated>2023-11-10T18:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One True King, an esports and gaming lifestyle brand and media company, was founded by creators like Asmongold and Mizkif. OTK's Chief Strategy Officer Zachary Diaz, who previously worked at TikTok and Twitch, shares with Decrypt's Kate Irwin about how the creator economy is changing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moisés Zamora on Videomart and Bucking the Hollywood System]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kyjQCle8/moises-zamora-on-videomart-and-bucking-the-hollywood-system</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kyjQCle8/moises-zamora-on-videomart-and-bucking-the-hollywood-system"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T17:11:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Selena: The Series" creator and co-showrunner Moisés Zamora joins Decrypt's Sander Lutz at the Film3 Summit 2023 to discuss why the Hollywood system is broken and why he founded the Videomart NFT digital film marketplace to give creators more power.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why OTK Is Making Video Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/1NCV4Fk0/why-otk-is-making-video-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/1NCV4Fk0/why-otk-is-making-video-games"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One True King (OTK) Chief Strategy Officer Zachary Diaz tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about OTK's long-term strategy and vision to become a content creator-powered media and video games company.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Questions With SCENE: LoVid]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/E8BZZBWX/5-questions-with-scene-lovid</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/E8BZZBWX/5-questions-with-scene-lovid"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T21:47:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artistic duo LoVid, aka Tali Hinkis and Kyle Lapidus, joins 5 Questions with SCENE to answer burning questions about art, lettuce, and the hellscape (in someone’s opinion) that is Miami.

Video shot and edited by Vincent Roazzi Jr.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Barney on DeFi, Privacy, and Vega]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/hgDzjboU/barney-on-defi-privacy-and-vega</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/hgDzjboU/barney-on-defi-privacy-and-vega"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T18:27:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week our host is joined by Barney the founder of Vega Protocol. 

They discuss the current state of DeFi, what's wrong with the apps being built today, whether or not privacy matters when its only applied to an L2, and most importantly-- which form of sales tax is the sexiest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Is Phantom Galaxies Releasing Two Versions of Its Game?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QtnWGSSJ/why-is-phantom-galaxies-releasing-two-versions-of-its-game</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QtnWGSSJ/why-is-phantom-galaxies-releasing-two-versions-of-its-game"/>
        <updated>2023-11-06T17:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animoca Brands-owned Blowfish Studios is building a space mech pilot game called Phantom Galaxies. Blowfish Cofounder Ben Lee tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about his plans for the game's release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sophie Maxx on NFTs, Augmented Reality, and Fashion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/VByufHjn/sophie-maxx-on-nfts-augmented-reality-and-fashion</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/VByufHjn/sophie-maxx-on-nfts-augmented-reality-and-fashion"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T23:37:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week our host is joined by Sophie Maxx (Web3Maxx) to discuss NFTs, augmented reality, the metaverse, how blockchain is sneaking into the fashion world, and more!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Questions With SCENE: Kevin Rose]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/u9LDX8Vr/5-questions-with-scene-kevin-rose</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/u9LDX8Vr/5-questions-with-scene-kevin-rose"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kevin Rose, co-founder and CEO of PROOF and co-creator of the hit Moonbirds NFT collection, joins 5 Questions with SCENE to answer some hard-hitting questions about his childhood dreams, his wife’s candy preferences, and his undying love of rap music.

Video shot and edited by Vincent Roazzi Jr.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Happened to Atari's Token? Inside Atari's Blockchain Plans]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/7OtQIdqa/what-happened-to-ataris-token-inside-ataris-blockchain-plans</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/7OtQIdqa/what-happened-to-ataris-token-inside-ataris-blockchain-plans"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T18:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin chats with Atari X director Tyler Drewitz about what happened with Atari's token plans, whether a token is coming, and what Atari games might be getting the blockchain treatment. Oh, and there's lots of Easter eggs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitch CEO Dan Clancy Is a 'Wild Card,' Says Marketing Director]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/qCOCtPKe/twitch-ceo-dan-clancy-is-a-wild-card-says-marketing-director</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/qCOCtPKe/twitch-ceo-dan-clancy-is-a-wild-card-says-marketing-director"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T20:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twitch Senior Director of Community Marketing Mary Kish speaks with Decrypt's Kate Irwin about Twitch CEO Dan Clancy, Ninja, Twitch's new simulcasting rules, the biggest differences between Twitch and rival platform Kick, and the role of esports on the streaming platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why NFT Paris has Launched a Loyalty Token]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/91tPVJff/why-nft-paris-has-launched-a-loyalty-token</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/91tPVJff/why-nft-paris-has-launched-a-loyalty-token"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T13:26:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NFT Paris founder Alexandre Tsydenkov told Decrypt what to expect from the upcoming 2024 edition of the conference, the launch of its loyalty token and its plans to create a Web3 loyalty program that rewards the most engaged members of the community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>