<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-09-15T02:21:36.586Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-09-15T02:21:36.586Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mila Kunis and Ashton Kutcher’s Stoner Cats NFT Sales Surge by 2,433% After SEC Charges]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754100aead</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/mila-kunis-and-ashton-kutchers-stoner-cats-nft-sales-surge-by-2433-after-sec-charges/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T02:17:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission’s (SEC) charges against Stoner Cats, the NFT project backed by Mila Kunis, the digital collectibles have witnessed a staggering surge in sales, soaring by a significant 2,433% within a mere 24-hour span. On September 14, the Stoner Cats’ floor value experienced a notable uptick, surging to 0.084 ether. 
 
SEC Crackdown Boosts Stoner Cats’ Secondary Sales
 
In the wake of the SEC’s actions against the Stoner Cats NFT project, there was a significant boost in both floor value and trade volume for the digital collection. According to data sourced from opensea.io and nftpricefloor.com, the floor value reached a high of 0.084 ETH, which translates to approximately $136. Prior to the SEC’s intervention, the Stoner Cats’ floor value was hoveri…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shockingly, Gary Gensler Doesn't Like Stoner Cats]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904586/Shockingly-Gary-Gensler-Doesnt-Like-Stoner-Cats</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904586/Shockingly-Gary-Gensler-Doesnt-Like-Stoner-Cats"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T01:53:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest SEC action is a settlement with NFT project Stoner Cats. NLW discusses the community's response, which ranges from not-that-surprised to appalled at yet another example of unelected bureaucrats trying to expand their authority through enforcement. Enjoying this content?SUBSCRIBE to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Market Bombshell: Crypto Firm Genesis Ceases Trading Operations]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7541038849</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-firm-genesis-ceases-trading-operations/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T01:41:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Per a report from The Block, Genesis, a prominent digital asset financial firm, has announced the discontinuation of crypto derivatives trading through its subsidiary GGC International (GGCI). The company conveyed this decision to its clients in an email on Wednesday.  
 
Genesis Continues To Scale Back Services
 
According to the report, The company clarified that this decision applies to all of its business entities and was made voluntarily based on strategic business considerations. 
 
 
Genesis has assured its clients that any open derivatives positions with GGCI will be honored until their expiry dates.
 
In recent weeks, Genesis has been implementing strategic changes and scaling back its services as part of its ongoing efforts to streamline operations and focus on core areas of expe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean crypto hacks down 80% but that could change overnight: Chainalysis]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904563/North-Korean-crypto-hacks-down-80-but-that-could-change-overnight-Chainalysis</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904563/North-Korean-crypto-hacks-down-80-but-that-could-change-overnight-Chainalysis"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T01:36:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto bad actors from the DPRK have stolen $340.4 million in 2023, down from $1.7 billion from the prior year, but that's no reason to feel at ease.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[August CPI unveiled: Crypto market’s response and trends]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904560/August-CPI-unveiled-Crypto-markets-response-and-trends</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904560/August-CPI-unveiled-Crypto-markets-response-and-trends"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T01:30:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August's CPI report stirs the crypto market, with Bitcoin's surge driving gains. But despite lower social buzz, the crypto market holds strong above the $1 trillion mark.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ZRX-backed Loan On Aave V2 Gets Closer To Liquidation]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904546/ZRX-backed-Loan-On-Aave-V2-Gets-Closer-To-Liquidation</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904546/ZRX-backed-Loan-On-Aave-V2-Gets-Closer-To-Liquidation"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T01:16:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lending Market Has Been Frozen Since November 2022 But Limited Liquidity For 0x Protocol’s Governance Token Could Result In Bad Debt If ZRX Drops Sharply]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin is the great economic equalizer #bitcoin #crypto #shorts]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904547/Bitcoin-is-the-great-economic-equalizer-bitcoin-crypto-shorts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904547/Bitcoin-is-the-great-economic-equalizer-bitcoin-crypto-shorts"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T01:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin creates equal opportunity for ALL. We are all part of the peaceful revolution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Market Bombshell: Crypto Firm Genesis Ceases Trading Operations]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904534/Market-Bombshell-Crypto-Firm-Genesis-Ceases-Trading-Operations</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904534/Market-Bombshell-Crypto-Firm-Genesis-Ceases-Trading-Operations"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T01:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Per a report from The Block, Genesis, a prominent digital asset financial firm, has announced the discontinuation of crypto derivatives trading through its subsidiary GGC International (GGCI). The company conveyed this decision to its clients in an email on Wednesday. Genesis Continues To Scale...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Faces First Important Resistance Level on Its Way Up]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904538/Ethereum-Faces-First-Important-Resistance-Level-on-Its-Way-Up</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904538/Ethereum-Faces-First-Important-Resistance-Level-on-Its-Way-Up"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T01:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BitMEX Co-Founder: Bitcoin ($BTC) Price Could Surge If Central Banks Keep Hiking Rates]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904524/BitMEX-Co-Founder-Bitcoin-BTC-Price-Could-Surge-If-Central-Banks-Keep-Hiking-Rates</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904524/BitMEX-Co-Founder-Bitcoin-BTC-Price-Could-Surge-If-Central-Banks-Keep-Hiking-Rates"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T00:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The co-founder of the popular cryptocurrency exchange BitMEX has recently suggested that the price of the flagship cryptocurrency Bitcoin ($BTC) could surge if central banks keep on raising interest rates. In a recently published blog post, Hayes challenged the deep-seated belief linking...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Active Addresses Hit 2nd Highest Count Ever, Bottom Signal?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75410fcff3</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-active-addresses-hit-2nd-highest-bottom/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T00:42:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data shows the Ethereum daily active addresses indicator has recently registered its second-highest spike.
 
Ethereum Daily Active Addresses Has Observed A Sharp Spike Recently
 
According to data from the on-chain analytics firm Santiment, the active addresses metric only achieved a higher value in December 2022. The “daily active addresses” indicator measures the daily total number of unique Ethereum blockchain addresses that interact in some way.
 
This metric naturally accounts for both senders and receivers. Note that “unique” means that even if an address makes several transactions in a single day, its contribution towards the active addresses metric will remain just one unit.
 
The benefit of this restriction is that unique addresses can be considered analogous to unique us…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hououin Kyouma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ether rise; Deutsche Bank to provide crypto custody services]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904523/Bitcoin-Ether-rise-Deutsche-Bank-to-provide-crypto-custody-services</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904523/Bitcoin-Ether-rise-Deutsche-Bank-to-provide-crypto-custody-services"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T00:40:53.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dont Miss These 3 Top Crypto | Polygon Matic Ecosystem Winners]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904505/DONT-MISS-THESE-3-TOP-CRYPTO-POLYGON-MATIC-ECOSYSTEM-WINNERS</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904505/DONT-MISS-THESE-3-TOP-CRYPTO-POLYGON-MATIC-ECOSYSTEM-WINNERS"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T00:30:11.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hedera’s stablecoin launch: Why this can accelerate the network’s growth]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904506/Hederas-stablecoin-launch-Why-this-can-accelerate-the-networks-growth</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904506/Hederas-stablecoin-launch-Why-this-can-accelerate-the-networks-growth"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T00:30:07.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase CEO Urges Defi Protocols to Challenge Regulatory Crackdowns in Court]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75410a7cfd</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/coinbase-ceo-urges-defi-protocols-to-challenge-regulatory-crackdowns-in-court/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T00:06:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CEO of the cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase has encouraged decentralized finance (defi) protocols to fight regulators in court if they face regulatory crackdowns. He stressed that the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) “should not be creating enforcement actions against decentralized (defi) protocols,” emphasizing that they are not financial service businesses. “The only thing this is accomplishing is to push an important industry offshore,” Armstrong cautioned.
 
Brian Armstrong Wants Defi Protocols to Fight Regulators in Court
 
The CEO of cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase (Nasdaq: COIN), Brian Armstrong, has urged decentralized finance (defi) protocols to challenge U.S. regulators in court after the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) cracked down on some defi platfo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Trader Says 2019-Style Market Expansion Coming to Crypto Markets – Here’s His Timeline]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904475/Top-Trader-Says-2019-Style-Market-Expansion-Coming-to-Crypto-Markets-Heres-His-Timeline</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904475/Top-Trader-Says-2019-Style-Market-Expansion-Coming-to-Crypto-Markets-Heres-His-Timeline"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T00:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Active Addresses Hit 2nd Highest Count Ever, Bottom Signal?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904483/Ethereum-Active-Addresses-Hit-2nd-Highest-Count-Ever-Bottom-Signal</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904483/Ethereum-Active-Addresses-Hit-2nd-Highest-Count-Ever-Bottom-Signal"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T00:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data shows the Ethereum daily active addresses indicator has recently registered its second-highest spike. Ethereum Daily Active Addresses Has Observed A Sharp Spike Recently According to data from the on-chain analytics firm Santiment, the active addresses metric only achieved a higher...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dreaded Bitcoin Death Cross Returns: Here’s What Happened The Last Time]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7542f43bbd</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dreaded-bitcoin-death-cross/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T23:43:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin has once again flashed another particularly deadly formation that often sends its price into a downward spiral. This time around, a death cross that has not been seen in the digital asset for more than one year has appeared again. This report takes a look at what happened the last time that this particular death cross was flagged.
 
Bitcoin Flashes Rare Death Cross
 
In a post on X (formerly Twitter), pseudonymous crypto analyst Game of Trades has alerted the Bitcoin community to an interesting formation on the BTC chart. The infamous death cross appeared just as the digital asset started marking its support above $25,800, sparking interest.
 
 
According to the analyst, this death cross is formed when the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average, which took p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Best Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin-Only Exchange Swan Pledges to Launch New Custodian with BitGo]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7542f4ca1a</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/bitcoin-exchange-swan-custodian-bitgo"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T23:36:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Swan Bitcoin is offering new insight into how Bitcoin stored on its exchange will be held in custody in the future, following a tumultuous month in which many of the company's users were left looking for clarity.
Announced Thursday, Swan Bitcoin says it intends to partner with BitGo to launch a "Bitcoin-only trust company," one that would require regulatory approval before ultimately being made live for customers.
"This strategic partnership aims to cater to the growing demand for Bitcoin-specific solutions while addressing the critical security and custody requirements within the Bitcoin ecosystem," a press release sent exclusively to Bitcoin Magazine read.
Swan Bitcoin CEO Cory Klippsten said in a statement that the plan is to either acquire an existing trust company, or build one. If th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Ventures Leads the Power Players in Crypto Investments Through Its Exchange]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904449/Coinbase-Ventures-Leads-the-Power-Players-in-Crypto-Investments-Through-Its-Exchange</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904449/Coinbase-Ventures-Leads-the-Power-Players-in-Crypto-Investments-Through-Its-Exchange"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T23:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ryan Selkis, Founder and CEO of crypto data and research firm Messari, recently shared on Twitter (X) that 33 investors have been actively involved in multiple crypto deals throughout this year. Among these investors, Selkis highlighted the “top 20 Chad deployers” in the cryptocurrency space. On...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dreaded Bitcoin Death Cross Returns: Here’s What Happened The Last Time]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904422/Dreaded-Bitcoin-Death-Cross-Returns-Heres-What-Happened-The-Last-Time</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904422/Dreaded-Bitcoin-Death-Cross-Returns-Heres-What-Happened-The-Last-Time"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T23:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Cast It Into the Fire': GOP Moves to Advance Bills That Ban CBDC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156790</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156790/cast-it-into-the-fire-gop-bills-ban-cbdc"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T22:59:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Republicans argue a CBDC would undermine existing stablecoins, and usher Americans down a slippery slope toward mass government surveillance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Cast It Into the Fire': GOP Moves to Advance Bills That Ban CBDC]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904424/Cast-It-Into-the-Fire-GOP-Moves-to-Advance-Bills-That-Ban-CBDC</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904424/Cast-It-Into-the-Fire-GOP-Moves-to-Advance-Bills-That-Ban-CBDC"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T22:59:31.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Defense Startup Helsing Raises $223 Million to 'Protect Democracies']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156787</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156787/ai-defense-startup-helsing-raises-223-million-protect-democracies"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T22:59:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With backing from Saab and General Catalyst, Helsing will focus on AI enhancements for the NATO Eurofighter and Future Combat Air System.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Defense Startup Helsing Raises $223 Million to 'Protect Democracies']]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904425/AI-Defense-Startup-Helsing-Raises-223-Million-to-Protect-Democracies</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904425/AI-Defense-Startup-Helsing-Raises-223-Million-to-Protect-Democracies"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T22:59:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With backing from Saab and General Catalyst, Helsing will focus on AI enhancements for the NATO Eurofighter and Future Combat Air System.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Govt. Should Engage With AI to Support Innovation, Safeguards: Zuckerberg]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904421/Govt-Should-Engage-With-AI-to-Support-Innovation-Safeguards-Zuckerberg</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904421/Govt-Should-Engage-With-AI-to-Support-Innovation-Safeguards-Zuckerberg"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T22:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano’s Catalyst Fund Draws 300K Votes on Over 1.4K Proposals]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904414/Cardanos-Catalyst-Fund-Draws-300K-Votes-on-Over-14K-Proposals</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904414/Cardanos-Catalyst-Fund-Draws-300K-Votes-on-Over-14K-Proposals"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T22:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Project Catalyst’s Community Voting has concluded, revealing interesting trends within this year’s proposals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bybit denies earlier reports that the exchange will exit UK]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904408/Bybit-denies-earlier-reports-that-the-exchange-will-exit-UK</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904408/Bybit-denies-earlier-reports-that-the-exchange-will-exit-UK"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T22:45:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bybit announced on Sept. 14 that it intends to continue operating its crypto exchange in the U.K., contradicting earlier reports that it would exit that country. On Twitter/X, a company spokesperson wrote: “We consider the UK to be a highly important market for the advancement of crypto and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Mt. Gox CEO Responds To FTX’s Sam Bankman-Fried Requesting For Freedom Before Trial]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7542f1325f</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/mt-gox-sam-bankman-fried/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T22:43:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The former CEO of the defunct Bitcoin exchange Mt. Gox, Mark Karpelès, has drawn an analogy between his case and that of FTX’s former CEO Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF) following the latter’s persistent request to be released in order to prepare his defense for his upcoming trial in October adequately. 
 
Only A Calculator To Work With
 
In a tweet shared on his X (formerly Twitter) platform, Karpelès stated that he had only a “simple calculator” to work with when he was arrested back in 2015. This was the “most computing power” he got when he had to review “20000 pages of evidence including over 5000 pages of accounting.” 
 
Related Reading: Binance.US Woes Continue As CEO Steps Down Amid Layoffs
 
He was, however, able to work with what he had as he credits the calculator as being integral to h…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SoftBank's Arm Stock Soars 25% as AI Chip Designer's IPO Nets $65 Billion Valuation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156772</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156772/softbank-arm-stock-soars-25-ai-chip-designer-ipo-nets-65-billion-valuation"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T22:10:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apparently fueled by AI hype, semiconductor technology company Arm Holdings had a sensational Nasdaq return on Thursday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMI Vantage Expands Crypto Reach With New Bitcoin Mining Facility in Sarawak]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7542fcbada</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/smi-vantage-expands-crypto-reach-with-new-bitcoin-mining-facility-in-sarawak/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T22:06:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Singapore-based investment management and software-as-a-service (SaaS) provider, SMI Vantage, plans to launch a bitcoin mining facility in the state of Sarawak in Borneo, Malaysia. The company has signed a rental agreement and anticipates operations to begin by the end of the third quarter.
 
SMI Vantage Charts New Territory With Sarawak Bitcoin Mining Venture
 
According to a report from The Edge Singapore, SMI Vantage, an investment and SaaS firm, has disclosed its intention to commence bitcoin mining operations in Sarawak. The firm is in the process of setting up two containers equipped with application-specific integrated circuit mining machines. Operations are projected to start by October 1, 2023, or the conclusion of the third quarter.
 
SMI’s recent agreement was advised by Sovereign Systemtechnik, a Singapore-based engineering and technology firm. The deal was inked in September 2022 and marks SMI’s third bitcoin mining venture. While SMI already has operations in Melaka, Malaysia, it also boasts a bitcoin mining facility in Bandar Seri Begawan, Brunei’s capital. Beyond SaaS and cryptocurrency mining, SMI has a keen interest in artificial intelligence (AI) and predictive analytics solutions.
 
 
While bitcoin mining is legal in Malaysia, using stolen electricity for crypto mining is highly discouraged. Reports indicate that from 2018, illegal crypto mining activities resulted in a loss of RM2.3 billion ($491,610) for Malaysia, with over 7,200 cases documented. SMI states that in Melaka, the company pays $0.07 to $0.08 per kilowatt-hour (kWh) and $0.05 to $0.06 per kWh in Bandar Seri Begawan.
 
What do you think about SMI expanding crypto mining operations to Sarawak? Share your thoughts and opinions about this subject in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Co-Founder Predicts: Crypto’s Future In The US Will Be Embraced]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7542ff15dc</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-co-founder-regulators-will-embrace-crypto/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T21:43:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent interview with CNBC’s “Capital Connection,” Joseph Lubin, co-founder of Ethereum (ETH) and CEO of ConsenSys, expressed his confidence that US regulators will recognize the alignment between decentralized protocols, blockchain technology, and the underlying philosophies that founded the United States. 
 
As the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) engages in legal battles with various crypto firms, Lubin remains optimistic that “clear heads will prevail.”
 
 
Ethereum Co-Founder Calls For A Nuanced Regulatory Approach
 
Lubin drew parallels to past technological advancements, such as the internet, the web, and crypto, emphasizing the eventual acceptance and integration of these innovations into society. 
 
Lubin anticipates a similar trajectory for decentralized protocols…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Christie's Turns Keith Haring Digital Art Into NFC-Equipped Patch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156777</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156777/christies-turns-keith-haring-digital-art-nfc-equipped-patch"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T21:15:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MNTGE and the auction house transformed one of Keith Haring's works—currently on sale as an NFT—into a patch with its own proof of ownership.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephanie Hirschmiller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Dilemma Of Distributing Tokens On XRP Ledger: Ripple CTO Chimes In]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7542e55af0</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/xrp-ledger-ripple-cto/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T20:43:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Xahau, a new smart contract sidechain, is set to launch, and as part of efforts to boost interoperability between the XRP Ledger and Xahau, the Chief Technology Officer of XRPL Labs, Richard AH, has proposed making an amendment to XRPL’s mainnet. 
 
A Reversed Burn2Mint Mechanism
 
In a tweet shared on his X (formerly Twitter) platform, Richard AH noted that XRP’s mainnet doesn’t support reversed Burn2Mint for issued currencies. According to him, if the protocol were to be amended, it would allow any form of wrapped XRP to be moved in both directions (from the XRP mainnet to the Xahau sidechain and back). 
 
 
Richard further noted that this amendment could also allow the wrapped XRP to be counter-party free if it was “made via a transactor on mainnet.” He stated this proposed move could h…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance.US Sees More Key Departures: Chief Risk Officer and Legal Head Exit]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7542e6aa23</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/binanceus-sees-more-key-departures-chief-risk-officer-and-legal-head-exit/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T20:31:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The winds of change continue to sweep through Binance.US  
as the cryptocurrency exchange witnesses the departure of two more high-ranking  
executives. The Head of Legal, Krishna Juvvadi, and the Chief Risk Officer,  
Sidney Majalya, have decided to part ways with the exchange.
This latest shake-up  
comes in the wake of CEO Brian Shroder's recent exit and coincides with  
escalating regulatory scrutiny. Juvvadi, who joined the company in May of the  
previous year, and Majalya, who assumed his role in December 2021, have chosen  
to leave their positions, as reported by the Wall Street Journal, citing  
insider sources.
Regulatory Storms Cause Executive Exit
While the reasons behind  
these departures remain undisclosed, their timing is conspicuous. Brian  
Shroder, the CEO of the Americ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gods Unchained's Daniel Paez on the Future of NFT Gaming Interoperability]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/obt7FGYr/gods-unchaineds-daniel-paez-on-the-future-of-nft-gaming-interoperability</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/obt7FGYr/gods-unchaineds-daniel-paez-on-the-future-of-nft-gaming-interoperability"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T20:27:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daniel Paez, executive producer on NFT card-battling game Gods Unchained, speaks with Decrypt Culture Editor Andrew Hayward about what the future of NFT game interoperability will really look like—and what it won't.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Inanity of the SEC 'Stoner Cat' Action]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7542e76e0b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/09/14/the-inanity-of-the-sec-stoner-cat-action/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T20:24:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's as stupid as it sounds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Kuhn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LaLiga NFT Fantasy Soccer Games Coming to North America]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156757</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156757/laliga-nft-fantasy-soccer-games-coming-north-america"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T20:17:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spanish soccer league LaLiga has tapped gaming startup GameOn to develop fantasy games built around NFTs for the U.S. and Canada.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Cohen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paul Krugman: ‘The War on Inflation Is Pretty Much Won’ – Claims ‘Remarkable Disinflation’ Occurred]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7542e1a19e</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/paul-krugman-the-war-on-inflation-is-pretty-much-won-claims-remarkable-disinflation-occurred/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T20:05:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Wednesday, Nobel Prize-winning economist Paul Krugman provided a brief analysis of the current economic landscape in the United States. Krugman asserted that the nation has experienced “remarkable disinflation.” According to him, the available data paints a compelling picture, suggesting that the “war on inflation has been pretty much won — without a recession.” Krugman emphasized that inflation turned out “to be transitory,” contrary to initial apprehensions.
 
Krugman Declares Victory — ‘Inflation Turns Out to Have Been Transitory After All’
 
On Wednesday, the U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics (BLS) unveiled its eagerly anticipated Consumer Price Index (CPI) report, shedding light on the nation’s current inflation rate. The report revealed a notable surge in the CPI for all urban consu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple CEO Has Important Message For Crypto Community Regarding Regulation]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7542e3f084</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ripple-ceo-important-message-for-crypto-community/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T19:44:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the debate for implementing crypto regulation continues to surface, Brad Garlinghouse, CEO of Ripple, has recently shared his perspective. 
 
At a recent conference in Singapore, Garlinghouse highlighted the importance of crafting appropriate regulatory frameworks for the crypto industry.
 
The Necessity Of Proper Regulation
 
While appearing at Token 2049 in Singapore, Garlinghouse emphasized the inevitability of governmental involvement in crypto. Garlinghouse highlighted a prevailing sentiment among certain factions of the crypto community that vehemently opposes any form of regulation.
 
 
According to the Ripple CEO, this is a stance that, if perpetuated, may hinder the industry’s long-term growth. Garlinghouse stated: 
 

In my judgment, if we want this industry to thrive and fund…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Most Important U.S. Senator for Crypto’s Future Tells Regulators to Use Existing Powers]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7542ecacee</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/09/14/most-important-us-senator-for-cryptos-future-tells-regulators-to-use-existing-powers/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T19:38:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Sen. Sherrod Brown (D-Ohio), whose chairmanship of the Senate Banking Committee gives him power over crypto’s congressional destiny, issued a call to arms to regulators on Thursday, demanding that they use whatever authority they currently have over digital assets to improve market transparency and protect the investors putting their money into the sector.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bull Bitcoin Exchange Expands From Canada to Costa Rica]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156750</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156750/bull-bitcoin-exchange-expands-canada-costa-rica"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T19:29:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company announced that it will tap into Costa Rica's widely used payment infrastructure SINPE Movil for Bitcoin swaps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Princess Peach to Pikachu: 6 Biggest Reveals From Nintendo Direct]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156719</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156719/from-princess-peach-to-pikachu-6-biggest-reveals-from-nintendo-direct"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T18:58:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Nintendo Direct stream offered fans a look at loads of upcoming Switch games. Here's a look at the biggest announcements and trailers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance US Legal and Risk Heads Step Down Amid Exec Exodus]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156716</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156716/binance-us-legal-and-risk-heads-step-down-amid-exec-exodus"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T18:46:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest departures include legal head Krishna Juvvadi and Chief Risk Officer Sidney Majalya, according to a report from WSJ.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aliens in Mexico's Congress: Earth-Shattering Revelation or Another Hoax?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156710</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156710/aliens-mexico-congress-revelation-or-hoax"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T18:46:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's not the first time supposed alien mummies were rolled out into a legislative building in Latin America—and by the same "ufologist."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chainalysis Crypto Adoption Index Shares Insights: Here Are The Countries Leading The Charge]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7542eae914</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-adoption-countries/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T18:45:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New York-based blockchain data analytics firm Chainalysis shared insights on its crypto adoption index for 2023 on Tuesday, September 12, 2023, revealing the top countries leading the charge in terms of grassroots cryptocurrency adoption.
 
Leading Countries In Terms Of Grassroot Cryptocurrency Adoption
 
Following an excerpt released by the blockchain data analytics firm Chainalysis on September 12, 2023, based on a variety of parameters to determine grassroots cryptocurrency adoption, India, Nigeria, and Vietnam have secured the top three positions respectively to become the leading countries in grassroots cryptocurrency adoption in 2023.
 
 
According to the index, the lower-middle-income (LMI) countries were identified to be leading the way in grassroots crypto adoption over the past 1…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joy Division NFT Includes Previously Unheard Ian Curtis Audio]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156720</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156720/joy-division-nft-includes-previously-unheard-ian-curtis-audio"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T18:45:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joy Division drummer Stephen Morris and "Unknown Pleasures" artist Peter Saville created the upcoming audiovisual project from Pace Verso.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ali Shutler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Exchange Updates Marketing and Fees After Hong Kong Regulator Warning]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156730</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156730/crypto-exchange-updates-marketing-and-fees-after-hong-kong-regulator-warning"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T18:32:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong requires crypto firms to register with its securities regulator. According to SFC, JPEX never applied for a license.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Singapore’s Monetary Authority Issues 9-Year Ban on Three Arrows Capital Founders]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7542d5f112</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/singapores-monetary-authority-issues-9-year-ban-on-three-arrows-capital-founders/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T18:22:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS) has issued nine-year prohibition orders against Three Arrows Capital (3AC) founders Zhu Su and Kyle Davies, banning them from regulated financial activities in the country. The orders come after a MAS investigation that reportedly uncovered multiple violations of securities laws by the now-defunct crypto hedge fund and its directors.
 
MAS Slaps 9-Year Ban on Three Arrows Capital Founders Over Violations
 
The prohibition orders prevent Zhu and Davies from performing any regulated activity or taking part in managing or becoming a major shareholder of any Singapore capital market services firm. The notice disclosed that the bans took effect on September 13.
 
MAS first reprimanded 3AC in June for providing false information and exceeding assets unde…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Jumps as European Central Bank Signals End to Rate Hikes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156714</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156714/bitcoin-jumps-as-european-central-bank-signals-end-to-rate-hikes"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T18:18:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The central bank said Thursday its current interest rate level may reign in inflation if "maintained" for long enough.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Genesis’ Exit: Crypto Lender Shuts Down All Trading Operations]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7542d0e170</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/genesis-exit-crypto-lender-shuts-down-all-trading-operations/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T18:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a dramatic turn of events, Genesis, the now-bankrupt  
crypto lender, has brought its entire crypto trading venture to an abrupt halt.  
The decision to cease all trading operations, including its international spot  
and derivatives trading services, comes amid legal disputes involving FTX and  
Gemini.
Genesis Global Trading,  
a subsidiary of Genesis Global, recently announced plans to close its U.S.-focused spot crypto  
trading operations by the end of this month, a report by Coindesk indicated.  
GGT will cease its over-the-counter trading platform's operations on September  
18, 2023. 
While Genesis Global  
Trading is winding  
down its U.S. operations,  
GGC International Limited, another trading-focused entity affiliated with  
Genesis, will reportedly continue operating GGT's…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bright Horizons: Fideum Group Anchors Spot in Mastercard Lighthouse Elite Program]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7542d201d1</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bright-horizons-fideum-group-anchors-spot-in-mastercard-lighthouse-elite-program/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T17:52:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. Fideum Group, an ambitious financial aggregator renowned for its commitment to enhancing both retail and institutional client experiences, announced its notable inclusion in the prestigious Mastercard Lighthouse FINITIV 2023 Fall Program. As one of 15 selectees from the Nordic and Baltic regions, Fideum Group is poised to redefine the fintech industry alongside other innovators, startups, and early-stage scaleups.
 
A Legacy of Innovation and Dedication
 
Born from the strategic union of GenBlock and blockbank, Fideum Group, the London-based entity, has since its inception demonstrated an unwavering commitment to pushing the boundaries of fintech solutions. The merger signified not just the unification of two powerful entities but also their shared vision of a more integrate…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance.US Head of Legal and Chief Risk Officer Leaving the Crypto Exchange: WSJ]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7542d23a85</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/09/14/binanceus-head-of-legal-and-chief-risk-officer-leaving-the-crypto-exchange-wsj/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T17:50:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The departure comes just days after the crypto exchange lost its CEO Brian Shroder.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aoyon Ashraf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried’s Father Attended Meetings on FTX Token Marketing and Tax Issues]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156704</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156704/sam-bankman-frieds-father-attended-meetings-on-ftx-token-marketing-and-tax-issues"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T17:37:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried’s father did more than appear in a commercial for FTX with comedian Larry David, per Bloomberg.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amboss Wants to Solve the Bitcoin Lightning Network Liquidity Problem]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156635</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156635/amboss-wants-to-solve-businesses-bitcoin-lightning-network-liquidity-problem"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T16:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Without liquidity, payments simply aren't possible,” Amboss CEO Jesse Shrader told Decrypt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alyssa Hertig</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deutsche Bank To Offer Crypto Custody With Swiss Fintech Taurus]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156670</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156670/deutsche-bank-to-offer-crypto-custody-with-swiss-fintech-taurus"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T12:03:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bank will establish digital asset custody and tokenization services, in a sign that "institutional interest is building," said Taurus.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3AC’s Su Zhu, Kyle Davies Slapped With 9-Year Finance Ban by Singapore Monetary Authority]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156666</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156666/3acs-zhu-su-kyle-davies-slapped-with-9-year-finance-ban-by-singapore-monetary-authority"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T11:34:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company hired a hedge fund manager without notifying authorities and then traded crypto with no risk framework in place.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase CEO: DeFi Projects Should Take Regulators to Court to ‘Establish Precedent’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156665</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156665/coinbase-ceo-defi-projects-should-take-regulators-to-court-to-establish-precedent"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T11:16:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brian Armstrong argued that the CFTC shouldn't be taking action against DeFi protocols, and that the courts would likely "uphold rule of law."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Like Star Wars Collectibles': SEC Commissioners Dissent on Stoner Cats Enforcement]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156659</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156659/like-star-wars-collectibles-sec-commissioners-dissent-on-stoner-cats-enforcement"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T10:27:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two SEC commissioners dissented on the regulator’s action against the Stoner Cats NFT series, likening them to 1970s Star Wars collectibles.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ralph Lauren, Burberry Alum Launches Digital Fashion Platform SYKY]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156644</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156644/ralph-lauren-burberry-alum-launches-digital-fashion-platform-syky"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T10:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The platform, which will offer both digital and physical fashion items, seeks to coax the traditional fashion industry onto the blockchain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diesel Debuts Digital Apparel for Meta Avatars With DressX]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156593</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156593/diesel-launches-digital-apparel-meta-avatars-dressx"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T08:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fashion brand Diesel joins the likes of Valentino and Balenciaga in dropping digital clothes on the Meta Avatars Store.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephanie Hirschmiller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Proposed California Legislation Would Protect Actors From AI Copycats]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156625</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156625/proposed-california-legislation-protect-actors-ai-copycats"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T01:42:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Assemblymember Ash Kalra's bill targets vague contracts that exploit an actor's digital likeness without clear consent or representation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No Bubble Here: Goldman Sachs Says AI Still in Early Stages]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156626</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156626/no-bubble-here-goldman-sachs-says-ai-still-in-early-stages"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T00:49:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Goldman Sachs foresees a promising future for AI investments, debunking bubble theories and projecting a bullish market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Game Developers Are 'Fucking Livid' Over Unity's New Fees]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156592</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156592/game-developers-fucking-livid-over-unity-new-fees"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T23:08:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The popular game engine's new fees have left some developers feeling stuck, although Unity is trying to explain its way out of the unrest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Up-and-Coming Generative Artists to Keep Your Eye On]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155352</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155352/community-spotlight-generative-artists-keep-your-eye-on"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T22:16:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The generative art world is thriving, and exciting new artists keep emerging all the time. Here are a few that you should know.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abigail Carlson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can't Beat the Real Thing? AI Is Making Coca-Cola Flavors Now]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156609</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156609/you-cant-beat-real-thing-ai-making-coca-cola-flavors-now"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T21:52:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t call it New Coke. Global beverage giant Coca-Cola offers a glimpse of the future with a new flavor co-created with AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It Wasn't PayPal—Paxos Fat Fingered $510,000 Bitcoin Transaction]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156571</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156571/it-wasnt-paypal-paxos-fat-fingered-510000-bitcoin-transaction"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T20:29:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paxos is now working with the lucky miner who received the fee to get its money back.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pedophile Rings Are Using AI to Create Child Pornography, UK Group Warns]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156558</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156558/pedophile-rings-are-using-ai-to-create-child-pornography-warns-iwf-uk-group"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T19:48:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The IWF says AI-generated child sexual abuse material is being spread on the dark web, complicating law enforcement efforts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Happens to Mila Kunis' Stoner Cats NFTs After SEC Settlement?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156555</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156555/what-happens-mila-kunis-stoner-cats-nfts-after-sec-settlement"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T19:44:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Questions remain as to the fate of the star-studded NFT animated series which was slapped with an SEC action Wednesday. Here's what we know.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Gets Court Approval to Sell Billions in Bitcoin, Ethereum and Solana]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156498</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156498/ftx-gets-approval-to-sell-bitcoin-ethereum-solana"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T18:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The collapsed exchange's new management now can sell billions of dollars in Solana, Bitcoin and other assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stoner Cats NFT Sales Surge After SEC Reveals Charges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156428</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156428/stoner-cats-nft-sales-surge-after-sec-reveals-charges"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T17:52:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enforcement action against the Mila Kunis-led cartoon series Stoner Cats has apparently led to a jump in NFT sales and prices alike.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mila Kunis' Stoner Cats NFT Project Sued by SEC, Settles for $1 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156245</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156245/mila-kunis-stoner-cats-nft-project-sued-by-sec-settles-for-1-million"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T14:54:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The creators of NFT-based cartoon series Stoner Cats will pay a civil fine and establish a fund to reimburse investors, as well.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward,Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Metamask]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156246</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156246/how-to-use-metamask"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T14:47:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MetaMask is a leading crypto wallet, and relies on browser integration and good design to serve as one of the main gateways to the world of Web3, decentralized finance (DeFi) and NFTs. Here's how it works, and how to get started with it. What Is MetaMask? MetaMask is a browser extension and mobile app that […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Euny Hong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Hold Ground Despite Rising Inflation in August]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156184</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156184/bitcoin-ethereum-hold-ground-despite-rising-inflation-in-august"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T12:52:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Inflation has fallen steadily since 9.1% last June, but it’s still above the Fed’s target of 2%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Judge Dismisses Sam Bankman-Fried's Pretrial Jail Release Request]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156183</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156183/judge-dismisses-sam-bankman-frieds-pretrial-jail-release-request"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T11:01:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Judge Lewis A. Kaplan explained that the FTX founder doesn’t have “a constitutional right to inspect every bit of discovery.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Exchange CoinEx Shuts Down Withdrawals Following Suspected Hack of $27M]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156173</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156173/crypto-exchange-coinex-shuts-down-withdrawals-following-suspected-hack-of-27m"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T10:30:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The exchange identified a number of suspicious wallets draining funds from the platform in "anomalous withdrawals."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alys Key</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TON Surges 13% after Telegram Integrates Blockchain’s Web3 Wallet]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156166</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156166/ton-surges-13-after-telegram-integrates-blockchains-web3-wallet"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T10:04:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The TON wallet is now accessible to the Telegram messaging app’s 800 million strong user base, prompting an overnight surge in the token’s price.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram Gets a Crypto Wallet—3 Years After SEC Pumped the Brakes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156109</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156109/telegram-gets-crypto-wallet-3-years-after-sec-pumped-brakes"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T06:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in 2020, Telegram announced an end to its participation in TON after the SEC filed suit. But now they're back together again.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Mino Games is Using Artificial Intelligence]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/SrT1Afj7/how-mino-games-is-using-artificial-intelligence</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/SrT1Afj7/how-mino-games-is-using-artificial-intelligence"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T22:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mino Games CEO Sasha McKinnon tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about how the studio's upcoming game Dimensionals will use real-time AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INTERVIEW: How Will Aurory Use NFTs and Crypto?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qv3VwNmM/interview-how-will-aurory-use-nfts-and-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qv3VwNmM/interview-how-will-aurory-use-nfts-and-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T15:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Natoli, Aurory's Head of Marketing and Business Development, tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how the Aurory games will use NFTs and crypto and shares the studio's broader stance on the tech.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Cloud's James Tromans on the Intersection of AI and Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OeD4uoLj/google-clouds-james-tromans-on-the-intersection-of-ai-and-web3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OeD4uoLj/google-clouds-james-tromans-on-the-intersection-of-ai-and-web3"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google's Global Head of Google Cloud for Web3 James Tromans sat down with Decrypt's Jason Nelson to discuss how AI can help Web3 companies come to market faster and the real value of Web3 tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastering NFT Trading - Degen U]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/HQGt1Vrq/mastering-nft-trading-degen-u</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/HQGt1Vrq/mastering-nft-trading-degen-u"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T07:08:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Take Degen U's new course, Mastering NFT Trading, and earn an on-chain certificate. A top instructor will help you identify trends, seize the right moment to trade, weed out scams—and have fun while doing it!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Space Nation CEO on Working With 'Independence Day' Director Roland Emmerich]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LpznLhtx/space-nation-ceo-on-working-with-independence-day-director-roland-emmerich</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LpznLhtx/space-nation-ceo-on-working-with-independence-day-director-roland-emmerich"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T17:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jerome Wu, CEO of Space Nation, tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the upcoming Space Nation Online game in development and shares details on Space Nation Cofounder Roland Emmerich's role in the project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GAME REVIEW: Champions Arena from Gala Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qUE1RlDx/game-review-champions-arena-from-gala-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qUE1RlDx/game-review-champions-arena-from-gala-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Champions Arena is a turn-based fantasy RPG from Gala Games, where characters can become NFTs and crypto can be used to purchase gems, one of the game's synthetic currencies. Decrypt's Kate Irwin takes us inside the game for her thoughts on the fun, mobile-first title.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apex Legends Voice Actor Ben Prendergast on the Future of Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/X3RKdsaG/apex-legends-voice-actor-ben-prendergast-on-the-future-of-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/X3RKdsaG/apex-legends-voice-actor-ben-prendergast-on-the-future-of-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T18:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Voice actor Ben Prendergast, who's voiced characters in games like Apex Legends and God of War Ragnarok, shares his opinions on the tech space's history of "bubbles" and whether blockchain gaming has a future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Future of AI Stardom and Robotics With SingularityNET COO Janet Adams and Desdemona]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yVQaZI71/the-future-of-ai-stardom-and-robotics-with-singularitynet-coo-janet-adams-and-desdemona</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yVQaZI71/the-future-of-ai-stardom-and-robotics-with-singularitynet-coo-janet-adams-and-desdemona"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T16:45:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this interview, SingularityNET COO Janet Adams explains the intricate details that went into creating the Desdemona robot AI from Hanson Robotics and future plans for the AI Diva.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto a 'No-Brainer' for Video Games, Says Mino Games CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rdynom8C/crypto-a-no-brainer-for-video-games-says-mino-games-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rdynom8C/crypto-a-no-brainer-for-video-games-says-mino-games-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T18:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mino Games CEO Sasha MacKinnon, developer of the upcoming Dimensionals game, tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the studio's approach to digital collectibles.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Wagner's 'Controversial Take' on Crypto in Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tc2nKeqA/michael-wagners-controversial-take-on-crypto-in-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tc2nKeqA/michael-wagners-controversial-take-on-crypto-in-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T16:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Solana's PlayGG, Star Atlas CEO Michael Wagner shares his "controversial take" on crypto in games, shares the challenges of developing the upcoming scifi game, and how crypto's volatility has changed his perspective with Decrypt's Jason Nelson.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interview: Angelic CEO on Building the Sci-Fi RPG on Solana and Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/uCzW3K7P/interview-angelic-ceo-on-building-the-sci-fi-rpg-on-solana-and-ethereum</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/uCzW3K7P/interview-angelic-ceo-on-building-the-sci-fi-rpg-on-solana-and-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T15:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Angelic is a sci-fi roleplay game in development that will be free-to-play and offer optional, opt-in crypto features on Solana and Ethereum and a governance token. Metaverse Game Studios CEO and Founder Erkan Bayol tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how he sees AAA traditional games as Angelic's main competitors and shares his vision for the game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apex Legends Voice Actor on AI's Impact on Video Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IOIrmb0N/apex-legends-voice-actor-on-ais-impact-on-video-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IOIrmb0N/apex-legends-voice-actor-on-ais-impact-on-video-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T17:28:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ben Prendergast is an actor who has voiced characters like Apex Legends' Fuse, God of War Ragnarok's Tyr, and Patroclus in Hades. But as debates swirl around the use of artificial intelligence in entertainment in light of the SAG-AFTRA and WGA strikes, Prendergast gives Decrypt's Kate Irwin his honest take on the potential use of AI actors in games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>