<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-11-23T12:29:12.157Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-11-23T12:29:12.157Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[60M+ HT Sent to HTX Exchange Platform Following Hack]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19058655/60M-HT-Sent-to-HTX-Exchange-Platform-Following-Hack</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19058655/60M-HT-Sent-to-HTX-Exchange-Platform-Following-Hack"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T12:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The whale tracking platform Whale Alert shared on X today that a substantial amount of Huobi Token (HT) was sent to the HTX exchange, formerly known as Huobi. According to the post, 60,005,287 HT, worth $177,900,201, was transferred from the Heco Chain. Meanwhile, over the past 24 hours, HT’s...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin user overpays $3 million in fees for a single transaction]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19058653/Bitcoin-user-overpays-3-million-in-fees-for-a-single-transaction</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19058653/Bitcoin-user-overpays-3-million-in-fees-for-a-single-transaction"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T12:16:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The whopping 83.65 BTC fee sets a new record in U.S. dollar terms for a single Bitcoin transaction, more than six times the previous.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 6 DeFi Lending Platforms]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19058656/Top-6-DeFi-Lending-Platforms</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19058656/Top-6-DeFi-Lending-Platforms"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T12:16:18.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano Founder Shares What To Expect After Binance CEO’s Exit]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e749d3564cc</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/cardano-founder-binance-ceo-exit/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T12:09:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The founder of Cardano has provided detailed insights into the impacts of the Binance CEO’s exit. He emphasized the shift in Binance’s management structure as it falls under the supervision of the US government. He also highlighted the possibilities of increased regulatory scrutiny in the growing crypto space. 
 
The End Of An Era, Says Cardano Founder
 
Founder of Cardano, Charles Hoskinson posted a YouTube video titled “The end of an era.” In the video, Hoskinson describes the resignation of Binance’s former CEO, Changpeng Zhao as the end of an era. He described Zhao from his early days when he grew Binance to becoming one of the world’s largest crypto exchanges. 
 
 
“The era of the Crypto industry I grew up in is over and Binance was the last hold out to that, and I’ve kind of watched …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Massive Amount Of Older DOGE Moving': Dogecoin Whales Awaken As 1M+ Wallets Keep Growing]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19058647/Massive-Amount-Of-Older-DOGE-Moving-Dogecoin-Whales-Awaken-As-1M-Wallets-Keep-Growing</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19058647/Massive-Amount-Of-Older-DOGE-Moving-Dogecoin-Whales-Awaken-As-1M-Wallets-Keep-Growing"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T12:03:42.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[After FTX shock, Bitcoin holders brace for the long haul with record dormancy]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19058624/After-FTX-shock-Bitcoin-holders-brace-for-the-long-haul-with-record-dormancy</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19058624/After-FTX-shock-Bitcoin-holders-brace-for-the-long-haul-with-record-dormancy"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T12:02:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quick Take Over 70% of the existing Bitcoin supply has remained unmoved for a year, marking a significant rise. This uptick is primarily attributed to the wave of buyers who emerged after the FTX collapse in November last year when Bitcoin fell to $15,500. The 14-day change in this unmoved...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano Founder Shares What To Expect After Binance CEO’s Exit]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19058621/Cardano-Founder-Shares-What-To-Expect-After-Binance-CEOs-Exit</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19058621/Cardano-Founder-Shares-What-To-Expect-After-Binance-CEOs-Exit"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T12:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The founder of Cardano has provided detailed insights into the impacts of the Binance CEO’s exit. He emphasized the shift in Binance’s management structure as it falls under the supervision of the US government. He also highlighted the possibilities of increased regulatory scrutiny in the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Chopping Block: What Does Binance’s Record $4.3 Billion Settlement Mean for Crypto? - Ep. 573]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19058635/The-Chopping-Block-What-Does-Binances-Record-43-Billion-Settlement-Mean-for-Crypto-Ep-573</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19058635/The-Chopping-Block-What-Does-Binances-Record-43-Billion-Settlement-Mean-for-Crypto-Ep-573"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to The Chopping Block – where crypto insiders Haseeb Qureshi, Tom Schmidt, Tarun Chitra, and Robert Leshner chop it up about the latest news. This week, the gang breaks down the record $4.3 billion settlement between Binance and the U.S. government — whether it was fair, the chances CEO...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase v. SEC: Here's What's Happening Now]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19058604/Coinbase-v-SEC-Heres-Whats-Happening-Now</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19058604/Coinbase-v-SEC-Heres-Whats-Happening-Now"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T11:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP gears up for a massive move to this price]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19058589/XRP-gears-up-for-a-massive-move-to-this-price</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19058589/XRP-gears-up-for-a-massive-move-to-this-price"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T11:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Effect on FTX Token! While FTT Climbed to the Top, Santiment Evaluated the Rise!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19058580/Binance-Effect-on-FTX-Token-While-FTT-Climbed-to-the-Top-Santiment-Evaluated-the-Rise</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19058580/Binance-Effect-on-FTX-Token-While-FTT-Climbed-to-the-Top-Santiment-Evaluated-the-Rise"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T11:47:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is the reason for the rise in FTT, the native token of FTX, the cryptocurrency exchange that went bankrupt in November 2022? Santiment evaluated. Continue Reading: Binance Effect on FTX Token! While FTT Climbed to the Top, Santiment Evaluated the Rise!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Layer 2 Blast Has Crypto Users Split on Its Impact]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e749d30b051</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/11/23/ethereum-layer-2-blast-has-crypto-users-split-on-its-impact/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T11:46:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blast, a layer-2 blockchain that will go live in March, has garnered more than $225 million in staked assets since Monday, but many crypto investors remain skeptical.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight, Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evernode Announces Airdrop For XRP Holders, Sets Launch Date]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19058572/Evernode-Announces-Airdrop-For-XRP-Holders-Sets-Launch-Date</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19058572/Evernode-Announces-Airdrop-For-XRP-Holders-Sets-Launch-Date"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T11:44:41.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA) Breakthrough Fails: Can Price Move Up Again?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19058544/Cardano-ADA-Breakthrough-Fails-Can-Price-Move-Up-Again</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19058544/Cardano-ADA-Breakthrough-Fails-Can-Price-Move-Up-Again"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T11:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano has failed to move past substantial resistance level, unfortunately future remains bleak]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a Satoshi? Smallest Unit on the Bitcoin Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19058547/What-is-a-Satoshi-Smallest-Unit-on-the-Bitcoin-Blockchain</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19058547/What-is-a-Satoshi-Smallest-Unit-on-the-Bitcoin-Blockchain"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T11:38:52.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring DefiLlama: An Extensive Guide to DeFi Tracking]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19058548/Exploring-DefiLlama-An-Extensive-Guide-to-DeFi-Tracking</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19058548/Exploring-DefiLlama-An-Extensive-Guide-to-DeFi-Tracking"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T11:33:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This guide unravels the complexities of DeFiLlama’s functions, such as yield analytics, an easy user interface, and multi-chain compatibility. Let us therefore travel together to explore what it means for Defillama and its role in promoting transparency, risk mitigation, and informed...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana protocol fees jump as SOL targets more upside]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19058534/Solana-protocol-fees-jump-as-SOL-targets-more-upside</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19058534/Solana-protocol-fees-jump-as-SOL-targets-more-upside"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T11:30:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Activity on Solana increased, resulting in more fees for the network. Technical indicators suggest that SOL may rise above $60. In the last 30 days, the Solana [SOL] protocol's fees have inc]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Upstart Eyes Market Gap Following BNB Price Crash]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19058646/Crypto-Upstart-Eyes-Market-Gap-Following-BNB-Price-Crash</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19058646/Crypto-Upstart-Eyes-Market-Gap-Following-BNB-Price-Crash"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amid Binance’s recent regulatory turmoil, CEO Changpeng Zhao agreed to step down and the price of BNB took a hit, plummeting over 9% in the past 24 hours. However, at the same time, a rising player, InQubeta (QUBE) is catching attention with its unique approach to democratizing investments in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Where’s the Bitcoin Withdrawn From Binance Going Following the DOJ Saga?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19058514/Wheres-the-Bitcoin-Withdrawn-From-Binance-Going-Following-the-DOJ-Saga</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19058514/Wheres-the-Bitcoin-Withdrawn-From-Binance-Going-Following-the-DOJ-Saga"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T11:27:10.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Layer 2 Blast Has Crypto Users Split on Its Impact]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19058535/Ethereum-Layer-2-Blast-Has-Crypto-Users-Split-on-Its-Impact</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19058535/Ethereum-Layer-2-Blast-Has-Crypto-Users-Split-on-Its-Impact"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T11:25:51.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase rallies for firm crypto regulations amid SEC scrutiny]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19058567/Coinbase-rallies-for-firm-crypto-regulations-amid-SEC-scrutiny</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19058567/Coinbase-rallies-for-firm-crypto-regulations-amid-SEC-scrutiny"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T11:25:09.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Poised for December Surge, CEO Kaj Leroy Claims]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19058524/XRP-Poised-for-December-Surge-CEO-Kaj-Leroy-Claims</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19058524/XRP-Poised-for-December-Surge-CEO-Kaj-Leroy-Claims"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T11:24:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kaj Leroy, CEO and founder of XPUNKS NFTs and onXRP, finds the current narrative around XRP “very interesting.” He shared a list of reasons why he believes “chances would be greater to have a good December” for XRP. At the top of the list, Leroy claimed that the new Binance CEO, Richard Teng, is “an […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Korea to Pilot CBDC With 100,000 Citizens in 2024: Report]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e749d3e31dc</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/11/23/south-korea-to-pilot-cbdc-with-100000-citizens-in-2024-report/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T11:08:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bank of Korea sees a CBDC as a potential answer to problems with existing government-issued grant systems, such as during the COVID-19 pandemic or childcare vouchers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Binance CEO Faces Travel Restrictions Ahead Of Sentencing]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e749d3f3c93</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/former-binance-ceo-faces-travel-restrictions/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T11:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Changpeng CZ Zhao, the former CEO of the world’s largest cryptocurrency exchange Binance, has recently been hindered by travel restrictions in the United States in advance of his sentencing expected to take place early next year.
 
Binance Ex-CEO To Remain In The United States 
 
On Tuesday, Zhao entered a guilty plea and exited the cryptocurrency exchange he established in 2017. In addition, Binance also pleaded guilty to several criminal and civil charges due to inefficient anti-money laundering and customer recognition procedures.
 
 
According to a Bond filing, Zhao has signed a $175 million personal recognizance bond and a separate $15 million cash held in Davis Wright Tremaine (DWT) trust account for his release. Additionally, the bond release will allow him to leave the US back to h…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Godspower Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dwallet Labs Says It Uncovered Infstones Validator Vulnerabilities Which Left $1 Billion in Staked Assets ‘Compromised’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e749d3a7ea6</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/dwallet-labs-says-it-uncovered-infstones-validator-vulnerabilities-which-left-1-billion-in-staked-assets-compromised/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T10:37:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cyber security firm Dwallet Labs said on Nov. 21 that vulnerabilities it found on several Infstones (a validator company) validators a few months ago “meant over $1B of staked assets were compromised.” Infstones has acknowledged the existence of the vulnerabilities but says it “disagrees with the severity of the potential impact.” 
 
Traditional Web2 Threats
 
According to the cyber security firm Dwallet Labs, a security research study initially showed that one validator belonging to Infstones had “a potential vulnerable entry point.” The security firm argued that the vulnerability, which was uncovered more than four months ago, highlights the still significant risks posed to validators by traditional Web2 threats.
 
 
1/ Web3 security usually focuses on native Web3 primitives like smart c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Verasity Announces the Launch of VeraAds]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e749d25464f</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/verasity-announces-the-launch-of-veraads/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T10:17:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. London, November 23rd 2023 – Verasity, a leading advertising ecosystem built on open-ledger principles and creators of internationally patented Proof of View technology for preventing ad fraud, today announces the launch of VeraAds. A new service from Verasity, VeraAds is designed to directly onboard Web3 publishers and companies into VeraViews, helping monetize their video inventory and grow their businesses through traditional advertising channels.
 
Web3, blockchain, and metaverse technologies have expanded rapidly in the last few years, leading to a multitude of publishers with high traffic and large user bases, who are not currently monetizing their inventory through programmatic ads — a huge lost revenue opportunity for publishers in the space, and a missing channel fo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bhutan Secretly Spent Millions On Its Bitcoin Mines: Report Reveals]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e749d277ad3</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bhutan-millions-bitcoin-mines/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T10:01:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Kingdom of Bhutan, traditionally known for its pursuit of Gross National Happiness, has been engaging in a covert but extensive Bitcoin mining operation.
 
According to Forbes, Bhutan has secretly spent millions building a national Bitcoin mining operation to avert an economic crisis. While it was revealed earlier this year that the Himalayan country mines Bitcoin, the extent was a mystery.
 
Forbes’ journalists Iain Martin and Sarah Emerson, leveraging insider sources and satellite imagery from multiple agencies, have now exposed the covert operations of what is now known as the world’s largest state-owned Bitcoin mines.
 
Bhutan Pours In Millions Of Dollars For Bitcoin Mining
 
According to Forbes, dozens of shipping containers, housing millions of dollars in Bitcoin mining machinery…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Austria’s Raiffeisen Bank to Roll Out Crypto Trading for Retail Customers in January]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e749d23ff6b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/11/23/austrias-raiffeisen-bank-to-roll-out-crypto-trading-for-retail-customers-in-january/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T09:28:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bank will start its crypto services to customers in Vienna, in partnership with Bitpanda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KyberSwap DEX Suffers Multi-Chain Exploit Resulting In $50 Million Loss]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e749d28b854</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/kyberswap-exploit-50-million-loss/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T08:51:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized exchange (DEX) KyberSwap has become the latest decentralized finance (DeFi) protocol to fall victim to the activities of hackers. According to reports on Wednesday night, the DEX was exploited across multiple chains and drained of around $50 million.
 
KyberSwap Hack Shocks Crypto
 
KyberSwap seems to have managed to evade hackers over the course of its operation even while multiple protocols fell victim to these bad actors. However, its streak of good luck seems to have come to an end after the DeFi protocol was exploited.
 
 
First reports of the hack came from crypto community members who drew the attention of the team to a possible exploit. One of these first posts was from crypto pundit OlimpioCrypto who posted on X confirming the hack from multiple sources.
 
By the tim…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prosecutors Move to Stop Binance's Founder Zhao from Leaving the US]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e749d17ed4e</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/prosecutors-move-to-stop-binances-founder-zhao-from-leaving-the-us/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T07:53:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US federal prosecutors are seeking the court's permission to stop Changpeng Zhao, the Founder and former CEO of Binance, from leaving the country, citing an "unacceptable risk of flight."  

Zhao Pleads Guilty to a Criminal Charge  

Zhao pled guilty on Tuesday in US federal court for violating the Bank Secrecy Act with his crypto exchange business. He is facing a maximum prison time of 8 months and is now awaiting his sentencing.   

Following his guilty plea, Zhao signed a $175-million bond agreement, putting up $15 million in a trust account, and also found guarantors for the additional funds. Although he is now allowed to leave the US, he needs to return to the US two weeks before his sentencing scheduled in February 2024.
A subsequent motion filed by the US prosecutors argued that…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arnab Shome</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Insider Targeted By FBI For Knowledge About Elite SEC Corruption]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e749d13df17</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-insider-fbi-sec-corruption-insights/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T07:20:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Steven Nerayoff, an early adviser to the Ethereum network, has come forward with grave accusations against the US government’s law enforcement and regulatory agencies. His statements, made in response to a recent post on X by Senator Elisabeth Warren’s about Binance, shed light on what he describes as systemic corruption within these agencies.
 
Senator Warren’s post drew attention to the guilty plea of Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao on breaking anti-money laundering laws, portraying it as part of a wider trend of criminality in the crypto space. She urged the DOJ to probe Binance for alleged deceit towards Congress. This tweet, highlighting the need for stringent regulatory oversight, inadvertently set the stage for Nerayoff’s revelations.
 
Ethereum Insider Targeted For SEC Corruption Insigh…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ghana’s Central Bank Names Eight Money Transfer Companies Operating Without Its Approval]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e749d1d6d7a</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ghanas-central-bank-names-eight-money-transfer-companies-operating-without-its-approval/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T07:05:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bank of Ghana recently pointed the finger at eight money transfer organizations which are allegedly operating in Ghana’s remittances and forex market without its approval. The central bank also warned the public and regulated financial institutions against having dealings with the eight firms. 
 
Eight Firms Did Not Adhere to the Requirements of the Foreign Exchange Act
 
The Ghanaian central bank has identified eight money transfer organizations (MTOs) that are operating in the country’s remittances and forex markets without its approval. In a notice issued on Nov. 16, the Bank of Ghana (BOG) also warned the public and regulated financial institutions against having dealings with said MTOs.
 
According to the notice, the eight MTOs are Lemfi, Wise, Transfer Go, Xoom-A Paypal Service, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Supply Inactive For a Year Hits Record High of 70%]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e749d1a9171</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/11/23/bitcoin-supply-inactive-for-a-year-hits-record-high-of-70/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T06:18:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It appears bitcoin holders are not planning on offloading inventory at these price levels or any time soon, one observer said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Seizes $9 Million in Tether Allegedly Linked to Pig Butchering Crypto Scams]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e749d018718</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/us-seizes-9-million-in-tether-allegedly-linked-to-pig-butchering-crypto-scams/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T05:08:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Department of Justice (DOJ) has seized $9 million in tether (USDT) allegedly linked to “pig butchering” crypto scams. The Justice Department explained that U.S. Secret Service agents and analysts tracked the laundering of victims’ crypto deposits through numerous cryptocurrency addresses, where they were exchanged for various cryptocurrencies.
 
DOJ Seizes $9M in USDT
 
The U.S. Department of Justice (DOJ) announced Tuesday “the seizure of nearly $9 million worth of tether, a cryptocurrency pegged to the U.S. dollar.” The Justice Department detailed:
 

These seized funds were traced to cryptocurrency addresses allegedly associated with an organization that exploited over 70 victims through romance scams and cryptocurrency confidence scams, which are widely known as ‘pig butcherin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance's Ex-CEO CZ 'Poses a Serious Risk of Flight,' Prosecutors Claim in Asking He Stay in U.S.]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e749d0e54ab</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/11/23/binances-ex-ceo-cz-poses-a-serious-risk-of-flight-prosecutors-claim-in-asking-he-stay-in-us/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T04:15:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zhao pleaded guilty to one charge of violating the Bank Secrecy Act on Tuesday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CryptoQuant Analyst Thinks Bitcoin Will See A “Significant Pullback” Soon]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e749d0f06e6</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/cryptoquant-analyst-bitcoin-significant-pullback/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T04:07:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A CryptoQuant analyst believes a significant pullback for Bitcoin could be inevitable based on the net taker volume indicator data.
 
Bitcoin Net Taker Volume Has Plunged Into Negative Zone Recently
 
As CryptoQuant Netherlands community manager Maartunn explained in a post on X, the BTC net taker volume has recently turned red. The “net taker volume” refers to a metric that keeps track of the difference between the taker buy and taker sell volumes of Bitcoin on the futures market.
 
When the value of this metric is positive, it means that the taker buy volume exceeds the taker sell volume right now. Such a trend implies a bullish mentality is dominant among the investors currently.
 
 
On the other hand, negative values suggest the majority shares a bearish sentiment, as the selling press…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KyberSwap DEX Hacked for $48 Million, Attacker Teases Negotiations]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e749d0adc1a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/11/23/kyberswap-dex-hacked-for-48-million-attacker-teases-negotiations/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T03:23:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized Exchange had over $80 million in total value locked before the incident.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Genesis Launches New Lawsuit Against Gemini For ‘Unfair’ $700M Transfers Before Bankruptcy]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e749ef440b1</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/genesis-launches-new-lawsuit-against-gemini-700m/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T03:07:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a dramatic turn of events, bankrupt crypto lender Genesis has initiated a new legal battle against its long-standing rival, Gemini. The lawsuit claims that Gemini received “unfair preferential transfers” of approximately $700 million shortly before the company declared bankruptcy. 
 
The complaint, filed on November 21, asserts that these transfers significantly disadvantaged Genesis’s other creditors and seeks their recovery.
 
New Revelations In Genesis Lawsuit
 
According to the filed document, the crypto lender alleges that, during the 90 days preceding its Chapter 11 bankruptcy proceedings, Gemini withdrew an aggregate gross amount of no less than $689,302,000 from Genesis. 
 
This action allegedly “purportedly benefited” Gemini at the expense of other creditors and continues to pr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Congressman Calls for Gensler’s Removal After SEC Sues a Crypto Exchange Twice in 10 Months]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e749ef45f8f</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/congressman-calls-for-genslers-removal-after-sec-sues-a-crypto-exchange-twice-in-10-months/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T03:06:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A U.S. lawmaker has urged Congress to pass his bill that would fire U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Chairman Gary Gensler. This call followed the securities regulator filing a second lawsuit against crypto exchange Kraken this year after the exchange paid $30 million to settle the initial lawsuit.
 
Lawmaker Seeks to Fire Gary Gensler
 
Congressman Warren Davidson (R-OH) has called on Congress to pass his bill that would fire Gary Gensler as the chairman of the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) after the securities regulator sued crypto exchange Kraken twice in 10 months. Rep. Davidson wrote on social media platform X on Tuesday:
 

Now would be a great time to pass my SEC Stabilization Act and fire Gary Gensler.
 
On Monday, the SEC filed its second lawsuit this …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Altman's Ouster Followed Dangerous AI Breakthrough Claim: Reuters]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207190</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207190/openai-ai-dangerous-breakthrough-led-to-sam-altman-ceo-removal"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T02:11:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unnamed sources say Altman's brief departure from OpenAI was sparked by a new AI discovery that some felt threatened humanity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Whale Buys $5.5M Of ETH: Will Ethereum Bulls Cruise Past $2,100?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e749ef16d2a</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/whale-buys-5-5m-of-eth-will-ethereum-bulls-cruise-past-2100/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T02:08:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to on-chain data platform Lookonchain, an unnamed crypto whale known for well-timed Ethereum (ETH) trades in the past, has purchased an additional $5.53 million worth of ETH on Binance amidst turbulent market conditions.
 
 
Ethereum Whale Ramping Up Purchase
 
According to an X post on November 22, the purchase follows an acquisition last week when $18 million of USDC, a stablecoin, was used to acquire ETH at around $1,971. With the whale appearing to ramp up ETH purchases, Lookonchain speculates that the same trader is positioning for an upcoming ETH breakout past the stubborn $2,100 resistance level that could signal a renewed bull market. 
 
 
It should be observed that despite recent expansions in ETH, the $2,100 level remains a crucial reaction point for traders. The only t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dalmas Ngetich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Indian AI Video Startup Rephrase.ai Announces Acquisition by Adobe]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207178</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207178/rephrase-ai-generative-video-startup-adobe-acquisition"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T01:11:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aimed somewhere between Photoshop and Premiere Pro, the tool lets users create videos from scratch with just a prompt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stability AI Audio Head Quits Over Training on Copyrighted Material. Will It Change Anything?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207149</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207149/ed-newton-rex-quit-stability-ai-over-fair-use-copyright-training"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T23:46:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ed Newton-Rex shares further insights into the AI industry's approach to copyright following his very public resignation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stable Video Diffusion Is Stability AI's Gambit for the Future of Video]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207132</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207132/stable-video-diffusion-stability-ai-generative-video"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T21:15:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Put text in, get vibrant video content out—Stability AI joins the fray with Meta, Runway and Pika Labs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Needs ‘Rules of the Road’: Apple CEO Tim Cook]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206985</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206985/tim-cook-on-ai-regulation-apple-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T02:40:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple's Tim Cook spoke with Dua Lipa about AI's potential and the necessity for regulatory frameworks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cruise CEO Steps Down Amid Self-Driving Car Safety Crisis]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206979</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206979/cruise-autonomous-self-driving-car-safety-ceo-resignation"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T02:02:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kyle Vogt said he was optimistic about his business, but regulatory actions may have made moving forward untenable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic Upgrades Claude With Nearly Twice The Capabilities of GPT-4 Turbo]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206966</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206966/anthropic-upgrades-claude-with-nearly-twice-the-capabilities-of-gpt-4-turbo"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T01:01:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While the drama at OpenAI captures most of the attention, OpenAI challenger Anthropic delivers the latest version of its capable chatbot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Allie Eve Knox on Spankchain and the life of a Crypto Financial Dominatrix]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/16rVeg6o/allie-eve-knox-on-spankchain-and-the-life-of-a-crypto-financial-dominatrix</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/16rVeg6o/allie-eve-knox-on-spankchain-and-the-life-of-a-crypto-financial-dominatrix"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T21:20:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the first IRL episode of This Time Will Be Different!

In this week's episode, our host, Reza Jafery, is joined by Allie Eve Knox, the Spankchain Chief of Staff and FinDomme. 

They discuss
- How to sell feet pics
- If crypto is really as permissionless as it seems
- the intersections between crypto and sex work]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Drug Giant AstraZeneca Launches Evinova to Quicken Clinical Trials]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206789</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206789/astrazeneca-launches-evinova-faster-clinical-trials"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T01:03:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Evinova aims to use AI to design studies, automate cost calculations, and determine feasibility for drug testing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[As ‘Decels’ Rise, Meta Dissolves Its Responsible AI Team]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206777</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206777/meta-dissolves-responsible-ai-team"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T23:12:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As calls to slow development of artificial intelligence to ensure safety grow louder, Meta is broadening its efforts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Sam Altman Was Pushed From OpenAI Into Microsoft's Open Arms]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206697</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206697/timeline-sam-altman-openai-departure"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T18:15:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A tumultuous weekend for the AI giant saw its co-founders depart for Microsoft amid a boardroom battle. Here’s how it happened.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SingularityNET Joins With Dfinity Foundation for AI Models That Run on Smart Contracts]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206640</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206640/singularitynet-joins-with-dfinity-foundation-for-ai-models-that-runs-on-smart-contracts"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T14:01:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dfinity founder Dominic Williams says the collaboration aims to provide trustworthy, decentralized, and tamper-proof large language models.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Ubisoft, Xbox, and Blizzard Are Using AI to Make Next-Generation Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147436</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147436/ai-game-development-ubisoft-roblox-blizzard"/>
        <updated>2023-11-19T22:26:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Game studios are turning to AI to automate the most tedious elements of development and instantly conjure characters.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Altman May Return to Lead OpenAI: Reports]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206614</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206614/sam-altman-may-return-to-lead-openai-reports"/>
        <updated>2023-11-19T02:22:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The battle is being framed as one between "decels" and Effective Altruists who want to slow down, and Altman allies who want to move faster.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK Won’t Regulate AI Anytime Soon As It Tries to Balance Innovation and Safety]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206580</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206580/uk-wont-regulate-ai-anytime-soon-as-it-tries-to-balance-innovation-and-safety"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T23:35:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While U.S. policymakers scramble to put guardrails around AI, a British minister eschews “premature regulation” by politicians.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Questions With SCENE: Jeff Davis]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PChJu1R8/5-questions-with-scene-jeff-davis</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PChJu1R8/5-questions-with-scene-jeff-davis"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artist Jeff Davis joins 5 Questions with SCENE to answer burning questions about his artistic practice, the path that brought him to Art Blocks, and his quietly sophisticated DJ abilities.

Video shot and edited by Vincent Roazzi Jr.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Clyde's Last Call: Discord AI Chatbot Shutting Down on December 1]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206528</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206528/clydes-last-call-discords-ai-chatbot-being-shut-down-on-december-1"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T21:13:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Without giving a reason, the popular chat platform says its Clyde AI beta will be deactivated next month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Altman Out as CEO of OpenAI, Was 'Not Consistently Candid' With Company Board]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206531</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206531/sam-altman-out-as-ceo-of-openai-was-not-consistently-candid-with-company-board"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T20:47:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[”The board no longer has confidence in his ability to continue leading OpenAI,” a company statement read.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Digital Despair: AI Girlfriends Ghost Users After CEO's Arrest Ignites Chaos]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206519</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206519/ai-girlfriends-caryn-forever-voices-ceo-arrest-austin-texas"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T20:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CEO of an AI-powered romantic chatbot service turned up the heat—allegedly, and literally.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Is Making People ‘Question Their Own Reality’: Chelsea Manning]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206449</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206449/chelsea-manning-web-summit-ai-technology-privacy"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T01:04:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manning highlighted the clash between humans and technology at Lisbon's Web Summit, questioning AI's rapid development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emu Video and Emu Edit: Meta Debuts AI Models for Video and Images]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206440</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206440/emu-video-edit-meta-ai-video-generation-image-editing"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T00:56:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The social giant’s latest tools can conjure stunning visuals from text, setting up a generative AI showdown.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Heatbit Founder Alex Busarov on the Bitcoin Miner That Heats Your Home]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DJuHqcGT/heatbit-founder-alex-busarov-on-the-bitcoin-miner-that-heats-your-home</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DJuHqcGT/heatbit-founder-alex-busarov-on-the-bitcoin-miner-that-heats-your-home"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T18:12:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt joined Heatbit founder Alex Busarov at Web Summit for a walkthrough of the firm's flagship product, a Bitcoin miner that acts as a domestic space heater—aimed at the casual user.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nym CEO Harry Halpin on Privacy, Decentralized VPNs and Tornado Cash]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/aLTtY2aq/nym-ceo-harry-halpin-on-privacy-decentralized-vpns-and-tornado-cash</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/aLTtY2aq/nym-ceo-harry-halpin-on-privacy-decentralized-vpns-and-tornado-cash"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T18:08:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The founder of privacy-preserving mixnet Nym sat down with Decrypt at Web Summit to talk about its new decentralized VPN, the Web3 privacy landscape and why "devs should be defended" in the wake of the Tornado Cash crackdown.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former VP Leaves Stability AI Over Copyright Concerns]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206307</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206307/former-vp-leaves-stability-ai-over-copyright-concerns"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T03:11:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ed Newton-Rex resigned from Stability AI, contesting the company's assertion that using copyrighted content in AI training is "fair use."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Maia and Cobalt, Microsoft's New Custom Chips Designed for AI Supremacy]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206286</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206286/microsoft-maia-cobolt-arm-chips-for-ai-datacenters"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T00:04:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft is shifting to an integrated strategy to grow both its AI and cloud computing portfolio.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT Puts Paid Plan Signups on Pause as Systems Strain]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206218</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206218/chatgpt-puts-paid-plan-signups-on-pause-as-systems-strain"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T18:56:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI CEO Sam Altman said usage of its services has "exceeded our capacity."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Open Source AI Model from China Boasts Twice the Capacity of ChatGPT]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206195</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206195/new-open-source-ai-model-from-china-boasts-twice-the-capacity-of-chatgpt"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T18:40:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Yi series model takes a giant leap over its American competitors, at least by some metrics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pat Felder - The worst is over [Macro Deep Dive Episode]]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MdcKPVo0/pat-felder-the-worst-is-over-macro-deep-dive-episode</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MdcKPVo0/pat-felder-the-worst-is-over-macro-deep-dive-episode"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T17:10:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the first Markets Edition of This Time Will Be Different! In this episode we dive into the current macroeconomic conditions around crypto and look at the data behind the price action. 


Reza sits down with Pat Felder, founder of Prismatic Capital to discuss the current macro environment, and to answer the question on everyone's mind-- is the bear market really over?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Sandbox Co-Founder Sebastien Borget: 'We're Already Integrating AI']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/HlARjhG1/the-sandbox-co-founder-sebastien-borget-were-already-integrating-ai</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/HlARjhG1/the-sandbox-co-founder-sebastien-borget-were-already-integrating-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T16:09:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt sat down with The Sandbox co-founder Sebastien Borget at Web Summit to talk about AI, the open metaverse and the creative challenges of interoperability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dacoco CEO Saro McKenna: How Alien Worlds is Creating an AI-Powered 'Lore DAO' with Kevin J Anderson]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QrQTrsjH/dacoco-ceo-saro-mckenna-how-alien-worlds-is-creating-an-ai-powered-lore-dao-with-kevin-j-anderson</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QrQTrsjH/dacoco-ceo-saro-mckenna-how-alien-worlds-is-creating-an-ai-powered-lore-dao-with-kevin-j-anderson"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T16:06:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt joined Dacoco CEO Sarojini McKenna at Web Summit 2023 to talk about Alien Worlds' new Lore DAO and its AI-powered collaboration with sci-fi author Kevin J Anderson.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avalon's Jeffrey Butler on Designing a Metaverse MMO That Lets Players Co-Create]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XDz9vsvT/avalons-jeffrey-butler-on-designing-a-metaverse-mmo-that-lets-players-co-create</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XDz9vsvT/avalons-jeffrey-butler-on-designing-a-metaverse-mmo-that-lets-players-co-create"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T00:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avalon Chief Product Officer Jeffrey Butler speaks with Decrypt reporter Jason Nelson and details his studio's new MMO game with interoperable assets—and how it will enable players to create and monetize their own content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mind-Reading AI Turns Thoughts Into Text, Gives ALS Patient His Voice Back]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206004</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206004/mind-reading-ai-turns-thoughts-into-text-gives-als-patient-his-voice-back"/>
        <updated>2023-11-14T22:16:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using brainwave sensors and AI, Unbabel’s new Project Halo hears messages and generates silent replies. Just think about it and the machine does all the work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GPT-5 Is Officially on the OpenAI Roadmap Despite Prior Hesitation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206044</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206044/gpt-5-openai-development-roadmap-gpt-4"/>
        <updated>2023-11-14T21:21:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After initial reluctance, new remarks show OpenAI is already laying the groundwork for GPT-5 mere days after turbocharging GPT-4.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Square Enix-Backed Atlas Uses AI to Turn Text and Images Into Game Worlds]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=205923</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/205923/final-fantasy-developer-square-enix-backs-3d-ai-platform-atlas"/>
        <updated>2023-11-14T16:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The generative AI startup Atlas emerges from stealth with $6 million in gaming and blockchain investments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia Created an AI to Better Understand COVID-19 and Accelerate Medical Discoveries]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=205969</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/205969/nvidia-created-an-ai-to-better-understand-covid-19-and-accelerate-medical-discoveries"/>
        <updated>2023-11-14T14:50:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new GenSLMs model can generate realistic and predictive SARS-CoV-2 genetic variants.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Puts Scammers On Blast for Exploiting AI Hype]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=205938</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/205938/google-sues-unnammed-scammers-for-fake-bard-ads-and-malware"/>
        <updated>2023-11-14T03:29:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lawsuit in California court aims to end malicious ads and malware distribution on Facebook.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Nvidia Supercomputing Chips to ‘Fuel the Acceleration’ of AI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=205899</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/205899/new-nvidia-supercomputing-chips-to-fuel-the-acceleration-of-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-11-14T00:57:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At its Supercomputing 2023 event, Nvidia unveiled upgraded chips and a supercomputer that can accelerate scientific research.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Offended Bots to Occult Gurus, The 7 Best Custom GPTs People Have Created—So Far]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=205688</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/205688/7-best-gpt-custom-chatgpt-openai"/>
        <updated>2023-11-11T02:22:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI just launched custom GPTs, and you can say goodbye to boring assistants.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can’t AI Take a Joke? Elon Musk and Sam Altman Trade Testy Tweets]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=205687</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/205687/ai-dad-jokes-humor-elon-musk-grok-sam-altman-chat-gpt"/>
        <updated>2023-11-11T01:24:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The tech moguls exchanged AI-themed insults about their rival chatbots, with Altman saying Grok has “cringy boomer humor.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Confidential’: Free ChatGPT Users Briefly Get Access to GPT-4]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=205523</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/205523/confidential-free-chatgpt-users-briefly-get-access-to-gpt-4"/>
        <updated>2023-11-10T22:35:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Could we see a free version of ChatGPT with the powerful GPT-4 under the hood? Only OpenAI knows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Gen Z Is Different: OTK Chief Strategy Officer Talks Creator Economy Shift and Rise of Kick]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PieshbpH/how-gen-z-is-different-otk-chief-strategy-officer-talks-creator-economy-shift-and-rise-of-kick</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PieshbpH/how-gen-z-is-different-otk-chief-strategy-officer-talks-creator-economy-shift-and-rise-of-kick"/>
        <updated>2023-11-10T18:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One True King, an esports and gaming lifestyle brand and media company, was founded by creators like Asmongold and Mizkif. OTK's Chief Strategy Officer Zachary Diaz, who previously worked at TikTok and Twitch, shares with Decrypt's Kate Irwin about how the creator economy is changing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI Battles Service Disruption Linked to Russian Hackers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=205446</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/205446/chatgpt-outage-openai-ddos-attack-russian-hackers"/>
        <updated>2023-11-10T02:51:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI links recent ChatGPT outages and its API to a Distributed Denial of Service attack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta's Next AI Gambit? Llama 3 Rumored for Early 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=205436</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/205436/llama-3-release-date-rumored-meta-ai-challenger"/>
        <updated>2023-11-10T02:39:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meta’s next Llama AI release could challenge the dominance of OpenAI's GPT-4, but Mark Zuckerberg remains mum on the timing of its release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google and Anthropic Are Gunning for AI Dominance with New Chips]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=205397</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/205397/google-anthropic-claude-ai-tpu-chips-openai"/>
        <updated>2023-11-10T01:02:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic's Claude LLM gains a competitive edge with Google's TPU v5e chips, pushing the boundaries of AI's computational frontier.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Humane Launches Wearable AI Pin With a $700 Price Tag]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=205422</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/205422/humane-wearable-ai-pin-700-dollars-privacy"/>
        <updated>2023-11-10T00:06:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The small device integrates AI into daily life for a price, but privacy concerns loom.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moisés Zamora on Videomart and Bucking the Hollywood System]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kyjQCle8/moises-zamora-on-videomart-and-bucking-the-hollywood-system</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kyjQCle8/moises-zamora-on-videomart-and-bucking-the-hollywood-system"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T17:11:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Selena: The Series" creator and co-showrunner Moisés Zamora joins Decrypt's Sander Lutz at the Film3 Summit 2023 to discuss why the Hollywood system is broken and why he founded the Videomart NFT digital film marketplace to give creators more power.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why OTK Is Making Video Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/1NCV4Fk0/why-otk-is-making-video-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/1NCV4Fk0/why-otk-is-making-video-games"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One True King (OTK) Chief Strategy Officer Zachary Diaz tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about OTK's long-term strategy and vision to become a content creator-powered media and video games company.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Arrives on YouTube With Comment Summaries and Video Suggestions]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=205285</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/205285/google-ai-youtube-comment-section-subscriber-chatbot"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T01:29:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[YouTube’s AI tool aims to turn comment chaos into organized insights.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Killer Combo: ChatGPT Merged With Dall-E, Vision, Web Browsing and Code Interpreter]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204934</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204934/what-can-you-do-with-chatgpt-gpt4-turbo-multimodal-features"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T23:14:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here's what you can do now with multimodal capabilities, where it's not just about what you say, but what you show.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mozilla Enlists Fakespot for AI Chatbot to Safeguard Online Shopping]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=205012</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/205012/mozilla-enlists-fakespot-for-ai-chatbot-to-safeguard-online-shopping"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T22:25:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is AI the solution to fake, AI-generated product reviews?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To AI: Best AI Tools for Teachers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204998</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204998/how-to-ai-best-ai-tools-for-teachers"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T22:20:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence is reshaping education and finding its way into the classroom, for better or worse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Questions With SCENE: LoVid]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/E8BZZBWX/5-questions-with-scene-lovid</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/E8BZZBWX/5-questions-with-scene-lovid"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T21:47:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artistic duo LoVid, aka Tali Hinkis and Kyle Lapidus, joins 5 Questions with SCENE to answer burning questions about art, lettuce, and the hellscape (in someone’s opinion) that is Miami.

Video shot and edited by Vincent Roazzi Jr.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Barney on DeFi, Privacy, and Vega]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/hgDzjboU/barney-on-defi-privacy-and-vega</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/hgDzjboU/barney-on-defi-privacy-and-vega"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T18:27:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week our host is joined by Barney the founder of Vega Protocol. 

They discuss the current state of DeFi, what's wrong with the apps being built today, whether or not privacy matters when its only applied to an L2, and most importantly-- which form of sales tax is the sexiest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Is Phantom Galaxies Releasing Two Versions of Its Game?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QtnWGSSJ/why-is-phantom-galaxies-releasing-two-versions-of-its-game</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QtnWGSSJ/why-is-phantom-galaxies-releasing-two-versions-of-its-game"/>
        <updated>2023-11-06T17:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animoca Brands-owned Blowfish Studios is building a space mech pilot game called Phantom Galaxies. Blowfish Cofounder Ben Lee tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about his plans for the game's release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sophie Maxx on NFTs, Augmented Reality, and Fashion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/VByufHjn/sophie-maxx-on-nfts-augmented-reality-and-fashion</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/VByufHjn/sophie-maxx-on-nfts-augmented-reality-and-fashion"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T23:37:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week our host is joined by Sophie Maxx (Web3Maxx) to discuss NFTs, augmented reality, the metaverse, how blockchain is sneaking into the fashion world, and more!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Questions With SCENE: Kevin Rose]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/u9LDX8Vr/5-questions-with-scene-kevin-rose</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/u9LDX8Vr/5-questions-with-scene-kevin-rose"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kevin Rose, co-founder and CEO of PROOF and co-creator of the hit Moonbirds NFT collection, joins 5 Questions with SCENE to answer some hard-hitting questions about his childhood dreams, his wife’s candy preferences, and his undying love of rap music.

Video shot and edited by Vincent Roazzi Jr.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Happened to Atari's Token? Inside Atari's Blockchain Plans]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/7OtQIdqa/what-happened-to-ataris-token-inside-ataris-blockchain-plans</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/7OtQIdqa/what-happened-to-ataris-token-inside-ataris-blockchain-plans"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T18:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin chats with Atari X director Tyler Drewitz about what happened with Atari's token plans, whether a token is coming, and what Atari games might be getting the blockchain treatment. Oh, and there's lots of Easter eggs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitch CEO Dan Clancy Is a 'Wild Card,' Says Marketing Director]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/qCOCtPKe/twitch-ceo-dan-clancy-is-a-wild-card-says-marketing-director</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/qCOCtPKe/twitch-ceo-dan-clancy-is-a-wild-card-says-marketing-director"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T20:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twitch Senior Director of Community Marketing Mary Kish speaks with Decrypt's Kate Irwin about Twitch CEO Dan Clancy, Ninja, Twitch's new simulcasting rules, the biggest differences between Twitch and rival platform Kick, and the role of esports on the streaming platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why NFT Paris has Launched a Loyalty Token]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/91tPVJff/why-nft-paris-has-launched-a-loyalty-token</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/91tPVJff/why-nft-paris-has-launched-a-loyalty-token"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T13:26:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NFT Paris founder Alexandre Tsydenkov told Decrypt what to expect from the upcoming 2024 edition of the conference, the launch of its loyalty token and its plans to create a Web3 loyalty program that rewards the most engaged members of the community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Game Review—Formula E: High Voltage Is a Fun Play-to-Earn Racer That Lacks Direction]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/hzkx0TDg/game-reviewformula-e-high-voltage-is-a-fun-play-to-earn-racer-that-lacks-direction</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/hzkx0TDg/game-reviewformula-e-high-voltage-is-a-fun-play-to-earn-racer-that-lacks-direction"/>
        <updated>2023-10-29T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Formula E: High Voltage is a play-to-earn racing game with a distinctive strategic approach. Decrypt contributor Ryan Gladwin put Animoca's web-based game through its paces in this review, highlighting the unique gameplay design, the role of NFTs and crypto, and where the game currently comes up short.

Follow Decrypt's GG on Twitter: https://twitter.com/ggdecrypt 

Check out GG for daily gaming news: https://decrypt.co/gg 

Subscribe to our GG newsletter with over 50,000 subscribers: https://decrypt.co/newsletters/gg 

Join our official Discord: https://discord.com/invite/3bc4QpA57C]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>