<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-10-25T14:13:44.470Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-10-25T14:13:44.470Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Flare and Etherspot Could Make Blockchain Easier to Use]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18993571/How-Flare-and-Etherspot-Could-Make-Blockchain-Easier-to-Use</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18993571/How-Flare-and-Etherspot-Could-Make-Blockchain-Easier-to-Use"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T14:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover how Flare’s partnership with Etherspot aims to make blockchain more accessible through Account Abstraction and gasless transactions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Major Exchange Delists XRP Pair, What’s Going On?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18993563/Major-Exchange-Delists-XRP-Pair-Whats-Going-On</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18993563/Major-Exchange-Delists-XRP-Pair-Whats-Going-On"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T14:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency exchange, OKX, is set to delist the XRP/OKB spot trading pair from its platform at the end of the month, along with several other spot trading pairs. This development takes place against the background of OKX’s rise in the industry. With assets of an astounding $11.32 billion, OKX...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Epic Bounceback To Pre-FTX Heights: Brace Yourself For What’s Next]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18993532/Solana-Epic-Bounceback-To-Pre-FTX-Heights-Brace-Yourself-For-Whats-Next</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18993532/Solana-Epic-Bounceback-To-Pre-FTX-Heights-Brace-Yourself-For-Whats-Next"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T14:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana (SOL) has experienced remarkable growth in the past month, outpacing its peers in the cryptocurrency market. According to data from Messari, SOL’s market capitalization surged over 60%, solidifying its position among the top ten crypto assets.  This rally comes after a challenging period...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash (BCH) Miners Cut Reserves to 5-Year Low – Can the Bulls Sustain the Rally?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18993560/Bitcoin-Cash-BCH-Miners-Cut-Reserves-to-5-Year-Low-Can-the-Bulls-Sustain-the-Rally</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18993560/Bitcoin-Cash-BCH-Miners-Cut-Reserves-to-5-Year-Low-Can-the-Bulls-Sustain-the-Rally"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bitcoin Cash (BCH) price recently retraced from the $265 level after scoring double-digit weekly gains. What are the critical factors holding back the BCH price rally?  Bitcoin Cash’s price bounced 10% this week, briefly reclaiming $265 for the first time since July. Will the ongoing...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Cloud’s Growth Slows as Microsoft’s Soars, With Focus on AI in 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18993523/Google-Clouds-Growth-Slows-as-Microsofts-Soars-With-Focus-on-AI-in-2024</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18993523/Google-Clouds-Growth-Slows-as-Microsofts-Soars-With-Focus-on-AI-in-2024"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T13:59:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the ever-expanding realm of cloud services, two major players, Google and Microsoft, have showcased contrasting performances in their latest financial reports. While Alphabet, Google’s parent company, fell short of cloud revenue expectations, Microsoft’s cloud arm exceeded forecasts. Beyond...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Judge sets the stage for Ripple’s crucial remedies phase]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18993524/Judge-sets-the-stage-for-Ripples-crucial-remedies-phase</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18993524/Judge-sets-the-stage-for-Ripples-crucial-remedies-phase"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T13:58:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Judge Analisa Torres has now set the stage for the next pivotal chapter in the SEC vs. Ripple case. Consequently, both parties have been tasked to recommend a joint briefing schedule for the remedies phase by November 9, 2023. This phase will shed light on the potential repercussions Ripple Labs...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ark Invest Makes Second-Day Sales of Grayscale and Coinbase Stocks]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18993550/Ark-Invest-Makes-Second-Day-Sales-of-Grayscale-and-Coinbase-Stocks</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18993550/Ark-Invest-Makes-Second-Day-Sales-of-Grayscale-and-Coinbase-Stocks"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T13:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cathie Wood’s ARK Invest continued reducing exposure to cryptocurrency assets for a second consecutive day on Tuesday. According to disclosures, the firm’s ARK Next Generation Internet ETF sold about $1.8 million worth of Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) shares and $1.7 million of Coinbase Global...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto giants drop hints: Is a major market shake-up imminent?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18993526/Crypto-giants-drop-hints-Is-a-major-market-shake-up-imminent</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18993526/Crypto-giants-drop-hints-Is-a-major-market-shake-up-imminent"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T13:55:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent series of cryptic posts on the platform formerly known as Twitter, the cryptocurrency community found itself embroiled in a guessing game that has set tongues wagging. The first enigmatic post was made by David Schwartz, the Chief Technical Officer (CTO) of Ripple. He shared an image...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bank of Spain champions the digital euro: A deep dive into its potential]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18993525/Bank-of-Spain-champions-the-digital-euro-A-deep-dive-into-its-potential</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18993525/Bank-of-Spain-champions-the-digital-euro-A-deep-dive-into-its-potential"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T13:54:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Madrid – On October 19, Banco de España, the central banking institution of Spain, unveiled its perspective on the much-discussed digital euro. This statement came amidst a series of endorsements from various European banks and was aimed at informing the public about the possible advantages of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin supply absorption by various cohorts suggests impending halving event not fully priced in]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18993508/Bitcoin-supply-absorption-by-various-cohorts-suggests-impending-halving-event-not-fully-priced-in</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18993508/Bitcoin-supply-absorption-by-various-cohorts-suggests-impending-halving-event-not-fully-priced-in"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T13:45:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quick Take A deep dive into Bitcoin’s issuance reveals a fascinating trend as the next Bitcoin halving event approaches. The current monthly issuance of Bitcoin stands at 27,000 BTC, calculated from 900 Bitcoin mined each day over 30 days. An analysis of various cohorts, along with exchanges and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nearly 4,800 Bitcoin (BTC) Linked to Defunct Darknet Marketplace Moved to Bitcoin Mixer]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18993561/Nearly-4800-Bitcoin-BTC-Linked-to-Defunct-Darknet-Marketplace-Moved-to-Bitcoin-Mixer</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18993561/Nearly-4800-Bitcoin-BTC-Linked-to-Defunct-Darknet-Marketplace-Moved-to-Bitcoin-Mixer"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, blockchain analyst, ZachXBT, revealed an intriguing money laundering case. An entity transferred approximately 4,800 BTC, equivalent to about $144 million, from the Abraxas darknet market to a Bitcoin mixer. Abraxas was an online dark marketplace that operated in the shadows until its...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Is Up 100% This Year. It's Not Just Because of Spot BTC ETF Hype]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18993492/Bitcoin-Is-Up-100-This-Year-Its-Not-Just-Because-of-Spot-BTC-ETF-Hype</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18993492/Bitcoin-Is-Up-100-This-Year-Its-Not-Just-Because-of-Spot-BTC-ETF-Hype"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T13:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As BTC has gained over 100% this year, most observers tied its recent strength to a looming approval of a spot BTC ETF. But its increasingly constrained supply, underinvested market participants and bitcoin's rejuvenated shine as a safe haven from spiraling debt levels, banking crises and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Falls Below This Key Level; Mina, Maker Among Top Losers]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18993514/Ethereum-Falls-Below-This-Key-Level-Mina-Maker-Among-Top-Losers</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18993514/Ethereum-Falls-Below-This-Key-Level-Mina-Maker-Among-Top-Losers"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T13:41:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (CRYPTO: BTC) traded lower, but the cryptocurrency prices traded above the $34,000 level on Wednesday. Ethereum (CRYPTO: ETH) also moved lower, trading below the key $1,800 mark this morning. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matrixport doubles down on $45K Bitcoin year-end prediction]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18993493/Matrixport-doubles-down-on-45K-Bitcoin-year-end-prediction</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18993493/Matrixport-doubles-down-on-45K-Bitcoin-year-end-prediction"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T13:40:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After first setting its 2023-year-end BTC price target at $45,000 in early 2023, Matrixport has reiterated its bold Bitcoin prediction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Are Stablecoins and How Do You Use Them?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=5761</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/stablecoins"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T13:36:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoins are cryptocurrencies that claim to be backed by fiat currencies. Unlike cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin, their prices remain steady.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Hussey,Scott Chipolina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlockFi to Pursue Asset Recovery Amid Bankruptcy Resurgence]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18993458/BlockFi-to-Pursue-Asset-Recovery-Amid-Bankruptcy-Resurgence</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18993458/BlockFi-to-Pursue-Asset-Recovery-Amid-Bankruptcy-Resurgence"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T13:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The firm has devised a post-bankruptcy plan to ensure the repayment of creditors and the resumption of digital asset distribution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PYUSD Supply Skyrockets by 49%, Marking a Shift in Distribution as New Holders Emerge]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a87efe3a</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/pyusd-supply-skyrockets-by-49-marking-a-shift-in-distribution-as-new-holders-emerge/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T13:34:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to current metrics, Paypal’s stablecoin PYUSD has increased its supply by more than 49% since the end of September, rising from 94.39 million to 140.86 million. Moreover, the number of PYUSD holders has risen by 55% since September 30, 2023. Concentration, however, is still evident in PYUSD, with the top 100 holders owning 99.95% of its current supply.
 
Paypal Stablecoin Witnesses Redistribution Among Top Holders
 
Paypal’s stablecoin ecosystem experienced growth in October. The number of unique addresses and transfers has risen, and more PYUSD has been issued. On September 30, 2023, 924 unique wallets held PYUSD. Today, that number stands at 1,438 holders. Additionally, PYUSD had only 180 transfers 25 days ago, but that count has now reached a total of 8,307 transactions. Still…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Fixes Issue That Impacted Crypto Withdrawals, Funds Safe?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a87f620a</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/binance-fix-issue-that-impacted-crypto-withdrawals/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T13:32:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto exchange Binance briefly halted withdrawals on its platform after experiencing a technical issue. The company launched an investigation, and an hour later, withdrawal resumed on the platform.
 
 
 
Binance Experiences Technical Issues
 
According to a post on social media platform X, withdrawals were paused due to an issue with the middleware service running on the platform. While crypto withdrawals were halted, users had access to fiat withdrawals.
 
Following an investigation that failed to provide details about the specifics of the issue, the crypto exchange restored the service. The company stated:
 

The issue is now fixed, and all crypto withdrawals on Binance are now back to functioning as usual. Thanks for your patience, and we apologize for the inconvenience.
 
In the crypto community, some took to X to promote their platforms over the centralized exchange. In particular, the team behind decentralized exchange (DEX) THORChain took the opportunity to remind users about their alleged advantages over Binance:
 

All cross-chain services deal with many, many issues and have to pause to deal with edge cases. The difference with TC is that you can jump in and see exactly what’s wrong at any time and don’t need a spokesperson so say “funds are safe” – because you can check it yourself.
 
Binance has experienced several obstacles lately, from the increasing regulatory oversight in major jurisdictions, such as the US and Europe, and key members leaving their positions. In addition, the exchanges are currently fighting many legal battles while their trading volumes crashed in some regions.
 
 
Still, the crypto company claims to be committed to continue offering its services to its millions of users. On the latest issue, the exchange’s CEO, Changpeng “CZ” Zhao, stated:
 

Technical issue with a middleware service impacting withdrawals. Funds are SAFU. Our team is on it.
 
Cover image from Unsplash, chart from Tradingview]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reynaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pope Francis Endorses “Code with Pope” Initiative to Promote Coding Education]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18993527/Pope-Francis-Endorses-Code-with-Pope-Initiative-to-Promote-Coding-Education</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18993527/Pope-Francis-Endorses-Code-with-Pope-Initiative-to-Promote-Coding-Education"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T13:30:14.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Good News: Telegram Trading Bot Maestro Refunds 610 ETH After Hack]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18993410/Good-News-Telegram-Trading-Bot-Maestro-Refunds-610-ETH-After-Hack</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18993410/Good-News-Telegram-Trading-Bot-Maestro-Refunds-610-ETH-After-Hack"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FLOKI Partners with World Table Tennis for Reaching Crypto Globally]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18993467/FLOKI-Partners-with-World-Table-Tennis-for-Reaching-Crypto-Globally</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18993467/FLOKI-Partners-with-World-Table-Tennis-for-Reaching-Crypto-Globally"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FLOKI Cryptocurrency and World Table Tennis Unite for WTT 2023 EventCryptocurrency $FLOKI has announced a strategic marketing partnership with the renowned table tennis organization, World Table Tennis (WTT), at the WTT Champions event held in Frankfurt in 2023. This collaboration is a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5050 Bitcoin for $5 in 2009: Helsinki’s claim to crypto fame]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18993421/5050-Bitcoin-for-5-in-2009-Helsinkis-claim-to-crypto-fame</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18993421/5050-Bitcoin-for-5-in-2009-Helsinkis-claim-to-crypto-fame"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Helsinki played host to the first Bitcoin for fiat transaction in 2009 — 5050 Bitcoin for $5 — 6 months before Pizza Day. Crypto City Guide.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maestro Telegram bot breached 280 ETH stolen in smart Contract flaw]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18993389/Maestro-Telegram-bot-breached-280-ETH-stolen-in-smart-Contract-flaw</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18993389/Maestro-Telegram-bot-breached-280-ETH-stolen-in-smart-Contract-flaw"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T13:25:44.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[India's Crypto Database Boosts the Blockchain Narrative]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a8796233</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/indias-crypto-database-boosts-the-blockchain-narrative/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T13:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to Bitcoin and crypto, the narratives around them move in waves, particularly as we’re dealing with such young technologies. Bitcoin was launched in 2009, and has surged in price towards blow-off tops, and subsequent crashes, multiple times. On each occasion, there were several factors at work, but key narratives can be identified.
 Back in 2013, we had very early, tech-savvy adopters picking up on what was envisioned as a new currency. In 2017, retail traders became caught up in the exuberance, and there was a sense that Bitcoin might be a kind of digital gold. And most recently, in 2021, we had the promise of institutional participation.
 In fact, as we progress, the narratives start to operate alongside one another. The Lightning Network, a Layer 2 payment protocol for Bit…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam White</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Shrapnel' Game Studio Neon Machine Raises $20 Million Led by Polychain]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203208</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203208/shrapnel-game-studio-neon-machine-raises-20-million-led-polychain"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T13:01:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neon Machine has completed its Series A funding round to polish the upcoming shooter Shrapnel, which is built around NFTs on Avalanche.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Millions in Ether, Chainlink Linked to FTX and Alameda Moved]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a8671e75</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/10/25/millions-in-ether-chainlink-linked-to-ftx-and-alameda-moved/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T12:44:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These funds seemed to be sent to wallets of crypto exchange Binance as per Nansen data, where they presumably could be sold.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Technical Analysis: BTC Consolidates Recent Gains, as Traders Anticipate Powell Speech]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a8608bad</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-ethereum-technical-analysis-btc-consolidates-recent-gains-as-traders-anticipate-powell-speech/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T12:35:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin profit takers swooped in to capture recent profits on Wednesday, as the cryptocurrency retreated below a recent high above $35,000. The decline comes ahead of Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell’s speech later today. Ethereum also edged lower, dropping under the $1,800 level.
 
Bitcoin
 
Bitcoin was trading lower on Wednesday, as traders appeared to have finally decided to secure profits, following recent gains.
 
BTC/USD slipped to an intraday low of $33,278.40 late in yesterday’s session, after an earlier peak above the $35,000 mark.
 
Although bulls have since pushed the cryptocurrency higher, with the price now at $34,246.74, it remains below heights seen on Tuesday.
 
 
Bitcoin chart by TradingView
 

 
 

 
One reason for this being the relative strength index (RSI), which was significantly overbought on Tuesday, tracking around 89.00.
 
Currently, the index is at a reading of 87.22, which is marginally lower, but still remains primed for a reversal.
 
Today’s speech could be the storm that traders are waiting to clear, before either intensifying recent momentum, or selling off further.
 
 
Ethereum
 
Ethereum (ETH) retreated below the $1,800 level on Wednesday, snapping a six-day winning streak.
 
Following a high of $1,852.68 during yesterday’s session, ETH/USD fell to a low of $1,758.69 earlier in the day.
 
ETH has since rebounded, marginally, and is now trading at $1,784.57, which is over 3% lower than Tuesday’s peak.
 
 
Ethereum chart by TradingView
 

 
 
Overall sentiment remains largely positive, with the 10-day (red) moving average extending its upward trend versus its 25-day (blue) counterpart.
 
Although the RSI in ethereum is also overbought, and tracking above 70.00, bulls could attempt to push the price above $1,900 in this upcycle.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
How will today’s Fed speech impact crypto prices? Leave your thoughts in the comments below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bull Run: Trading Desks Awaken As Price Crosses $35,000 After A Year]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a860d94b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-comeback-trading-desks-awaken/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T12:32:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OK
 
Trading firms and cryptocurrency enthusiasts have been buzzing with activity as Bitcoin’s resurgence has stirred up the market, rekindling hopes of a major bull run.
 
With Bitcoin’s current price listed at $34,136 according to CoinGecko at the time of writing, the cryptocurrency has gained 0.8% over the past 24 hours and a significant 19% in the last seven days, marking a notable upswing not seen in months. BTC hit the vaunted $35K mark Tuesday, to the delight of traders and enthusiasts alike.
 
Amidst this fervor, market experts are pointing towards a potential interplay between derivative trades and the recent spike in the top crypto’s value. 
 
Spencer Hallarn, global head of OTC trading at GSR, in a Blockworks report highlighted the mounting speculation regarding the approval of …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Mover Americas: Bitcoin Retreats Slightly; FTX Receives Bids for Restart]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a861ef96</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/10/25/first-mover-americas-bitcoin-retreats-slightly-ftx-receives-bids-for-restart/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T12:26:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest price moves in bitcoin (BTC) and crypto markets in context for Oct. 25, 2023. First Mover is CoinDesk’s daily newsletter that contextualizes the latest actions in the crypto markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lyllah Ledesma, Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bain Capital, Polychain, Lead $6M Funding Round For Privacy Protocol Firm Nocturne Labs]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a8637bb2</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/10/25/bain-capital-polychain-lead-6m-funding-round-for-privacy-protocol-firm-nocturne-labs/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T12:16:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Other investors included Ethereum co-founder Vitalik Buterin, Bankless Ventures and HackVC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Margaux Nijkerk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK Regulator Warns Crypto Firms of 'Hard to Read' Risk Warnings]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a8637b81</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/10/25/uk-regulator-warns-crypto-firms-of-hard-to-read-risk-warnings/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T12:16:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Financial Conduct Authority has blocked Binance's chosen ad approver and added 221 firms to its warnings list since a new crypto marketing regime took effect on Oct.8.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandali Handagama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vodafone, Chainlink Show Blockchain Can Support Global Trade Processes]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a86e7684</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/10/25/vodafone-chainlink-show-blockchain-can-support-global-trade-processes/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T11:57:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The proof of concept enabled devices to act autonomously and produce accurate information to support global trade processes, the companies said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camomile Shumba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zero Hash and Shift4 Collaborate on Fiat-to-Crypto On-Ramp for Web3]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a86e7ca3</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/zero-hash-and-shift4-collaborate-on-fiat-to-crypto-on-ramp-for-web3/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T11:56:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zero  
Hash, a crypto infrastructure platform, has unveiled its collaboration with  
Shift4, an integrated payments and commerce technology platform. This  
partnership aims to empower web3 merchants by building a fiat-to-crypto on-ramp  
using Zero Hash's full-stack API.
Customizable Fiat-to-Crypto  
On-Ramp Enabled by Zero Hash's API Stack
Key  
highlights of the collaboration are as follows:

Comprehensive  
Solution:  
Shift4 has integrated Zero Hash's turnkey crypto infrastructure, offering web3  
merchants a unified solution that combines fiat and crypto capabilities.
Identity  
Verification:  
Shift4 has harnessed Zero Hash's customer identity verification-as-a-service,  
ensuring secure and compliant onboarding of users for crypto services.
Customizable  
On-Ramp: Using  
Zero Hash…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tareq Sikder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Crypto Withdrawals Temporarily Unavailable Due to Technical Issues]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a86fbaae</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/10/25/binance-crypto-withdrawals-temporarily-unavailable-due-to-technical-issues/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T11:49:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Withdrawals on cryptocurrency exchange Binance are temporarily unavailable due to a "technical issue," according to a post on the exchange's X account.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Israeli Crypto-Based Aid Organization Says Nearly $200,000 Raised for October 7 Terror Victims]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a869d44f</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/israeli-crypto-based-aid-organization-says-nearly-200000-raised-for-october-7-terror-victims/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T11:35:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nearly $200,000 has been raised by a non-profit organization launched by members of Israel’s Web3 community. More than 30 Web3 companies have since joined the campaign while the accounting firm KPMG is said to be assisting with fundraising and distribution. 
 
Web3 Companies Join Campaign
 
Crypto Aid Israel, a non-profit organization launched by influential leaders within the Israeli Web3 community, said nearly $200,000 has been raised as part of the Emergency Relief Initiative. Some of the funds raised have been distributed to organizations leading relief efforts for victims of the Oct. 7 attacks by Hamas.
 
 
.@CryptoAidIsrael with almost $200K in Donations as 30+ Global Web3 Companies Join The Initiative  Am Israel Chai  #StandWithIsrael pic.twitter.com/WAU5FpTj5N
 
— CryptoAidIsrael (…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Spot ETF: Crypto Research Firm Reveals What Will Happen In The First Three Years]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a86a6385</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-spot-etf-three-years/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T11:31:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The potential approval of a Spot Bitcoin ETF by the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) is expected to have significant effects on Bitcoin and the Spot Bitcoin ETF market. Addressing what investors can expect, the crypto research firm Galaxy Digital recently provided insights as to what could happen in the first three years upon the launch of this fund. 
 
What To Expect In The First Three Years
 
In a research paper released on October 24, Galaxy Digital’s research associate Charles Yu provided a vivid illustration of the heights a Spot Bitcoin ETF could attain in terms of market size and inflows in the first three years. 
 
 
As to market size, Yu made his predictions on the addressable market size of a US Bitcoin ETF based on how they expect various wealth channels to adopt the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Hovers Over $34K as BlackRock IBTC Ticker Euphoria Fades Out]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a86b9ef5</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/10/25/bitcoin-hovers-over-34k-as-blackrock-ibtc-ticker-euphoria-fades-out/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T11:24:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Growth among most crypto majors seemed to lull as traders likely took profits on gains since the start of this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TopHash: Your Gateway to Cloud Mining]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a856b923</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/tophash-your-gateway-to-cloud-mining/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T11:04:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This sponsored post was written by the TopHash team. Read disclaimer below.
 
Undeniably, the endeavor to amplify secondary sources of income has become more pertinent in today’s economic landscape. The conventional job market often falls short of providing a stable financial foundation for modern individuals. This reality propels us to introduce this comprehensive guide on cloud mining, showcasing our enterprise, TopHash, as a prime starting point. If you are looking for an entryway into the cryptocurrency realm—irrespective of your experience level in mining—we offer well-informed resources and strategies for your utilization. With the recent surge of BTC reaching $35,000, the allure of the cryptocurrency domain has magnified. Our guide elucidates the substantial knowledge and technical …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[POL Contracts Go Live on Ethereum Mainnet as Part of Polygon 2.0]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a8572e26</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/10/25/pol-contracts-go-live-on-ethereum-mainnet-as-part-of-polygon-20/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T11:02:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[POL token will power every blockchain that runs atop the Polygon network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Fear & Greed Index Hits Highest Since November 2021]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a8572e06</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/10/25/crypto-fear-greed-index-hits-highest-since-november-2021/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T11:02:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The index, coupled with an overbought reading on the RSI indicator, suggests bitcoin's bull run might take a breather.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon Deploys New POL Token Contracts on Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203226</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203226/polygon-launches-new-pol-token-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T11:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As part of Polygon's updated roadmap, the new POL token will replace the MATIC token as the ecosystem's primary coordination tool.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biggest Marketing Pitfalls in the Crypto Industry]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a857fa67</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/biggest-marketing-pitfalls-in-the-crypto-industry/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T10:56:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The  
cryptocurrency business, known for its rapid growth and ground-breaking  
developments, has piqued the interest of investors, traders, and enthusiasts  
all over the world. Nonetheless, there are substantial hurdles that must be  
navigated carefully in the field of bitcoin marketing. 
Inadequate  
Regulation and Oversight
Due to the lack  
of adequate regulatory frameworks, the bitcoin marketing landscape is fraught  
with ambiguity. Cryptocurrencies, by definition, operate in a decentralized and  
global environment, making it difficult for regulators to establish clear laws.  
This regulatory ambiguity can expose investors to dangers and impede efforts to  
protect investors. As a result, marketing strategies that exaggerate or mislead  
potential investors can undermine trust and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Ferreira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried’s Defunct Exchange FTX Receives Multiple Bids for Restart]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a85184d1</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/10/25/sam-bankman-frieds-defunct-exchange-ftx-receives-multiple-bids-for-restart/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T10:47:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Options also include a sale of the exchange, which boasted 9 million users before going bankrupt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Biggest Winners of This Week's Crypto Rally? MINA, Chainlink, and PEPE]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203218</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203218/biggest-winners-week-crypto-rally-mina-chainlink-pepe"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T09:43:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Besides heavyweights in Bitcoin and Ethereum, several notable altcoins also enjoyed serious rallies amid the spot ETF craze.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain Tech 'Stuck in the Eighties': Fantom's Andre Cronje]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203217</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203217/blockchain-tech-is-stuck-eighties-says-fantoms-andre-cronje"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T09:35:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the release of Sonic's testnet yesterday, Andre Cronje is hoping to bring Fantom and blockchain technology back to the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Artists Could Use a Poison Pill to Combat AI Exploitation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203153</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203153/ai-prompt-data-poisoning-nightshared"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T02:05:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers hope Nightshade will serve as an example of "data poisoning" that can prevent unauthorized ingestion of artists' works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[While Meta Pushes Into AI, 34 States File Suit Over Child Manipulation Claims]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203194</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203194/while-meta-pushes-into-ai-34-states-file-suit-for-child-manipulation-claims"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T01:30:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite Meta’s claims of a safe environment, states argue that Facebook and Instagram pose risks to the mental health of kids.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Habitat is Meta's Vision for the Future of Human-Robot Cohabitation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203160</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203160/meta-human-robot-habitat-embodied-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T00:58:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From following you around to helping you tidy up your room, Meta's latest AI advancements promise a future where robots are more than just tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adult Entertainment Actors Say Their Defenses Against AI Are More Elusive]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203159</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203159/porn-stars-fight-ai-deepfakes-with-less-support"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T00:35:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like SAG-AFTRA, Adult film performers seek protection from unauthorized AI deepfake porn and compensation for their work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Execs Are Deserting The Company–Here’s Who They Are]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203181</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203181/who-are-the-executives-leaving-binance"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T00:03:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Although the reasons varied, sixteen executives have left the company over the past few years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Senators Set in Motion Bipartisan Proof-of-Reserves Bill]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203131</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203131/u-s-senators-set-in-motion-bipartisan-proof-of-reserves-bill"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T22:44:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto advocates across the spectrum applaud the legislative action.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Submits Final Argument to Dismiss SEC Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203106</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203106/coinbase-submits-final-argument-to-dismiss-sec-lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T22:35:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Legal loggerheads have persisted between the SEC and Coinbase since June.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Fines BlackRock $2.5 Million as Bitcoin ETF Review Awaits]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203120</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203120/sec-fines-blackrock-bitcoin-etf-review"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T21:39:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s not the first time the Wall Street giant has been fined by the SEC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Funds Gain $57 Million in Fresh Cash Amid ETF Mania]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203101</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203101/bitcoin-funds-gain-57-million-amid-etf-mania"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T20:43:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most deposits went to spot Bitcoin ETFs in Canada and Germany, showing that investors want physical Bitcoin over anything else, said Coinshares.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Ally Tom Emmer Drops Out of Race for House Speaker After Trump Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203109</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203109/tom-emmer-nominated-as-house-speaker-to-crypto-cheers-trump-jeers"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T20:32:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ardently pro-crypto congressman was one vote away from the gavel, but the former president torpedoed his chances.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Lender BlockFi Ends Bankruptcy With a Plan to Repay Customers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203099</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203099/blockfi-ends-bankruptcy-prepares-to-return-customer-funds"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T19:26:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlockFi custodial wallet customers can submit withdrawal requests today, but interest bearing account customers will have to wait until 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maison Margiela Invites Its Fans To Play Blockchain Bingo]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203053</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203053/maison-margiela-numbers-mint-blockchin-bingo"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T17:40:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To advance in the numerological project, minters have got to collect them all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephanie Hirschmiller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Wobbles as BlackRock ETF Removed From DTCC List]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203012</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203012/bitcoin-wobbles-as-blockrock-etf-removed-from-dtcc-list"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T17:23:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The removal puts a damper on suspicions that a spot Bitcoin ETF was only days away.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can a FanDuel Co-Founder's 'Fantasy Music' Game Help Discover the Next Taylor Swift?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202927</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202927/fanduel-cofounder-fantasy-music-game-help-discover-next-taylor-swift"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T15:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vault’s Solana NFT music platform is spinning up a fantasy sports-like experience around emerging artists. Can it push them to prominence?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ali Shutler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacker Denis Katana Helped Russian Crime Boss Launder Money With Bitcoin, Says Spanish Judge]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202807</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202807/hacker-denis-katana-bitcoin-money-laundering"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T15:16:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 'Bitcoin czar' is accused of advising a crime ring to launder their money with Bitcoin because of its “lack of state control.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[dYdX Releases Cosmos-Based Chain Source Code Ahead of Mainnet Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202941</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202941/dydx-releases-cosmos-based-chain-source-code-ahead-mainnet-launch"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T12:07:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The release of the open source code marks the initial phase of dYdX Chain’s mainnet launch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Soar Double Digits as Crypto Markets Add $100 Billion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202944</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202944/bitcoin-ethereum-soar-crypto-markets-add-100-billion"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T12:03:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin and Ethereum soared nearly double digits early on Tuesday, as the wider crypto market added nearly 10% to its market cap overnight.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Andreessen Horowitz Backs Nym's $300M Privacy-Centric 'Innovation Fund']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202861</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202861/andreessen-horowitz-backs-nym-300m-privacy-centric-innovation-fund"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T11:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Applications for the innovation fund, which is not strictly limited to Nym’s privacy-preserving tech, will be accepted starting in November.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cathie Wood's Ark Invest Sells $5.8M in Coinbase, Grayscale Bitcoin Trust Shares as Crypto Market Surges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202938</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202938/cathie-woods-ark-invest-sells-5-8m-in-coinbase-grayscale-bitcoin-trust-shares-as-crypto-market-surges"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T09:29:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Bitcoin jumped over 10% amid renewed hopes of a spot ETF approval, Ark Invest opted to sell some of its Bitcoin-related assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deepfakes Made Simple With AI: An In-Depth Look at FaceFusion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201688</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201688/how-to-ai-deepfake-video-facefusion-face-swap-ai-tool"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T08:07:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The open-source FaceFusion tool is described as a next-generation face swapper and enhancer, and an accessible entry into the world of deepfake creation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Next Snapdragon Chip Leaks: The Upcoming Mobile CPU Is Packed with AI Power]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202905</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202905/snapdragon-8-generation-3-artificial-intelligence-smartphone-chip"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T01:20:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From enhanced performance to groundbreaking AI capabilities, the Qualcomm Snapdragon 8 Gen 3 is set to redefine what you can do with your smartphone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Touches $34K as $114 Million in Shorts Liquidated]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202894</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202894/bitcoin-price-34000-35000-liquidiations-2023-record"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T23:41:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A second rally for the day triggered $145 million in overall crypto market liquidations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Film3 Summit Returns to L.A. Alongside Streaming Festival With Theta]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202668</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202668/film3-summit-returns-la-alongside-streaming-festival-theta"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T23:15:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The live Film3 Summit will run alongside MetaFilm3 Fest, an on-chain festival powered by Theta that includes multiple film premieres.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ghost in the Machine: OpenAI CEO Sees ChatGPT on Track From AI to AGI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202877</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202877/openai-ai-agi-sam-altman-wall-street-journal"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T22:54:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI CEO Sam Altman delved into the transformative potential of AI, hinting at a future where data takes a backseat to reasoning.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Are the Odds Sam Bankman-Fried Testifies in His Trial?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202863</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202863/what-are-the-odds-sam-bankman-fried-testifies-in-his-trial"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T21:18:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The formal crypto mogul has remained silent in court so far. But that could change as his trial progresses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Ordered to Review Grayscale’s Bitcoin ETF Application]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202874</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202874/sec-must-again-review-grayscale-bitcoin-etf-application"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T20:39:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Will the SEC find another reason to reject Grayscale, or will it finally approve a spot Bitcoin ETF?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These Crypto Stocks Are Still Outperforming Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202865</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202865/crypto-stocks-beating-bitcoin-grayscale-microstrategy-coinbase"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T20:10:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While Bitcoin has been a great buy, many companies built around it are flying even higher this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock Preps for Bitcoin ETF Launch, Lines Up Seed Investor and Reveals Ticker]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202862</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202862/blackrock-preps-for-bitcoin-etf-launch-with-amendment-showing-seed-fund-investor"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T19:59:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock's iShares Bitcoin Trust has a ticker and seed funding lined up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Blasts Past $31,000 as Optimism for BTC Spot ETF Surges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202840</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202840/bitcoin-31000-spot-btc-etf-optimism"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T17:19:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The last time the asset was this high was back in July.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF Coming Soon? Delays Have SEC’s Hester Peirce ‘Mystified’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202826</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202826/bitcoin-etf-coming-soon-delays-have-secs-hester-peirce-mystified"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T16:56:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After Grayscale's court victory, Hester Peirce doesn't know what her agency is waiting for.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microstrategy’s Bitcoin Billions Back in Profit as ‘Digital Gold’ Nears $31K]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202813</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202813/microstrategys-bitcoin-in-the-green-digital-gold-rallies"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T16:37:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC is fast closing in on $31,000 per coin—which means the largest public owner of the asset is making a return on its investment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is the Lightning Network? Bitcoin's Scalability Solution.]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=5684</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/bitcoin-lightning-network"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T14:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lightning Network is a scaling solution that attempts to address Bitcoin's slow transaction speeds and high transaction costs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Hussey,Tim Copeland,Daniel Phillips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Banking Crisis Destroyed Institutional Crypto Trading: Chainalysis]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202791</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202791/us-banking-crisis-destroyed-institutional-crypto-trading-chainalysis"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T13:10:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto activity saw a sharp drop following Silicon Valley Bank and crypto-friendly banks Signature and Silvergate shutting down.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Almost All Mining Stocks Have Outpaced Bitcoin This Year]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202776</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202776/almost-all-mining-stocks-have-outpaced-bitcoin-this-year"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T11:01:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most mining stocks, except two, have outperformed Bitcoin by more than double this year despite the ongoing bear market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Midnight Society's Rob Bowling on Deadrop's New Cars and User-Generated Modes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/A0auyZzn/midnight-societys-rob-bowling-on-deadrops-new-cars-and-user-generated-modes</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/A0auyZzn/midnight-societys-rob-bowling-on-deadrops-new-cars-and-user-generated-modes"/>
        <updated>2023-10-22T01:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt reporter and GG producer Kate Irwin interviews Midnight Society Studio Head Rob Bowling about Deadrop's development and Snapshot VII.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Game Review: 'Raini: The Lords of Light' Brands Itself With Memes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/32YyJHCJ/game-review-raini-the-lords-of-light-brands-itself-with-memes</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/32YyJHCJ/game-review-raini-the-lords-of-light-brands-itself-with-memes"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T19:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Raini: Lords of Light is an NFT-optional card game bursting with crypto memes. From SBF to CZ and Elon, this free-to-play game has some truly wild animations. Decrypt contributor Ryan S. Gladwin shares his honest thoughts on the game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Art Blocks Marfa Weekend Recap]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/QaTBP6eO/art-blocks-marfa-weekend-recap</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/QaTBP6eO/art-blocks-marfa-weekend-recap"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T19:19:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Relive the Art Blocks Marfa Weekend 2023 event with this highlights video, produced by Vincent Roazzi Jr. for Decrypt Studios in partnership with Art Blocks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Phantom Galaxies: A Look Inside the Mech Shooter NFT Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QI1uDwQv/phantom-galaxies-a-look-inside-the-mech-shooter-nft-game</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QI1uDwQv/phantom-galaxies-a-look-inside-the-mech-shooter-nft-game"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T21:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animoca Brands and game studio Blowfish are developing Phantom Galaxies, an upcoming sci-fi mech shooter game inspired by mech battlers like Transformers. Decrypt's Kate Irwin asks Blowfish Studios Cofounder and Managing Director Ben Lee about what it's like to play the game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Clip: DeepMedia's DeepID Deepfake Detection Tool at Work]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/m4Vy4vhC/clip-deepmedias-deepid-deepfake-detection-tool-at-work</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/m4Vy4vhC/clip-deepmedias-deepid-deepfake-detection-tool-at-work"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T16:48:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A clip showcasing how DeepMedia's DeepID deepfake detection tool works. Courtesy: DeepMedia]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentraland AI World Fair Trailer]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/3tUb56Fv/decentraland-ai-world-fair-trailer</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/3tUb56Fv/decentraland-ai-world-fair-trailer"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A trailer for the AI World Fair event in metaverse game Decentraland, taking place from October 25-27. Courtesy: Decentraland.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BackTheBunny - Money, Conspiracy, Milady]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BRoKZzer/backthebunny-money-conspiracy-milady</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BRoKZzer/backthebunny-money-conspiracy-milady"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T19:48:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our host Reza Jafery sits down with BackTheBunny to dive deep into money, the fight against crypto that we're witnessing in real-time, and milady culture. 

Our Host: https://twitter.com/rezajafery
Our Guest: https://twitter.com/BackTheBunny

Our Sponsors
https://decrypt.co/1000x]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['A Grand Experiment': Shrapnel Studio Head Don Norbury Talks Game Economics]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Z2OMMsC5/a-grand-experiment-shrapnel-studio-head-don-norbury-talks-game-economics</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Z2OMMsC5/a-grand-experiment-shrapnel-studio-head-don-norbury-talks-game-economics"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T17:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How much of Shrapnel's in-game items are tradeable NFTs? Don Norbury, Studio Head at Shrapnel and CTO at game studio NEON, tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about Shrapnel's approach to game economics, including different game pricing models and how NFT game economies create different challenges for developers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trezor Safe 3 and Trezor Keep Metal Unboxing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/IjqnO9pR/trezor-safe-3-and-trezor-keep-metal-unboxing</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/IjqnO9pR/trezor-safe-3-and-trezor-keep-metal-unboxing"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T14:45:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trezor has launched the Safe 3, a hardware wallet aimed at "new entrants to crypto," alongside the new Keep Metal recovery seed storage device. We take a first look at what comes in the box.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why AI Arena is Building on Arbitrum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Gl80TQOm/why-ai-arena-is-building-on-arbitrum</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Gl80TQOm/why-ai-arena-is-building-on-arbitrum"/>
        <updated>2023-10-12T14:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI Arena CEO Brandon Da Silva and COO Wei Xie discuss the challenges that come with building on Ethereum, ETH sidechains, and layer-two blockchains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pet3rPan_ on venture DAOs and blockchain games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DawNLI3O/pet3rpan-on-venture-daos-and-blockchain-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DawNLI3O/pet3rpan-on-venture-daos-and-blockchain-games"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T18:24:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the 4th episode of this time will be different.

Our guest for today's episode is Pet3rpan_ from Metacartel, 1kx, HydraVentures, and more!

https://twitter.com/pet3rpan_

This Time Will Be Different is sponsored by 1000x
https://decrypt.co/1000x]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Shrapnel's Marketplace, New Map, and 'AI Director' Feature]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/F5RQCmvH/inside-shrapnels-marketplace-new-map-and-ai-director-feature</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/F5RQCmvH/inside-shrapnels-marketplace-new-map-and-ai-director-feature"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T16:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin chats with Shrapnel's Head of Studio Don Norbury to get the latest updates on how the NFT-powered first-person sci-fi extraction shooter's development is progressing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Art of the Times': Art Blocks Founder Erick Calderon on the State of Generative Art]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zSjfRrl5/art-of-the-times-art-blocks-founder-erick-calderon-on-the-state-of-generative-art</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zSjfRrl5/art-of-the-times-art-blocks-founder-erick-calderon-on-the-state-of-generative-art"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T18:10:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Art Blocks founder and CEO Erick Calderon sat down with Sander Lutz, lead culture reporter at Decrypt's SCENE, at Art Blocks Marfa Weekend 2023. They discuss the evolution of the company and the generative art world, along with what draws art enthusiasts to be an active part of the community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt Learn: Digital Ownership Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/6udZCotB/decrypt-learn-digital-ownership-explained</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/6udZCotB/decrypt-learn-digital-ownership-explained"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T10:57:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most powerful aspects of blockchain technology is its ability to provide us genuine ownership of our digital assets. This is called digital ownership. In this video, we’ll deep dive into digital ownership, why it matters, and how web3 makes owning digital assets like our social networks, music libraries, personal data, and beyond possible. Author: Clarissa Watson, Senior Writer at Consensys.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Martin Shkreli on E/ACC and SBF in Prison]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QONaWXKZ/martin-shkreli-on-e-acc-and-sbf-in-prison</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QONaWXKZ/martin-shkreli-on-e-acc-and-sbf-in-prison"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T22:03:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reza Jafery and Martin Shkreli sit down for a casual conversation about the growing movement that is E/ACC, what songs they could recite at gunpoint, and whether or not SBF will thrive or just survive during his time in prison.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Can AI Do in Gaming?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JKuqCMao/what-can-ai-do-in-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JKuqCMao/what-can-ai-do-in-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T17:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI Arena CEO Brandon Da Silva and COO Wei Xie discuss how artificial intelligence can shape the video game experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['There Are No Real Standards': Ready Player Me CEO Timmu Tõke on Building for an Open Gaming Ecosystem]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TH3KEAI0/there-are-no-real-standards-ready-player-me-ceo-timmu-tke-on-building-for-an-open-gaming-ecosystem</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TH3KEAI0/there-are-no-real-standards-ready-player-me-ceo-timmu-tke-on-building-for-an-open-gaming-ecosystem"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T17:29:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Timmu Tõke, co-founder and CEO of Ready Player Me, joins Decrypt contributor Ryan Gladwin to discuss the startup's approach to powering avatars that are interoperable across games and metaverse platforms—and what's needed to convince the industry to adopt standards and open up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain Is 'Only Way' Forward for Gaming, Says Shrapnel Studio Head]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/fhoy7Z8f/blockchain-is-only-way-forward-for-gaming-says-shrapnel-studio-head</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/fhoy7Z8f/blockchain-is-only-way-forward-for-gaming-says-shrapnel-studio-head"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T21:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shrapnel Studio Head Don Norbury tells Kate Irwin the reasons why the upcoming first-person shooter game will offer a wide range of NFTs. He also reveals team-based gameplay plans and shares how game maps have already changed this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Social Media Sentiment Is Key to Crypto Price Discovery]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/981TBppa/social-media-sentiment-is-key-to-crypto-price-discovery</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/981TBppa/social-media-sentiment-is-key-to-crypto-price-discovery"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T23:47:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sacha Ghebali, Director of Strategy and Business Development at The TIE, says social media sentiment remains a key factor in price movements for major cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin and Ethereum. However, he notes that sentiment has turned more negative lately amid regulatory uncertainty. Ghebali believes events like the Ripple lawsuit ruling significantly impacted sentiment and prices. André Beganski interviewed him at Messari Mainnet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[500Altcoins discusses DeFi Summer and the Dubai Crypto Scene - This Time Will Be Different - Episode 2]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cI7p8AK3/500altcoins-discusses-defi-summer-and-the-dubai-crypto-scene-this-time-will-be-different-episode-2</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cI7p8AK3/500altcoins-discusses-defi-summer-and-the-dubai-crypto-scene-this-time-will-be-different-episode-2"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our host Reza Jafery is joined by Gareth Fenney aka 500Altcoins. They discuss the glory days of DeFi Summer and whether or not its a smart move for builders in the crypto space to relocate to Dubai.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>