<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-08-07T12:28:41.544Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-08-07T12:28:41.544Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Data Platform Coinecko Publishes Altcoins Considered by SEC as Securities!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18822002/Cryptocurrency-Data-Platform-Coinecko-Publishes-Altcoins-Considered-by-SEC-as-Securities</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18822002/Cryptocurrency-Data-Platform-Coinecko-Publishes-Altcoins-Considered-by-SEC-as-Securities"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T12:15:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinecko shared the list of altcoins considered securities by the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). Continue Reading: Cryptocurrency Data Platform Coinecko Publishes Altcoins Considered by SEC as Securities!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP On-chain Data Has Something to Tell Us]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18822000/XRP-On-chain-Data-Has-Something-to-Tell-Us</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18822000/XRP-On-chain-Data-Has-Something-to-Tell-Us"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T12:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XRP's on-chain metrics hint at continuing downtrend, mirroring its current price trajectory]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Museum Makeover: A Solution For Curbing Artifacts Hoarding?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18821958/Ethereum-Museum-Makeover-A-Solution-For-Curbing-Artifacts-Hoarding</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18821958/Ethereum-Museum-Makeover-A-Solution-For-Curbing-Artifacts-Hoarding"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T12:05:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An Ethereum-based blockchain tool known as Salsal is under development, set to transform the way museums and cultural institutions manage and safeguard their invaluable historical collections. Spearheaded by Mark Altaweel, a distinguished professor in the archeology department at the University...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Highest of Stakes with Richard Heart encapsulates the narcissism of crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18821966/The-Highest-of-Stakes-with-Richard-Heart-encapsulates-the-narcissism-of-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18821966/The-Highest-of-Stakes-with-Richard-Heart-encapsulates-the-narcissism-of-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T12:04:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In his latest review, Cas Piancey explains why Hex founder Richard Heart's documentary The Highest of Stakes is actually essential viewing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WorldCoin faces renewed headwinds as WLD price retreats]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18821959/WorldCoin-faces-renewed-headwinds-as-WLD-price-retreats</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18821959/WorldCoin-faces-renewed-headwinds-as-WLD-price-retreats"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T12:02:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WorldCoin, the new blockchain project started by Sam Altman, is going through major headwinds as regulators remain concerned about data privacy. As a result, the WLD token price has plunged by more than 72% from the highest level this year. The total volume of the tokn traded in exchanges has...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UTXOracle: A Decentralized Approach To The Oracle Problem]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755f0ca2dc</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/technical/utxoracle-model-could-bring-use-cases-to-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T12:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is an opinion editorial by Daniel Hinton, the head of finance and operations for sFOX, a bitcoin prime broker and custodian, and Steve Jeffress, creator of Bitcoin UTXO set visualizer UTXO.live.
We now know how to infer the daily price of bitcoin within 1% by looking only at the unspent transaction output (UTXO) set.
With this, we can build decentralized applications that rely on the UTXO set — rather than on trusted third-party oracles — for the USD price used in discreet log contracts (DLCs) and smart contracts.
The possibilities for decentralized applications on Bitcoin using this “UTXOracle” are enormous.
 
         
         
         
        Source: author 
    
When You Want To Know ‘The’ Price Of Bitcoin, Where Do You Look?
There is no single price of bitcoin. Every second of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Hinton,Steve Jeffress</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin expects more companies to integrate in the coming months, says product head]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18821920/Worldcoin-expects-more-companies-to-integrate-in-the-coming-months-says-product-head</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18821920/Worldcoin-expects-more-companies-to-integrate-in-the-coming-months-says-product-head"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The head of product at Tools for Humanity told Cointelegraph that Worldcoin is expecting more companies to integrate in the second half of the year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UTXOracle: A Decentralized Approach To The Oracle Problem]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18821918/UTXOracle-A-Decentralized-Approach-To-The-Oracle-Problem</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18821918/UTXOracle-A-Decentralized-Approach-To-The-Oracle-Problem"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using the UTXO set to calculate a bitcoin price.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Veteran Trader Peter Brandt Says 99.8% Of Altcoins Will Meet Similar Fate To Internet Marketer Richard Heart's HEX]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18821993/Veteran-Trader-Peter-Brandt-Says-998-Of-Altcoins-Will-Meet-Similar-Fate-To-Internet-Marketer-Richard-Hearts-HEX</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18821993/Veteran-Trader-Peter-Brandt-Says-998-Of-Altcoins-Will-Meet-Similar-Fate-To-Internet-Marketer-Richard-Hearts-HEX"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T11:59:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Popular veteran trader Peter Brandt on Sunday said that 99.8% of altcoins will eventually meet a similar fate as HEX coin. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Victory Is Ours,’ Lawyers, Community Celebrate ‘Best Day in Crypto’]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18821947/Victory-Is-Ours-Lawyers-Community-Celebrate-Best-Day-in-Crypto</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18821947/Victory-Is-Ours-Lawyers-Community-Celebrate-Best-Day-in-Crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T11:56:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pro-XRP lawyer John Deaton, the founder and host of Crypto Law TV, expressed his excitement and satisfaction in his show, with the recent ruling in the SEC vs. Ripple case. Deaton hailed the decision as a significant milestone for the cryptocurrency industry, asserting that it was arguably the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trader Makes 800 ETH In Five Minutes On Blur NFT Marketplace]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755f0d6b8e</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/nft-trader-makes-800-eth-in-5-minutes/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T11:53:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent development, the attention of crypto Twitter has been captured by a string of transactions that occurred on the  Blur NFT marketplace. The transactions have raised questions of legality after a creative trader with the name, Hanwe Chang, deceived a competitor into purchasing specific Azuki NFTs at an inflated price. 
 
A Highly Controversial Transaction
 
Despite being a newcomer in comparison to other popular NFT marketplaces such as SuperRare and OpenSea, Blur has grown ahead of others in terms of trading volumes earlier this year, partly due to the gamified incentives that reward participants with tokens according to trade-based activity. 
 
 
This includes rewards in the form of an airdrop offered to users that bid on Non-Fungible Tokens (NFTs) by trait, a practice which, a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$52.3 million Recovered From Curve Finance Heist]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18821926/523-million-Recovered-From-Curve-Finance-Heist</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18821926/523-million-Recovered-From-Curve-Finance-Heist"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T11:53:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Curve CRV-ETH exploiter is yet to return $19.7 million worth of cryptocurrency stolen during the reentrancy attacks on July 30. DeFi projects Alchemix Finance, JPEGd, and Metronome recovered a combined $48.1 million through asset returns from exploiters and white hat efforts. Curve Finance...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Now Is a Good Time to Accumulate Altcoins, According to Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18821946/Now-Is-a-Good-Time-to-Accumulate-Altcoins-According-to-Analyst</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18821946/Now-Is-a-Good-Time-to-Accumulate-Altcoins-According-to-Analyst"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T11:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The renowned cryptocurrency trader and analyst Michael van de Poppe tweeted yesterday that the cryptocurrency market is in an accumulation phase. In the post, he added that the accumulation phase can be seen in the weekly chart for the total market cap for cryptocurrencies excluding Ethereum...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Investor Who Called Crypto Bottom Doubles Down on Bull Market Forecast – But There’s a Catch]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18821913/Investor-Who-Called-Crypto-Bottom-Doubles-Down-on-Bull-Market-Forecast-But-Theres-a-Catch</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18821913/Investor-Who-Called-Crypto-Bottom-Doubles-Down-on-Bull-Market-Forecast-But-Theres-a-Catch"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T11:45:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Venture capitalist Chris Burniske is staying confident in his call that crypto is gearing up to enter a new bull market. Burniske, a partner at Placeholder and the former head of crypto at Ark Invest, says that the digital asset space is essentially reacting to every obstacle thrown at it, and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 5 cryptocurrencies pumping this Monday, August 7]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18821912/Top-5-cryptocurrencies-pumping-this-Monday-August-7</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18821912/Top-5-cryptocurrencies-pumping-this-Monday-August-7"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T11:45:14.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[List of 'Crypto Securities' Published by SEC: BNB, ADA, MATIC, SOL and Other Tokens]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18821914/List-of-Crypto-Securities-Published-by-SEC-BNB-ADA-MATIC-SOL-and-Other-Tokens</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18821914/List-of-Crypto-Securities-Published-by-SEC-BNB-ADA-MATIC-SOL-and-Other-Tokens"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T11:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FBI Issues Warning on Scam Involving Criminals Impersonating NFT Developers]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755f0f671e</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/fbi-issues-warning-on-scam-involving-criminals-impersonating-nft-developers/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T11:38:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) has issued a Public Service Announcement (PSA) warning about criminals impersonating non-fungible token (NFT) developers in social media. According to the PSA, criminals can impersonate these developers on social media by hijacking accounts or using similar account names and directing interested users to fake NFT sales pages to drain their wallets.
FBI Warns Users About NFT Scams
The Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) has issued a Public Service Announcement (PSA) warning users about non-fungible token (NFT) scams involving criminals impersonating developers of renowned projects. To target NFT-interested users, the criminals might take different routes, hijacking the accounts of these significant NFT projects or using almost identical account na…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monetary Authority of Singapore commits funding for fintech innovation, including web3]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18821890/Monetary-Authority-of-Singapore-commits-funding-for-fintech-innovation-including-web3</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18821890/Monetary-Authority-of-Singapore-commits-funding-for-fintech-innovation-including-web3"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T11:34:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Monetary Authority of Singapore has committed funding to, among other things, the support of fintech innovation — including web3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JD Sports Teams Up With ZERO10 To Offer Virtual Fitting Of Nike Collection In Stores]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18821883/JD-Sports-Teams-Up-With-ZERO10-To-Offer-Virtual-Fitting-Of-Nike-Collection-In-Stores</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18821883/JD-Sports-Teams-Up-With-ZERO10-To-Offer-Virtual-Fitting-Of-Nike-Collection-In-Stores"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T11:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AR try-on store, Zero10 has announced its recent partnership with JD Sports to animate the new Need It Now Collection, a new release by Nike in collaboration with JD Sports. Zero10 will deploy its AR Mirrors to allow users to virtually try on each outfit with advanced features and design to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin sees the second-highest number of new Inscriptions per day]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18821884/Bitcoin-sees-the-second-highest-number-of-new-Inscriptions-per-day</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18821884/Bitcoin-sees-the-second-highest-number-of-new-Inscriptions-per-day"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T11:31:30.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Announces Listing A New Altcoin For Futures]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18821867/Binance-Announces-Listing-A-New-Altcoin-For-Futures</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18821867/Binance-Announces-Listing-A-New-Altcoin-For-Futures"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T11:31:06.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kenyan police reportedly seize Worldcoin machines in warehouse raid]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18821889/Kenyan-police-reportedly-seize-Worldcoin-machines-in-warehouse-raid</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18821889/Kenyan-police-reportedly-seize-Worldcoin-machines-in-warehouse-raid"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T11:30:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin was suspended in Kenya last week with authorities citing “a number of legitimate regulatory concerns that require urgent attention.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Aave in the clear following the Curve hack?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18821878/Is-Aave-in-the-clear-following-the-Curve-hack</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18821878/Is-Aave-in-the-clear-following-the-Curve-hack"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T11:30:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Risk exposure of Aave to Curve declines materially as the condition of the protocol improves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Curve Finance Recovers over 70% of Hacked Funds: Report]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755f0aa386</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/curve-finance-recovers-over-70-of-hacked-funds-report/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T11:15:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The hackers who exploited Curve Finance have returned 73%  
of the tokens stolen from the decentralized finance (DeFi) platform. So far,  
the amount of tokens returned is estimated at USD $53 million, according  
to a report by a blockchain data analytics platform.
About a week ago, Curve  
Finance, the DeFi platform for stablecoins, was exploited through a reentrancy bug on its smart contracts programming language, Vyper. This action led to price  
volatility in CRV, the native token of the DeFi platform. Additionally, it  
prompted the cryptocurrency exchange, Upbit to suspend deposits and withdrawals of the  
token.
"A number of  
stablepools (alETH/msETH/pETH) which are using Vyper 0.2.15 have been exploited  
as a result of a malfunctioning reentrancy lock," a representative from Cur…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin's Nairobi Warehouse Raided by Kenyan Police: Local Reports]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755f0bc283</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/08/07/worldcoins-nairobi-warehouse-raided-by-kenyan-police-local-reports/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T11:06:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kenyan police raided Worldcoin's Nairobi warehouse and confiscated documents and machines on Saturday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amitoj Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Major Week Ahead For Bitcoin And Crypto: 3 Must-Watch Events]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7558f5812a</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/major-week-ahead-bitcoin-crypto-3-must-watch/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T10:54:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the Bitcoin and crypto market, the upcoming week promises to be a pivotal one. While the US Consumer Price Index (CPI), Jobless Claims, Producer Price Index (PPI) and Michigan Consumer Sentiment are all on the horizon, three events stand out as particularly: the July release of the CPI and PPI data, as well as the much-anticipated Bitcoin ETF decision for ARK Invest.
 
Consumer Price Index (CPI) On Thursday (8:30 am EST)
 
The CPI, a key measure of inflation, has been under the microscope as the US grapples with fluctuating inflation rates. The headline CPI is expected to rise from 3% to 3.3% YoY in July, a notable shift as beneficial base effects from the previous year begin to fade. The Cleveland Fed’s Inflation Nowcast model even forecasts a 3.42% headline CPI, slightly above the co…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong Raises Alarm on Crypto Platforms Just Two Months after Easing Regulations]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7558f6d048</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/hong-kong-raises-alarm-on-crypto-platforms-just-two-months-after-easing-regulations/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T10:45:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More than two months ago, cryptocurrency regulations in Hong Kong loosened  
considerably, allowing retail traders back into the market. However, as it  
turns out, the Securities and Futures Commission (SFC) has recently identified increased  
improper activities being carried out by some unlicensed virtual asset trading  
platforms (VATPs). Not only are these practices deceptive, but they endanger investors. The regulator raised four main concerns and their  
implications for both VATPs and retail investors.
SFC Warns against Improper  
Practices
In its  
latest warning, the SFC drew attention to several important issues concerning  
cryptocurrency trading in Hong Kong. The first issue pertains to false  
information about applying for a cryptocurrency license in the special  
administra…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Damian Chmiel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano Blockchain Transactions Jumped 49% Last Quarter as ADA Sentiment Grew]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7558f7ae8e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/08/07/cardano-blockchain-transactions-jumped-49-last-quarter-as-ada-sentiment-grew/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T10:38:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain load – a measure of how much data is contained in blocks over a certain period – rose to 50% in the second quarter from under 40% in the first. It peaked at 81% in May.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Long-Term Bitcoin Holder Metric Hits New All-Time High]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151561</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151561/long-term-bitcoin-holder-metric-hits-new-all-time-high"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T10:31:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data shows Bitcoin long-term holders now hold 14.599 million BTC, the highest value the metric has ever seen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoin Deposits on Maker Soar as DAI Interest Rates Hit 8%]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151557</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151557/stablecoin-deposits-maker-soar-dai-interest-rates-hit-8"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T10:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The amount of DAI minted and deposited back into the Maker protocol has surged dramatically since the latest upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exclusive: Vanuatu Regulator Brings Brokers to The "Shore". In Person.]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7558f3fa14</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/exclusive-vanuatu-regulator-brings-brokers-to-the-shore-in-person/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T10:06:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the watchdog series, we provide our readers with direct insights from the regulators that shape the retail trading industry. After an in-depth interview with the Chair of CySEC (who spoke about investors' responsibility and AI integration), and an exclusive comment from the FCA about the consumer duty deadline, today we bring you Nicolas Ritoux, the Communications Officer at the Vanuatu Financial Services Commission. His article sheds light on why and how the quintessential offshore jurisdiction wants to draw in brokers to the Island.
In a recent symposium hosted by the Vanuatu Financial Services Commission (VFSC), the nation's budding fintech industry took center stage as a strategic sector with immense potential for the country's economic growth. The "Virtual Assets: Navigating the Le…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicolas Ritoux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$1.8M Bounty Now Open to Public as Curve Finance Hacker Misses Deadline]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151555</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151555/1-8m-bounty-now-open-public-curve-finance-hacker-misses-deadline"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T09:59:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Curve bounty sits at 10% of the stolen funds, roughly $1.85 million, and was announced via an on-chain Ethereum message.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Exchange OPNX Emerges As Potential Savior For Troubled Hodlnaut – Report]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7558fda60d</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/opnx-as-potential-savior-for-hodlnaut/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T09:53:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OPNX Exchange emerges as a potential savior for crypto lender Hodlnaut as it navigates the complexities of bankruptcy proceedings. A recent report from Bloomberg reveals that the exchange has extended a lifeline to the struggling company. By presenting a proposition to acquire 75% ownership, OPNX Exchange aims to rejuvenate Hodlnaut’s fortunes. 
 
The proposal entails an infusion of $30 million worth of FLEX tokens into the enterprise, a strategic move aimed at facilitating partial restitution to the company’s creditors, as disclosed in the report. 
 
This development underscores the intricate interplay between the world of digital finance and traditional economic mechanisms, signaling a potential turning point for Hodlnaut’s future.
 
 
Innovative Creditor Restitution Plan Unveiled
 
If g…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Options Traders Are Still Shorting Bitcoin Volatility]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7558fbb579</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/08/07/crypto-options-traders-are-still-shorting-bitcoin-volatility/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T09:03:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Given the absence of big news in August, selling volatility and taking a vacation for solid theta gains is the only thing I can do right now," one trader said. Crypto traders typically short volatility by selling or writing call/put options.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scottish Author Exposing Onecoin Cancels ‘Devil’s Coin’ Book Tour After Death Threats]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7558e6bebd</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/scottish-author-exposing-onecoin-cancels-devils-coin-book-tour-after-death-threats/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T08:38:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An author from Scotland has been targeted for her work to expose one of crypto history’s most notorious Ponzi schemes, Onecoin. Jennifer McAdam recently canceled book signings after receiving death threats for writing about the massive fraud and its ‘Cryptoqueen’ mastermind.
 
Writer Cancels Promotional Events for Book on Onecoin on Advice From Scottish Police and FBI
 
Author Jennifer McAdam has been forced to cancel a promotional tour for her book ‘Devil’s Coin’ exposing the crypto pyramid Onecoin which defrauded millions of investors around the world, the Scottish Sun newspaper reported.
 
McAdam writes about Onecoin’s founder Ruja Ignatova, dubbed the “missing Cryptoqueen” as she is still wanted by Interpol, Europol, and the U.S. Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI), which put it on i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lubomir Tassev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Huobi's Stablecoin Reserves Down 30% Amid Reports of Executive Arrests]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7558e08bb3</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/08/07/huobis-stablecoin-reserves-down-30-amid-reports-of-executive-arrests/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T08:23:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data from Nansen.ai shows that users have withdrawn $44.8 million in stablecoins during the last week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zuck v. Musk and Other Famous Feuds in Web3 History]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151495</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/zuck-v-musk-and-other-famous-feuds-in-web3-history"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T08:15:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In such a turbulent world dominated by strong personalities and potentially large sums of speculative cash flying around, it’s perhaps to be expected that high-profile feuds and fights will develop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Reiff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Curve Recoups 73% of Hacked Funds, Bolstering CRV Sentiment]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7558e2a56d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/08/07/curve-recoups-73-of-hacked-funds-bolstering-crv-sentiment/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T08:04:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A public bounty is now open for finding the remaining funds with a $1.8 million reward.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Huobi's $500 Million Nightmare: From a Rumor to Alleged Insolvency]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7558e83a62</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/huobis-500-million-nightmare-from-a-rumor-to-alleged-insolvency/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T07:13:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rumors can  
act as a dangerous weapon, triggering panic and leading to capital flight. The  
cryptocurrency exchange, Huobi learned this the hard way, losing $500 million due  
to gossip that its leadership had been arrested in China and that the platform  
was on the verge of bankruptcy.
Huobi's TVL Drops by $500  
Million
Initial  
reports of Huobi's troubles emerged on 4 August after the initial news that  
representatives from the exchange had been arrested in China in relation to  
investigations involving ties to gambling platforms. On Twitter, Huobi's  
spokesperson stated that rumors regarding the arrest of high-ranking exchange  
representatives were false.

The source has been verified as a senior executive at Tron who has first hand knowledge of the investigation and has been a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Damian Chmiel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Huobi Insolvency Fears Surge Post-Exec Arrests: Crypto Storm Ahead?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7558ea6a22</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/huobi-insolvency-exec-arrests-crypto-storm/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T06:53:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent series of tweets, Adam Cochran, a well-known analyst in the crypto community and angel investor, has raised serious concerns about the solvency of Huobi, the world’s 12th largest crypto exchange by spot volume. This comes in the wake of reports that several executives from Huobi and Tron have been taken into custody by Chinese authorities for investigation.
 
Cochran’s claims are based on a detailed analysis of Huobi’s balance sheets and the recent activities of Justin Sun, the founder of Tron. He alleges that Sun has been using the exchange as a personal piggy bank, diverting funds to his other DeFi projects, and leaving the exchange with insufficient assets to meet its obligations.
 
“So users think they have balances of $631M in Huobi, but there is only $90M there. The rest …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Latam Insights — Honduras Opens Public CBDC Consultation, Venezuela Applies to Enter BRICS]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7558d1bb26</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/latam-insights-honduras-opens-public-cbdc-consultation-venezuela-applies-to-enter-brics/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T05:37:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Latam Insights, a compendium of Latin America’s most relevant crypto and economic news during the last week. In this issue: Honduras opens a central bank digital currency (CBDC) consultation, Venezuela applies officially to join BRICS, and Trubit launches Pix payment integration in Brazil.
Honduras Opens CBDC Issuance Public Consultation
The Central Bank of Honduras has opened a public consultation regarding issuing a central bank digital currency (CBDC). The public consultation marks the next phase of a plan to modernize the country’s payment systems. In a report issued by the bank, titled “The Future of Money and Payments in Honduras, which route to Follow?” the institution considers the implications and changes it must apply to its legal system to adopt a CBDC.
The poll asks …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Huobi Crypto Exchange Grapples with Rumors of Insolvency Amidst Hefty Outflows]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151535</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151535/huobi-insolvency-police-rumors-adam-cochran-justin-sun"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T03:03:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto analyst Adam Cochran dismissed claims by the company's community manager that his information "has been pure rumors."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt AI, Edited by Ryan Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[G20 President India Proposes ‘Action Points’ for Implementing Global Crypto Rules]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7558c17db2</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/g20-president-india-proposes-action-points-for-implementing-global-crypto-rules/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T02:36:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Indian Presidency of G20 has put forward proposals for a roadmap to introducing a global regulatory framework for crypto assets. India believes a more coordinated policy will be needed to enforce international standards in the field and adequately minimize associated risks.
 
India’s G20 Presidency Provides Its Input for FSB and IMF Global Crypto Regulatory Roadmap
 
India, the current President of the Group of 20 forum of the world’s largest economies (G20), has made some suggestions regarding the regulation of crypto assets. With the proposals, New Delhi seeks to help prioritize certain “areas of work essential to achieving a comprehensive, cohesive and coordinated global policy” for the sector.
 
In a Presidency Note released on Aug. 1, India said that while “considerable work” has …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lubomir Tassev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Mover Asia: Bitcoin Teases $30K While the Long Wait for an ETF Continues]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7558c3bcfa</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/08/07/first-mover-asia-bitcoin-teases-30k-while-the-long-wait-for-an-etf-continues/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T02:06:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trading volume is down, but all signs point to a break-out around the corner.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Superconductor Hype Sparks Flurry of LK-99 Memecoins]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151533</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151533/superconductor-hype-sparks-flurry-of-lk-99-memecoins"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T01:05:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The nascent cluster of coins seeks to surge on the latest technological buzz.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Court Dismisses Former Celsius Network CEO’s Motion to Block New York Attorney General’s Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7558b5d990</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/us-court-dismisses-former-celsius-network-ceos-motion-to-block-new-york-attorney-generals-lawsuit/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-06T23:41:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celsius Network Alex Mashinsky will now have to defend himself against a lawsuit filed by New York Attorney General Letitia James after a New York County Supreme Court Justice rejected his attempts to have the suit dismissed. The court’s decision blocks the attempt by Mashinsky to stop James from seeking to preclude him from issuing securities or serving as a company officer in the state.
 
Mashinsky Misstatements Induced Investors to Deposit Assets on Celsius
 
A United States judge has rejected former Celsius Network CEO Alex Mashinsky’s attempt to have the court dismiss a lawsuit filed by New York Attorney General (NYAG) Letitia James, a report has said. The court’s decision blocks the attempt by Mashinsky to stop James from seeking to preclude him from issuing securities or serv…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFT Trader Admits Nabbing $1.5 Million in Ethereum After ‘Elizab.eth’ Gets Rekt on Blur]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151528</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151528/nft-trader-admits-nabbing-1-5-million-in-ethereum-after-elizab-eth-gets-rekt-on-blur"/>
        <updated>2023-08-06T21:31:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spotting a bot mimicking his trades, Hanwe Chang used the strategy against its owner to earn a huge premium.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Try On Copenhagen Fashion Week's Latest Styles in the Metaverse]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151520</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151520/copenhagen-fashion-week-drest-game"/>
        <updated>2023-08-06T18:59:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Luxury mobile style game Drest is teaming up with the leading fashion event in Scandinavia, enhancing its product with Web3 elements.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephanie Hirschmiller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dungeons &#038; Dragons Publisher to Tighten Artist Guidelines After AI Art Found in Book]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151515</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151515/dungeons-dragons-ai-artificial-intelligence-art-artwork-artist-ilya-shkipin"/>
        <updated>2023-08-06T18:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[California artist and musician Ilya Shkipin defended his use of artificial intelligence on Twitter, sharing examples before deleting them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week on Crypto Twitter: SBF Accused of Executing Massive Rug Pull from House Arrest]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151498</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151498/this-week-on-crypto-twitter-sbf-bald-base-coinbase-rug-pull"/>
        <updated>2023-08-06T17:50:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It probably wasn’t him, however, given the austere technological limitations under which he's living.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Meta, Amazon, Google, Apple and AMD Are Saying About AI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151463</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151463/ai-apple-google-meta-amazon-amd-artificial-intelligence-strategy"/>
        <updated>2023-08-06T00:39:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AI hype is real, and based on their latest earnings reports, all of the multibillion-dollar behemoths of tech sector are going all in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk: 'We Never Will' Launch a Twitter or X Crypto Token]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151461</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151461/elon-musk-twitter-x-crypto-token-denial"/>
        <updated>2023-08-06T00:22:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The blunt declaration came after the Tesla CEO replied to a warning about scam tokens claiming to be affiliated with his company.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Friday Night Bet to Astrology Star: The Story of Kundli GPT]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151450</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151450/kundli-gpt-ai-astrology-taro-psychic"/>
        <updated>2023-08-05T17:04:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kundli GPT, a chatbot based on OpenAI's technology, provides individualized astrological data to users, amassing 20 million visitors thanks to social media.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KPMG Bitcoin Report Marks 'A Milestone The Bitcoin Ecosystem Should Celebrate': Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151443</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151443/bitcoin-esg-environment-social-corporate-governance-kpmg"/>
        <updated>2023-08-05T16:43:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Demonstrating how Bitcoin makes positive contributions is critical to both mainstream and institutional comfort,” says Daniel Batten, ESG analyst and CH4 Capital co-founder.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Does AI Affect Kids? Psychologists Weigh In]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151434</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151434/ai-effects-on-kids-children"/>
        <updated>2023-08-05T16:23:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Experts warn children may form emotional bonds with AI, overshadowing human relationships and hindering social skills development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Sparse News Extends Streak of Underwhelming Bitcoin and Ethereum Prices]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151424</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151424/this-week-in-coins-six-weeks-weak-bitcoin-and-ethereum-prices"/>
        <updated>2023-08-05T15:45:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Although Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong did reveal that the SEC asked his exchange to delist all cryptocurrencies except Bitcoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Curve Finance Chaos Is a $110 Million Gut Check for DeFi]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151336</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151336/curve-finance-chaos-is-110-million-gut-check-defi"/>
        <updated>2023-08-05T10:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If DeFi still needs "handshake" deals and fleet of crypto influencers to keep it afloat, is it really better than traditional finance?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitter User Has @Music Handle 'Ripped Away' by Elon Musk]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151378</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151378/twitter-music-handle-ripped-away-elon-musk"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T21:44:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[First "@X" and now "@Music." Popular Twitter handles are being seized by the newly rebranded X.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FDIC Sends Cease-and-Desist to Crypto Firm That Shuttered in June]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151398</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151398/fdic-cease-desist-crypto-firm-shuttered"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T21:32:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The FDIC alleges the firm made false claims about FDIC insurance coverage two months after the company announced ceasing operations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Researchers Claim They Can Double the Efficiency of Chatbots]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151392</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151392/ai-researchers-can-double-llm-efficiency"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T20:47:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Abacus AI claims to have found a way to fine-tune LLMs, making them capable of processing 200% their original context token capacity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mech Shooter 'MetalCore' Is 'Titanfall' Meets 'Destiny' With an NFT Twist]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151380</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151380/mech-shooter-metalcore-titanfall-meets-destiny-nft-twist"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T20:31:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PREVIEW: Ever wanted to own a mech? Immutable zkEVM game MetalCore will let you do just that, and the early playtest shows serious promise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['MetalCore' Game Preview: Hands-on With the 'Titanfall' Meets 'Destiny' NFT Mash-Up]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/tjK6i7lv/metalcore-game-preview-hands-on-with-the-titanfall-meets-destiny-nft-mash-up</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/tjK6i7lv/metalcore-game-preview-hands-on-with-the-titanfall-meets-destiny-nft-mash-up"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T19:46:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MetalCore is an upcoming mech shooter developed by Studio 369, and it's being developed on Ethereum scaling network Immutable zkEVM. Decrypt contributor Ryan Gladwin played through the prologue and tested out the recent Alpha 3 online experience to get a sense of the NFT-infused mash-up of Titanfall and Destiny.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can Live Music NFTs Revive 'Cassette Culture' and Boost Indie Bands?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151371</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151371/can-live-music-nfts-revive-cassette-culture-boost-indie-bands"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T18:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana music platform Vault’s latest initiative could elevate and support underground artists via exclusive NFT drops from live performances.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ali Shutler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Wants SEC Lawsuit Thrown Out, Says Gensler Overstepped His Authority]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151368</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151368/coinbase-wants-sec-lawsuit-dismissed-gensler-overstepped-authority"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T17:24:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[America’s largest crypto exchange said Friday that the SEC had no authority to pursue its lawsuit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zero10 and JD Sports Offer Virtual Try-On of Nike Apparel at IRL Stores]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151310</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151310/zero10-and-jd-sports-offer-virtual-try-on-of-nike-apparel-at-irl-stores"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T16:36:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ZERO10’s AR Mirrors animate the new JD Sports x Nike Need it Now collection, allowing visitors to virtually try on 18 items—some of which come with additional AR enhancement effects like water droplets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephanie Hirschmiller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt’s Guide to Stable Diffusion: The Most Powerful Open-Source Tool for AI Image Generation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151298</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/decrypts-guide-to-stable-diffusion-the-most-powerful-open-source-tool-for-ai-image-generation"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T16:19:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Be it a "hyperrealistic portrait of Emma Watson as a sorceress" or an "intricate digital painting of a pirate in a fantasy setting," the only limit is your imagination.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitter Bot Activity Increased After FTX Listed Tokens, Report Finds]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151307</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151307/twitter-bot-activity-increased-after-ftx-listed-tokens-report-finds"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T15:46:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A report by the Network Contagion Research Institute found that "inauthentic chatter" increased to 50% after being listed by FTX.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Comedian Adam Devine the New Matt Damon as Face of Crypto Exchange BitGet]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151299</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151299/comedian-adam-devine-crypto-exchange-bitget"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T15:07:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Will fortune favor this latest celebrity and crypto exchange pairing?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Room-Temperature Superconductor Race Shines Light on Crypto’s ‘DeSci’ Movement]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151300</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151300/room-temperature-superconductor-race-shines-light-crypto-desci-movement"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T14:52:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the world races towards validating LK-99, the crypto community, specifically DeSci, is up to another experiment all together.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SHIB Surges 10% Over the Week Amid Push for Identity Service, Binance Integration]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151284</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151284/shib-surges-10-week-amid-push-identity-service-binance-integration"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T12:58:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance added SHIB as a collateral asset, while its developers are working hard to shed the meme coin status.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Germany's Far-Right AfD: Worldcoin Orbs 'Solely for the Global Surveillance of People']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151282</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151282/germanys-far-right-afd-worldcoin-orbs-solely-for-the-global-surveillance-of-people"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T12:24:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A member of the far-right Alternative for Germany party has clashed head-on with privacy claims made by Worldcoin and its Orb activity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin Bug Allowed Anyone to Become Orb Operator: CertiK]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151279</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151279/worldcoin-bug-allowed-anyone-become-orb-operator-certik"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T10:34:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Worldcoin team has reportedly confirmed the security vulnerability and issued the required fix to the issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi Teams Issue Stark On-Chain Warning to Curve Finance Hacker]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151273</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151273/defi-teams-issue-stark-warning-curve-finance-hacker"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T09:54:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The on-chain message stated that the DeFi teams intend to pursue the Curve Finance hacker "from all angles with the full extent of the law."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Revolut to Shutter US Crypto Operations Due to 'Regulatory Environment']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151272</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151272/revolut-shutter-us-crypto-operations-due-regulatory-environment"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T09:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From September 2, Revolut will suspend its cryptocurrency services in the U.S., with complete access disabled from October 3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brave's New Image and Video Search Doesn't Rely on Google or Bing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151221</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151221/braves-new-image-video-search-doesnt-rely-google-bing"/>
        <updated>2023-08-03T23:24:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking to enhance user privacy, crypto-friendly browser Brave now offers independent image and video search results.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Guild of Guardians' RPG Could Be Your Next Mobile Gaming Fix]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151220</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151220/guild-guardians-rpg-next-mobile-gaming-fix-preview"/>
        <updated>2023-08-03T23:14:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PREVIEW: Immutable’s upcoming Guild of Guardians blends dungeon strategy with casual, mobile fun. We go hands-on.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI’s ChatGPT Just Got Smarter: Here’s the Latest on the AI Chatbot]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151205</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151205/openai-chatgpt-updates-latest-ai-chatbot"/>
        <updated>2023-08-03T22:01:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Upload multiple files, suggested prompts and replies, and a whole lot more. OpenAI just released a bevy of updates for ChatGPT.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ukraine Charity Soccer Match Hits the Metaverse Pitch to Raise Funds]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151194</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151194/ukraine-charity-soccer-match-hits-metaverse-pitch-raise-funds"/>
        <updated>2023-08-03T21:38:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Saturday's Game4Ukraine match will raise money for Ukraine, and if you can't be in London, then you can watch (and donate) in the metaverse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Cohen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Seeks to 'Optimize' Amid Bitcoin Bear Market, Beats Earnings Expectations]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151191</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151191/coinbase-bitcoin-bear-market-beats-earnings-q2"/>
        <updated>2023-08-03T21:13:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[America’s leading crypto exchange beat analysts' profit and revenue expectations for the second quarter in a row.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Give Projects a Chance,' Says Aurory's Michael Natoli on NFT Game Challenges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/nBNKKZdK/give-projects-a-chance-says-aurorys-michael-natoli-on-nft-game-challenges</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/nBNKKZdK/give-projects-a-chance-says-aurorys-michael-natoli-on-nft-game-challenges"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aurory is an NFT-driven game franchise that started life on Solana and is expanding to other chains. Decrypt's Jason Nelson spoke with Aurory Head of Marketing Michael Natoli at Solana's PlayGG event, where Natoli shared his thoughts on the challenges that blockchain games face in reaching players.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Is Only Network Ready for Gaming: Solana Foundation's Johnny Lee]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5OvV3ZXn/solana-is-only-network-ready-for-gaming-solana-foundations-johnny-lee</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5OvV3ZXn/solana-is-only-network-ready-for-gaming-solana-foundations-johnny-lee"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T17:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Foundation General Manager Johnny Lee tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how the Solana network will tackle the scaling problem that blockchain games pose for the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Com2uS Is Going "Full Speed" on Crypto Gaming: Kyu Lee]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pYMZRoYy/com2us-is-going-full-speed-on-crypto-gaming-kyu-lee</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pYMZRoYy/com2us-is-going-full-speed-on-crypto-gaming-kyu-lee"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kyu Lee is the President of game studio Com2uS USA. In an interview, he shares the studio's approach to Web3 and crypto gaming with Decrypt GG's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Discord Game with AI and Blockchain: 'Alchemy: Battle for Ankhos' Creative Lead Alex Finden]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mF18GHGo/building-a-discord-game-with-ai-and-blockchain-alchemy-battle-for-ankhos-creative-lead-alex-finden</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mF18GHGo/building-a-discord-game-with-ai-and-blockchain-alchemy-battle-for-ankhos-creative-lead-alex-finden"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T21:55:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Jason Nelson interviews Alchemy: Battle for Ankhos Creative Director Alex Finden at the Solana PlayGG event in San Diego, California.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Big Respect Between Ethereum and Cosmos Developer Communities': dYdX Foundation CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/XU5MbCGE/big-respect-between-ethereum-and-cosmos-developer-communities-dydx-foundation-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/XU5MbCGE/big-respect-between-ethereum-and-cosmos-developer-communities-dydx-foundation-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T13:24:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CEO of the dYdX Foundation Charles d'Haussy unpacks the decision behind moving one of the largest decentralized exchange protocol's over to its very own chain built on Cosmos. A key driver, he told Decrypt at this year's EthCC event, was that instead of launching on a rollup or another layer-1, launching a fully customized chain will allow dYdX to fine tune the network for its product's needs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Staking Solution Lido 'Had Perfect Product Market Fit' at Launch, Says DAO's Biz Dev Contributor]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/fUHhelhV/ethereum-staking-solution-lido-had-perfect-product-market-fit-at-launch-says-daos-biz-dev-contributor</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/fUHhelhV/ethereum-staking-solution-lido-had-perfect-product-market-fit-at-launch-says-daos-biz-dev-contributor"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T08:43:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marin Tvrdić, a business development contributor to the Lido DAO, sat down with Decrypt during this year's EthCC to break down how the liquid staking protocol has managed such a massive lead, how it plans to keep that lead, and the protocol's new dual-governance tokenomics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's Going to Stop All the DeFi Hacks? 'Standards,' Says OpenZepplin Security Architect]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/aYNuFdAi/whats-going-to-stop-all-the-defi-hacks-standards-says-openzepplin-security-architect</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/aYNuFdAi/whats-going-to-stop-all-the-defi-hacks-standards-says-openzepplin-security-architect"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T08:04:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenZeppelin's security solutions architect Michael Lewellen sat down with Decrypt to discuss how the industry can become a little safer for users at this year's EthCC Paris. The key? Introducing security standards across the industry so folks know what an audit actually means and where risks lie, be it bad faith actors or poor implementation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Ev.io' Game Review: Earn Solana While Blasting Enemies]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/2ZmkuhL2/evio-game-review-earn-solana-while-blasting-enemies</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/2ZmkuhL2/evio-game-review-earn-solana-while-blasting-enemies"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T22:21:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ev.io is a web-based first-person shooter that's free to play, but lets NFT holders earn in-game currency that can be redeemed for Solana (SOL). Decrypt contributor Ryan Gladwin shares his review of the fun throwback to Quake-style blasting, albeit with a modern crypto twist.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Moving Fast and Breaking Things Isn't the Web3 Ethos': MetaMask Product Lead]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/l1EbLgl3/moving-fast-and-breaking-things-isnt-the-web3-ethos-metamask-product-lead</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/l1EbLgl3/moving-fast-and-breaking-things-isnt-the-web3-ethos-metamask-product-lead"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T15:45:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Account abstraction this, smart wallets that. Discussions at EthCC Paris about improving user experience have pointed at industry leader MetaMask as an example of what not to do. But that may soon change, with a host of updates and optimizations coming to crypto's number one wallet, said its product lead Alex Jupiter. It still may take some time, though, before these changes take effect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling Smart Wallets on Starknet 'Was The Winning Combination', Says Argent Co-Founder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/gnBsxw4D/scaling-smart-wallets-on-starknet-was-the-winning-combination-says-argent-co-founder</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/gnBsxw4D/scaling-smart-wallets-on-starknet-was-the-winning-combination-says-argent-co-founder"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T07:35:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Argent co-founder Julien Niset told Decrypt at EthCC Paris that he wants to make crypto wallets disappear. Or at least how they're currently conceived. From clunky seed phrases to a stiff user experience, Argent hopes to make using crypto a little less intimidating and a whole lot more fun.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Mighty Action Heroes' Open Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/litL6kKs/inside-mighty-action-heroes-open-beta</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/litL6kKs/inside-mighty-action-heroes-open-beta"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T18:23:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mighty Action Heroes is the flagship blockchain title from Mighty Bear Games. But is the browser-based battle royale shooter worth checking out? Decrypt's Kate Irwin offers her thoughts and a first look at the upcoming game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dr. Disrespect's 'Deadrop': Early Access Gameplay From Snapshot VI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/8l21EHoa/dr-disrespects-deadrop-early-access-gameplay-from-snapshot-vi</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/8l21EHoa/dr-disrespects-deadrop-early-access-gameplay-from-snapshot-vi"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T18:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin playtests Dr. Disrespect and Midnight Society's first-person shooter Deadrop and shares the latest game updates, as well as her opinions on the game in development. Currently, Deadrop offers Polygon Founders Pass NFTs with no other crypto plans revealed just yet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['More and More' Game Publishers Will Embrace NFTs: Mythical Games CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/wBWogSkl/more-and-more-game-publishers-will-embrace-nfts-mythical-games-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/wBWogSkl/more-and-more-game-publishers-will-embrace-nfts-mythical-games-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T22:28:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the wake of EA Sports and Fortnite creator Epic Games embracing Nike's NFT platform, Mythical Games CEO John Linden tells Decrypt's Andrew Hayward how quickly he expects to see more major traditional game publishers enter the blockchain space and how quickly the industry will scale.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gran Saga Unlimited Early Access: Inside the Anime MMORPG on Aptos]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JeFWMVwo/gran-saga-unlimited-early-access-inside-the-anime-mmorpg-on-aptos</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JeFWMVwo/gran-saga-unlimited-early-access-inside-the-anime-mmorpg-on-aptos"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T21:46:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin plays Gran Saga: Unlimited's second community playtest, reports her findings, and offers her opinion and insights on the upcoming game, which will offer optional Aptos NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[100 Thieves' Moe Says Blockchain Games Will 'Eventually' Be Accepted by Livestreamers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/xHhh62ID/100-thieves-moe-says-blockchain-games-will-eventually-be-accepted-by-livestreamers</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/xHhh62ID/100-thieves-moe-says-blockchain-games-will-eventually-be-accepted-by-livestreamers"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T16:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[100 Thieves content creator and gamer Moe also goes by "Yassuo" online after his favorite League of Legends character. Decrypt's Kate Irwin asks him about 100 Thieves' future crypto plans and whether Moe thinks creators like xQc and Pokimane might ever come around to blockchain games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>