<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-01-16T08:19:45.779Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-01-16T08:19:45.779Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Giant Bitcoin Exchange Continues to Improve Its Domain! Received a License from Dubai!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19178353/Giant-Bitcoin-Exchange-Continues-to-Improve-Its-Domain-Received-a-License-from-Dubai</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19178353/Giant-Bitcoin-Exchange-Continues-to-Improve-Its-Domain-Received-a-License-from-Dubai"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T08:08:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The giant cryptocurrency exchange has successfully obtained a license from the Dubai Virtual Assets Regulatory Authority (VARA). Continue Reading: Giant Bitcoin Exchange Continues to Improve Its Domain! Received a License from Dubai!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Stalls At Under 43K: Bull Run Hits Pause Button Until Next Halving]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fd9ed62b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-stalls-at-under-43k-bull-run-hits-pause/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T08:07:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the aftermath of the groundbreaking approval of Bitcoin ETFs, the cryptocurrency landscape is undergoing a period of introspection, with Bitcoin finding stability in the vicinity of $42,000. The initial euphoria that accompanied the ETF approvals has subsided, prompting a contemplative phase marked by strategic maneuvers and intricate market dynamics.
 
Blockchain analytics firm Santiment has provided insights into the pre-ETF climate, uncovering a fascinating dance among Bitcoin’s major players. It discovered large wallets engaging in a shuffle of older coins at an accelerated pace.
 
Deciphering Bitcoin’s Motives
 
This strategic reshuffling caused the average age of these holdings to plummet, leaving analysts to decipher the motives behind such maneuvers. Some interpret it as a tacti…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celsius CEO Requests to Drop Two Charges Linked to Fraud and Manipulation]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19178340/Celsius-CEO-Requests-to-Drop-Two-Charges-Linked-to-Fraud-and-Manipulation</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19178340/Celsius-CEO-Requests-to-Drop-Two-Charges-Linked-to-Fraud-and-Manipulation"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T08:05:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinspeaker Celsius CEO Requests to Drop Two Charges Linked to Fraud and Manipulation The court filing contends that the government's handling of cryptocurrencies creates an inconsistency and contradiction between the second count of commodities fraud and the first count of securities fraud....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Trader Issues Bitcoin Alert, Says BTC Flashing Same Signal That Preceded 2016 and 2019 Corrections]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19178348/Crypto-Trader-Issues-Bitcoin-Alert-Says-BTC-Flashing-Same-Signal-That-Preceded-2016-and-2019-Corrections</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19178348/Crypto-Trader-Issues-Bitcoin-Alert-Says-BTC-Flashing-Same-Signal-That-Preceded-2016-and-2019-Corrections"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T08:04:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A closely followed crypto strategist warns that Bitcoin (BTC) is giving off the same technical reading that flashed before the crypto king’s deep corrective moves in 2016 and 2019. Analyst Jason Pizzino tells his 94,700 followers on the social media platform X that BTC respected the Gann 50%...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Egypt Wants to Have a Functioning CBDC by 2030]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fd9f8b9e</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/report-egypt-wants-to-have-a-functioning-cbdc-by-2030/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T08:01:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Egypt reportedly aims to launch a central bank digital currency by 2030 to boost the competitiveness of its national currency. According to an Egyptian economic expert, a digital currency issued by the central bank is more secure than privately issued cryptocurrencies. 
 
Enhancing Monetary Policy Efficiency
 
According to a report, Egypt plans to issue a central bank digital currency (CBDC), the e-pound, by 2030. The Central Bank of Egypt (CBE) will issue this digital currency, which is expected to boost the competitiveness of Egypt’s national currency and enhance the efficiency of monetary policy.
 
Details of the North African country’s CBDC goals are explained in a report of a study commissioned by the Egyptian Council of Ministers’ Information and Decision Support Center. Dubbed the “…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashKey Group Raises Nearly $100 Million in Series A Financing Round]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19178333/HashKey-Group-Raises-Nearly-100-Million-in-Series-A-Financing-Round</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19178333/HashKey-Group-Raises-Nearly-100-Million-in-Series-A-Financing-Round"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T08:01:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashKey Group, a prominent digital asset financial services group in Asia, has successfully concluded a Series A financing round that garnered nearly $100 million. This fundraising round brings the pre-money valuation of HashKey to over $1.2 billion. The Series A financing round saw active...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance’s Review of 2023 and Outlook for 2024: Bitcoin Narratives, AI Integration, RWAs, and Institutional Adoption of Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19178342/Binances-Review-of-2023-and-Outlook-for-2024-Bitcoin-Narratives-AI-Integration-RWAs-and-Institutional-Adoption-of-Crypto</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19178342/Binances-Review-of-2023-and-Outlook-for-2024-Bitcoin-Narratives-AI-Integration-RWAs-and-Institutional-Adoption-of-Crypto"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T08:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In their comprehensive report titled “Full-Year 2023 & Themes for 2024,” Binance provided an in-depth analysis of the cryptocurrency market’s performance in 2023 and its potential trajectory in 2024. Bitcoin Narratives at the Forefront Binance notes that Bitcoin remained a central focus...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pro-crypto Republican candidate Vivek Ramaswamy suspends presidential campaign]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19178317/Pro-crypto-Republican-candidate-Vivek-Ramaswamy-suspends-presidential-campaign</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19178317/Pro-crypto-Republican-candidate-Vivek-Ramaswamy-suspends-presidential-campaign"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T07:56:51.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OKX obtains VASP license in Dubai to operate crypto exchange services]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19178326/OKX-obtains-VASP-license-in-Dubai-to-operate-crypto-exchange-services</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19178326/OKX-obtains-VASP-license-in-Dubai-to-operate-crypto-exchange-services"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T07:51:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto exchange OKX said that its local unit will offer spot trading pairs once the VASP license becomes operational.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arthur Hayes Believes Bitcoin ETFs Could Bring in Billions From TradFi]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fd997894</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/01/16/arthur-hayes-believes-bitcoin-etfs-could-bring-in-billions-from-tradfi/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T07:46:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETFs could open up a line of trading avenues centered around arbitrage, options and financing, Hayes said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Stalls At Under 43K: Bull Run Hits Pause Button Until Next Halving]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19178277/Bitcoin-Stalls-At-Under-43K-Bull-Run-Hits-Pause-Button-Until-Next-Halving</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19178277/Bitcoin-Stalls-At-Under-43K-Bull-Run-Hits-Pause-Button-Until-Next-Halving"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T07:38:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the aftermath of the groundbreaking approval of Bitcoin ETFs, the cryptocurrency landscape is undergoing a period of introspection, with Bitcoin finding stability in the vicinity of $42,000. The initial euphoria that accompanied the ETF approvals has subsided, prompting a contemplative phase...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Partners With Gulf Innova to Launch Binance Thailand]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19178285/Binance-Partners-With-Gulf-Innova-to-Launch-Binance-Thailand</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19178285/Binance-Partners-With-Gulf-Innova-to-Launch-Binance-Thailand"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T07:34:49.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin's 'Sell The Fact' Pullback Came From Binance, OKX: Kaiko]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fd9b0e10</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/01/16/bitcoins-sell-the-fact-pullback-came-from-binance-okx-kaiko/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T07:33:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cumulative volume delta (CVD) indicator show traders from Binance have led the so-called "sell-the-fact" pullback in bitcoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arthur Hayes Believes Bitcoin ETFs Could Bring in Billions From TradFi]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19178302/Arthur-Hayes-Believes-Bitcoin-ETFs-Could-Bring-in-Billions-From-TradFi</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19178302/Arthur-Hayes-Believes-Bitcoin-ETFs-Could-Bring-in-Billions-From-TradFi"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T07:31:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETFs could open up a line of trading avenues centered around arbitrage, options and financing, Hayes said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin: Exchange volume rises despite price drop – Why?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19178276/Bitcoin-Exchange-volume-rises-despite-price-drop-Why</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19178276/Bitcoin-Exchange-volume-rises-despite-price-drop-Why"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T07:30:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin has seen surging exchange volumes over the last 183 days.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance launches in Thailand, challenges dominant local exchange Bitkub]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19178253/Binance-launches-in-Thailand-challenges-dominant-local-exchange-Bitkub</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19178253/Binance-launches-in-Thailand-challenges-dominant-local-exchange-Bitkub"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T07:25:56.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OKX Cements Middle East Presence: Secures Crypto License in Dubai]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fd84b0b1</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/okx-cements-middle-east-presence-secures-crypto-license-in-dubai/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T07:19:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Dubai-based subsidiary of crypto exchange OKX, named OKX Middle East Fintech FZE, announced today (Tuesday) that it has received a Virtual Asset Service Provider (VASP) license from the Dubai Virtual Assets Regulatory Authority (VARA), enabling the company to offer virtual asset exchange services.
OKX Enters Middle East
The newly gained license would allow the global crypto exchange to offer spot services and spot pairs to institutional and qualified retail customers in the Middle East. However, the newly gained license will remain non-operational as the company needs to “fully satisfy all remaining conditions and select localization requirements,” which is expected to be completed in the coming weeks.
The operational license came months after the Dubai subsidiary of OKX was granted a …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arnab Shome</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Dogecoin Killer' Shiba Inu Sees 1600% Rise In Burn Rate — 88M Tokens Sent To Dead Wallet In A Single Day]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19178278/Dogecoin-Killer-Shiba-Inu-Sees-1600-Rise-In-Burn-Rate-88M-Tokens-Sent-To-Dead-Wallet-In-A-Single-Day</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19178278/Dogecoin-Killer-Shiba-Inu-Sees-1600-Rise-In-Burn-Rate-88M-Tokens-Sent-To-Dead-Wallet-In-A-Single-Day"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T07:17:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Self-proclaimed ‘Dogecoin (CRYPTO: DOGE) killer' Shiba Inu (CRYPTO: SHIB), has witnessed a surge in token burn activity with an increase exceeding 1600% within a 24-hour window. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto-Forward US Presidential Hopeful Vivek Ramaswamy Bows Out of Election Race]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19178303/Crypto-Forward-US-Presidential-Hopeful-Vivek-Ramaswamy-Bows-Out-of-Election-Race</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19178303/Crypto-Forward-US-Presidential-Hopeful-Vivek-Ramaswamy-Bows-Out-of-Election-Race"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T07:15:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shaking the political and crypto worlds alike, Vivek Ramaswamy, the entrepreneur-turned-presidential hopeful, announced his exit from the 2024 election race. Ramaswamy, garnering only 8% of the GOP caucus vote in Iowa, declared his endorsement for former President Donald Trump, acknowledging the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin's 'Sell The Fact' Pullback Came From Binance, OKX: Kaiko]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19178251/Bitcoins-Sell-The-Fact-Pullback-Came-From-Binance-OKX-Kaiko</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19178251/Bitcoins-Sell-The-Fact-Pullback-Came-From-Binance-OKX-Kaiko"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T07:12:05.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shark Tank Star Kevin O’Leary Critiques Spot Bitcoin ETFs for High Fees, Foresees Market Dominance by Major Players]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19178238/Shark-Tank-Star-Kevin-OLeary-Critiques-Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-for-High-Fees-Foresees-Market-Dominance-by-Major-Players</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19178238/Shark-Tank-Star-Kevin-OLeary-Critiques-Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-for-High-Fees-Foresees-Market-Dominance-by-Major-Players"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T07:10:26.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ukrainian Police Collaborate With Europol to Apprehend Alleged Cryptojacking Mastermind]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fd85d3ea</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ukrainian-police-collaborate-with-europol-to-apprehend-alleged-cryptojacking-mastermind/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T07:09:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ukrainian police, in collaboration with Europol, recently apprehended the alleged mastermind behind a cryptojacking scheme. According to a statement released by Europol, the arrest underscores why the private sector should collaborate with law enforcement.
 
Law Enforcement and Private Sector Collaboration
 
The Ukrainian police recently arrested a 29-year-old man accused of masterminding a complex cryptojacking scheme. The unnamed man, who was apprehended in Mykolaiv, is believed to have mined cryptocurrencies worth over $2 million using illegally accessed cloud resources.
 
According to a statement released via European Police (Europol), the alleged cryptojacker’s arrest followed months of collaboration between Ukrainian law enforcement, Europol and an unidentified cloud services provider. The statement said the arrest underscores why the private sector should collaborate with law enforcement.
 
Explaining how the probe, which saw law enforcement agents comb three properties associated with the cryptojacker, unfolded, Europol said:
 
“A cloud provider approached Europol back in January 2023 with information regarding compromised cloud user accounts of theirs. Europol shared this information with the Ukrainian authorities, who subsequently opened an investigation.”
 
On the day of the arrest, the European Cybercrime Centre (EC3) of the law enforcement agency set up a command post to support the National Police of Ukraine.
 
 
Meanwhile, in the statement, Europol shared some anti-cryptojacking tips that cloud service providers can use to stop criminals from illegally accessing cloud computing infrastructure. One way cloud providers can do this is by having strong access controls in place.
 
Cloud service providers can also block cryptojackers by regularly monitoring cloud environments for suspicious activities and keeping cloud resources updated, the statement added.
 
What are your thoughts on this story? Let us know what you think in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Goldman Sachs Economists Predicted When and How Many Times the Fed Will Cut Interest Rates in 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19178226/Goldman-Sachs-Economists-Predicted-When-and-How-Many-Times-the-Fed-Will-Cut-Interest-Rates-in-2024</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19178226/Goldman-Sachs-Economists-Predicted-When-and-How-Many-Times-the-Fed-Will-Cut-Interest-Rates-in-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T07:06:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Analysts from Goldman Sachs made some predictions about when the FED will start reducing interest rates. Continue Reading: Goldman Sachs Economists Predicted When and How Many Times the Fed Will Cut Interest Rates in 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple CTO Clarifies: 25 Billion XRP ‘Transaction’ Was Not A Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fd865d4e</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ripple-cto-clarifies-25-billion-xrp-transaction/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T07:05:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Schwartz, Chief Technology Officer (CTO) of Ripple, has commented on the alleged “transaction” of 25.6 billion (almost 15 billion US dollars) XRP on January 14. This amount represented almost half of the total circulating supply of XRP, which stands at approximately 54.26 billion. The supposed transaction was reported by the highly-regarded blockchain tracking service Whale Alert to have originated from an unknown wallet, destined for the crypto exchange Bitfinex.
 
Subsequent investigations, however, quickly debunked the initial concerns. Paolo Ardoino, the Chief Technology Officer (CTO) at Bitfinex, clarified that the event was not a transaction but an attempted exploit of the “Partial Payments” feature in the XRP Ledger. This revelation came as a relief to many in the crypto commu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Daily Roundup, 16 Jan: Are Altcoins Poised to Outshine Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19178225/Crypto-Daily-Roundup-16-Jan-Are-Altcoins-Poised-to-Outshine-Bitcoin</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19178225/Crypto-Daily-Roundup-16-Jan-Are-Altcoins-Poised-to-Outshine-Bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T07:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Klatyn and LINE-backed Finschia propose blockchain merger]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19178221/Klatyn-and-LINE-backed-Finschia-propose-blockchain-merger</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19178221/Klatyn-and-LINE-backed-Finschia-propose-blockchain-merger"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T07:01:20.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple CTO Clarifies: 25 Billion XRP ‘Transaction’ Was Not A Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19178216/Ripple-CTO-Clarifies-25-Billion-XRP-Transaction-Was-Not-A-Vulnerability</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19178216/Ripple-CTO-Clarifies-25-Billion-XRP-Transaction-Was-Not-A-Vulnerability"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T07:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Thailand Crypto Exchange Open for Trading]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fd80c6d1</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2024/01/16/binance-thailand-crypto-exchange-open-for-trading/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T06:44:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto exchange is a joint venture between Binance and Thailand's Gulf Innova.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OKX’s Middle East Business Wins Dubai Virtual Assets License]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fd8c5c11</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2024/01/16/okxs-middle-east-business-wins-dubai-virtual-assets-license/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T06:12:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OKX Middle East Fintech FZE will be offering local currency trading pairs such as AED/BTC, AED/ETH, and more in the coming weeks, said OKX General Manager for MENA Region Rifad Mahasneh.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vivek Ramaswamy, Crypto-Friendly U.S. Presidential Candidate, Suspends Campaign]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fd8c5c07</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/01/16/vivek-ramaswamy-crypto-friendly-us-presidential-candidate-suspends-campaign/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T06:12:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The former biotech executive was the only Republican contender to have a crypto plan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashKey Becomes Crypto Unicorn After Closing $100M Raise]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fd880fd5</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2024/01/16/hashkey-becomes-crypto-unicorn-after-closing-100m-raise/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T05:38:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Operator of licensed Hong Kong exchange says raise will promote compliant, innovative global growth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple’s XRP Ousted From Hong Kong Virtual Asset Consortium’s Top Crypto Index]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fd882033</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ripples-xrp-ousted-from-hong-kong-virtual-asset-consortiums-top-crypto-index/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T05:38:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Hong Kong strengthens its crypto regulatory framework and embraces ETFs, the Hong Kong Virtual Asset Consortium (HKVAC) has updated its crypto indexes, showing a preference for tokens with market performance and growing industry partnerships.
 
Ripple’s XRP Loses Ground in HVAC’s Crypto Index Revamp
 
The Hong Kong Virtual Asset Consortium has revised its key crypto indexes, notably excluding Ripple’s XRP. HKVAC, a non-profit organization that rates digital asset trading platforms and compiles crypto market indexes, announced these revisions in a recent statement. The adjustments include the top five, top 10, and overall crypto indexes.
 
December 2023 saw a notable shift in the crypto market, with Solana (SOL) surpassing XRP in market capitalization, becoming the fourth-largest cryptoc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Sencil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple and Google Remove Several Major Crypto Exchanges From App Stores in India Following Regulatory Crackdown]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fd7114f7</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/apple-and-google-remove-several-major-crypto-exchanges-from-app-stores-in-india-following-regulatory-crackdown/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T04:07:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple and Google have removed several major crypto exchanges from their app stores in India after the Indian Financial Intelligence Unit flagged nine crypto service providers as operating illegally in the country. Various telecom networks and internet service providers in India are also blocking the websites of affected crypto exchanges.
 
India Continues Crackdown on Uncompliant Crypto Platforms
 
Tech giants Google and Apple have taken action against several major crypto exchange apps in India following the crackdown on offshore crypto exchanges by Financial Intelligence Unit India (FIU IND).
 
On Saturday, Google removed major crypto exchanges like Binance and Kraken from Google Play Store in India while Apple pulled crypto exchange apps from its App Store a few days earlier. In additio…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Receives Blunt Message From IMF Managing Director: ‘It’s Not Money’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fd714131</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-receives-blunt-message-from-imf/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T04:05:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amid the highly-anticipated approval of Bitcoin spot exchange-traded funds (ETFs), which has sparked excitement within the crypto industry and opened doors for institutional investments, the International Monetary Fund (IMF) managing director, Kristalina Georgieva, has expressed critical views towards the nascent sector.
 
Are Crypto Assets Not Equivalent To Money?
 
In a recent interview with Yahoo Finance, Georgieva emphasized the distinction between money and crypto assets when discussing cryptocurrencies. 
 
According to Georgieva, crypto should be regarded as an asset class rather than a form of currency. She highlighted the alleged varying levels of security and risk associated with different cryptocurrencies, depending on whether assets back them. Georgieva likened crypto to a money…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Giant At Crossroads: Coinbase’s High Stakes Game In The Spot Bitcoin ETF Market]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fd7eda5c</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/coinbases-high-stakes-game-spot-bitcoin-etf-market/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T03:05:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase, a leading crypto asset exchange, is at a pivotal juncture with the recent advent of US spot Bitcoin Exchange-Traded Funds (ETFs). While this development signals a mainstream breakthrough for crypto, it also places Coinbase in a spotlight fraught with potential rewards and significant risks.
 
The approval and commencement of the first spot exchange-traded funds investing directly in Bitcoin by the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) have marked a significant moment in BTC’s journey toward mainstream acceptance.
 
 
This move has put Coinbase at the ‘center of action,’ as many spot ETF issuers, including industry giants like BlackRock and Ark Invest, rely on the exchange for essential services such as custodianship, trading, and lending.
 
 
The Dual-Edged Sword Of Central…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Chair Gary Gensler Sees Irony in Spot Bitcoin ETF Approval — ‘This Was About Centralization’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fd7938ef</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/sec-chair-gary-gensler-sees-irony-in-spot-bitcoin-etf-approval-this-was-about-centralization/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T02:39:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Chair Gary Gensler sees irony in the approval of spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs). “This was about centralization and traditional means of finance,” said Gensler, warning: “Investors should be aware that this underlying asset is a highly speculative, volatile asset, and amongst its use cases is really for illicit activity, money laundering, sanctions, ransomware, and the like.”
 
SEC Chair on Spot Bitcoin ETF Approval and Centralization
 
The chairman of the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), Gary Gensler, discussed the irony of spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) in an interview with CNBC Friday. The securities regulator approved 11 spot bitcoin ETFs last week.
 
“There’s an irony in the midst of that. Satoshi Nakamo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Mobile to Sell Second Crypto Smartphone: Source]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fd793fa3</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2024/01/16/solana-mobile-to-sell-second-crypto-smartphone-source/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T02:39:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The successor to Saga will have new hardware and a cheaper price point, according to a person familiar with the plans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Replacing Ethereum As The Home Of Meme Coins?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fd644d94</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/solana-replacing-ethereum-as-the-home-of-meme-coins/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T02:07:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is a growing sentiment that minting and trading meme coins on Ethereum is no “longer viable” since Solana is emerging as a potential alternative, looking at recent on-chain activity. This shift in dynamics is evident in the recent success of Solana-based meme coins like BONK, which has captured significant attention within the cryptocurrency community.
 
Solana Dominating Meme Coin Activities
 
Taking X on January 15, a user, Moon, highlighted this development, backing Solana as the “ultimate retail chain” for meme coins. The crypto trader added that trading meme coins in Ethereum doesn’t make “sense.” 
 
Moon alludes to Ethereum’s high gas fees and slower processing speeds through these remarks. Considering the nature of meme coins, these factors make it impractical for their tradin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dalmas Ngetich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Misinformation Could Rock the 2024 Elections—Here's How OpenAI Plans to Fight It]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212946</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212946/ai-misinformation-could-rock-2024-elections-how-openai-plans-fight"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T01:31:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI has intensified its efforts to prevent AI misuse, including deepfakes, to protect democratic processes amid the upcoming elections.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IMF Chief Sees Crypto as Asset Class — Says Bitcoin Won’t Dethrone US Dollar as Dominant Currency]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fd61a519</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/imf-chief-sees-crypto-as-asset-class-says-bitcoin-wont-dethrone-us-dollar-as-dominant-currency/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T01:06:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[International Monetary Fund (IMF) chief Kristalina Georgieva sees crypto as an asset class, not money. She dismissed concerns of bitcoin potentially displacing the U.S. dollar as the world’s dominant currency, citing the size of the U.S. economy and the depth and sophistication of its capital markets as key factors.
 
IMF Chief on Crypto and US Dollar Dominance
 
The managing director of the International Monetary Fund (IMF), Kristalina Georgieva, dismissed crypto as money and explained why she didn’t see bitcoin as a threat to the U.S. dollar’s dominance in an interview with Yahoo Finance Live last week. Georgieva said:
 

Our view is that we have to differentiate between money and assets. When we talk about crypto, we are actually talking about an asset class.
 
“It could be backed up an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Predicts 7 Influential Events Shaping Bitcoin, Ethereum, Ripple, And Cardano In 2024]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fd61c922</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/binance-predicts-7-influential-events-bitcoin/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T01:05:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent research report published by Binance, the world’s largest cryptocurrency exchange by trading volume, several key events were identified that are expected to influence the trajectory of the crypto market in 2024 significantly. 
 
Paving The Way For Institutional Inflows
 
One of the most significant events is the approval of spot Bitcoin Exchange-Traded Funds (ETFs) by the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), which took place on January 10th. 
 
According to the report, the market expects that the approval of these index funds can open the floodgates of interest by institutional investors, potentially leading to substantial inflows of institutional capital into Bitcoin over the long term. 
 
According to the exchange, this development is considered one of the most signif…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Rise and Fall of GameStop's NFT Marketplace]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212944</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212944/rise-fall-gamestop-nft-marketplace"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T00:12:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What happened to GameStop’s blockchain plans? Here’s a look back into how the gaming retailer got into NFTs—and then bailed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Assassin's Creed Maker Ubisoft Backs Yet Another Crypto Gaming Network]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212928</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212928/assassins-creed-maker-ubisoft-backs-yet-another-crypto-gaming-network"/>
        <updated>2024-01-15T22:15:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Major video game publisher Ubisoft is among Wemix's 40 "node council partners" that will validate its blockchain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mysterious Ordinals Inscription Teases 'Cursed' Bitcoin Art Project]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212908</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212908/mysterious-ordinals-inscription-teases-cursed-bitcoin-art-project"/>
        <updated>2024-01-15T21:47:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptic '10,000 sats' message on Ordinal 55,365,041 baffles Ordinals experts, igniting speculation in the Bitcoin community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Saylor Sounds Alarm on Deepfake Bitcoin Scams]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212892</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212892/microstrategy-michael-saylor-deepfake-bitcoin-scams"/>
        <updated>2024-01-15T20:09:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No, Michael Saylor won’t be sending you some Bitcoin, despite what you think he might have said on YouTube.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jupiter Finally Sets a Date for JUP Airdrop, Teases Meme Coin Drop on Solana]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212884</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212884/jupiter-finally-sets-date-jup-airdrop-teases-meme-coin-drop-solana"/>
        <updated>2024-01-15T19:51:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nearly a million Solana DeFi users will be able to claim JUP later this month in the airdrop, with Jupiter teasing a meme coin launch too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GTA 6 Preview: Everything You Need to Know About the New Grand Theft Auto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154049</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154049/grand-theft-auto-6-release-date-rumors-leaks-news"/>
        <updated>2024-01-15T19:15:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATE: T-Pain says he's working on GTA 6—and that Rockstar asked him to stay away from a particular game server in the meantime.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Steal Over $4 Million in Fake Airdrops and Other Scams on Solana]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212875</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212875/hackers-steal-over-4-million-fake-airdrops-other-scams-solana"/>
        <updated>2024-01-15T18:12:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The attacks have duped thousands of Solana users by employing a variety of tactics, swiping millions of dollars worth of tokens like BONK.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Biggest Games Coming Out in 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210052</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210052/biggest-games-coming-out-nintendo-playstation-xbox-pc"/>
        <updated>2024-01-15T17:14:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATED: From Final Fantasy VII Rebirth to Star Wars Outlaws and plenty in between, these are our most anticipated games of 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xai Gaming Token Surges 35% as Airdrop Value Hits $140 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212866</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212866/xai-gaming-token-surges-35-as-airdrop-value-hits-140-million"/>
        <updated>2024-01-15T16:53:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arbitrum’s XAI token tied to a layer-3 gaming network spiked to a new all-time high price Monday, less than a week after its airdrop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CES 2024: Mercedes-Benz Previews In-Car NFT Gallery, 'Emotional' AI Assistant]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212831</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212831/ces-2024-mercedes-benz-previews-in-car-nft-gallery-emotional-ai-assistant"/>
        <updated>2024-01-15T13:54:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The German automaker's updated MBUX Virtual Assistant will leverage an LLM to interact with drivers using one of four "emotional profiles."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Dips Under $42,000 as Market Sentiment Turns Neutral Post-ETF]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212828</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212828/bitcoin-dips-under-42000-as-market-sentiment-turns-neutral-post-etf"/>
        <updated>2024-01-15T11:21:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin briefly dropped below $42,000 Monday morning, as the Crypto Fear & Greed Index turned neutral for the first time since November 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week on Crypto Twitter: The ETF Circus Comes to Town]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212824</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212824/this-week-on-crypto-twitter-bitcoin-etf-circus"/>
        <updated>2024-01-14T17:11:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Multiple plot twists upended a week that was already guaranteed to be high octane.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Art Blocks Founder Erick Calderon Approached Printing 'Chromie Squiggle']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212814</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212814/how-art-blocks-founder-erick-calderon-approached-printing-chromie-squiggle"/>
        <updated>2024-01-14T15:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Erick Calderon discussed his premium print run of Chromie Squiggle #8107 at Rug Radio’s R Haus event at Art Basel Miami 2023. Watch the interview now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Bitcoin Flashes and Fades as ETFs Launch—But Ethereum Soars]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212773</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212773/this-week-coins-bitcoin-fanaticism-flashes-fades-etfs-launch-ethereum-soars"/>
        <updated>2024-01-13T21:38:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin's big week was a rollercoaster. Ethereum closed up. And the rest of the top five were largely flat for the past seven days.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Kawailani Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Will Make Workers More Effective But Adapting to Its Rapid Spread Is ‘Scary’: Sam Altman]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212793</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212793/sam-altman-openai-bill-gates-microsoft"/>
        <updated>2024-01-13T20:35:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI CEO Sam Altman sat down with Bill Gates to explore the positive potential and threats of artificial intelligence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Play Super Nintendo and Other Classic Games on Bitcoin—Here’s How]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212729</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212729/you-can-play-super-nintendo-classic-games-bitcoin-heres-how"/>
        <updated>2024-01-13T16:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks to Ordinals, you can find working video games inscribed on the Bitcoin blockchain. Here’s how to play them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nike Will 'Go Way Deeper' Into Video Game Fashion Amid NFT Push]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212723</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212723/nike-will-go-way-deeper-video-game-fashion-amid-nft-push"/>
        <updated>2024-01-13T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nike says it will continue to expand into video game wearables through its .Swoosh platform, but it's unclear if there will be more NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Chair Gary Gensler Recaps Takeover of Agency's Twitter Account]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212765</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212765/sec-chair-gary-gensler-addresses-cyberattack-on-agencys-twitter-account"/>
        <updated>2024-01-13T00:49:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The agency head gave an update on the investigation into a cyberattack that falsely announced Bitcoin ETF approvals earlier this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop Bails on Crypto Gaming, Killing NFT Marketplace]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212761</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212761/gamestop-bails-on-crypto-gaming-killing-nft-marketplace"/>
        <updated>2024-01-13T00:21:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The news comes four months after the storied video game retailer axed its NFT wallet, with GameStop set to exit the space entirely.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Is ’Bigger Than Any Government’: BlackRock CEO Larry Fink]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212727</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212727/bitcoin-bigger-than-any-government-blackrock-ceo-larry-fink"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T23:16:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a Fox Business interview, the former Bitcoin skeptic defended the cryptocurrency as a shield against government manipulation and economic instability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Super Mario AI Hologram Is Creeping People Out in Vegas]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212708</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212708/super-mario-ai-hologram-creeping-people-out-vegas"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T21:21:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The unauthorized AI hologram of gaming icon Super Mario becomes a viral sensation at CES, dubbed an "abomination" by one visitor.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Game Over: More Than 30% of Crypto Games Have Been Discontinued]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212689</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212689/game-over-more-than-30-percent-crypto-games-discontinued"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T19:39:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New research documents a slew of inactive crypto and NFT games that have been abandoned or otherwise inactive for months.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gary Gensler Remains Cagey on Ethereum, Punts on Potential ETF]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212681</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212681/gary-gensler-remains-cagey-ethereum-punts-potential-etf"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T18:45:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On a CNBC segment this morning, the SEC chair also remained vague about Ethereum's status as a security following Bitcoin ETF approvals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Game 'Nyan Heroes' Hits Epic Store Ahead of Airdrop]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212680</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212680/solana-game-nyan-heroes-hits-epic-store-ahead-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T18:17:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nyan Heroes pairs cats and crypto in a Fortnite-like battle royale shooter on Solana, with big moves apparently ahead in 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Plunges on Day Two of ETF Mania as Liquidations Soar]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212671</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212671/bitcoin-plunges-day-two-etf-mania-liquidations-soar"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T17:16:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bitcoin ETF buzz calmed Friday as the leading cryptocurrency dipped down near $43,000. Are traders selling the news after the frenzy?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Genesis Pays $8 Million and Forfeits BitLicense to Settle New York Charges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212656</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212656/genesis-pays-8-million-and-forfeits-bitlicense-to-settle-new-york-charges"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T16:27:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Genesis Trading has had its BitLicense since 2018.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Rallies as BlackRock Boss Eyes ETH ETF After Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212662</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212662/ethereum-rallies-blackrock-boss-eyes-eth-etf-after-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T16:17:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Analysts think an ETH ETF is now a slam dunk, sending Ethereum pumping 18% in the last week amid the Bitcoin ETF rollout in the U.S.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinShares Acquires Valkyrie Funds—And the BRRR Bitcoin ETF With It]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212627</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212627/coinshares-acquires-valkyrie-funds-brrr-bitcoin-etf"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T15:38:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The acquisition includes the Valkyrie Bitcoin Fund, which trades under the BRRR ticker on Nasdaq.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taproot Wizards Launch Quantum Cats Collection As Bitcoin Inscriptions]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212594</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212594/taproot-wizards-launch-quantum-cats-bitcoin-ordinals-collection"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T15:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 3,333-image images on the Bitcoin blockchain cost $66,000 to create.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taki Brings Play-to-Earn Mobile Games to Polygon After Merger, Acquisitions]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212607</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212607/taki-brings-play-earn-mobile-games-polygon-after-merger-acquisitions"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T13:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After launching a social app on Solana, Taki Games has merged with Unite, has a new CEO, and is launching Polygon mobile games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terra Co-Founder Do Kwon Requests SEC Trial Delay So He Can Attend]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212616</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212616/terras-do-kwon-requests-sec-trial-delay-so-he-can-attend"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T13:14:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lawyers for Kwon said that an adjournment to mid-March "would provide a realistic possibility" for him to attend.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elizabeth Warren: SEC 'Wrong on the Law' Over Bitcoin ETF Approval]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212614</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212614/elizabeth-warren-sec-wrong-on-the-law-over-bitcoin-etf-approval"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T10:48:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Senator claimed that the SEC had let crypto "burrow even deeper into our financial system," and pressed for AML rules.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generative Art Across Mediums: Artists Discuss the Evolving Space]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/GK3aN0zo/generative-art-across-mediums-artists-discuss-the-evolving-space</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/GK3aN0zo/generative-art-across-mediums-artists-discuss-the-evolving-space"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T02:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this panel discussion from Rug Radio's R Haus at Art Basel Miami 2023, Sofia Garcia, Ismail Tazi, Emily Edelman, and Aleksandra Art discuss the expanding generative art space—and why "generative" doesn't necessarily have to mean digital.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI-Backed 1X Wants to Put a Humanoid Robot to Work in Your Home]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212584</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212584/household-robots-1x-neo-eve-himanoid-biped"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T01:45:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The robotics company raised $100 million to build NEO, its second bipedal robot design that can perform domestic tasks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These Are All the Bitcoin ETFs That Are Now Trading in the US]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=62912</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/62912/high-profile-bitcoin-etf-applications"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T23:44:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spot Bitcoin ETFs are finally trading in the United States following SEC approval. Here are all the Bitcoin ETFs you can invest in today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves,Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nintendo Switch 2 Preview: Everything You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197793</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197793/nintendo-switch-2-rumors-leaks-latest-news"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T23:15:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATED: More and more signs are pointing to a release window for the Nintendo Switch 2. Here's the latest about Nintendo's next console.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Gas Hero' NFTs Top Charts—But the 'Stepn' Maker's Game Is Blocked in the US]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212500</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212500/gas-hero-nfts-top-charts-but-stepn-maker-game-blocked-us"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T22:36:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gas Hero, the latest NFT game from Find Satoshi Lab, is blocking players in 16 regions around the world, including the United States.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETFs Start With a Bang: $4.5 Billion on Day One of Trading]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212570</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212570/bitcoin-etf-4-billion-day-one-trading"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T22:19:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock stole the show, but Grayscale may have been the biggest winner. The crypto-native fund enjoyed its best day of trading ever.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The AI Coin to Rule Them All with Mike Grantis]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rkYpU8TJ/the-ai-coin-to-rule-them-all-with-mike-grantis</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rkYpU8TJ/the-ai-coin-to-rule-them-all-with-mike-grantis"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T18:46:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reza is joined by Mike Grantis from Contango Digital to discuss
- The AI coin to rule them all
- The Solana Ecosystem 
- What's next for Solana airdrops]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conversation With Snowfro: Bringing 'Chromie Squiggle' #8107 to the Physical Space]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DcrU04gG/conversation-with-snowfro-bringing-chromie-squiggle-8107-to-the-physical-space</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DcrU04gG/conversation-with-snowfro-bringing-chromie-squiggle-8107-to-the-physical-space"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Art Blocks founder and CEO and "Chromie Squiggle" project creator Erick "snowfro" Calderon spoke with Benny Redbeard Gross at Rug Radio's R Haus event at Art Basel 2023, to discuss how and why "Chromie Squiggle" NFT #8107 was given a special edition print run in collaboration with Avant Arte.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don't Underestimate Mobile Gaming: Qualcomm's Matthew Grossman]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/34Oil4Qu/dont-underestimate-mobile-gaming-qualcomms-matthew-grossman</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/34Oil4Qu/dont-underestimate-mobile-gaming-qualcomms-matthew-grossman"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Qualcomm product marketing manager Matthew Grossman tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin why mobile esports is exploding in popularity around the world—and dispels some of the misconceptions around mobile gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF: This Is the 'Calm Before the Storm', Says ETF Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/VOX04ytt/bitcoin-etf-this-is-the-calm-before-the-storm-says-etf-analyst</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/VOX04ytt/bitcoin-etf-this-is-the-calm-before-the-storm-says-etf-analyst"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T20:20:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bloomberg Senior ETF Analyst Eric Balchunas joins Farokh Sarmad, Michael Anderson, and Ovie Faruq on the FOMO Hour to share the latest intel on the looming approval for a spot Bitcoin ETF, what might happen when the very different worlds of TradFi and crypto collide, and his insights on “Genslish,” the unique and strategic language of SEC chair Gary Gensler.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Losing 1500 BTC on Mt Gox and the Problem with Women in Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/EfNuNu8a/losing-1500-btc-on-mt-gox-and-the-problem-with-women-in-web3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/EfNuNu8a/losing-1500-btc-on-mt-gox-and-the-problem-with-women-in-web3"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T19:02:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week our host is joined by Brooke Lacey! 

They discuss:  
- Making and losing generational wealth
- Trauma Bond
- Women in Web3
- The Problem with WAGMI]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ESL Faceit Group Exploring Blockchain 'Opportunistically,' Says Exec]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/yvrs4lBx/esl-faceit-group-exploring-blockchain-opportunistically-says-exec</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/yvrs4lBx/esl-faceit-group-exploring-blockchain-opportunistically-says-exec"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T02:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Braithwaite—ESL Faceit Group's VP of Game Ecosystems, Mobile, and Snapdragon Pro Series—shares the esports firm's approach to blockchain technology with GG's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bryan Johnson Explains His Quest for Immortality and Why He Started with the Penis]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tAwP55g9/bryan-johnson-explains-his-quest-for-immortality-and-why-he-started-with-the-penis</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tAwP55g9/bryan-johnson-explains-his-quest-for-immortality-and-why-he-started-with-the-penis"/>
        <updated>2023-12-24T19:38:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Billionaire biohacker Bryan Johnson shared with Decrypt's Jason Nelson why he began his longevity quest and how technology has shaped the endeavor. Johnson also discusses some of his controversial experiments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wildcard's Plans for 2024 with Founders Paul and Katy Bettner]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/TI3aFBhO/wildcards-plans-for-2024-with-founders-paul-and-katy-bettner</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/TI3aFBhO/wildcards-plans-for-2024-with-founders-paul-and-katy-bettner"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T21:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wildcard developers Paul and Katy Bettner tell Decrypt's Kate Irwin about why they see their game as a "Web3 game," not a crypto game, and share why they've stuck with their initial vision despite the challenging broader market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt and Rug Radio Merge to Create Global Web3 Publishing Company]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/VTEBYFD8/decrypt-and-rug-radio-merge-to-create-global-web3-publishing-company</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/VTEBYFD8/decrypt-and-rug-radio-merge-to-create-global-web3-publishing-company"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T17:04:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt and Rug Radio have announced their intent to merge, creating the world’s biggest decentralized publishing company. Codenamed [REDACTED], the alliance is aimed at revolutionizing tech-media, bringing together the forces of content creation and consumption.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>