<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-05-06T10:16:11.798Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-05-06T10:16:11.798Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There Are Two Separate Taxes on Cryptocurrency Transactions in Turkey! Will Rates Disappoint Investors?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19462958/There-Are-Two-Separate-Taxes-on-Cryptocurrency-Transactions-in-Turkey-Will-Rates-Disappoint-Investors</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19462958/There-Are-Two-Separate-Taxes-on-Cryptocurrency-Transactions-in-Turkey-Will-Rates-Disappoint-Investors"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T10:12:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to Habertürk's news, the Revenue Administration is preparing to impose two separate taxes on Bitcoin and cryptocurrency transactions. Continue Reading: There Are Two Separate Taxes on Cryptocurrency Transactions in Turkey! Will Rates Disappoint Investors?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Justin Sun Grabs Nearly Half Of Deposits In Liquid Staking Protocol]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74283f00de</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/justin-sun-grabs-nearly-half-of-deposits-in-staking/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T10:07:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tron founder Justin Sun has once again sent ripples through the cryptocurrency world with a hefty deposit into a liquid restaking protocol. This move puts Sun squarely in the center of a booming DeFi niche: liquid staking.
 
 
Justin Sun: A Champion For Liquid Staking?
 
Sun, known for his fondness for Ethereum-based currencies, deposited a staggering 120,000 eETH (around $376 million) into Swell L2, a relatively new player in the liquid restaking arena. This single deposit makes up a whopping 46.6% of all funds Swell L2 has ever received.
 
While some might see this as a purely financial move, Sun has recently downplayed profit motives. He positions himself as an advisor to these platforms, emphasizing the potential of liquid staking to become a global revenue stream for institutions and …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Vs. SEC Legal Saga: Expert Outlines Timeline For Settlement And Ruling]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74283f00d1</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/timeline-for-settlement-in-ripple-vs-sec-case/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T10:07:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ashley Prosper, an XRP enthusiast deeply invested in the outcome of the legal clash between Ripple and the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), shared insights on the subject, outlining the possible timeline for a settlement and final ruling of the case.
 
Potential Settlement And Final Ruling Timeline In The Ripple Case
 
According to the expert, the SEC’s final response in the remedies phase in its case between Ripple is anticipated to be released tomorrow, on May 7. Following the response, US Judge Analisa Torres is expected to make her final decision on the matter, which Ashley Prosper believes will take place between July and August, or possibly September.
 
 
While the XRP enthusiast is confident that an appeal could be filed from both parties after this, she affir…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Godspower Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Bitcoin ETFs: ‘Good’ for crypto or not? Analyst weighs in]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19462930/US-Bitcoin-ETFs-Good-for-crypto-or-not-Analyst-weighs-in</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19462930/US-Bitcoin-ETFs-Good-for-crypto-or-not-Analyst-weighs-in"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T10:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Though Bitcoin ETFs have turned institutional investors towards BTC, there's more work to be done.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Justin Sun Grabs Nearly Half Of Deposits In Liquid Staking Protocol]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19462934/Justin-Sun-Grabs-Nearly-Half-Of-Deposits-In-Liquid-Staking-Protocol</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19462934/Justin-Sun-Grabs-Nearly-Half-Of-Deposits-In-Liquid-Staking-Protocol"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T10:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tron founder Justin Sun has once again sent ripples through the cryptocurrency world with a hefty deposit into a liquid restaking protocol. This move puts Sun squarely in the center of a booming DeFi niche: liquid staking. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Owners, Beware: Impersonators Are Targeting...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Pumps 13% | Is The Rally A Trap Or Just The Beginning?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19462948/Bitcoin-Pumps-13-Is-The-Rally-A-Trap-Or-Just-The-Beginning</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19462948/Bitcoin-Pumps-13-Is-The-Rally-A-Trap-Or-Just-The-Beginning"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T10:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#bitcoin #crypto #cryptocurrencies Consider dropping a like if you enjoyed the video! 👍Check out our partner, DeGate: https://degate.com/Check out our partner, DED: https://www.dotisded.io/Sign up for the DashReport 💹➡️ http://nicholasmerten.com/dashreport/00:00 - Intro00:45 - Bitcoin Analysis |...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Vs. SEC Legal Saga: Expert Outlines Timeline For Settlement And Ruling]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19462886/Ripple-Vs-SEC-Legal-Saga-Expert-Outlines-Timeline-For-Settlement-And-Ruling</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19462886/Ripple-Vs-SEC-Legal-Saga-Expert-Outlines-Timeline-For-Settlement-And-Ruling"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ashley Prosper, an XRP enthusiast deeply invested in the outcome of the legal clash between Ripple and the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), shared insights on the subject, outlining the possible timeline for a settlement and final ruling of the case. Potential Settlement...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Peck on Digital Assets at WisdomTree (EP.526)]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19462942/Will-Peck-on-Digital-Assets-at-WisdomTree-EP526</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19462942/Will-Peck-on-Digital-Assets-at-WisdomTree-EP526"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Will Peck, Head of Digital Assets at WisdomTree re-joins the show. In this episode we discuss: WisdomTree’s journey in digital assets and the firm’s strategy in the area. Views on the launch of spot Bitcoin ETFs in the United States. Will’s views on tokenization and how the firm is approaching...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sui Foundation Addresses Concerns Over Token Supply Distribution]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19462876/Sui-Foundation-Addresses-Concerns-Over-Token-Supply-Distribution</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19462876/Sui-Foundation-Addresses-Concerns-Over-Token-Supply-Distribution"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T09:48:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In response to recent community concerns regarding the token supply of Sui, Wu Blockchain, a crypto news reporter, reports the official statement from Sui addressing the doubts. According to the statement, Mysten Labs’ founder does not control crucial aspects such as the Sui Foundation treasury,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rekt Capital on the “3 Phases of The Bitcoin Halving”]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19462879/Rekt-Capital-on-the-3-Phases-of-The-Bitcoin-Halving</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19462879/Rekt-Capital-on-the-3-Phases-of-The-Bitcoin-Halving"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T09:45:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to the insights of crypto analyst Rekt Capital, Bitcoin’s much-anticipated halving event continues to be a pivotal catalyst in defining its market dynamics. Occurring just over two weeks ago, this event purportedly initiates a cyclical influence on Bitcoin’s price and investor...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Started the Week Positively, Rising Above 65 Thousand Dollars! These Altcoins Overshadowed BTC With Their Rise!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19462862/Bitcoin-Started-the-Week-Positively-Rising-Above-65-Thousand-Dollars-These-Altcoins-Overshadowed-BTC-With-Their-Rise</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19462862/Bitcoin-Started-the-Week-Positively-Rising-Above-65-Thousand-Dollars-These-Altcoins-Overshadowed-BTC-With-Their-Rise"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T09:45:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin started the week positively, exceeding $65,000. Investors with short positions in BTC and altcoins were left in reverse and liquidated. Continue Reading: Bitcoin Started the Week Positively, Rising Above 65 Thousand Dollars! These Altcoins Overshadowed BTC With Their Rise!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin network celebrates 1 billion transactions as a Satoshi-era wallet awakens]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19462840/Bitcoin-network-celebrates-1-billion-transactions-as-a-Satoshi-era-wallet-awakens</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19462840/Bitcoin-network-celebrates-1-billion-transactions-as-a-Satoshi-era-wallet-awakens"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T09:41:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin network processed its one billionth transaction 15 years after it mined its genesis block in January 2009. Notably, the network achieved this milestone the same day a Satoshi-era Bitcoin address came to life. 1 billion transactions According to data from the Bitcoin dashboard on Clark...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Horizen partners with Gateway to boost leading Web3 projects]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19462842/Horizen-partners-with-Gateway-to-boost-leading-Web3-projects</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19462842/Horizen-partners-with-Gateway-to-boost-leading-Web3-projects"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T09:40:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Horizen Labs, a company specializing in zero-knowledge cryptography, made an extensive partnership with Gateway.fm, a distributed blockchain infrastructure company, per … Continue reading]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Sets 81 Million SHIB Ablaze as Burn Rate Soars 4,085%]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19462826/Shiba-Inu-Sets-81-Million-SHIB-Ablaze-as-Burn-Rate-Soars-4085</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19462826/Shiba-Inu-Sets-81-Million-SHIB-Ablaze-as-Burn-Rate-Soars-4085"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T09:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB) burn rate tops 4,085% amid mild price rebound]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analysts: Gold Rush In China Is Propping Prices Up]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74283bdcf5</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/analysts-china-gold-rush-is-propping-prices-up/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T09:32:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The interest and high demand for gold products in China is one of the factors that is propping the price of the precious metal up in international markets. Several analysts believe that the loss of confidence in traditional investment options in China, and the geopolitical factors and U.S. sanctions have contributed to this end. China […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB) Outperforms Bitcoin and Dogecoin on This Front: Details]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19462808/Shiba-Inu-SHIB-Outperforms-Bitcoin-and-Dogecoin-on-This-Front-Details</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19462808/Shiba-Inu-SHIB-Outperforms-Bitcoin-and-Dogecoin-on-This-Front-Details"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T09:31:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SHIB generated more trading volume than BTC and DOGE on this popular crypto exchange: check out for details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Recorded One Billion Transactions On Bitcoin Network]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19462812/Bitcoin-Recorded-One-Billion-Transactions-On-Bitcoin-Network</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19462812/Bitcoin-Recorded-One-Billion-Transactions-On-Bitcoin-Network"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin finally recorded its one Billion transactions on its Bitcoin Network setting an example for other Cryptocurrencies. It also highlights the history of 15 years with its one billion hits. What Estimates Bitcoin Shows?The statistics and dynamics shows that Bitcoin recorded 178,475 average...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Have Been Lied To, Bitcoin Is GOING TO HIT $100,000+ Per Coin]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19462811/You-Have-Been-Lied-To-Bitcoin-Is-GOING-TO-HIT-100000-Per-Coin</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19462811/You-Have-Been-Lied-To-Bitcoin-Is-GOING-TO-HIT-100000-Per-Coin"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T09:28:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome back to another Bitcoin price cycle everyone, the amount of price manipulation in the market is STAGGERING right now. People are actively making SURE that you leave the market and sell your coins so that they can buy at a lower price while making themselves richer. Bitcoin will reach new...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin privacy will survive despite CoinJoin closure — zkSNACKs CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19462820/Bitcoin-privacy-will-survive-despite-CoinJoin-closure-zkSNACKs-CEO</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19462820/Bitcoin-privacy-will-survive-despite-CoinJoin-closure-zkSNACKs-CEO"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T09:28:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The impending closure of zkSNACKs’ CoinJoin service has been described as a setback for Bitcoin developers and privacy proponents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why is the Ripple (XRP) Price Up Today?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19462784/Why-is-the-Ripple-XRP-Price-Up-Today</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19462784/Why-is-the-Ripple-XRP-Price-Up-Today"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T09:23:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple's price is on the move. Here are a few possible technical reasons why XRP is up today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOJ Crypto Crackdown: Cartier Heir Charged; BTC-e Operator Pleads Guilty]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19462875/DOJ-Crypto-Crackdown-Cartier-Heir-Charged-BTC-e-Operator-Pleads-Guilty</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19462875/DOJ-Crypto-Crackdown-Cartier-Heir-Charged-BTC-e-Operator-Pleads-Guilty"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T09:22:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US Department of Justice (DOJ) has escalated its crackdown on international money laundering. Authorities have indicted Maximilien de Hoop Cartier, allegedly linked to the Cartier family, for laundering drug proceeds through cryptocurrency. In a parallel development, Alexander Vinnik,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin hits massive milestone: One billion transactions processed]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19462786/Bitcoin-hits-massive-milestone-One-billion-transactions-processed</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19462786/Bitcoin-hits-massive-milestone-One-billion-transactions-processed"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T09:20:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marking an incredible milestone in the history of the world’s first and most valuable cryptocurrency, the Bitcoin network has processed its 1 billionth transaction. That milestone moment came 15 years, four months, and four days after its pseudonymous creator, Satoshi Nakamoto, mined the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) Whale Sales Surge: Are Whales Giving up on It? Ethereum (ETH)]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19462780/Ethereum-ETH-Whale-Sales-Surge-Are-Whales-Giving-up-on-It-Ethereum-ETH</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19462780/Ethereum-ETH-Whale-Sales-Surge-Are-Whales-Giving-up-on-It-Ethereum-ETH"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T09:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum whales might be getting enough of ETH]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Less Than 10% of Stablecoin Transaction Volume Coming from Real Users: Report]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74282f5299</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/05/06/less-than-10-of-stablecoin-transaction-volume-coming-from-real-users-report/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T08:05:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Less than 10% of stablecoin transaction volumes are organic or come from real people, according to new findings by Visa and data platform Allium Labs, Bloomberg reported.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amitoj Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Legal Storm Brewing For Coinbase: Lawsuit Claims Deceptive Practices]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74282f755b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/legal-storm-brewing-for-coinbase/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T08:03:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase, a leading cryptocurrency exchange, finds itself embroiled in a multi-front legal war. From disgruntled investors to the watchful eye of the SEC, the company faces challenges that threaten its operations and cast a shadow over the future of crypto regulation.
 
 
Coinbase Accused Of Selling Unregistered Securities
 
A new class-action lawsuit filed in California alleges Coinbase knowingly violated state securities laws by selling unregistered securities. The plaintiffs, a group of investors, target specific tokens like Solana and Uniswap, arguing they should be classified as investments and not mere digital assets.
 
They point to a possible contradiction within the exchange’s own user agreement, which may define the company as a “Securities Broker.” This lawsuit echoes a similar …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nigerian Court Postpones Binance, Tigran Gambaryan Money Laundering Trial to May 17]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7428291ad2</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/nigerian-court-postpones-binance-tigran-gambaryan-money-laundering-trial-to-may-17/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T07:50:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Nigerian court recently adjourned the trial of Binance and its executive, Tigran Gambaryan, to May 17. The adjournment came after the cryptocurrency exchange’s attorney stated that he had not received the necessary documents to prepare a defense. However, Nigerian authorities reportedly provided the attorney with an additional 300-page document containing further evidence during a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Massive Rumor: Hong Kong’s Bitcoin ETFs May Open To Mainland Chinese]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7428134977</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/hong-kong-bitcoin-etfs-may-open-mainland-chinese/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T06:22:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Richard Byworth, Managing Partner at SyzCapital, has ignited rumors suggesting that Bitcoin ETFs listed in Hong Kong could soon be accessible to investors from mainland China. Byworth’s remarks on X, formerly known as Twitter, highlight the ongoing discussions about the possibility of the integration of these ETFs into the Stock Connect system. This integration could pave the way for a massive wave of capital inflow from the mainland into these digital asset funds.
 
Byworth stated, “I just got back from Hong Kong. There is talk that the ETF could be added to stock connect. The implications for this are absolutely enormous (basically means mainland money can buy it)”. This statement followed a dialogue initiated by Samson Mow, who commented on the impressive initial performance of the Chin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Latam Insights: South African Ponzi Scheme Boss Dies in Brazil, Argentine House Passes Crypto Tax Regularization Bill]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7428181f99</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/latam-insights-south-african-ponzi-scheme-boss-dies-in-brazil-argentine-house-passes-crypto-tax-regularization-bill/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T05:36:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Latam Insights, a compendium of Latin America’s most relevant crypto and economic news during the last week. In this issue: South African Ponzi scheme mastermind dies of a heart attack in Brazil, the Argentine House advances crypto tax regularization bill, and Buenos Aires targets Worldcoin with a new bill. South African Ponzi Scheme […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Faces Another Class Action Lawsuit: Investors Allege Illegal Offerings]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7428191e22</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/coinbase-faces-another-class-action-lawsuit-investors-allege-illegal-offerings/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T05:26:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The American cryptocurrency exchange, Coinbase, is embroiled in yet another class-action lawsuit. This lawsuit alleges that investors were misled into purchasing tokens classified as unregistered securities. Filed last Friday, the class action also contends that the exchange’s business model is unlawful.
Another Class Action Against Coinbase
According to the lawsuit, Coinbase's listed tokens—such as Solana, Polygon, Near Protocol, Decentraland, Algorand, Uniswap, Tezos, and Stellar Lumens—are considered securities, rendering their listings on the exchange illegal.
The lawsuit further claims that in its user agreement, the exchange acknowledged its role as a “securities broker,” thereby categorizing the digital assets it offers as investment contracts or securities. Additionally, the lawsui…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arnab Shome</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Market Making Mastery: Coinrate.pro CEO Reveals the 12x Market Caps Strategy]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74281b23f1</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/market-making-mastery-coinrate-pro-ceo-reveals-the-12x-market-caps-strategy/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T05:07:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. Abu Dhabi, AE, May 6, 2024 – Amidst the 2024 resurgence of the bull market, with Bitcoin breaking the $72,000 mark, the demand for sophisticated market making has skyrocketed. Coinrate.pro has emerged as a trailblazer with its innovative market making strategies and forward-looking vision. Sergey Smotrov, the CEO of Coinrate.pro, unveils the company’s […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Australian Court Rules Against BPS Financial for Unlicensed Crypto Operations]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742803cf0f</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/australian-court-rules-against-bps-financial-for-unlicensed-crypto-operations/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T03:35:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Federal Court of Australia has ruled against BPS Financial for operating “Qoin Wallet” without proper licenses. The Australian Securities and Investments Commission (ASIC) underscores the importance of regulatory compliance to protect consumers in the volatile crypto market. ‘First Court Outcome’ Against Crypto Payment Facility The Federal Court of Australia has found that BPS Financial […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[India Announces ‘Successful’ Crackdown on E-Nugget Scam — Seizes $10M in Crypto From Exchanges]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7429f5e218</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/india-announces-successful-crackdown-on-e-nugget-scam-seizes-10m-in-crypto-from-exchanges/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T01:32:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[India’s Enforcement Directorate has declared its multi-year crackdown on the “E-Nugget” scam in Kolkata successful. The operation has resulted in cash and crypto seizures, along with the arrest of the mastermind. Investigations uncovered numerous dummy accounts and led to the freezing of digital assets at various crypto exchanges, which were then transferred to the ED’s […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Wealth Bolsters Real Estate Markets and Consumer Spending, Study Finds]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7429fe746a</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/crypto-wealth-bolsters-real-estate-markets-and-consumer-spending-study-finds/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T23:39:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As cryptocurrency becomes a significant part of American investment portfolios, its influence extends beyond digital transactions into tangible impacts on real estate markets and household spending, a recent study finds. Report Shows Cryptocurrency Wealth Adds ‘Meaningful Implications for the Real Economy’ The study, first reported on by Bloomberg, analyzes bank and credit card data from […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sui Surpasses Solana in Daily Transactions Amidst Spam Token Frenzy]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7429e0b1fa</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/sui-surpasses-solana-in-daily-transactions-amidst-spam-token-frenzy/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T21:29:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sui, a scalability-focused blockchain, has surpassed Solana, a top 10 cryptocurrency network, in activity levels, registering 41 million transactions on April 3. The activity overheating on Sui is caused by ‘spam’, a Sui native token designed to stress test the network’s capabilities, assigning tokens to users equivalent to the number of transactions issued. Sui Surpasses […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blackrock’s BUIDL Fund Overtakes Franklin Templeton to Become Largest RWA Tokenized Offering]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7429ebdbac</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/blackrocks-buidl-fund-overtakes-franklin-templeton-to-become-largest-rwa-tokenized-offering/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T19:15:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Based on the most recent figures, Blackrock’s USD Institutional Digital Liquidity Fund, also known as BUIDL, has expanded to $381.76 million, overtaking Franklin Templeton’s onchain investment vehicle, BENJI, as the largest real-world asset (RWA) tokenized offering. Blackrock’s Digital Fund Surpasses BENJI as Leader in Tokenized Treasury Offerings Blackrock’s BUIDL has now eclipsed all other tokenized […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Ordinals Size Record Broken Again—How Much Bigger Can They Get?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229421</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229421/bitcoin-block-size-record-broken-again-how-much-bigger"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T18:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The largest-ever Bitcoin file was just inscribed, as an Ordinals asset broke the two-month-old size record. Can it be broken again?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Owners, Beware: Impersonators Are Targeting Your Pack!]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7429dc47ce</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-owners-beware-impersonators-are-targeting-your-pack/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T17:46:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The booming Shiba Inu (SHIB) community faces a growing threat: imposters posing as prominent developers on social media platforms like Telegram. Shibarmy Scam Alerts, a watchful community group, recently exposed this deceptive tactic, urging investors to exercise caution in the face of these digital wolves in sheep’s clothing.
 
 
Shiba Inu Developers Targeted: Kusama And Dhairya In The Crosshairs
 
Shibarmy Scam Alerts identified fake Telegram accounts masquerading as Shytoshi Kusama and Kaal Dhairya, two leading figures within the Shiba Inu ecosystem. The imposters meticulously crafted usernames that mimicked the real developers, with subtle alterations designed to bypass casual scrutiny. This highlights the sophistication of these scams, emphasizing the need for investors to be meticulo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Epic Satoshi ​​Spurs Launch of New Runes Tokens With $88M Market Cap]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7429df167a</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/epic-satoshi-spurs-launch-of-new-runes-tokens-with-88m-market-cap/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T17:17:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to onchain data, the ‘epic satoshi’ sold for 33.3 BTC has been inscribed, now linked to a freshly minted Runes protocol coin named “EPIC•EPIC•EPIC•EPIC.” The newly introduced EPIC runes tokens have already commenced trading, achieving a market capitalization of $88 million by 11 a.m. Eastern Time on Sunday. From Epic Satoshi to EPIC•EPIC•EPIC•EPIC Runes […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Crypto Games: Supercell's Investment, Saga Airdrop, 'Parallel' Adds Expansion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229459</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229459/this-week-crypto-games-supercell-investment-saga-airdrop-parallel-expansion"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T16:53:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Catch up on this week’s biggest crypto and NFT gaming news and find some weekend reads in our latest roundup.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week on Crypto Twitter: Ethereum, CZ, and Roger Ver in US Government Crosshairs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229391</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229391/this-week-on-crypto-twitter-ethereum-cz-roger-ver-government-wrath"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T16:19:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CZ got sentenced, Ver got arrested, and Ethereum has been secretly considered a regulated security since April 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Halving Effect: Bitcoin Hashrate Decreases as Miners Prepare for Probable Difficulty Drop]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7429c5b136</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/the-halving-effect-bitcoin-hashrate-decreases-as-miners-prepare-for-probable-difficulty-drop/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T16:16:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just over two weeks have passed since the fourth Bitcoin halving took place. During this period, the network’s hashprice dropped from over $100 per petahash to below $45 at the beginning of May. It has since increased to $50 per petahash. Despite the modest rebound, the network’s total hashrate has experienced a decrease, with a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bull Michael Saylor Wants SEC To Corral Crypto Herd: ETH, ADA, SOL In The Crosshairs]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7429c2d7c2</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-bull-michael-saylor-wants-sec-to-corral-crypto-herd-eth-ada-sol-in-the-crosshairs/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T15:31:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Saylor, the tech entrepreneur who steered MicroStrategy into a Bitcoin behemoth, is back in the headlines. This time, he’s not championing the orange coin, but rather aiming his laser focus at its altcoin rivals.
 
 
At the recent Bitcoin For Corporations conference, Saylor unleashed a flurry of predictions, painting a picture of a future where the SEC cracks down on leading altcoins like Ethereum (ETH), Binance Coin (BNB), Solana (SOL), Ripple (XRP), and Cardano (ADA).
 
Bitcoin’s Lone Wolf? Saylor Casts Doubt On Altcoin Legitimacy
 
Saylor’s stance on altcoins is about as subtle as a Bitcoin mining rig – there simply isn’t room for another top dog. He boldly claimed that the SEC will reject all applications for spot ETH ETFs, effectively throwing cold water on the hopes of invest…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Class Action Lawsuit Claims Coinbase Operates as Unregistered Broker]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7429ca06ab</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/class-action-lawsuit-claims-coinbase-operates-as-unregistered-broker/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T14:24:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new class action lawsuit was initiated against the San Francisco-based cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase on May 3. The legal action claims that Coinbase deliberately sold securities that are unregistered with regulatory authorities. Additionally, the lawsuit charges Coinbase with operating as an unregistered securities broker. Lawsuit Alleges Coinbase Illegally Sold Securities Without Registration According to legal […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biggest Video Games Releasing in May 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229400</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229400/biggest-video-games-releasing-may-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-05-04T15:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's a busy month of sequels as Senua's Saga: Hellblade II, Homeworld 3, and World of Goo 2 lead May 2024's video game releases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Frederiksen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moonbirds Copyright Controversy Exposes Flaws in Crypto's IP Obsession]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229373</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229373/moonbirds-copyright-controversy-exposes-flaws-in-cryptos-ip-obsession"/>
        <updated>2024-05-04T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most NFT brands think ‘IP’ is the future. But as a Moonbirds announcement revealed this week, does anyone actually understand what that means?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Bitcoin Battered But Rebounds As Meme Coin Mania Abides]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229314</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229314/this-week-in-coins-bitcoin-battered-but-rebounds-as-meme-coin-mania-abides"/>
        <updated>2024-05-04T10:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From Bitcoin's mid-week plunge to the prurient LIVEMOM pump, it was a wild seven days in crypto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI Could Challenge Google and Perplexity With AI-Powered Search: Reports]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229381</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229381/search-chatgpt-openai-web-google-perplexity"/>
        <updated>2024-05-04T00:29:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The leader in AI could dethrone the leader in search, with web sleuths uncovering signs of a search tool linked to ChatGPT.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale Bitcoin ETF Snaps Losing Streak, Pulls In $63 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229415</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229415/grayscale-bitcoin-etf-snaps-losing-streak-pulls-in-63-million"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T22:32:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After 80 days of outflows, the battered long-standing Bitcoin fund grew by $63 million.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Kawailani Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Most Dogecoin Holders Didn't Buy the Elon Musk Top]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229375</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229375/most-dogecoin-holders-didnt-buy-elon-musk-top"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T20:49:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A strong majority of Dogecoin holders are currently in the green, even at prices well below Elon Musk-led highs in 2021.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Game ‘Nyan Heroes’ Returning With Expanded Play-to-Airdrop Rewards]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229370</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229370/solana-game-nyan-heroes-returning-expanded-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T19:54:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cats-in-mechs shooter Nyan Heroes will bring its servers back online next week as the second play-to-airdrop season kicks off.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy Orange: Everything You Need to Know About Decentralized ID on Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229320</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229320/what-is-microstrategy-orange-decentralized-identity-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T18:47:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The largest institutional holder of Bitcoin is getting into decentralized identity. But how does MicroStrategy Orange work?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[As Bitcoin Pumps, These Altcoins Are Doing Even Better]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229325</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229325/bitcoin-altcoin-ordi-ton-bonk"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T18:21:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While Bitcoin is up 4.62% in the last 24 hours, ORDI, TON, and BONK are outperforming the market leader with impressive gains. Here's a closer look at their recent performance and potential price movements.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Time to Buy? MicroStrategy Stock Premium Shrinks After Bitcoin Pullback]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229323</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229323/microstrategy-mstr-btc-premium-shrinks"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T18:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MSTR still trades much higher than the value of the Bitcoin behind it, but one analyst believes fundamentals aren’t important for investors right now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saga Reveals First ‘Power-Level Over 9,000’ Airdrop With $10 Million in Tokens]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229319</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229319/saga-power-level-over-9000-airdrop-10-million-tokens"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T17:50:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gaming-heavy layer-1 network Saga is serving up more SAGA rewards as it prepares to tee up airdrops from 100+ partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jack Dorsey's Block Will Reinvest 10% of Bitcoin Profits Into BTC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229317</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229317/jack-dorsey-block-reinvest-10-percent-bitcoin-profits-btc"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T17:35:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After selling $2.7 billion worth of Bitcoin in Q1 2024, Jack Dorsey's Block unveiled a plan to reinvest Bitcoin-related profits into the coin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Rebound Smashes $100 Million in Crypto Shorts]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229313</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229313/bitcoin-price-rebound-smashes-100-million-crypto-shorts"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T16:44:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin is back up again—and as a result, traders betting on a dip in the asset's price have had their positions liquidated.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Leaps Over $61K Following US Unemployment Data]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229310</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229310/bitcoin-price-leaps-over-61k-following-us-unemployment-data"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T14:30:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a government employment report was published, showing unemployment is higher than expected, Bitcoin leaped over $61k.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Billionaire Arthur Hayes Predicts Market Bottom Is In, 'Slow Grind Higher']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229288</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229288/bitcoin-billionaire-arthur-hayes-predicts-market-bottom-is-in-slow-grind-higher"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T13:33:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin has hit its bottom, BTC billionaire Arthur Hayes argued. And now, he predicts markets will see "a slow grind higher."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Week in Polkadot: JAM Pushes Toward ‘Original Concept’ of World Computer: Gavin Wood]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229293</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229293/the-week-in-polkadot-jam-pushes-toward-original-concept-of-world-computer-gavin-wood"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T13:09:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Polkadot founder Gavin Wood sat down for an hour-long podcast to answer questions about the network’s JAM upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will McCurdy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Asked AI to Predict Kentucky Derby Winners—Here Are Its Picks]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229239</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229239/ai-picks-kentucky-derby-horse-race-winners-horsegpt"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We built an AI agent and fed it bales of race horse statistics. Our HorseGPT slate matched human expert predictions well.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friend.tech Community in Uproar Amid Token and V2 Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229273</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229273/friend-tech-community-in-uproar-amid-token-and-v2-launch"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T11:43:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Community members are upset after web3 social media platform, Friend.tech, fumbles its token and V2 launch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Clock is Ticking' on Bitcoin Privacy: Edward Snowden]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229262</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229262/bitcoin-privacy-edward-snowden-clock-is-ticking"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T11:20:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CIA whistleblower took to Twitter to issue a "final warning" on Bitcoin privacy, amid a U.S. crackdown on privacy projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why This Hedge Fund Bought Dogwifhat at 1 Cent: ‘It Had a Hat’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229263</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229263/hedge-fund-bought-dogwifhat-1-cent"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T11:13:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto hedge fund, Stratos, invested in WIF at $0.01. Now that WIF has climbed to $2.76, the firm outlines its meme coin philosophy to Decrypt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jito Price Jumps After Topping Solana DeFi Protocols With $1 Billion Locked]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229227</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229227/jito-price-jumps-after-topping-solana-defi-protocols-with-1-billion-locked"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T21:36:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jito Network became the top DeFi protocol on Solana, with liquid staking pool token JitoSOL rising by 8.5%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bulletproof Cadillac, Butler, and $1.5M Titanic Watch: FTX Exec's Lavish Spending Continues]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229212</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229212/ftx-exec-lavish-spending-continues-1-5-million-watch-titanic"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T21:20:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former FTX Europe head Patrick Gruhn is spending his crypto riches— but his fortune is not without controversy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase $1.6 Billion Quarterly Profits Boosted By Stablecoins, Rising Crypto Prices]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229217</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229217/coinbase-first-quarter-profit-report"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T21:10:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The San Francisco-based exchange has reported better-than-expected 2024 Q1 results.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo,André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will the Fed Cut Rates? Crypto and Wall Street Traders Aren’t Betting on It]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229213</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229213/fed-rate-cut-odds-crypto-polymarket-cme-tradfi"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T20:13:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Just cut the rates bro please,” pleaded a down-bad trader on Polymarket.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Transactions Plummet Following Absurd Runes and Halving Surge]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229185</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229185/bitcoin-transaction-fees-fall-after-halving-highs"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T18:50:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cost to send BTC skyrocketed immediately following the halving, but fees have since fallen back to Earth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elizabeth Warren's Latest Crypto Crusade: Bitcoin Mining In Iran]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229189</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229189/elizabeth-warren-iran-bitcoin-mining-terrorism"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T18:39:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The leading crypto critic in the U.S. Senate says the Iranian mining sector supports terrorism.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mom Sexualizes Herself on Livestream for Son’s Meme Coin—Then Ghosts]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229175</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229175/livemom-livestream-mom-son-meme-coin"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T17:41:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A mom used her boobs to help her son pump a meme coin, called LIVEMOM, to a $300K market cap before the token crashed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETFs Shed $563 Million as BlackRock's IBIT Marks First Daily Loss]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229168</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229168/bitcoin-etfs-shed-563-million-blackrock-ibit-losses"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T16:46:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spot Bitcoin ETFs posted record daily net outflows on Wednesday as BlackRock's IBIT faltered for the very first time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum and Solana Meme Coin Prices Surge Amid Modest Bitcoin Gains]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229150</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229150/ethereum-solana-meme-coins-surge-modest-bitcoin-gains"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T16:29:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin is rising after a rough week, but meme coins like Pepe, Bonk, Dogwifhat, and Dogecoin are the biggest winners today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are Parachains? Polkadot's Secret Weapon Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229149</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-are-parachains-polkadots-secret-weapon-explained"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T15:44:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Polkadot’s parachains offer a unique technical approach to achieving scalability and interoperability for blockchains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will McCurdy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Blogging Protocol Mirror Embraces Farcaster in Social Media Pivot]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229077</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229077/ethereum-blogging-protocol-mirror-farcaster-social-media-pivot"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T15:10:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mirror's team is now building a Farcaster-based social app called Kiosk, while Paragraph will take over Mirror. Collectively, they've raised $15 million.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Do A Little With Mike Demarais]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ajrh0oiK/we-do-a-little-with-mike-demarais</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ajrh0oiK/we-do-a-little-with-mike-demarais"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T15:11:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mike dropped knowledge bombs from years of building in the trenches alongside some deep cuts on the early Williamsburg crypto mafia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eth Rally Fails]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Gj7TMrbP/eth-rally-fails</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Gj7TMrbP/eth-rally-fails"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T12:45:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto falls, ETH/BTC rally again marks mini sell-off. Yen carry-trade implosion linked to worries. ETH gas fees hit 6-month lows. 3rd straight week of institutional outflows. Slowing BTC ETF flows are just a pause: Bernstein. BTC now on track for 5 red weeks in a row. BTC may have topped, could hit $35k: Brandt. ETFs may become big sellers: Bianco. Consensys list 4 reasons ETH isn’t a security. Rumours continue to grow of EigenLayer airdrop. Perp DEX volumes continue fall, GMX underperforms. Wallets begin to block US users after Samourai case. WLD in reported partnership talks with OpenAI. Large unlocks this week for SUI, PYTH & MEME.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Sasha Stiles’ Experiential, AI-Infused NFT Drop with Bang & Olufsen]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/6Vi2IgYj/inside-sasha-stiles-experiential-ai-infused-nft-drop-with-bang-olufsen</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/6Vi2IgYj/inside-sasha-stiles-experiential-ai-infused-nft-drop-with-bang-olufsen"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T22:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At a launch party for the collection in New York’s SoHo neighborhood, the artist broke down her latest art experiment, “Four Core Texts,” with Decrypt’s Sander Lutz.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interview: How 'Notcoin' Will Evolve After the NOT Token Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PprnGP14/interview-how-notcoin-will-evolve-after-the-not-token-launch</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PprnGP14/interview-how-notcoin-will-evolve-after-the-not-token-launch"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Open Builders founder Sasha Plotvinov speaks with Decrypt's Sander Lutz at Token 2049 Dubai about how he envisions Notcoin's expansion and evolution after the token drop—into something akin to the "Netflix of social, viral games."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Magic Runes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IGWg0R64/magic-runes</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IGWg0R64/magic-runes"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T13:59:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC stables at $66k, liquidations in narrow range. BTC funding again turns negative in bullish sign. ETFs net inflow after Grayscale moves to lower fees. BTC demand 5x vs supply post-halving: Bitfinex. SOL congestion issue now largely solved. Two SEC lawyers resign after ‘gross abuse of power’. Ripple fights to lower $2bn SEC fine. SAFE trades at $2.8bn FDV after OKX lists. MANEKI hits $150m on first day, China memes pump. Memecoins are ‘black hole you can’t ignore’. DeGods up 20%, may switch back to SOL. Magic Eden launches Runes platform ahead of time.  Louis Vuitton gifts Pharrell jacket to NFT holders. Melania Trump launches necklace with SOL NFTs. Hoodie Punk trades for $620K.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Luxury Watches, Designer Shoes Will Soon Trade Like NFTs: Arianee CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/CSNQG2md/luxury-watches-designer-shoes-will-soon-trade-like-nfts-arianee-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/CSNQG2md/luxury-watches-designer-shoes-will-soon-trade-like-nfts-arianee-ceo"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arianee CEO Pierre-Nicolas Hurstel sat down with Rug Radio founder Farokh and Decrypt’s Sander Lutz at NFT Paris to discuss everything from the future of on-chain luxury to the secret hack to finding the best restaurants in France.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notcoin's Co-Creator Explains the Game's Token Delay—And When to Expect NOT Now]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/7Zx33xo5/notcoins-co-creator-explains-the-games-token-delayand-when-to-expect-not-now</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/7Zx33xo5/notcoins-co-creator-explains-the-games-token-delayand-when-to-expect-not-now"/>
        <updated>2024-04-22T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Notcoin co-creator Sasha Plotvinov spoke with Decrypt's Sander Lutz at Token 2049 Dubai to discuss why the NOT token launch was pushed back from the original 4/20 target, when to expect the listing, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TON’s Justin Hyun Breaks Down The Importance of USDT Coming to Telegram]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ODQI6ACA/tons-justin-hyun-breaks-down-the-importance-of-usdt-coming-to-telegram</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ODQI6ACA/tons-justin-hyun-breaks-down-the-importance-of-usdt-coming-to-telegram"/>
        <updated>2024-04-19T10:14:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Token 2049 in Dubai, The Open Network’s director of investments sat down with Decrypt’s Sander Lutz to discuss what he sees as the game-changing integration of USDT onto TON, and his plans for getting Telegram’s 900 million users to start using crypto in the immediate future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Influencer Ansem Explains His Meme Coin Thesis and Why He’s Bullish on Bitcoin Runes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/u9DHFoK0/crypto-influencer-ansem-explains-his-meme-coin-thesis-and-why-hes-bullish-on-bitcoin-runes</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/u9DHFoK0/crypto-influencer-ansem-explains-his-meme-coin-thesis-and-why-hes-bullish-on-bitcoin-runes"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T21:56:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ansem, the crypto trader who's amassed a sizable following on the back of meme coin Dogwifhat (WIF) and other calls, chats with Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz at Token 2049 Dubai about his meme coin thesis, why he's bullish on Bitcoin Runes, and what he sees ahead for the crypto markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Sander Lutz Braves the Dubai Floods for a Crypto Conference]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/mtjVHGa3/decrypts-sander-lutz-braves-the-dubai-floods-for-a-crypto-conference</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/mtjVHGa3/decrypts-sander-lutz-braves-the-dubai-floods-for-a-crypto-conference"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T21:33:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz reports from Dubai amid a historic storm that flooded the famed city, trudging through the streets to complete his essential task: Attending the Token 2049 crypto conference.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gold Beats Its All Time High]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/6ULgUKVk/gold-beats-its-all-time-high</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/6ULgUKVk/gold-beats-its-all-time-high"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T09:53:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) maintains its trend of reaching higher lows amidst choppy market conditions. Exchange-traded funds (ETFs) witness another influx of $125 million. There's anticipation of Hong Kong approving ETFs for both Bitcoin and Ethereum (ETH) come Monday. Notable institutional investor BlackRock shows interest in Bitcoin. Recent filings reveal increased Bitcoin purchases by banks. A Bitcoin-friendly political party secures victory in the South Korean election. Analyst Kang predicts Bitcoin could surge to $80-100k by May. Meanwhile, Ethereum sees accumulation by stablecoin whales on the rise. A new Ethereum Improvement Proposal (EIP) aims to streamline signing requests. Solana (SOL) experiences a resurgence in activity, reaching yearly highs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NASA’s Next Deep Space Mission Won’t Use Artificial Intelligence]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/0WGP33Rp/nasas-next-deep-space-mission-wont-use-artificial-intelligence</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/0WGP33Rp/nasas-next-deep-space-mission-wont-use-artificial-intelligence"/>
        <updated>2024-04-13T18:42:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Thursday, Decrypt Media visited NASA's Jet Propulsion Laboratory in Pasadena, CA to meet with the Engineering team behind the Europa Clipper before its launch to Jupiter's Europa moon in October.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Do A Little with Weesh]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LnaOT9bF/we-do-a-little-with-weesh</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LnaOT9bF/we-do-a-little-with-weesh"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T07:46:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week’s episode, we did a little something different. We took the man who is usually behind the camera and put him in front of it. We sat down with our producer Weesh to dive into how in fell in love with art and became a collector, how he met Andy and fun childhood memories together, his biggest wins in crypto, and so much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside VanEck’s Crypto Takeover of the New York Stock Exchange]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9YAY4wGD/inside-vanecks-crypto-takeover-of-the-new-york-stock-exchange</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9YAY4wGD/inside-vanecks-crypto-takeover-of-the-new-york-stock-exchange"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T14:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worlds collide as Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz heads to the floor of the NYSE to witness a special closing bell ceremony hosted by VanEck in honor of Web3. Featuring Choose Rich Nick, VanEck Head of Web3 Matt Bartlett, and more!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wormhole Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9SNiIVfU/wormhole-wednesday</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9SNiIVfU/wormhole-wednesday"/>
        <updated>2024-04-07T17:42:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC hits $64.5K then rebounds, SOL outperforms. Government sends $2B BTC to Coinbase to sell. Funding rates stay low after sweep lower. ETFs see small inflow, Ark outflow more than GBTC. Wormhole W launches at $15B FDV. BTC ‘inflection point’ if it follows rates or gold. Gold & BTC very correlated for the last year. Expect slower ETF volume this month: Bloomberg. BTC 2x and 3x levered ETFs launch yesterday. BTC ETFs now half the size of gold.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>