<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-12-19T09:15:13.510Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-12-19T09:15:13.510Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Challenges and Solutions in Safeguarding Language Model Agents from Prompt Injection]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118821/Challenges-and-Solutions-in-Safeguarding-Language-Model-Agents-from-Prompt-Injection</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118821/Challenges-and-Solutions-in-Safeguarding-Language-Model-Agents-from-Prompt-Injection"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T09:08:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The development and integration of Language Model Agents (LLMs) into real-world applications have garnered significant attention due to their remarkable natural language processing capabilities. However, the rise of prompt injection as a potential threat to LLM integrity has raised concerns...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Postpones Decision on Hashdex Nasdaq Ethereum ETF]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118827/SEC-Postpones-Decision-on-Hashdex-Nasdaq-Ethereum-ETF</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118827/SEC-Postpones-Decision-on-Hashdex-Nasdaq-Ethereum-ETF"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T09:03:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SEC delays decision on Hashdex Nasdaq Ethereum ETF, affecting firms like VanEck, ARK Invest, and creating investor uncertainty in the crypto market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Most Searched Altcoin of the Last 2 Months on Google Search Engine Has Been Announced! Here are the Details!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118787/The-Most-Searched-Altcoin-of-the-Last-2-Months-on-Google-Search-Engine-Has-Been-Announced-Here-are-the-Details</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118787/The-Most-Searched-Altcoin-of-the-Last-2-Months-on-Google-Search-Engine-Has-Been-Announced-Here-are-the-Details"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T08:48:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The popular altcoin's Google search volume witnessed a significant increase of 0 from early October to early December. Continue Reading: The Most Searched Altcoin of the Last 2 Months on Google Search Engine Has Been Announced! Here are the Details!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Central Bank of Brazil Opens Public Consultation on Virtual Assets Service Provider Rulemaking]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748d5053db</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/central-bank-of-brazil-opens-public-consultation-on-virtual-assets-service-provider-rulemaking/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T08:38:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Central Bank of Brazil opened a new public consultation to obtain feedback for regulating the operations of virtual assets service providers (VASPs) in the country. The bank organized a questionnaire of 38 questions divided into different themes that can be partially, or fully answered until January 31, 2024.
Central Bank of Brazil Seeks Input on VASP Regulation
The Central Bank of Brazil is preparing to finally issue rules for Virtual Assets Service Providers (VASPs) operating in the country. The institution opened a public consultation seeking input from market participants and individuals to prepare the rules VASPs would have to follow, according to the faculties it received since the approval and sanction of the cryptocurrency assets law in December 2023.
The bank introduced a 38-item questionnaire that can be answered totally or partially, indicating the numbers and themes respondents want to address in their statements.
Each question is part of a broader subject of the public consultation, including areas such as asset segregation and risk management, activities developed and virtual assets traded, hiring essential services, governance and conduct rules, cyber ​​security, providing information and protecting customers, transition rules, and general manifestations.
The issue of asset segregation has significance, given that it was initially proposed to be part of the final text of the approved cryptocurrency assets law, but was finally left out due to the limitations it would impose on the operations that VASPs could conduct. Tax exemptions for mining projects leveraging renewable energy were also left out of the final text and might be affected by these rules.
The public consultation process will be open until January 31, 2024, and all answers will be publicly available for review on the bank’s page.
What do you think about the public consultation of the Central Bank of Brazil to regulate the operation of VASPs? Tell us in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elevate and Transform Ideas: Participate in Internet Computer Hackathons Across North America]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118770/Elevate-and-Transform-Ideas-Participate-in-Internet-Computer-Hackathons-Across-North-America</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118770/Elevate-and-Transform-Ideas-Participate-in-Internet-Computer-Hackathons-Across-North-America"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T08:37:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 is constantly expanding; therefore, tech professionals in the industry are urged to hone their skills continuously. However, doing it without competition and support may lead to a lack of motivation. Therefore, tech professionals are always encouraged to mingle with other talents in the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taiwanese Authorities Issue Warning Against Cryptocurrency Betting on Upcoming Presidential Election]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118768/Taiwanese-Authorities-Issue-Warning-Against-Cryptocurrency-Betting-on-Upcoming-Presidential-Election</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118768/Taiwanese-Authorities-Issue-Warning-Against-Cryptocurrency-Betting-on-Upcoming-Presidential-Election"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T08:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the Taiwan presidential election scheduled for January 13, 2024, approaches, Taiwanese citizens have been...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock opts for cash-only redemptions in Bitcoin ETF application]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118741/BlackRock-opts-for-cash-only-redemptions-in-Bitcoin-ETF-application</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118741/BlackRock-opts-for-cash-only-redemptions-in-Bitcoin-ETF-application"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T08:30:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a significant development, BlackRock, one of the world’s largest asset managers, has made a pivotal adjustment to its Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) application. The company has decided to embrace ‘cash creations’ for fund redemptions, aligning itself with the stance of US financial...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ARK Sells $28M Grayscale Bitcoin Trust Shares as Bitcoin Nears $43K]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748d51912e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/12/19/ark-sells-28m-grayscale-bitcoin-trust-shares-as-bitcoin-nears-43k/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T08:28:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ARK Invest offloaded $13M worth of GBTC shares last week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Might Be Backing Down on Ethereum: Bloomberg Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118752/SEC-Might-Be-Backing-Down-on-Ethereum-Bloomberg-Analyst</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118752/SEC-Might-Be-Backing-Down-on-Ethereum-Bloomberg-Analyst"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T08:24:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent episode of crypto journalist Laura Shin’s Unchained Podcast, Bloomberg analyst James Seyffart discussed a noteworthy development suggesting a potential shift in the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission’s (SEC) stance towards Ethereum.  Seyffart shared his perspective on the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ARK Sells $28M Grayscale Bitcoin Trust Shares as Bitcoin Nears $43K]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118731/ARK-Sells-28M-Grayscale-Bitcoin-Trust-Shares-as-Bitcoin-Nears-43K</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118731/ARK-Sells-28M-Grayscale-Bitcoin-Trust-Shares-as-Bitcoin-Nears-43K"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T08:18:12.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum MEV relay giant takes a U-turn, rejects OFAC-sanctioned blocks]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118717/Ethereum-MEV-relay-giant-takes-a-U-turn-rejects-OFAC-sanctioned-blocks</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118717/Ethereum-MEV-relay-giant-takes-a-U-turn-rejects-OFAC-sanctioned-blocks"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T08:16:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a surprising reversal of its stance on censorship resistance, bloXroute Labs, a prominent producer of Ethereum blocks, has announced that it will begin censoring blocks containing transactions sanctioned by the United States Office of Foreign Asset Control (OFAC). The decision has stirred...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Most Interesting Man' Jonathan Goldsmith Stars In Bitwise's Advertisement To Promote Bitcoin ETF Provider]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118759/Most-Interesting-Man-Jonathan-Goldsmith-Stars-In-Bitwises-Advertisement-To-Promote-Bitcoin-ETF-Provider</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118759/Most-Interesting-Man-Jonathan-Goldsmith-Stars-In-Bitwises-Advertisement-To-Promote-Bitcoin-ETF-Provider"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T08:15:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jonathan Goldsmith, famously known as “the most interesting man in the world” from Dos Equis beer commercials, is now portraying his charisma in a Bitcoin (CRYPTO: BTC) ad for the cryptocurrency company Bitwise. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Balmain and Space Runners: the Generative-AI to customize sneakers on Polygon]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118737/Balmain-and-Space-Runners-the-Generative-AI-to-customize-sneakers-on-Polygon</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118737/Balmain-and-Space-Runners-the-Generative-AI-to-customize-sneakers-on-Polygon"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T08:13:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new collaboration involves the American artist Ant Kai.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock Makes Move to Finalize its Application Before the Holidays]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118727/BlackRock-Makes-Move-to-Finalize-its-Application-Before-the-Holidays</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118727/BlackRock-Makes-Move-to-Finalize-its-Application-Before-the-Holidays"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T08:12:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock updates ETF filing for IBIT, switching to cash-only strategy; move aligns with SEC, joins ARK Invest and 21Shares in ETF push.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Postpones Approval Decision on Multiple Ethereum ETFs until mid-2024]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118683/SEC-Postpones-Approval-Decision-on-Multiple-Ethereum-ETFs-until-mid-2024</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118683/SEC-Postpones-Approval-Decision-on-Multiple-Ethereum-ETFs-until-mid-2024"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T08:08:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has once again deferred its decision on whether to approve or disapprove the Hashdex Nasdaq Ethereum ETF. The filing stated that despite the proposal being published for comment on October 3, 2023, the SEC has opted to extend the evaluation period....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto asset manager 7RCC applies to offer bitcoin ETF]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118696/Crypto-asset-manager-7RCC-applies-to-offer-bitcoin-ETF</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118696/Crypto-asset-manager-7RCC-applies-to-offer-bitcoin-ETF"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T08:07:39.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analyst Unveils ‘Max Pain’ Scenario for Bitcoin, Says Crypto Never Witnessed Secular Bear Market]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118697/Analyst-Unveils-Max-Pain-Scenario-for-Bitcoin-Says-Crypto-Never-Witnessed-Secular-Bear-Market</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118697/Analyst-Unveils-Max-Pain-Scenario-for-Bitcoin-Says-Crypto-Never-Witnessed-Secular-Bear-Market"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T08:04:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A closely followed crypto analyst is unveiling a scenario that would devastate those who hopped on late on the Bitcoin (BTC) bandwagon. Pseudonymous trader Credible Crypto tells his 360,900 followers on the social media platform X that Bitcoin will likely leave most retail traders on the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto mining giant Cipher invests $99.5 million in Bitmain equipment]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118691/Crypto-mining-giant-Cipher-invests-995-million-in-Bitmain-equipment</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118691/Crypto-mining-giant-Cipher-invests-995-million-in-Bitmain-equipment"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T08:02:57.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Development in Binance Investigation: US Court Approves Agreement Between CFTC and Binance!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118652/New-Development-in-Binance-Investigation-US-Court-Approves-Agreement-Between-CFTC-and-Binance</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118652/New-Development-in-Binance-Investigation-US-Court-Approves-Agreement-Between-CFTC-and-Binance"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T07:41:06.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Circle Launches EURC Stablecoin on Solana, Expanding Euro Access in the Crypto Space]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748d5fc4cc</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/circle-launches-eurc-stablecoin-on-solana-expanding-euro-access-in-the-crypto-space/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T07:37:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Expanding the global reach of euro-based stablecoins, Circle has debuted its EURC token on the Solana blockchain, offering a fully reserved, euro-backed digital asset.
 
Circle Expands its Stablecoin Portfolio With EURC Launch on Solana, Boosting Euro Integration in Digital Finance
 

 
Circle, a leading stablecoin issuer, has announced the launch of its euro-backed digital currency, EURC, on the Solana blockchain. The addition of EURC to Solana’s platform is set to provide new options for users and developers in the realm of digital currency transactions.
 

 
EURC is designed as a fully reserved, euro-backed stablecoin, aiming to facilitate global, instant settlement and 24/7 on-chain foreign exchange (FX) operations. Its launch on Solana, known for its high-speed and low-cost network, r…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Sencil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance and CZ to Pay Over $2.7 Billion in Fines to CFTC: Court Rules]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118627/Binance-and-CZ-to-Pay-Over-27-Billion-in-Fines-to-CFTC-Court-Rules</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118627/Binance-and-CZ-to-Pay-Over-27-Billion-in-Fines-to-CFTC-Court-Rules"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T07:32:51.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Is How Much Binance and CZ Will Actually Have to Pay to Settle With the CFTC]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118600/This-Is-How-Much-Binance-and-CZ-Will-Actually-Have-to-Pay-to-Settle-With-the-CFTC</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118600/This-Is-How-Much-Binance-and-CZ-Will-Actually-Have-to-Pay-to-Settle-With-the-CFTC"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T07:30:22.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friend Tech Releases V2 Teaser Trailer Amid Activity Slump]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118684/Friend-Tech-Releases-V2-Teaser-Trailer-Amid-Activity-Slump</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118684/Friend-Tech-Releases-V2-Teaser-Trailer-Amid-Activity-Slump"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T07:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Court Approves $2.7 Billion Settlement of Binance and Zhao with the CFTC]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748d5b2bd1</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/us-court-approves-27-billion-settlement-of-binance-and-zhao-with-the-cftc/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T07:08:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A United States court yesterday (Monday) entered an order against Binance and its former CEO, Changpeng Zhao, approving the massive settlement against the charges brought by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC).
“In formalizing the settlement initially announced on November 21, the court finds Zhao and Binance violated the Commodity Exchange Act (CEA) and CFTC regulations,” the CFTC wrote in a statement.
Hefty Monetary Fines
With the agreement of the US District Court for the Northern District of Illinois, Zhao will now pay a civil monetary penalty of $150 million, whereas three entities headed by him, Binance Holdings Limited, Binance Holdings (IE) Limited, and Binance (Services) Holdings Limited (together, Binance), will need to $1.35 billion of ill-gotten transaction fees, al…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arnab Shome</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Ending ‘Givecrypto’ Initiative — ‘We Were Unable to Create a Lasting Impact’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748d46cce5</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/coinbase-ending-givecrypto-initiative-we-were-unable-to-create-a-lasting-impact/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T06:36:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto exchange Coinbase is winding down Givecrypto, a nonprofit set up to provide crypto to those in need. “Over the years, Givecrypto distributed cryptocurrency to thousands of individuals in need,” Coinbase said. However, the exchange admitted: “We were unable to create lasting change purely through unconditional cash transfers.”
 

 
Coinbase Drops Givecrypto
 
Cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase (Nasdaq: COIN) announced Friday that it is winding down the Givecrypto initiative, a nonprofit funded by its CEO, Brian Armstrong, to provide crypto to those in need. The announcement details:
 

Despite the positive impact it has had, we were unable to create lasting change purely through unconditional cash transfers.
 
Givecrypto has been one of Coinbase’s charitable programs dedicated to “incr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche Users Shell Out Over $4M In Inscription Fees: A Five-Day Crypto Phenomenon]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748d42e172</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/avalanche-users-shell-out-over-4m-inscription-fees/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T06:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past five days, users of the Avalanche network have collectively paid more than $4 million in transaction fees. This significant expenditure is primarily attributed to creating and moving tokens and non-fungible tokens (NFTs) using inscriptions, a novel method gaining traction in the blockchain world.
 
Inscriptions have emerged as a creative bypass on networks like Bitcoin, which lack native token support. By embedding text in standard blockchain transactions and employing an external numbering system, these inscription-based tokens offer a unique approach to token creation and movement.
 
Initially developed for Bitcoin, their utility has extended to other blockchains such as Arbitrum, Polygon PoS, and so on, mainly due to the cost-effectiveness of transferring these tokens comp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Saga Phone Interest Soars Following BONK Meme Coin Surge]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748d4cb612</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/solana-saga-phone-interest-soars-following-bonk-meme-coin-surge/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T05:43:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fueled by the explosive growth of the BONK meme coin, the Solana Saga phone’s market interest has soared, with units selling for up to $5,000 on Ebay, far exceeding its reduced price of $599
 
Saga Phone Resurgence: BONK’s Rise Turns Solana Device Into Hot Commodity
 
The Solana Saga phone, once struggling to find its market, has seen its fortunes reversed this week, with units selling for as much as $5,000 on Ebay, a staggering increase from its discounted price earlier this summer. This dramatic shift in demand is primarily attributed to the explosive rise of the Solana-based meme coin, BONK, which experienced more than a 10,000% surge in the past two months.
 
The Saga phone, initially released earlier this year with a price tag of $1,000 and later reduced to $599, had faced disappointi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Sencil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock Revises Spot Bitcoin ETF Proposal Ahead of Rumored SEC Approvals]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748d4e630e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/12/19/blackrock-revises-spot-bitcoin-etf-proposal-ahead-of-rumored-sec-approvals/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T05:27:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Black Rock's ETF proposal now includes cash redemptions, a concession to the SEC that may improve the fund's approval odds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Napolitano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockstream CEO Says “JPEGs” On Bitcoin Will Force Innovation, What Happens Next?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748d4843b7</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/blockstream-ceo-jpegs-bitcoin-force-innovation/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T05:09:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adam Back, CEO of Blockstream, a blockchain firm developing the Lightning Network, a layer-2 solution for Bitcoin, believes that prohibiting non-fungible tokens on Bitcoin would be futile. Taking to X on Dec. 17, the CEO said those complaining “can’t stop JPEGs” on the world’s most valuable network, adding that those who try to stop them “will only do it in worse ways.”  
 
“JPEGs” Is Good: Will Force Innovation And Adoption Of Layer-2s
 
Central to Back’s arguments lies the recently rising cost of transacting on the mainnet. Though the most valuable, Bitcoin has remained unchanged, especially on throughput, for the last 15 years. Under light loads, Bitcoin can only process seven transactions every second (TPS), a concern considering its role in the sphere. 
 
 
Despite this flaw, Back arg…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dalmas Ngetich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Survey: 4 in 5 Institutional Investors Agree Crypto Has Important Role in Global Financial Industry]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748d35b3d2</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/survey-4-in-5-institutional-investors-agree-crypto-has-important-role-in-global-financial-industry/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T04:11:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An institutional investor survey conducted by digital asset bank Sygnum indicates a shift from skepticism to advocacy, “with over 80% now agreeing that crypto has an important role to play in the global financial industry,” said the bank’s digital asset research manager. “It’s now truly becoming a trusted gateway that is rapidly transforming the economic landscape.”
 

 
Sygnum’s Institutional Investor Survey
 
Digital asset bank Sygnum launched its inaugural institutional crypto market report last week. The report, titled “Future Finance 23,” features an institutional investor survey the bank conducted at the beginning of Q4 with more than 150 respondents possessing an average of over 10 years of investment experience. They included Sygnum’s institutional client base and equity investors,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple CEO Calls For Industry Collaboration To Support Pro-Crypto Candidates In 2024 US Election]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748d35e255</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ripple-ceo-calls-support-pro-crypto-2024-us-elect/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T04:09:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a year marked by regulatory pressure on the crypto industry, Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse has renewed his call for industry cohesion to rally behind pro-crypto candidates in the upcoming 2024 US presidential election. 
 
Garlinghouse emphasizes the urgent need to counter the anti-crypto and anti-innovation stance the Biden administration took, particularly about blockchain technology. Ripple CEO believes supporting candidates who champion innovation and responsible regulation is crucial to avoid falling behind on the global stage.
 
Ripple CEO Calls For Industry Unity
 
Garlinghouse took to X (formerly Twitter) to assert Ripple’s commitment to lead the charge alongside other industry leaders in endorsing pro-innovation and pro-crypto candidates. 
 
Ripple’s CEO highlights the negative i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quant Reveals The Indicator That Predicted Bitcoin Top In Advance]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748d3c2424</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/quant-indicator-predicted-bitcoin-top-advance/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T03:01:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An analyst has revealed a pattern in a Bitcoin indicator that may have signaled the cryptocurrency’s recent decline in advance.
 
Bitcoin Taker Buy Sell Ratio 100-Day EMA Has Seen Rejection From 1.0 Recently
 
In a CryptoQuant Quicktake post, an analyst explained a relationship between the BTC spot price and the 365-day moving average (MA) and 100-day exponential moving average (EMA) of the Taker Buy Sell Ratio.
 
The “Taker Buy Sell Ratio” here refers to an indicator that keeps track of the ratio between the taker buy and taker sell volumes of Bitcoin on all derivative exchanges.
 
When the value of this metric is greater than 1, it means that the taker buy volume is greater than the taker sell volume right now. Such a trend implies the majority sentiment in the sector is currently bullis…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Expected to Approve Multiple Spot Bitcoin ETFs in One Day, Says Vaneck CEO]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748d3ecfcd</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/sec-expected-to-approve-multiple-spot-bitcoin-etfs-in-one-day-says-vanceck-ceo/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T02:32:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CEO of asset management firm Vaneck expects the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to approve multiple spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) applications in one day. “I very much expect it will be all in one day because that’s what happened with the ethereum futures,” he explained.
 
Vaneck’s CEO on Spot Bitcoin ETF Approvals
 

 
Jan van Eck, the CEO of asset management firm Vaneck, shared his bitcoin outlook and expectations around spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) in an interview with CNBC on Friday. Vaneck is among the asset managers that have applied to launch a spot bitcoin ETF with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).
 

 
“I think bitcoin is the obvious asset that is growing up in front of our eyes,” the executive began, adding: “There are 50 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple And Coinbase Power Play: $78M Into 2024 Election Influence]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748d398ada</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ripple-coinbase-78m-into-2024-election-influence/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T02:02:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a striking display of financial muscle, cryptocurrency companies, such as Ripple and Coinbase, and investors have collectively contributed $78 million to super Political Action Committees (PACs) focused on shaping the 2024 US elections. This substantial sum underscores the crypto industry’s intensified efforts to sway political tides favoring digital asset-friendly policies.
 
 
Ripple And Others Rally Behind Pro-Crypto Super PACs
 
Influential players like venture capital behemoth Andreessen Horowitz, US cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase, Ripple, and the Winklevoss twins Cameron and Tyler are leading the charge. Their backing marks a significant revival of the crypto industry’s political operations, especially following the fall of previous crypto megadonor Sam Bankman-Fried.
 
As repor…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reynaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Franklin Templeton’s Executive Expects All Nations to Hold Bitcoin — ‘Every Country Is Going to Have to Hold Some Reserves’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748d251614</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/franklin-templetons-executive-expects-all-nations-to-hold-bitcoin-every-country-is-going-to-have-to-hold-some-reserves/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T01:23:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An executive at trillion-dollar asset manager firm Franklin Templeton expects bitcoin to become “something that every treasury needs to hold.” She believes that “every country is going to have to hold some reserves,” emphasizing that the cryptocurrency is “working its way increasingly into the traditional banking ecosystem as just a foundational part of that system.”
 
Kaul: Bitcoin Could Be Used as Base Unit of International Trade
 
Franklin Templeton’s senior vice president and head of Digital Asset and Industry Advisory Services, Sandy Kaul, discussed the future outlook for bitcoin in an interview with Natalie Brunell, published Thursday. Before joining Franklin Templeton, Kaul held positions at Shearson Lehman Brothers, Citi, and Goldman Sachs Asset Management.
 
A global leader in inv…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Small ESG-Focused Crypto Asset Manager Is Another Late Entrant to Bitcoin ETF Race]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748d210596</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/12/19/small-esg-focused-crypto-asset-manager-is-another-late-entrant-to-bitcoin-etf-race/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T00:41:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A small ESG-focused crypto asset manager, 7RCC, is the latest applicant to join the race for a spot-bitcoin exchange traded fund (ETF), a filing with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) shows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Spot Bitcoin ETF Effect: Analysts Predict ‘Bloodbath’ Impact On Crypto Trading Platforms]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748d221804</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/spot-bitcoin-etf-effect-analysts-predict-bloodbath/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T00:30:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Industry analysts Nate Geraci, President of The ETF Store, and Eric Balchunas, a prominent Bloomberg Exchange Traded Fund (ETF) analyst, have recently spotlighted a potential game-changer in the crypto world: introducing a spot Bitcoin ETF in the United States.
 
According to their analysis, this development could bring benefits and notable challenges, particularly for established crypto exchanges such as Coinbase.
 
The duo’s insights, shared on X, paint a picture of a changing market dynamics. Geraci’s post highlighted the potential impact of a spot Bitcoin ETF, which he describes as a “bloodbath” for crypto exchanges.
 
 
Their argument hinges on transaction fees – a critical revenue stream for platforms like Coinbase.
 
 
Gonna be a bloodbath for crypto exchanges…
 
— Nate Geraci (@Nat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Tax Planning: Merging Tax-Loss Harvesting With Charitable Giving]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748d22f43b</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/crypto-tax-planning-merging-tax-loss-harvesting-with-charitable-giving/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T00:21:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the year winds down, cryptocurrency investors can combine tax-loss harvesting with cryptocurrency donations to charities, a move that optimizes tax benefits while supporting worthy causes.
 
Embrace Year-End Tax Strategy With Charitable Giving Twist
 

 
As the end of the year rapidly approaches, crypto investors are not only focusing on tax-loss harvesting but also exploring the benefits of charitable contributions in cryptocurrency. This strategic approach allows investors to potentially reduce their tax liabilities while supporting charitable causes.
 

 
The concept of tax-loss harvesting in the crypto realm involves selling digital assets at a loss to offset capital gains taxes. This method can be particularly advantageous given the volatility and potential for significant price fl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Sencil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitter Faces EU Inquiry Over Failing to Moderate Illegal Content and Disinformation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210217</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210217/twitter-faces-eu-inquiry-over-failing-to-moderate-illegal-content-and-disinformation"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T00:07:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first-of-its-kind investigation will review whether Twitter did what it said it would do about Israel-Palestine content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gianluigi Buffon Invests in OQtima, Signaling a Shift in Sports-Finance Collaborations]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748d2cda63</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/gianluigi-buffon-invests-in-oqtima-signaling-a-shift-in-sports-finance-collaborations/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T00:02:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. Renowned Italian football goalkeeper Gianluigi Buffon has recently confirmed his strategic investment in OQtima, an innovative online trading company, marking a significant departure from traditional sponsorship deals.
 
Buffon’s active involvement in OQtima signifies a profound collaboration between the realms of professional sports and financial trading platforms. This move establishes a new era where sports legends become not only brand ambassadors but key stakeholders and strategic partners in the financial sector, thereby revolutionizing the landscape of partnerships.
 
A New Age For Partnerships
 
In a groundbreaking development at the crossroads of finance and sports, partnerships between online trading platforms, cryptocurrency exchanges, and sports icons are undergo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ubisoft's 'Champions Tactics' Ethereum NFTs Generate Millions After Free Mint]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210213</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210213/ubisoft-champions-tactics-ethereum-nfts-generate-millions-after-free-mint"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T23:42:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following a drop that minted out in under 20 minutes, Ubisoft’s Warlords NFTs for Champions Tactics are reselling for $600 or more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Lead Dev Reflects On New Partnership To Drive Global Adoption]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748d2ae642</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-dev-global-adoption/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T23:02:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Shiba Inu team seems to be hard at work over the last few months and the latest development has been a special announcement teased by lead developer Shytoshi Kusama. Kusama first mentioned the announcement last week where he said that it would be ‘game-changing’ and Shiba Inu marketing lead Lucie said it would break the internet. As the community tentatively anticipates this announcement, Kusama has shared more insight into the partnership and why they’re doing it.
 
Promoting The Worldwide Adoption Of Shiba Inu
 
In a December 16 thread post on X (formerly Twitter), developer Kusama said that he was looking forward to the announcement which is supposed to happen this week. However, the post didn’t only focus on the announcement as Kusama also alluded to the SHIB burns that the team is…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Best Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK Builds Digital Securities Sandbox to Test New Technolgies]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210202</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210202/uk-builds-digital-securities-sandbox-to-test-new-technolgies"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T22:46:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The setup aims to house controlled testing of blockchain and other emerging infrastructure technologies before wider deployment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Game 'Aurory' Suffers $830K Exploit, Disables Arbitrum Bridge]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210153</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210153/solana-game-aurory-suffers-830k-exploit-disables-arbitrum-bridge"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T22:30:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An exploit on Aurory's marketplace led to one user siphoning about 600,000 AURY tokens. The game's bridge is down while devs work on a fix.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitwise Is First to Bitcoin ETF Ad Race With ‘Most Interesting Man in the World’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210186</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210186/bitwise-firstbitcoin-etf-ad-with-most-interesting-man-in-the-world"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T22:05:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The message: "Bitwise Is Interesting.” It stars Jonathan Goldsmith, well-known for portraying “The Most Interesting Man in the World” in beer ads.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Fees Continue to Surge Thanks to Ordinal Mania]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210168</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210168/bitcoin-fees-continue-to-surge-thanks-to-ordinal-mania"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T22:01:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s again very expensive to make a transaction on Bitcoin’s blockchain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Next BONK? Solana Meme Coin Dogwifhat Pumps 2,000X in a Month]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210151</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210151/next-bonk-solana-meme-coin-dogwifhat-pumps-2000x-month"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T20:04:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s a dog. With a hat. And the Solana token based on the dogwifhat meme is the latest to surge in value after BONK's boom.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Funds See 'Profit-Taking' Dip, But Investors Still Like Solana]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210155</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210155/bitcoin-funds-see-profit-taking-dip-but-investors-still-like-solana"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T19:16:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana and other altcoin funds saw $21 million deposited last week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Helium Tokens Surge Amid Network Expansion, Solana Saga BONK Mania]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210147</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210147/helium-tokens-surge-amid-network-expansion-solana-saga-bonk-mania"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T14:04:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following Helium's nationwide U.S. rollout, the Solana-based tokens powering the decentralized 5G network have surged.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Slips Below $41,000 as Crypto Price Rally Cools]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210131</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210131/bitcoin-slips-below-41000-as-crypto-price-rally-cools"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T10:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price slump comes as Bitcoin's average transaction fee has surged to a yearly high, driven by the growing popularity of Ordinals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week on Crypto Twitter: BONK Simply Won’t Quit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210073</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210073/this-week-on-crypto-twitter-bonk-simply-wont-quit"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T10:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ever-ascendant Solana meme coin dominated Twitter discourse for yet another week, as inscriptions hobbled traffic on multiple layer 2 networks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Biggest Games Coming Out in 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210052</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210052/biggest-games-coming-out-nintendo-playstation-xbox-pc"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From Final Fantasy VII Rebirth to Star Wars Outlaws and plenty in between, these are our most anticipated games of 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Bonk Continues Surge With Solana Hype, Bitcoin Dips]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210009</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210009/this-week-in-coins-bonk-continues-surge-with-solana-hype-bitcoin-dips"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T10:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin and other major coins and tokens are down. But new meme coin BONK is still rallying.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Voice Generating Startup Resemble AI Promises to Restore Old Audio]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210063</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210063/resemble-ai-voice-enhance-recordings"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T01:34:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An AI startup has built a tool that it says can make low-fidelity speech recordings sound like new.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not That Grok: Musician Grimes and OpenAI Launch Plush Toy with AI Inside]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210024</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210024/grok-ai-twitter-toy-elon-musk-grimes-trademark"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T22:36:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk’s ex partners with Curio to launch a line of AI-powered toys designed to cut back on screen time and enhance interaction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jupiter Airdrop Set for January With a Billion JUP for Solana DeFi Users]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210017</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210017/jupiter-airdrop-set-january-billion-jup-solana-defi-users"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T22:10:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Half of the 10 billion JUP supply will ultimately go to the Jupiter community, with 10% landing in Solana wallets during the first airdrop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Weighs Demand for Saga Phones After Sellout Amid BONK Boom]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210036</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210036/solana-weighs-demand-saga-phones-after-sellout-amid-bonk-boom"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T21:51:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Saga is sold out in the U.S. and EU supplies are nearly tapped out. Solana Labs told Decrypt how it’s assessing next moves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Tech Giant Alibaba Unveils New AI Video Tool]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210018</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210018/alibaba-ai-text-to-video-generative-cloud"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T21:07:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alibaba says its I2VGen-XL model can handle “visualization, sampling, training, inference, join training using images and videos, acceleration, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitch Walks Back Changes After Surge in Nudity: 'We Went Too Far']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209998</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209998/twitch-walks-back-changes-after-surge-nudity-went-too-far"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T19:37:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, Twitch announced it would allow artistic nudity. Now, it’s blocked again, in part because of concerns around AI realism.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Plans to Challenge SEC Denial of Crypto Rulemaking Petition]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209997</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209997/coinbase-plans-challenge-sec-denial-crypto-rulemaking"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T18:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC today denied crypto exchange Coinbase's petition to clarify new crypto rules for the digital assets industry. Coinbase isn't taking "no" for an answer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Scaler Arbitrum Suffers Outage—And Inscriptions Are to Blame]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209996</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209996/ethereum-scaler-arbitrum-suffers-outage-inscriptions-blame"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T18:12:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arbitrum and other chains have recently been bombarded by users making "inscriptions" as on Bitcoin, even though such networks support NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gary Gensler: SEC 'Taking a New Look' at Bitcoin ETF Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209964</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209964/gary-gensler-sec-taking-new-look-bitcoin-etf-applications"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T16:06:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC chair stated that the regulator is reviewing spot Bitcoin ETF applications in light of a recent court ruling.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BONK Spikes 101% Amid Solana Saga Sales Frenzy to Claim Airdrop]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209966</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209966/bonk-spikes-101-amid-solana-saga-sales-frenzy-to-claim-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T15:40:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana-based meme coin BONK has continued to soar in value and hit new all-time highs—and the Saga smartphone is an unexpected beneficiary.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SocialFi Startup Reach Aims to Improve Crypto Twitter With Anti-Bot Protocol]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209903</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209903/socialfi-reach-crypto-twitter-anti-bot-protocol-token"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T15:01:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest addition to the "point" meta seeks to address the challenges of Crypto Twitter with the support of Seedphrase, Pranksy, Gmoney, and Zeneca.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SafeMoon Files for Bankruptcy, SFM Token Crashes 50% to All-Time Low]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209951</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209951/safemoon-files-for-bankruptcy-sfm-token-crashes-50-to-all-time-low"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T10:08:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Chapter 7 bankruptcy filing comes after SafeMoon's founders were indicted by the DOJ for a "multi-million dollar international fraud scheme."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Casio Drops Virtual G-Shock Watches as Ethereum NFTs—With Exclusive Perks]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209939</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209939/casio-drops-virtual-g-shock-watches-ethereum-nfts-exclusive-perks"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T03:02:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The G-Shock watch brand debuts a pair of fantastical digital designs on Ethereum, with a variety of special benefits for holders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vatican Says AI Is the ‘Highest-Stakes Gamble of Our Future’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209925</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209925/pope-declares-ai-the-highest-stakes-gamble-of-our-future"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T00:46:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pope Francis urged global leaders to work together to adopt a binding international treaty that regulates AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grindr Dating App Adds an AI ‘Wingman’ to Help Users Find Love]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209919</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209919/grindr-dating-app-adds-an-ai-wingman-to-help-users-find-love"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T00:18:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“If you’re not first to market with something in AI, you’re going to miss out," says Grindr CEO George Arison.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Devs Got a BONK Airdrop Worth $300 Last Christmas—It's Now Worth $500,000]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209906</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209906/solana-devs-bonk-airdrop-worth-300-last-christmas-now-worth-500000"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T23:01:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers in LamportDAO received a gift of billions of BONK last year. It helped some pay rent—and others get crypto-rich (maybe).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Instagram Adds Generative AI That Swaps Image Backgrounds]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209868</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209868/instagram-adds-generative-ai-that-swaps-image-backgrounds"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T21:59:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The green screen-like Backdrop feature lets users replace their messy kitchens with lush tropical forests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Native Bitcoin Staking on Ethereum and Solana Could Soon Be a Reality]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209867</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209867/native-bitcoin-staking-ethereum-solana-soon-reality-babylon"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T21:24:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto startup Babylon says it's developed a way to stake Bitcoin on any proof-of-stake blockchain. Here's how it works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana DeFi Hacker Pleads Guilty in First-Ever Smart Contract Fraud Conviction]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209859</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209859/solana-defi-hacker-pleads-guilty-smart-contract-fraud-conviction"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T21:01:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's the "first ever conviction for such a hack,” according to the DOJ. The hacker will be sentenced in March.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Did Michael Cohen Let AI Write His Legal Briefs?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209869</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209869/did-michael-cohen-let-ai-write-his-legal-briefs"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T20:53:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cohen's attorneys must prove the existence of cases they cited as speculation swirls around potential AI-generated content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emerge 2023 Project of the Year: OpenAI ChatGPT 3.5]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209784</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209784/emerge-2023-project-of-the-year-openai-chatgpt"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T19:37:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In barely over a year, ChatGPT rocketed from obscure, largely academic roots to the embodiment of a global revolution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Kawailani Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana's BONK Becomes 69th Largest Coin as Market Cap Tops $1 Billion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209850</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209850/solanas-bonk-69th-largest-coin-market-cap-tops-1-billion"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T18:55:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BONK continues its recent boom with a 64% surge on the day, landing in the meme-friendly #69 spot on CoinGecko’s market ranking.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Farcana Raises $10 Million for NFT Esports Shooter That Pays Out Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209817</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209817/farcana-raiases-10-million-nft-esports-shooter-pays-out-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T18:36:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Exclusive: The sci-fi, team-based hero shooter Farcana is still in early development. Now, it has a fresh round of capital to tap into.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a Single Phishing Link Unleashed Chaos on Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209838</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209838/single-phishing-link-unleashed-chaos-on-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T18:14:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ledger has confirmed the attack began because “a former Ledger employee fell victim to a phishing attack.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating peaceful money & taking over your local government w/ Joseph Schiarizzi]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zb0VG27G/creating-peaceful-money-taking-over-your-local-government-w-joseph-schiarizzi</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zb0VG27G/creating-peaceful-money-taking-over-your-local-government-w-joseph-schiarizzi"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T23:23:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week our host Reza Jafery is joined by Joseph Schiarizzi, founder of OpenDollar and prolific solidity developer. 


We discuss: 
- Onchain beer
- Taking over your local government
- His Emmy and 3 patents?!?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INTERVIEW: Ember Sword CEO Says NFT Games Are More 'Transparent']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/M9OHCVpA/interview-ember-sword-ceo-says-nft-games-are-more-transparent</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/M9OHCVpA/interview-ember-sword-ceo-says-nft-games-are-more-transparent"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T21:58:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ember Sword CEO Mark Laursen shares why some big game studios "irk" him—and why he got into game development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Director Jordan Bayne on the State of Film3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZLoEDkL9/director-jordan-bayne-on-the-state-of-film3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZLoEDkL9/director-jordan-bayne-on-the-state-of-film3"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T00:11:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the 2023 Film3 Summit, Jordan Bayne—director and founder of The Squad—spoke with Decrypt's Sander Lutz about how the Film3 world has progressed over the last year and what decentralized technologies can offer to creators that want to buck the Hollywood system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Questions With SCENE: Phil Mohun]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TwOjXfOR/5-questions-with-scene-phil-mohun</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TwOjXfOR/5-questions-with-scene-phil-mohun"/>
        <updated>2023-12-01T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bright Moments co-founder Phil Mohun joins 5 Questions With SCENE to recount some favorite moments from the road, including negotiating with Patagonian gauchos, falling in love with Tokyo, and gaining a newfound appreciation for shrooms chocolate bars.

Shot and edited by Vincent Roazzi Jr.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are NFTs Ever Coming Back?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qLmFpNKE/are-nfts-ever-coming-back</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qLmFpNKE/are-nfts-ever-coming-back"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T18:38:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this weeks episode we sit down with Cashtro from Arcade.xyz to discuss NFTs, shitcoins, what collections have held onto their floor prices, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Summit: Will Web3 Gaming Ever be Mainstream?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OvVWhGbW/web-summit-will-web3-gaming-ever-be-mainstream</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OvVWhGbW/web-summit-will-web3-gaming-ever-be-mainstream"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T19:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animoca Brands CEO Robby Yung, EndeavorXR CEO Amy Peck and Gamee co-founder CEO Bozena Rezab joined Decrypt's Stephen Graves on stage at Web Summit to talk about the future of Web3 gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Allie Eve Knox on Spankchain and the life of a Crypto Financial Dominatrix]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/16rVeg6o/allie-eve-knox-on-spankchain-and-the-life-of-a-crypto-financial-dominatrix</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/16rVeg6o/allie-eve-knox-on-spankchain-and-the-life-of-a-crypto-financial-dominatrix"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T21:20:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the first IRL episode of This Time Will Be Different!

In this week's episode, our host, Reza Jafery, is joined by Allie Eve Knox, the Spankchain Chief of Staff and FinDomme. 

They discuss
- How to sell feet pics
- If crypto is really as permissionless as it seems
- the intersections between crypto and sex work]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>