<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-01-03T08:18:52.805Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-01-03T08:18:52.805Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Macro Guru Lyn Alden Says $100,000 Bitcoin Would Be Disappointing for Bull Market Cycle – Here’s Her Target]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19146955/Macro-Guru-Lyn-Alden-Says-100000-Bitcoin-Would-Be-Disappointing-for-Bull-Market-Cycle-Heres-Her-Target</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19146955/Macro-Guru-Lyn-Alden-Says-100000-Bitcoin-Would-Be-Disappointing-for-Bull-Market-Cycle-Heres-Her-Target"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T08:04:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Popular macro expert Lyn Alden believes that a peak of $100,000 for Bitcoin (BTC) during the next market expansion would be an underwhelming outcome. In a new interview on the What Bitcoin Did podcast, Alden says that the rise or fall of global liquidity is a solid indicator of Bitcoin’s cycles....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple revolutionizes cross-border transactions in the IT sector]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19146951/Ripple-revolutionizes-cross-border-transactions-in-the-IT-sector</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19146951/Ripple-revolutionizes-cross-border-transactions-in-the-IT-sector"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T08:04:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Labs, a leading blockchain technology company, has recently published a comprehensive guide titled “Accelerating Global Payments for Your IT Services Business,” aimed at shedding light on the potential integration of blockchain technology in the IT sector.  This guide also highlights the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Etherscan acquires Solana block explorer Solscan amid SOL rally]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19146918/Etherscan-acquires-Solana-block-explorer-Solscan-amid-SOL-rally</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19146918/Etherscan-acquires-Solana-block-explorer-Solscan-amid-SOL-rally"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T07:45:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Etherscan said its Solscan acquisition was a “collaborative merging” to help the firm expand its blockchain data services across multiple networks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Meme Coins BONK, SHIB, PEPE Opened the 2024 Trading Week]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19146924/How-Meme-Coins-BONK-SHIB-PEPE-Opened-the-2024-Trading-Week</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19146924/How-Meme-Coins-BONK-SHIB-PEPE-Opened-the-2024-Trading-Week"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T07:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meme coins registered tremendous price rallies in the last month of the 2023 trading year. One such crypto asset was Solana-based dog-themed Bonk [BONK], whose value climbed by over 250% during the 31-day period, according to data from Coingecko. Other coins, such as Pepe [PEPE] and Shiba Inu...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Executive with $500 Million Wealth Reveals He Sold Bitcoin, Explains Why]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19146926/Executive-with-500-Million-Wealth-Reveals-He-Sold-Bitcoin-Explains-Why</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19146926/Executive-with-500-Million-Wealth-Reveals-He-Sold-Bitcoin-Explains-Why"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T07:43:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Steve Weiss, who has a fortune of $ 500 million, announced that he sold half of his Bitcoin assets and explained why. Continue Reading: Executive with $500 Million Wealth Reveals He Sold Bitcoin, Explains Why]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘You Can’t Kill Bitcoin,’ Jim Cramer Flips Bullish on Crypto (Again)]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19146888/You-Cant-Kill-Bitcoin-Jim-Cramer-Flips-Bullish-on-Crypto-Again</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19146888/You-Cant-Kill-Bitcoin-Jim-Cramer-Flips-Bullish-on-Crypto-Again"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T07:31:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[American television personality and former hedge fund manager Jim Cramer has changed his stance towards crypto and Bitcoin yet again. In a flip to a more bullish perspective, he may have just jinxed the rally that has seen BTC hit its highest price for almost two years. CNBC’s “Mad Money” host...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin BRC-20 standard faces debate over UniSat Wallet’s proposed split]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19146877/Bitcoin-BRC-20-standard-faces-debate-over-UniSat-Wallets-proposed-split</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19146877/Bitcoin-BRC-20-standard-faces-debate-over-UniSat-Wallets-proposed-split"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T07:28:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On January 2nd, prominent X (formerly Twitter) user Domo, the creator of the Bitcoin BRC-20 token standard, expressed strong opposition to an upcoming fork proposed by UniSat Wallet. This move has ignited a debate within the cryptocurrency community, with Domo raising concerns about the rushed...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spot Bitcoin ETFs Will Boost Institutional Investment: CBOE Predicts]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19146883/Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-Will-Boost-Institutional-Investment-CBOE-Predicts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19146883/Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-Will-Boost-Institutional-Investment-CBOE-Predicts"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T07:28:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CBOE predicts spot Bitcoin ETF approval to attract major institutional investors, with key SEC decision due Jan. 10.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global Concerns Mount Over AI Ethics and Regulation Amidst Technological Advancements]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19146878/Global-Concerns-Mount-Over-AI-Ethics-and-Regulation-Amidst-Technological-Advancements</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19146878/Global-Concerns-Mount-Over-AI-Ethics-and-Regulation-Amidst-Technological-Advancements"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T07:27:50.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Etherscan acquires Solscan to expand blockchain data services]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19146868/Etherscan-acquires-Solscan-to-expand-blockchain-data-services</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19146868/Etherscan-acquires-Solscan-to-expand-blockchain-data-services"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T07:16:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The block explorer plans to integrate useful features across Etherscan and Solscan to offer enhanced support.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Enhances IT Sector’s Cross-Border Transactions: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19146872/Ripple-Enhances-IT-Sectors-Cross-Border-Transactions-Report</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19146872/Ripple-Enhances-IT-Sectors-Cross-Border-Transactions-Report"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T07:12:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Labs published a guide entitled “Accelerating Global Payments for Your IT Services Business,” providing insights on the potential IT- blockchain integration. The paper also sheds light on the key advantages of blockchain-powered payments through Ripple’s payment solution, Ripple Payments....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Daily Roundup 03 Jan: Market Resets as Daily Gains Disappear]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19146851/Crypto-Daily-Roundup-03-Jan-Market-Resets-as-Daily-Gains-Disappear</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19146851/Crypto-Daily-Roundup-03-Jan-Market-Resets-as-Daily-Gains-Disappear"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T07:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jim Cramer Changes Tune On Bitcoin Amid Price Surge: ‘You Can’t Kill It’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7485a36399</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/jim-cramer-on-bitcoin-you-cant-kill-it/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T07:09:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the price of bitcoin surged to 21-month highs Monday, “Mad Money” anchor Jim Cramer abruptly changed his perspective on digital assets, hailing it as an innovative and profitable investment.
 
Cramer said during his interview on CNBC that the recovery was impressive and had taken many by surprise, with the exception of those optimistic investors who proved to be right in their forecasts.
 
 
 
“This was a remarkable comeback that was unexpected, except for all the bulls who turned out to be right,” the former hedge fund manager said during the interview. 
 
Jim Cramer Says You Can’t Kill Bitcoin
 
Cramer declared Bitcoin a powerful force, emphatically stating “This thing, you can’t kill it.” He further lauded it as a “technological marvel” deserving of recognition as a permanent fixture…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jim Cramer Changes Tune On Bitcoin Amid Price Surge: ‘You Can’t Kill It’]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19146836/Jim-Cramer-Changes-Tune-On-Bitcoin-Amid-Price-Surge-You-Cant-Kill-It</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19146836/Jim-Cramer-Changes-Tune-On-Bitcoin-Amid-Price-Surge-You-Cant-Kill-It"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T07:06:47.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden-Backed Bill Triggers IRS Reporting For $10K+ Crypto Transactions In 2024 — Coin Center Responds]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19146863/Biden-Backed-Bill-Triggers-IRS-Reporting-For-10K-Crypto-Transactions-In-2024-Coin-Center-Responds</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19146863/Biden-Backed-Bill-Triggers-IRS-Reporting-For-10K-Crypto-Transactions-In-2024-Coin-Center-Responds"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T07:04:38.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF issuers set fees as approval hopes rise]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19146841/Bitcoin-ETF-issuers-set-fees-as-approval-hopes-rise</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19146841/Bitcoin-ETF-issuers-set-fees-as-approval-hopes-rise"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T07:03:40.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Legal Tech Startup Secures $26 Million in Series B Funding to Propel AI Contract Automation]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19146842/Legal-Tech-Startup-Secures-26-Million-in-Series-B-Funding-to-Propel-AI-Contract-Automation</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19146842/Legal-Tech-Startup-Secures-26-Million-in-Series-B-Funding-to-Propel-AI-Contract-Automation"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T07:03:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robin AI, a legal tech startup founded in 2019 by Richard Robinson, a lawyer at Clifford Chance, and James Clough, a machine learning research scientist at Imperial College, has successfully raised $26 million in Series B funding, with Temasek, a prominent Singaporean global investment company,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Dogecoin Killer' Shiba Inu Burn Rate Spikes 300% As 12M SHIB Permanently Destroyed In A Single Day]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19146837/Dogecoin-Killer-Shiba-Inu-Burn-Rate-Spikes-300-As-12M-SHIB-Permanently-Destroyed-In-A-Single-Day</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19146837/Dogecoin-Killer-Shiba-Inu-Burn-Rate-Spikes-300-As-12M-SHIB-Permanently-Destroyed-In-A-Single-Day"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T06:51:03.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Exchange Binance Announces That It Will Support Network Upgrades and Hard Forks of These Altcoins!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19146806/Bitcoin-Exchange-Binance-Announces-That-It-Will-Support-Network-Upgrades-and-Hard-Forks-of-These-Altcoins</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19146806/Bitcoin-Exchange-Binance-Announces-That-It-Will-Support-Network-Upgrades-and-Hard-Forks-of-These-Altcoins"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T06:41:06.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ordinals Founder Casey Rodarmor Warns Bitcoin Maxis That ‘Whining’ Makes Them ‘Look Weak’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7485ae6fbb</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ordinals-founder-casey-rodarmor-warns-bitcoin-maxis-that-whining-makes-them-look-weak/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T06:37:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Casey Rodarmor, the developer of the Ordinals protocol, has called out ideological Bitcoin maxis for their views on inscriptions and censoring transactions on the Bitcoin blockchain. Rodarmor stated that the “whining” around the protocol and its usage of block space make them “look weak,” contradicting the idea that Bitcoin is “unstoppable internet money.”
Ordinals Dev Casey Rodarmor Blasts Bitcoin Maxis ‘Whining’
Casey Rodarmor, the developer of the Ordinals protocol, which enables the possibility of issuing inscriptions, media embedded directly on the Bitcoin blockchain, has called out Bitcoin maxis for its complaints.
In a recent blog post, Rodarmor explained that the philosophy of the so-called Bitcoin maxis was incompatible with their beliefs, making them “look weak” with their “whini…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CBOE predicts approval of spot Bitcoin ETF will attract institutional investors]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19146777/CBOE-predicts-approval-of-spot-Bitcoin-ETF-will-attract-institutional-investors</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19146777/CBOE-predicts-approval-of-spot-Bitcoin-ETF-will-attract-institutional-investors"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T06:35:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Chicago Board Options Exchange (CBOE) Digital president, John Palmer, has expressed optimism about the potential approval of a spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) and its impact on the cryptocurrency market. Palmer said this approval could usher in a new era of institutional and retail...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI in Healthcare: Americans Trust AI for Diagnoses and Treatment Recommendations]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19146763/AI-in-Healthcare-Americans-Trust-AI-for-Diagnoses-and-Treatment-Recommendations</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19146763/AI-in-Healthcare-Americans-Trust-AI-for-Diagnoses-and-Treatment-Recommendations"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T06:27:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Americans are increasingly turning to Artificial Intelligence (AI) for healthcare insights, diagnoses, and treatment recommendations. A recent study of 2,000 American adults conducted by UserTesting revealed that 52% of respondents had sought assistance from large language models (LLMs) like...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jim Cramer: Bitcoin Can’t Be Killed — It’s a Technological Marvel That Is Here to Stay]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7485968752</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/jim-cramer-bitcoin-cant-be-killed-its-a-technological-marvel-that-is-here-to-stay/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T05:08:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jim Cramer, the host of CNBC’s Mad Money show, has made some bullish statements regarding Bitcoin. Noting that the crypto cannot be killed, he emphasized: “It’s a technological marvel, and people have to start recognizing that it’s here to stay.” He further stated that the late Charlie Munger, Warren Buffett’s former right-hand man, was wrong about bitcoin.
 
Jim Cramer on Bitcoin: ‘You Can’t Kill It’
 

 
Mad Money host Jim Cramer, who has outwardly expressed his skepticism about bitcoin and the crypto industry over the past years, made some bullish statements on CNBC Tuesday regarding bitcoin. Cramer is a former hedge fund manager who co-founded Thestreet.com, a financial news and literacy website.
 

 
Commenting on Tuesday’s bitcoin price surge and the looming decision on spot exchange…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Filing Reveals Morgan Stanley Opportunity Fund’s Potential $140 Million Bitcoin Move]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748596b40d</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/morgan-stanley-potential-140-million-bitcoin-move/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T05:06:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the anticipation for the potential approval of Bitcoin (BTC) spot exchange-traded funds (ETFs) applications in the United States by regulators intensifies, institutions such as Morgan Stanley are gearing up for what could be a game-changer not just for Bitcoin but for the entire crypto industry. 
 
In line with these developments, evidence suggests that Morgan Stanley has filed a new N-CSR (annual shareholder report) for its traded Morgan Stanley Opportunity Fund, with new text allowing for a potential 25% allocation of the fund to Bitcoin through the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC).
 
Morgan Stanley Seeks Bitcoin Potential 
 
According to the report, the Fund has outlined its intention to invest up to $140 million of its total assets in a wholly-owned subsidiary called Europe Opportunit…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cracking The Crypto Tax Code: Pro-XRP Lawyer’s Vital Advice For Digital Currency Traders]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7485938f30</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/cracking-the-crypto-tax-code-pro-xrp-lawyers-advice/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T04:07:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jeremy Hogan, a respected lawyer in crypto, particularly the XRP community, recently shed light on the tax implications for crypto investors. In a recent post on X (formerly Twitter), Hogan highlighted the need for investors to understand the nuances of tax laws, particularly the contrast between short and long-term capital gains taxes.
 
Hogan’s guidance centers on a prevalent practice among crypto holders: the short-term reallocation of funds from one digital asset to another, including moves from XRP to alternative digital currency. He highlights the potential tax implications of such strategies, emphasizing how they could unintentionally result in increased tax burdens.
 
 
According to Hogan, engaging in activities like selling XRP only to buy it back later might interfere with eligib…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Crypto Tax Law Takes Effect in US: Transactions of $10,000 or More Must Be Reported to IRS Within 15 Days]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74859dd678</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/new-crypto-tax-law-takes-effect-in-us-transactions-of-10000-or-more-must-be-reported-to-irs-within-15-days/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T03:39:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new tax reporting law has entered into force in the U.S. Starting on Jan. 1, all Americans receiving $10,000 or more in crypto in the course of their trade or business must file a report with the Internal Revenue Service (IRS) within 15 days. “If you don’t file a report within 15 days of receiving the transaction, you could be found guilty of a felony offense,” Coin Center warned.
 
New Crypto Tax Law Takes Effect on Jan. 1
 

 
Effective Jan. 1, 2024, the Infrastructure Investment and Jobs Act, which passed in November 2021, requires “anyone who receives $10,000 or more in cryptocurrency in the course of their trade or business to make a report to the IRS about that transaction,” crypto policy advocate Coin Center explained in a blog post on Tuesday.
 

 
“The report must include, among…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock Delays $10 Million Bitcoin Purchase, New Date Unveiled]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748598654b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/blackrock-delays-10-million-bitcoin-purchase/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T03:08:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a move that aligns with the growing anticipation surrounding the potential approval of a Bitcoin spot exchange-traded fund (ETF) by the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), BlackRock, the world’s largest asset manager, had initially planned to purchase an impressive $10 million worth of BTC on January 3rd. However, recent reports indicate that Blackrock has now postponed this purchase.
 
BlackRock Adjusts Schedule For Bitcoin ETF Seeding
 
The SEC’s anticipated approval of a Bitcoin ETF has generated significant interest and speculation within the cryptocurrency market. 
 
To pave the way for the Bitcoin ETF launch, BlackRock’s affiliate, Seed Capital Investor, initially purchased Seed Shares on October 27, 2023. The Seed Shares consisted of 4,000 shares at a per-share price of …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Still Processing Spot Bitcoin ETF Paperwork, Report]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7485855590</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/sec-still-processing-spot-bitcoin-etf-paperwork/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T02:10:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anticipation of spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) approvals by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) remains high, but the securities regulator reportedly still has a lot of paperwork to go through. While some speculate on a late-week announcement, others expect it early next week as the Jan. 10 deadline approaches.
 
SEC Still Has Lots of Spot Bitcoin ETF Paperwork to Sort Through
 
Anticipation of an imminent decision by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) that could finally unlock the U.S. spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) market drove the price of bitcoin above $45,000 on Tuesday.
 
Bloomberg analyst James Seyffart shared on social media platform X details of spot bitcoin ETFs that the SEC is currently considering. “Here’s a view of the Cointucky D…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Not Increasing Gas Limit: Are They “Digging Their Own Grave”?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7485857111</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-not-increasing-gas-limit-digging-own-grave/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T02:08:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recent changes to Ethereum’s roadmap have drawn criticism from some in the community. Taking to X on January 2, Justin Bons, the founder of Cyber Capital, argues that removing the plan to increase layer-1 gas limits over time is a major misstep. 
 
Is Ethereum “Digging Its Own Grave”?
 
According to Bons, deciding not to pursue sharding and instead relying on layer-2 platforms like Arbitrum, Base, and OP Mainnet will “gradually see Ethereum dig their own grave.” 
 
 
The founder added that removing the phrase “increase layer-1 gas limits” entirely sends a clear signal to the market that “Ethereum is not scaling at all.” This decision, the founder continued, is a “punch to the gut for early adopters” who supported Ethereum based on the promise of scalability.
 
 
In Ethereum, the gas limit …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dalmas Ngetich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Powered Cybercrime Will Explode in 2024: CrowdStrike Executive]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211596</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211596/ai-powered-cybercrime-will-explode-in-2024-crowdstrike-executive"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T02:08:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security exec Shawn Henry says the capability of AI to deceive and misinform is coming of age just in time for the 2024 elections.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Midjourney Leaps into AI Video Creation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211583</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211583/midjourney-leaps-into-ai-video-creation"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T01:16:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AI image generator MidJourney will begin training its video model in the upcoming days and they expect to release a final product "in a few months"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Saylor Commences Plan to Sell $216M Worth of MicroStrategy Stock Options]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748582188e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2024/01/03/michael-saylor-commences-plan-to-sell-216m-worth-of-microstrategy-stock-options/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T01:12:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Saylor said in an earlier earnings call that he will use the proceedings to meet personal obligations and buy additional bitcoin to his personal account.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s When to Expect the Jupiter JUP Airdrop for Solana DeFi Users]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211576</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211576/heres-when-expect-jupiter-jup-airdrop-solana-defi-users"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T00:56:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jupiter’s airdrop draws nearer and nearer. Here’s when the Solana DEX aggregator plans to launch JUP to the community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Coinbase Premium Shoots Up: What It Says About $45,000 Break]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74858cf15b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-coinbase-premium-shoots-up-what-45000-break/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T00:39:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data shows the Bitcoin premium on Coinbase has shot up alongside the latest rally. Here’s what this suggests about the source of the surge.
 
Bitcoin Coinbase Premium Gap Has Become Highly Positive
 
As CryptoQuant Netherlands community manager Maartunn pointed out in a new post on X, the cryptocurrency’s price observed its latest break after the Coinbase Premium Gap started rising.
 
The “Coinbase Premium Gap” is an indicator that keeps track of the difference between the Bitcoin prices listed on cryptocurrency exchanges Coinbase and Binance.
 
 
When the value of this metric is positive, it means that the price listed on Coinbase is currently higher than on Binance. Such a trend implies that the buying pressure from the former users is greater than that of the latter (or the selling pres…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale Updates Spot Bitcoin ETF Application but Left out Some Key Information]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74858da0fa</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/grayscale-updates-spot-bitcoin-etf-application-but-left-out-some-key-information/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T00:31:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto asset management firm Grayscale Investments has updated its spot bitcoin ETF filing in hope of being included in the initial round of decisions by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). However, the firm has omitted some key information that the SEC reportedly wants included in the filing, which several other asset managers have disclosed, including details relating to authorized participants.
 
Grayscale Files 3rd Amendment to Spot Bitcoin ETF Filing
 
Most asset managers seeking to launch a spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) updated their applications with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) on Friday, which was the deadline given by the regulator for amended filings. Grayscale filed the third amendment to its S-3 filing to convert its bitcoin trust …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spot ETF Approvals Will See BTC Value Rising to $50,000 in January — Matrixport]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748574916f</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/spot-etf-approvals-will-see-btc-value-rising-to-50000-in-january-matrixport/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T23:14:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The expected approval of spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) applications by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission will see the top crypto asset’s price jumping to $50,000 in January, the latest market preview by Matrixport has predicted. The crypto financial services platform said the approval of ETFs, combined with bitcoin halving, will likely see the price of BTC rising to $125,000.
 
BTC Poised to Break out in Early 2024
 

 
Following its now common mid-to-end December consolidation, the USD price of bitcoin is “poised to break out on a robust beginning-of-the-year buying flow.” According to the latest Matrixport market preview, the crypto financial services platform foresees the top crypto asset’s price jumping to $50,000 in January.
 

 
Matrixport, like many of its peer…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open Source or OpenAI: What's the Best Path to Advanced AI?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211563</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211563/open-source-or-openai-whats-the-best-path-to-advanced-ai"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T23:11:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A long tweet went viral among AI enthusiasts, revisiting a decades-long debate over how AI will best evolve.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Machine Learning Algorithm Predicts Dogecoin Price For January 2024]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748575c2cd</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-price-january-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T23:01:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The future price of meme coins such as Dogecoin has always been of interest to crypto users, especially given their widespread popularity even among non-investors. There have been multiple predictions for where the DOGE price might be in 2024. And one of those predictions has been given by the machine learning algorithm at CoinCodex.
 
Dogecoin Outlook For January Is Bearish
 
The machine learning algorithm at CoinCodex has predicted where the Dogecoin price will be this January and it has been far from negative. Contrary to the calls for a rally for the meme coin, especially as the DOGE-1 space mission draws closer, the algorithm expects the price to fall rather than climb.
 
 
The one-month prediction from the machine learning algorithm puts the price of Dogecoin at $0.081. Now, taking i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Best Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Buckles 10% as Crypto Stocks Falter Despite Bitcoin Topping $45K]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7485764e65</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/01/02/coinbase-buckles-10-as-crypto-stocks-falter-despite-bitcoin-topping-45k/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T22:56:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The decline happened as bitcoin spiked above $45,000 during the day as traders anticipate an imminent spot BTC ETF decision in the U.S.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Traders Flock to Sei and Its Dragon Ball-Inspired Meme Coin—Will It Last?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211551</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211551/crypto-traders-flock-to-sei-and-its-dragon-ball-inspired-meme-coin-will-it-last"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T22:12:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Dragon Ball-themed SEIYAN meme coin has been gathering energy—and gains—on the Sei Network's Layer 1 blockchain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analyst Predicts 25% Flash Crash For Dogecoin, Here Are The Targets]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748573ad3b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/25-flash-crash-for-dogecoin/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T22:01:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin is still trading at a lower range than expected and this has triggered a wave of bearishness among investors. Despite previously breaking through the $0.1 level late last year, it was unable to maintain the bullish momentum, especially as indicators are turning quite bearish. In this vein, one crypto analyst has presented a bearish short-term for the asset which is still ranging through low levels.
 
Dogecoin Gearing Up For Massive 25% Crash
 
In an analysis posted on the TradingView website, crypto analyst Alan Santana has sounded a warning alarm for the Dogecoin price going forward. According to the analysis, there could be a massive crash ahead for the meme coin.
 
 
The chart shows that the Dogecoin price has been trending lower since it first crossed $0.1 in early December. T…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana NFT Sales Skyrocket, Topping Ethereum in Monthly Volume for First Time]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211547</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211547/solana-nft-sales-skyrocket-ethereum-monthly-volume"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T21:43:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rising momentum around Solana catapulted NFT sales above Ethereum in December, according to data from CryptoSlam.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Steamboat Willie’s Mickey Mouse Goes NFT After Entering Public Domain]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74857e5479</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/steamboat-willies-mickey-mouse-goes-nft-after-entering-public-domain/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T21:35:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the first depictions of the Mickey Mouse character has finally entered the public domain, and it is now immortalized in a non-fungible token collection. A limited edition of 2,000 NFTs featuring the famous mouse in one of its first animated shorts, “Steamboat Willie,” was minted during New Year’s Eve to commemorate the occasion.
 
Steamboat Willie’s Mickey Mouse Celebrated in NFT Collection
 

 
The cryptocurrency community has made Disney’s Mickey Mouse one of the pop culture characters that already have their non-fungible tokens (NFT) collections. One of the first depictions of Mickey Mouse, as the character was seen in a 1928 animated short titled “Steamboat Willie,” is now part of an Ethereum NFT collection launched by Truth cofounder Alexander Taub.
 

 
The NFT collection was …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Phishing Scams Decimate $300 Million From Users In 2023, Key Insights Revealed]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748564f18e</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-phishing-scams-decimate-300-million/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T20:30:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a comprehensive annual report released by web3 security firm Scam Sniffer, alarming statistics highlight the growing threat of phishing scams in the crypto industry. According to the report, these scams resulted in the theft of approximately $300 million of cryptocurrencies.
 
Rising Tide Of Sophisticated Crypto Scams
 
Per the report, phishing activities have surged throughout the year, with scammers employing increasingly “sophisticated tactics” to evade security measures. Notably, Scam Sniffer identified a type of malware called “Wallet Drainers,” which has gained significant traction and posed a severe risk during the past year. 
 
These malicious software are deployed on phishing websites, deceiving users into signing malicious transactions and subsequently siphoning assets from th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sell Signal? Jim Cramer Pulls U-Turn on Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211530</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211530/sell-signal-jim-cramer-pulls-u-turn-on-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T20:19:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The infamous crypto skeptic admits Bitcoin's resilience in the face of government pressure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Drake Reveals Crypto Casino Stake's Rebranded F1 Racing Team]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211523</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211523/drake-reveals-crypto-casino-stakes-rebranded-f1-racing-team"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T20:14:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sauber's F1 team is now officially the Stake team. Rapper, spokesperson, and frequent bettor Drake took to social media to share the news.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Black Swan Looms in 2024, Expert Warns of Unprecedented Economic Upheaval and US Election Disruption]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748567ca8e</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/black-swan-looms-in-2024-expert-warns-of-unprecedented-economic-upheaval-and-us-election-disruption/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T20:04:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The economic forecast for 2024 has undergone significant shifts, with lawmakers and the U.S. Federal Reserve anticipating a “soft landing” for the year. The prevailing belief is that while the economy will decelerate in 2024, the slowdown will be relatively mild. Nonetheless, financier and business magnate Gary Cardone predicts an impending black swan event in 2024, one with the potential to disrupt the U.S. general election.
 
Amid ‘Soft Landing’ Outlooks, Gary Cardone Predicts 2024 Black Swan, Warns of U.S. Election Chaos
 

 
The economic prognosis for 2024 presents a diverse picture. While some forecasters see a light to medium downturn, with differing schedules and effects among sectors, others hold a brighter, or at least controllable, outlook dependent on robust monetary strategies …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OKX Achieves Compliance Just Days before UK Crypto Rule Deadline]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748560054e</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/okx-achieves-compliance-just-days-before-uk-crypto-rule-deadline/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T20:02:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cryptocurrency  
exchange OKX has announced it is working to comply with new crypto asset  
regulations in the United Kingdom that go into effect in a few days, on 8  
January 2024. From that date, new local regulations will be enacted regarding  
the marketing and promotion of cryptocurrency services.
Initially scheduled to take effect in October, the local regulator extended the  
deadline, granting companies more time. OKX managed to comply at the last minute, but many other firms have not yet adapted their rules.
OKX Announces Compliance  
with New UK Crypto Rules ahead of Deadline
In a  
statement published on 2 January, OKX said that it is "developing a new user  
experience that is compliant with the requirements set out in the Financial  
Promotions Regime." The new rules, enac…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Damian Chmiel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dymension Is the Latest Airdrop for Solana, Ethereum, and Cosmos Users]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211515</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211515/dymension-latest-airdrop-solana-ethereum-cosmos-users"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T19:56:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More than a million crypto users and NFT owners across chains can now claim DYM tokens in Dymension’s airdrop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale Bitcoin ETF: Here’s What’s in the Latest SEC Filing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211514</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211514/grayscale-bitcoin-etf-latest-sec-filing"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T19:19:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale is one of many high-profile firms vying to launch a spot Bitcoin ETF.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These Are the High-Profile Spot Bitcoin ETF Applications Currently in Play]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=62912</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/62912/high-profile-bitcoin-etf-applications"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T18:25:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. SEC has dragged its heels on approval of a Bitcoin spot ETF—but analysts are optimistic that there's light at the end of the tunnel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fear and Loathing in Miami: Inside Art Basel and the Rug Radio Merger]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210169</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210169/fear-and-loathing-miami-inside-art-basel-rug-radio-merger"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T18:05:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Writer’s note: Every time I mention something illegal in this story, it's intended as satire or for educational purposes only.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Final Fantasy Maker Square Enix Plans 'Aggressive' AI Moves in 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211477</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211477/final-fantasy-maker-square-enix-plans-aggressive-ai-moves-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T17:40:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Square Enix wants to use AI to increase productivity and create content—despite broader industry backlash against the use of generative AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Crystal Ball 2024: Are NFTs Dead—Or Reborn?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211258</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211258/crypto-crystal-ball-2024-are-nfts-dead-reborn"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T16:20:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Analysts predict that NFTs will make a major rebound in 2024. But that doesn't mean old projects are going to surge again.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Still Soaring on ETF Hype as $133 Million in Shorts Liquidated]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211442</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211442/bitcoin-soaring-etf-hype-133-million-shorts-liquidated"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T15:59:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin has gained 7% in the past day and ORDI, the biggest token built on the BRC-20 standard, is still rising.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is a Bitcoin ETF, and Why Does Everyone from BlackRock to Grayscale Want One?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=12006</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-bitcoin-etf-explained-guide-learn-easy"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T11:40:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A spot Bitcoin ETF creates a simple, legally compliant way to trade the price of Bitcoin, accessible on markets that investors are already familiar with.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Stevens,Ki Chong Tran,Daniel Roberts,Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Over $80 Million Stolen in Orbit Chain Exploit, Assets 'Remain Unmoved']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211436</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211436/over-80-million-stolen-in-orbit-chain-exploit-assets-remain-unmoved"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T10:53:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Orbit Chain said that it would use "all available methods" to recover the stolen funds, which have yet to be moved by the attacker.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Greets 2024 With a Peek Over $45,000]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208683</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208683/bitcoin-btc-45k-crypto-market-etf"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T01:58:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The eyes of the crypto world remain on the SEC as bullish traders eagerly await the regulator’s decision on a Bitcoin spot ETF.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ezra Makes Full-Body MRI Scans More Accessible for Earlier Cancer Detection]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211382</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211382/ezra-mri-mra-full-body-scan-early-cancer-detection"/>
        <updated>2024-01-01T19:52:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Early detection boosts cancer survival rates from 20% to 80%, the company says.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Early Mickey Mouse Now Belongs To Everyone—So Of Course There's a Meme Token]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211373</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211373/mickey-mouse-belongs-to-everyone-so-of-course-theres-now-a-meme-token"/>
        <updated>2024-01-01T19:14:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first-ever cartoon of Mickey Mouse  entered the public domain today, and the free-for-all predictably sparked a new meme couin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Crystal Ball 2024: When Will Regulatory Clarity Come to the US?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211253</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211253/crypto-crystal-ball-2024-when-regulatory-clarity-come-us"/>
        <updated>2024-01-01T16:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto builders and investors have been asking for clarity for years—and 2024 could be a defining year for policy in the United States.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biggest Video Games Releasing in January 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211229</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211229/biggest-video-games-releasing-january-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-01-01T15:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From The Last of Us Part II Remastered to a new Prince of Persia adventure, these are the games worth checking out in January.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biggest Crypto and NFT Games of 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210698</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210698/biggest-crypto-nft-games-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T18:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Numerous crypto and NFT games made waves this year with early access launches and full releases. These are the ones to play.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Behind Bryan Johnson's $4 Million Bid for Immortality]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211346</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211346/behind-bryan-johnsons-4-million-bid-for-immortality"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T18:05:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The serial entrepreneur ruminates on what his “don’t die” mantra means for mere mortals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Crystal Ball 2024: Bitcoin Meets TradFi—For Real]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211244</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211244/crypto-crystal-ball-2024-bitcoin-meets-tradfi-real"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T17:15:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Analysts weigh in on when, if ever, Bitcoin and the crypto market will begin to sway the global economy. Hint: pretty soon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week on Crypto Twitter: Ethereum vs. Solana Rivalry Heats Up]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211298</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211298/this-week-on-crypto-twitter-ethereum-vs-solana-rivalry-heats-up"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T12:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After weeks of non stop gains, Solana advocates found themselves playing defense this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biggest Gaming Fails and Blunders of 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210770</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210770/biggest-gaming-fails-blunders-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T20:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From Logan Paul's NFT game lawsuit to leaked seed phrases and digital lumps of coal, here are 2023's biggest gaming-related fails.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Crystal Ball 2024: Will a Bitcoin ETF Be a Game-Changer?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211243</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211243/crypto-crystal-ball-2024-will-bitcoin-etf-game-changer"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T18:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A spot Bitcoin ETF is most likely around the corner in the United States. Will it deliver at the scale everyone in crypto is banking on?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Bitcoin Dips, Ordinals Mania Continues, Solana Slows]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211190</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211190/this-week-in-coins-bitcoin-dips-ordinals-mania-continues-solana-slows"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T18:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meme coin mania also slowed down this week. But investors are still interested in the potential of Bitcoin's blockchain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biggest NFT Stories of 2023: From Bitcoin Ordinals to Blur's Surge]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211265</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211265/biggest-nft-stories-2023-bitcoin-ordinals-blur-surge"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T17:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was a bumpy, yet transformative year for NFTs and on-chain media across Ethereum, Bitcoin, and beyond. Here’s a look back.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Is Being Flooded With Thousands of New Tokens as Traders Hunt for Next 1,000x]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211234</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211234/solana-being-flooded-thousands-new-tokens-traders-hunt-next-1000x"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T16:07:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After BONK's recent boom and the ecosystem's rebound, Solana is seeing more new tokens created than ever before. Who's behind them?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia Makes a Slower GPU for China Under New U.S. Trade Restrictions]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211222</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211222/nvidia-rtx-4090d-gpu-chinese-market"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T05:08:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new GPU specifically designed for the Chinese market won’t be a top performer, but will still be good enough for gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ESL Faceit Group Exploring Blockchain 'Opportunistically,' Says Exec]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/yvrs4lBx/esl-faceit-group-exploring-blockchain-opportunistically-says-exec</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/yvrs4lBx/esl-faceit-group-exploring-blockchain-opportunistically-says-exec"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T02:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Braithwaite—ESL Faceit Group's VP of Game Ecosystems, Mobile, and Snapdragon Pro Series—shares the esports firm's approach to blockchain technology with GG's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VanEck Joins Bitcoin ETF Ad War With New Teaser Trailer]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211215</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211215/vaneck-joins-bitcoin-etf-ad-war-with-new-teaser-trailer"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T23:06:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The investment firm teased the as-of-yet non-existent financial product days before the latest of several supposed deadlines the SEC faces to approve one.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock Bitcoin ETF Names JP Morgan, Jane Street as Authorized Participants]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211208</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211208/blackrock-bitcoin-etf-jp-morgan-jane-street"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T21:37:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The amendment is one of the last steps in the application process, experts say.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Free Money': These Are the Hottest Airdrops Around Right Now]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209179</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209179/free-money-hottest-airdrops-around-right-now"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T20:50:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATED: More and more airdrops are coming, including from Jupiter, Portal, Blast, and Frame, plus Solana Saga owners can claim more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Got 'Worthless' NFTs? This Startup Buys JPEGs for a Penny to Harvest Tax Losses]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211186</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211186/got-worthless-nfts-startup-buys-jpegs-penny-harvest-tax-losses"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T19:16:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unsellable says it has helped NFT collectors realize $4.2 million worth of tax losses to date by buying up their illiquid assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Token ORDI Surges to New High, Nearing Top 50 Coins]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211185</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211185/bitcoin-token-ordi-surges-new-high-nearing-top-50-coins"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T18:44:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price of ORDI, the biggest token minted on the Bitcoin network, is surging again today—and is one of this week's best-performers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF Race Could Get Tighter After This Deadline]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211188</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211188/bitcoin-etf-race-amendment-deadline"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T18:14:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fund managers vying to release a spot Bitcoin ETF have until today to file a key amendment to their applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wildcard's Plans for 2024 with Founders Paul and Katy Bettner]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/TI3aFBhO/wildcards-plans-for-2024-with-founders-paul-and-katy-bettner</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/TI3aFBhO/wildcards-plans-for-2024-with-founders-paul-and-katy-bettner"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T21:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wildcard developers Paul and Katy Bettner tell Decrypt's Kate Irwin about why they see their game as a "Web3 game," not a crypto game, and share why they've stuck with their initial vision despite the challenging broader market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt and Rug Radio Merge to Create Global Web3 Publishing Company]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/VTEBYFD8/decrypt-and-rug-radio-merge-to-create-global-web3-publishing-company</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/VTEBYFD8/decrypt-and-rug-radio-merge-to-create-global-web3-publishing-company"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T17:04:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt and Rug Radio have announced their intent to merge, creating the world’s biggest decentralized publishing company. Codenamed [REDACTED], the alliance is aimed at revolutionizing tech-media, bringing together the forces of content creation and consumption.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['If You Play Well, You're Gonna be Rewarded': How FPS Web3War is Bringing 'Skill-to-Earn' to Crypto Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Jl5AEFuD/if-you-play-well-youre-gonna-be-rewarded-how-fps-web3war-is-bringing-skill-to-earn-to-crypto-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Jl5AEFuD/if-you-play-well-youre-gonna-be-rewarded-how-fps-web3war-is-bringing-skill-to-earn-to-crypto-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T10:20:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roll1ng Thund3rz co-founder Valentin Cobelea and Zilliqa CEO Matt Dyer joined Decrypt to discuss how the new FPS game Web3War is shaking up the crypto gaming space with a novel "skill to earn" mechanic that rewards players for high-quality gameplay.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating peaceful money & taking over your local government w/ Joseph Schiarizzi]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zb0VG27G/creating-peaceful-money-taking-over-your-local-government-w-joseph-schiarizzi</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zb0VG27G/creating-peaceful-money-taking-over-your-local-government-w-joseph-schiarizzi"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T23:23:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week our host Reza Jafery is joined by Joseph Schiarizzi, founder of OpenDollar and prolific solidity developer. 


We discuss: 
- Onchain beer
- Taking over your local government
- His Emmy and 3 patents?!?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INTERVIEW: Ember Sword CEO Says NFT Games Are More 'Transparent']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/M9OHCVpA/interview-ember-sword-ceo-says-nft-games-are-more-transparent</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/M9OHCVpA/interview-ember-sword-ceo-says-nft-games-are-more-transparent"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T21:58:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ember Sword CEO Mark Laursen shares why some big game studios "irk" him—and why he got into game development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Director Jordan Bayne on the State of Film3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZLoEDkL9/director-jordan-bayne-on-the-state-of-film3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZLoEDkL9/director-jordan-bayne-on-the-state-of-film3"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T00:11:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the 2023 Film3 Summit, Jordan Bayne—director and founder of The Squad—spoke with Decrypt's Sander Lutz about how the Film3 world has progressed over the last year and what decentralized technologies can offer to creators that want to buck the Hollywood system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>