<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-12-08T06:20:07.559Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-12-08T06:20:07.559Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matrixport's $45K End of Year Target for Bitcoin Looks to Be Accurate]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7494aafe0c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/12/08/matrixports-45k-end-of-year-target-for-bitcoin-looks-to-be-accurate/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T05:59:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2023 has been a five-phased bitcoin rally, Matrixport says in a report.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Transforming Poverty Analysis with AI and Satellite Data]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19094439/Transforming-Poverty-Analysis-with-AI-and-Satellite-Data</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19094439/Transforming-Poverty-Analysis-with-AI-and-Satellite-Data"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T05:56:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an unprecedented effort to tackle the global challenge of measuring poverty and economic development, a groundbreaking study has emerged, utilizing artificial intelligence (AI) in conjunction with satellite imagery. AI meets satellite imagery in poverty analysis At the heart of this research...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[El Salvador leverages Tether’s tech for the Freedom Visa Program – Who Is eligible?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19094424/El-Salvador-leverages-Tethers-tech-for-the-Freedom-Visa-Program-Who-Is-eligible</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19094424/El-Salvador-leverages-Tethers-tech-for-the-Freedom-Visa-Program-Who-Is-eligible"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T05:55:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The government of El Salvador and Tether, the largest crypto company, announced the commencement of the “Adopting El Salvador Freedom Visa Program” on December 7, 2023. This visa program is designed to foster an atmosphere in which individuals can contribute to the creation of a new...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bridging the AI Literacy Gap – Addressing Challenges in Upskilling for Tomorrow’s Workforce]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19094420/Bridging-the-AI-Literacy-Gap-Addressing-Challenges-in-Upskilling-for-Tomorrows-Workforce</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19094420/Bridging-the-AI-Literacy-Gap-Addressing-Challenges-in-Upskilling-for-Tomorrows-Workforce"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T05:44:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a fast-paced world increasingly dominated by artificial intelligence (AI), the burgeoning AI literacy gap poses a critical challenge to organizations striving to stay ahead. Pluralsight’s recent survey reveals a stark reality: while 92% of organizations accelerate AI initiatives, a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Evaluated “Global Licensing Needs” under CZ: Withdrew Abu Dhabi Bid]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e749495bd3b</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/binance-evaluated-global-licensing-needs-under-cz-withdrew-abu-dhabi-bid/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T05:32:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance, the largest crypto exchange in terms of trading volume, has withdrawn its bid for a collective investment fund applied with the financial market regulator in Abu Dhabi. The decision came as, according to Binance, it is reassessing its “global licensing needs.  

Is Binance Rethinking Its MENA Strategy?  

As seen on the Abu Dhabi Global Market (ADGM) register, Binance’s local subsidiary, BV Investment Management Limited, applied for the license on 15 November 2022 and withdrew the application on 7 November 2023. The license would have enabled the exchange to offer services to professional clients.  

Notably, during those decisions, Changpeng Zhao was still heading Binance as the CEO. Zhao stepped down last month, following his plea agreement with the US prosecutors, handing over …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arnab Shome</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Founder CZ Remanded to Remain in Continental US, Travel to UAE Prohibited]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e749495d4f0</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/binance-founder-cz-remanded-to-remain-in-continental-us-travel-to-uae-prohibited/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T05:32:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Changpeng Zhao, better known as CZ, the founder of Binance, has recently grappled with significant legal hurdles in the U.S. His guilty plea in a notable case led a Seattle federal judge to impose movement restrictions on him.
 
Former Binance Boss CZ Restricted to U.S. Soil
 
As the pivotal figure of Binance, CZ admitted guilt for not establishing anti-money laundering measures and breaching U.S. sanctions. His plea, which included resigning as the CEO, brought considerable repercussions for both him and the crypto exchange firm.
 
U.S. District Judge Richard Jones, on Thursday, reversed a previous ruling that would have permitted Zhao to travel back to the United Arab Emirates (UAE). Pointing to Zhao’s substantial assets and weak connections to the U.S., Judge Jones highlighted the flight risk he poses. This decision came after Jones consented to the plea agreement between the U.S. authorities and CZ, amid Binance’s settlement process.
 
Judge Jones expressed that the court wasn’t persuaded by assurances that CZ wouldn’t flee if allowed to go to the UAE, a country with which the U.S. lacks an extradition agreement. Consequently, he ordered CZ to remain within the mainland U.S. until his sentencing in February 2024. CZ could face up to 18 months in prison for these offenses.
 
 
Many speculate that CZ might avoid jail time, akin to Arthur Hayes, the ex-CEO of Bitmex. Hayes received a sentence of six months of house arrest and two years probation for violating the Bank Secrecy Act (BSA) by not instituting an anti-money laundering (AML) system at Bitmex. Although Hayes faced a potential prison sentence, his guilty plea and the settlement of fines helped him evade incarceration.
 
What do you think about the latest court ruling against the former Binance boss CZ? Share your thoughts and opinions about this subject in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matrixport's $45K End of Year Target for Bitcoin Looks to Be Accurate]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19094405/Matrixports-45K-End-of-Year-Target-for-Bitcoin-Looks-to-Be-Accurate</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19094405/Matrixports-45K-End-of-Year-Target-for-Bitcoin-Looks-to-Be-Accurate"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T05:30:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2023 has been a five-phased bitcoin rally, Matrixport says in a report.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Naver’s AI and Cloud Sector Ready for Global Market Penetration]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19094406/Navers-AI-and-Cloud-Sector-Ready-for-Global-Market-Penetration</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19094406/Navers-AI-and-Cloud-Sector-Ready-for-Global-Market-Penetration"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T05:28:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[South Korea’s Naver is setting its sights high, aiming to double its AI and cloud computing exports in three years. Standing apart from its American and Chinese counterparts, Naver, a powerhouse in South Korea’s tech scene, is uniquely poised to offer AI solutions and cloud services that cater...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance CEO: Fiat Role in Global Crime 100 Times That of Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19094401/Binance-CEO-Fiat-Role-in-Global-Crime-100-Times-That-of-Crypto</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19094401/Binance-CEO-Fiat-Role-in-Global-Crime-100-Times-That-of-Crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T05:21:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent post on X, Binance CEO Richard Teng shared a viewpoint that challenges the prevailing narratives from the banking sector regarding cryptocurrency’s alleged association with illicit activities. Teng highlighted facts from an authority source to counter the frequent calls to shut down...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI Employees’ Bluff – Most Prefer Perks Over Microsoft Move, Reveals Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19094385/OpenAI-Employees-Bluff-Most-Prefer-Perks-Over-Microsoft-Move-Reveals-Report</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19094385/OpenAI-Employees-Bluff-Most-Prefer-Perks-Over-Microsoft-Move-Reveals-Report"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T05:17:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent twist of events within the tech sector, OpenAI, currently one of the most talked-about startups, faced upheaval as its CEO, Sam Altman, was abruptly fired and later reinstated after a brief tumult. The aftermath saw a reported rebellion among OpenAI employees, threatening to defect...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Shorts Take A $27 M Hit, Bitcoin Long Positions Suffer Liquidations — Analytics Firm Reveals Large ETH Wallets Hit Record Highs]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19094388/Ethereum-Shorts-Take-A-27-M-Hit-Bitcoin-Long-Positions-Suffer-Liquidations-Analytics-Firm-Reveals-Large-ETH-Wallets-Hit-Record-Highs</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19094388/Ethereum-Shorts-Take-A-27-M-Hit-Bitcoin-Long-Positions-Suffer-Liquidations-Analytics-Firm-Reveals-Large-ETH-Wallets-Hit-Record-Highs"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T05:09:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over $27 million worth of short Ethereum (CRYPTO: ETH) positions were liquidated in the past 24 hours as the price of Ethereum soared, nearly reaching the $2400 level. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto investors fear a ‘Bull Trap’ as Bitcoin price continues to drop – What’s the problem?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19094370/Crypto-investors-fear-a-Bull-Trap-as-Bitcoin-price-continues-to-drop-Whats-the-problem</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19094370/Crypto-investors-fear-a-Bull-Trap-as-Bitcoin-price-continues-to-drop-Whats-the-problem"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T04:56:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bitcoin (BTC) rally came to a halt on Thursday, giving way to the crypto majors ether (ETH) and Solana (SOL), which surged to a new 19-month high and led the crypto rally. Following its meteoric rise to near $45,000 earlier this week, Bitcoin fell to $43,000 during the day, indicating that...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Guru Who Nailed Bitcoin’s 2018 Bottom Predicts Major Surge for Solana (SOL)]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19094379/Crypto-Guru-Who-Nailed-Bitcoins-2018-Bottom-Predicts-Major-Surge-for-Solana-SOL</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19094379/Crypto-Guru-Who-Nailed-Bitcoins-2018-Bottom-Predicts-Major-Surge-for-Solana-SOL"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T04:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A popular cryptocurrency strategist who has gained a large following on social media after accurately calling Bitcoin’s 2018 bear market bottom above $3,000 has recently revealed he believes Solana (SOL) will keep outperforming Bitcoin in the near future. In a post shared with their over 230,000...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lessons Learned – A Year After the FTX Collapse]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19094363/Lessons-Learned-A-Year-After-the-FTX-Collapse</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19094363/Lessons-Learned-A-Year-After-the-FTX-Collapse"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T04:40:51.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-CEO of Binance 'Is a Flight Risk': Must Stay in the US Until Sentencing]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74949cbbc0</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/ex-ceo-of-binance-is-a-flight-risk-must-stay-in-the-us-until-sentencing/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T04:22:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Changpeng Zhao, the founder and former CEO of Binance, must stay in the United States until his sentencing is scheduled in February, a US federal judge ruled on Thursday. The decision overruled Zhao's previous bail agreement that allowed him to visit his UAE residency but needed him to return to the US two weeks before his sentencing.  

The ruling came only a day after the court accepted Zhao's guilty plea for violating one count of one count of Bank Secrecy Act violation.  

Bail Agreement Does not Guarantee Free Movement  

Zhao entered the guilty plea last month and consecutively signed a $175 million bond agreement. He already put up about $15 million in an escrow account and found guarantors for the additional funds.  

Although the initial bail agreement allowed him to leave the Uni…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arnab Shome</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Schiff Says Global Tax Chiefs’ Only Enforcement Success Is Its ‘Failed’ Action Against His Bank]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74949df761</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/peter-schiff-says-global-tax-chiefs-only-enforcement-success-is-its-failed-action-against-his-bank/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T04:10:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Economist Peter Schiff says the only enforcement success of the Joint Chiefs of Global Tax Enforcement (J5) is its “failed” action against his bank, allegedly aimed to “put a stop to the suspected facilitation of offshore tax evasion.” Schiff stressed: “Other than the failed investigation of my bank, which did not result in any charges being filed against anyone, the J5 has not had a single enforcement success in its 5-year plus history of existence.”
 
Peter Schiff Says J5’s Only Success Is a Failure
 
Economist Peter Schiff slammed the Joint Chiefs of Global Tax Enforcement (J5) on Wednesday, claiming its only success is a failed action against his bank, Euro Pacific Bank. J5 was established in 2018 by leaders of tax enforcement authorities from Australia, Canada, the Netherlands, the U.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashKey Claims Thailand is a Crypto Haven, But Not So Fast]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19094367/HashKey-Claims-Thailand-is-a-Crypto-Haven-But-Not-So-Fast</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19094367/HashKey-Claims-Thailand-is-a-Crypto-Haven-But-Not-So-Fast"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T04:06:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new report from crypto venture capital firm HashKey Capital has lauded Thailand for being a crypto haven due to increasing trading volume. However, the truth of the matter may not be as simple with crypto payments remaining outlawed in the Southeast Asian nation.  On December 7, HashKey...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Solana-Based Meme Coin Reached All-Time Highs Again, Even As Shiba Inu, Dogecoin Slip]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19094320/This-Solana-Based-Meme-Coin-Reached-All-Time-Highs-Again-Even-As-Shiba-Inu-Dogecoin-Slip</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19094320/This-Solana-Based-Meme-Coin-Reached-All-Time-Highs-Again-Even-As-Shiba-Inu-Dogecoin-Slip"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T03:49:06.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IBM CEO Arvind Krishna Challenges the Imperfections of AI Regulations]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19094291/IBM-CEO-Arvind-Krishna-Challenges-the-Imperfections-of-AI-Regulations</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19094291/IBM-CEO-Arvind-Krishna-Challenges-the-Imperfections-of-AI-Regulations"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T03:24:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a candid conversation with CNBC, Arvind Krishna, the CEO of International Business Machines Corp (IBM), delved into the intricate landscape of AI regulations and shared his perspectives on President Biden’s recent executive order. Unveiling his thoughts on the imperfections inherent in any...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[America Has a New Threat and It’s Crypto, Claims Elizabeth Warren]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19094306/America-Has-a-New-Threat-and-Its-Crypto-Claims-Elizabeth-Warren</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19094306/America-Has-a-New-Threat-and-Its-Crypto-Claims-Elizabeth-Warren"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T03:19:11.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Founder Changpeng Zhao Barred From Traveling To UAE, Must Remain In US Until Sentencing]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19094287/Binance-Founder-Changpeng-Zhao-Barred-From-Traveling-To-UAE-Must-Remain-In-US-Until-Sentencing</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19094287/Binance-Founder-Changpeng-Zhao-Barred-From-Traveling-To-UAE-Must-Remain-In-US-Until-Sentencing"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T03:14:57.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Short Sellers Lose Over $6 Billion as Bitcoin and Crypto Stocks Soar]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19094285/Short-Sellers-Lose-Over-6-Billion-as-Bitcoin-and-Crypto-Stocks-Soar</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19094285/Short-Sellers-Lose-Over-6-Billion-as-Bitcoin-and-Crypto-Stocks-Soar"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T03:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price of the flagship cryptocurrency Bitcoin (BTC) has moved up more than 23% over the past month and over 160% year-to-date in sharp moves that helped cryptocurrency-related stocks recover amid renewed optimism. As cryptocurrency-related stock prices grew, short sellers lost over $2.6...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Australian Government Allocates A$17 Million to Propel AI Adoption Among SMEs]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19094267/Australian-Government-Allocates-A17-Million-to-Propel-AI-Adoption-Among-SMEs</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19094267/Australian-Government-Allocates-A17-Million-to-Propel-AI-Adoption-Among-SMEs"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T02:57:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a move to redefine the technological landscape of Australian businesses, the government has unveiled the AI Adopt Program, pledging A$17 million to propel the integration of Artificial Intelligence (AI) across small to medium enterprises (SMEs). This initiative, marked by its commitment to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Judge Bans Changpeng ‘CZ’ Zhao from Leaving the Country]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209060</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209060/us-judge-bans-changpeng-cz-zhao-from-leaving-the-country"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T02:51:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["The defendant has enormous wealth and property abroad," wrote Judge Richard Jones, "and no ties to the United States."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Judge Bans Changpeng ‘CZ’ Zhao from Leaving the Country]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19094265/US-Judge-Bans-Changpeng-CZ-Zhao-from-Leaving-the-Country</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19094265/US-Judge-Bans-Changpeng-CZ-Zhao-from-Leaving-the-Country"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T02:51:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["The defendant has enormous wealth and property abroad," wrote Judge Richard Jones, "and no ties to the United States."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Waste Of Block Space Or Egalitarian Issuance Mechanism? Inscriptions Divide Web3 Community]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19094266/Waste-Of-Block-Space-Or-Egalitarian-Issuance-Mechanism-Inscriptions-Divide-Web3-Community</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19094266/Waste-Of-Block-Space-Or-Egalitarian-Issuance-Mechanism-Inscriptions-Divide-Web3-Community"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T02:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robert Kiyosaki Warns ‘This Next Crash May Turn Into a Depression’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7494869b72</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/robert-kiyosaki-warns-this-next-crash-may-turn-into-a-depression/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T02:38:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rich Dad Poor Dad author Robert Kiyosaki has warned that a soft landing for the U.S. economy is a fantasy, emphasizing that a crash landing is more likely. Noting that he already warned of this giant crash in his Rich Dad’s Prophecy book, the famous author stressed: “This next crash may turn into a depression.”
 
Robert Kiyosaki on Giant Crash and a Depression
 
The author of Rich Dad Poor Dad, Robert Kiyosaki, has once again sounded the alarm about the U.S. economy. Rich Dad Poor Dad is a 1997 book co-authored by Kiyosaki and Sharon Lechter. It has been on the New York Times Best Seller List for over six years. More than 32 million copies of the book have been sold in over 51 languages across more than 109 countries.
 
Kiyosaki wrote on social media platform X Wednesday: “Soft landing is a fantasy. Crash landing more likely. I warned of this giant crash in my book Rich Dad’s Prophecy pub 2012.” He continued:
 

This next crash may turn into a depression.
 
The renowned author also shared in an X post on Sunday that the Israel-Hamas war has motivated him to buy an electric vehicle. “The war is about oil,” he said. “Higher gas prices will make the poor poorer.” He proceeded to reiterate his recommendation of buying gold, silver, and bitcoin, which he believes to be the best investment for unstable times.
 
 
The well-known author has repeatedly expressed concerns about challenging times ahead for the U.S. economy. Last week, he similarly cautioned about a possible next Great Depression and a war, predicting “really hard times ahead” for millions of people. Kiyosaki also previously warned of the “greatest real estate crash ever,” emphasizing that the Federal Reserve’s rate hikes will also crash stocks, bonds, and the U.S. dollar.
 
What do you think about the warnings by Rich Dad Poor Dad author Robert Kiyosaki about the next crash turning into a depression? Let us know in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Early Bitcoin Ordinals Art Sells for Record $450,000]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209032</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209032/early-bitcoin-ordinals-art-sells-for-record-450000"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T02:21:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Honey Badger inscription number eight, created on Jan. 15, sold on Magic Eden on Thursday for 10.4 BTC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Founder Changpeng 'CZ' Zhao Stuck in U.S. Until Sentencing]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74948105cb</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/12/08/binance-founder-changpeng-cz-zhao-stuck-in-us-until-sentencing/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T02:13:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance founder and former CEO Changpeng Zhao must remain in the U.S. until he is sentenced next February, a federal judge ruled Thursday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft May Be Working On an AI Edition of Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209025</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209025/microsoft-ai-windows-2024-germanium-copilot"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T02:06:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 Windows release is rumored to have AI in everything from its graphical user interface to its command line.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JPMorgan CEO Jamie Dimon Says He’d Close Crypto Down if He Were the Government]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74948f3472</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/jpmorgan-ceo-jamie-dimon-says-hed-close-crypto-down-if-he-were-the-government/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T01:07:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JPMorgan Chase CEO Jamie Dimon told U.S. senators in a congressional hearing that he would close down crypto if he were the government. Emphasizing that he has always been “deeply opposed” to crypto and bitcoin, the executive stressed that the true use case of crypto is criminals, drug traffickers, money laundering, and tax avoidance.
 
Jamie Dimon Wants to Shut Down Crypto, Bitcoin
 
The chief executive officer of global investment bank JPMorgan Chase shared his view about crypto and bitcoin on Wednesday during the Senate Banking Committee’s annual Wall Street oversight hearing.
 
Responding to U.S. Senator Elizabeth Warren’s question about why cryptocurrencies are an attractive tool for criminals, Dimon stated:
 

I’ve always been deeply opposed to crypto, bitcoin, etc. You pointed out t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain Victory: US Congress Committee Unanimously Approves Pioneering Legislation]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74948fb9cd</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/major-win-blockchain-us-congress-passes-legislation/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T01:02:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a significant move towards embracing blockchain technology, the United States Congress Committee on Energy and Commerce recently achieved a milestone by unanimously passing the Deploying American Blockchains Act of 2023. The bill voted in favor with a 46-0 majority, was part of a comprehensive session tackling 44 pieces of legislation. 
 
Secretary Of Commerce Develops Guidelines For Implementation
 
The primary objective of the legislation is to empower the Secretary of Commerce to take essential and appropriate actions that promote the United States’ competitiveness in the realm of the nascent technology. 
 
Under the bill, the Secretary assumes the crucial role of the principal advisor to the President, providing policy guidance on various aspects related to applications, tokens, and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 20 DEXes Like Uniswap, PancakeSwap Have Cumulatively Processed Over $4.4 Trillion]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7494758533</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dexes-uniswap-processes-over-4-4-trillion/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T00:01:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The decentralized finance (DeFi) sector continues to gain traction if on-chain data, especially from decentralized exchanges (DEXes), is anything to go by. According to Token Terminal data on December 6, the top 20 DEXes have accumulated over $4.4 trillion in trading volume since launching. 
 
Rise And Rise Of DEXes: Uniswap, Curve Dominate
 
Considering the state of centralized trading in the wake of regulatory pressures in 2023, this expansion points to increasing adoption of DEXes, especially from crypto fans who might treasure and seek non-custodial trading options and exposure of tokens not yet listed on mainstream platforms like Binance or Coinbase. 
 
 
Looking at Token Terminal data, Curve, Uniswap, PancakeSwap, and 1inch stand out among the leading DEXes, each catering to a specif…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dalmas Ngetich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brazil to Discuss Digital Currency Usage for Financial Transactions in G20]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74947003d5</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/brazil-to-discuss-digital-currency-usage-for-financial-transactions-in-g20/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T23:36:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brazil will address the subject of digital currencies and how they can improve the financial system for the Group of Twenty (G20). Roberto Campos Neto, president of the Central Bank of Brazil, stated he wants the G20 to consider the benefits of using these currencies for making financial transactions and to work towards adapting rules to take advantage of this.
Brazil to Discuss Digital Currencies as G20 President
The government of Brazil will discuss digital currencies and the possible benefits of implementing them for financial transactions as part of the Group of the Twenty (G20). Having assumed the G20 presidency on December 1, Brazil will leverage its position to advance the digital agenda and assess how the twenty largest economies could adapt their regulatory frameworks to take adva…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jito Airdrop Hands Out $225 Million to Solana Users]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209010</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209010/jito-airdrop-hands-out-225-million-solana-users"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T23:22:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana DeFi users are celebrating after Jito launched JTO, with 90 million tokens up for grabs for eligible users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ether, Solana Hit 19-Month Highs as Bitcoin Rally Halts with Traders Fearing 'Bull Trap']]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e749472791e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/12/07/ether-solana-hit-19-month-highs-as-bitcoin-rally-halts-with-traders-fearing-bull-trap/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T23:13:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BitMex founder Arthur Hayes speculated about SOL hitting near $100 in a bullish weekend for altcoins.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOGE In Hollywood: Dogecoin Make An Appearance On Family Guy]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e749473aff9</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-appearance-family-guy/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T23:02:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Dogecoin have been mentioned in the latest episode of Family Guy, one of the longest-running shows in American history. The three cryptocurrencies were mentioned in reference to crypto payments as a character from the show, Meg, tries to pay for a service.
 
Accepting Bitcoin, Dogecoin, And Maybe Ethereum
 
In the latest episode of the Family Guy series, the appearance of Bitcoin, Dogecoin, and Ethereum center around Meg, the first daughter of Peter and Lois. The episode sees Meg going to a therapist to figure out how to cry again, after her tears dry up, which happens to be the main ingredients of her newfound cookie recipe.
 
 
The success of the cookie recipe sees Meg booking a gig for a billionaire party. But with no tears left to cry, the businesswoman goes to n…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Best Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Protocol Kamino Eyes Airdrop Following Jito Token Launch]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74947d7fe2</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/12/07/solana-protocol-kamino-eyes-airdrop-following-jito-token-launch/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T22:44:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana's SOL token has more than tripled since mid-October as DeFi traders return to the ecosystem's on-chain trading, borrowing, lending and yield-generating projects, most notably Kamino.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This $28K Pixelated Avocado Could Add to Bitcoin's Raging Censorship Debate]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74947f6553</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/12/07/this-28k-pixelated-avocado-could-add-to-bitcoins-raging-censorship-debate/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T22:26:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NFT-like Ordinals inscriptions are anathema to some Bitcoin purists who want to preserve the blockchain for financial applications. But a few of the images are fetching eye-popping sums in the in-real-life art world.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bradley Keoun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Terraform Labs Co-Founder Do Kwon to Be Extradited to the US]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74947995b8</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/report-terraform-labs-co-founder-do-kwon-to-be-extradited-to-the-us/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T22:05:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Labs’ co-founder, Do Kwon, is on the brink of extradition to the United States from Montenegro. This development follows a decisive ruling by a high court and the endorsement from a top official. According to The Wall Street Journal, Justice Minister Andrej Milovic has confidentially agreed to the extradition, signifying a crucial twist in Terraform Labs’ continuing narrative and its profound repercussions on the crypto economy.
 
High Court Approves U.S. Extradition of Terraform Labs Co-Founder Do Kwon Amid Fraud Charges
 
The Wall Street Journal released an exclusive report on Thursday regarding Do Kwon’s extradition. This follows the judgment of a Montenegrin high court, which received subsequent support from Justice Minister Andrej Milovic during closed-door and private conve…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miners Cash Out: $131 Million Worth Of BTC Offloaded]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e749479fda5</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-miners-cash-out-132-million-btc-offloaded/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T22:02:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data shows that Bitcoin miners have participated in a selloff during the past day as they have offloaded 3,000 BTC from their wallets.
 
Bitcoin Miners Have Sold $131 Million Worth Of The Asset During Past Day
 
As pointed out by analyst Ali in a new post on X, the BTC miner reserve has plunged during the last day. The “miner reserve” here refers to the total amount of Bitcoin that the miners as a whole are carrying in their wallets right now.
 
When the value of this metric declines, it means that the miners are taking out a net number of coins from their wallets. Generally, the main reason why these chain validators would withdraw from their reserve is for selling purposes, so this kind of trend can have bearish implications for the price.
 
 
On the other hand, the indicator go…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INTERVIEW: Ember Sword CEO Says NFT Games Are More 'Transparent']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/M9OHCVpA/interview-ember-sword-ceo-says-nft-games-are-more-transparent</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/M9OHCVpA/interview-ember-sword-ceo-says-nft-games-are-more-transparent"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T21:58:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ember Sword CEO Mark Laursen shares why some big game studios "irk" him—and why he got into game development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Money Fight]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74946646e7</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/print/the-money-fight"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T21:24:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article is featured in Bitcoin Magazine’s “The Primary Issue”. Click here to get your Annual Bitcoin Magazine Subscription.
I always find it funny when I am attending a Bitcoin event like Bitcoin 2023 — or next year’s Bitcoin 2024 in Nashville — and a fight fan recognizes me with a bewildered look in their eyes and asks, 
“Cyborg?!…What are YOU doing here?”
The answer always seems obvious to me, “because I am a Bitcoiner!” 
One thing that makes Bitcoin special is that it is for everyone and that the more you understand it, the more certain you become of its success. Whenever I meet someone and find out they are also a Bitcoiner, I instantly feel a connection with them — a sense of respect. It’s hard to explain to someone who isn’t involved in martial arts, but it’s a feeling very simi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cris Cyborg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code Is Not (Always) Law]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e749466776c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/12/07/code-is-not-always-law/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T21:21:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes, the law is the law, industry experts say.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Kuhn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Unveils Open-Source Path for AI Development on Its Silicon Chips]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209003</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209003/apple-ai-ml-development-mlx-silicon"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T21:07:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MLX speeds AI development on Apple hardware, connecting its users with the broader AI development community on other platforms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Takes Center Stage: US Presidential Candidates Criticize Gensler, Call For Clear Regulations]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e749460b16f</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-takes-center-stage-presidential-candidates/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T21:02:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During the recent Republican Party presidential debate, a notable shift in political discourse regarding crypto emerged as US presidential candidate Vivek Ramaswamy openly criticized US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Chair Gary Gensler, alongside other federal agencies, for their handling of digital currency regulation.
 
Presidential Candidates Throws Jabs At Gensler And Current Policies
 
Ramaswamy, addressing the audience, described the SEC’s approach as “nothing short of embarrassing,” particularly highlighting Gensler’s refusal to classify the Ethereum token as a commodity in congressional hearings.
 
 
His comments were motivated by the scrutiny of regulatory bodies of crypto enthusiasts, and industry stakeholders. When the moderator asked Ramaswamy if his crypto plan, whic…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What the Bitcoin Halving Means for Investors]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208164</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208164/bitcoin-halving-what-it-means-investors"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T19:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The next Bitcoin halving takes place in April—but this time is different, insiders say. Here's what retail investors should know.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reebok Follows Nike Into Digital Fashion and Gaming, With an AI Twist]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208993</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208993/reebok-follows-nike-into-digital-wearables-gaming-with-ai-twist"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T19:31:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Footwear brand Reebok will debut an on-chain gaming experience next year that it promises will be “mind-bending.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meme Coins Dogecoin, SHIB Slip—But Solana's BONK Continues to Soar]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208973</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208973/meme-coin-dogecoin-shib-solana-bonk"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T18:38:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bullish traders are once again eyeing up risky assets for quick gains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ronin and Beam Gaming Tokens Surge, Outpacing Bitcoin and Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208986</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208986/ronin-beam-gaming-tokens-surge-outpacing-bitcoin-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T18:16:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gaming tokens remain hot, with RON and BEAM the biggest winners this week with huge double-digit weekly percentage jumps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gamers Can Now Livestream to Twitter via Streamlabs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208972</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208972/gamers-can-now-livestream-twitter-streamlabs"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T17:01:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Streamlabs’ new X feature allows gamers to go live on Twitter from a phone or computer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Montenegro Set to Extradite Terra Co-Founder Do Kwon to US: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208983</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208983/montenegro-extradite-terra-co-founder-do-kwon-us"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T17:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Terraform Labs co-founder has been caught in a jurisdictional tug-of-war between the U.S. and his native South Korea.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These Are the High-Profile Spot Bitcoin ETF Applications Currently in Play]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=62912</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/62912/high-profile-bitcoin-etf-applications"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T15:06:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. SEC has dragged its heels on approval of a Bitcoin spot ETF—but analysts are optimistic that there's light at the end of the tunnel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Auction House Sotheby's Announces First Sale of Bitcoin Ordinals Collection]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208961</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208961/auction-house-sothebys-announces-first-sale-of-bitcoin-ordinals-collection"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T13:22:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The sale marks the first occasion on which works from the BitcoinShrooms collection will be made available to the public, Sotheby's said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood Crypto Launches in EU With 'Crypto Back' Bitcoin Rewards Program]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208954</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208954/robinhood-crypto-launches-in-eu-with-crypto-back-bitcoin-rewards-program"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T10:06:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood Crypto's EU users will receive a percentage of trading volume back in Bitcoin, as well as Bitcoin rewards for referrals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rising Bitcoin Fees Prompt Renewed Battle Over Ordinals, BRC-20 Tokens]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208945</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208945/rising-bitcoin-fees-prompt-renewed-battle-over-ordinals-brc-20-tokens"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T02:01:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While some call for purging the NFT-like inscriptions, others say they are good for the network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t ‘AI Wash’ Investment Pitches: SEC Chair Gary Gensler]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208944</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208944/dont-ai-wash-investment-pitches-sec-chair-gary-gensler"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T01:33:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While excited by AI technology, Gensler highlighted its potential biases and conflicts of interest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Adds AI Across Its Apps, Launches Standalone Image Generator]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208935</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208935/meta-adds-ai-across-its-apps-launches-standalone-image-generator"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T01:02:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Facebook, Instagram, Messenger, and WhatsApp get new AI features, and the Meta Imagine tool lets users create AI art.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Set to List Jito Following Airdrop of Solana Token]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208923</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208923/coinbase-set-list-jito-following-airdrop-solana-token"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T00:07:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase has announced it will list Solana-based DeFi project Jito's token on its platform following the JTO airdrop Thursday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Merit Circle Brings Immutable zkEVM Into Beam Crypto Gaming Ecosystem]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208912</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208912/merit-circle-brings-immutable-zkevm-into-beam-crypto-gaming-ecosystem"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T23:31:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Merit Circle’s Beam tech is expanding beyond Avalanche to the Immutable zkEVM as a part of the DAO's "chain agnostic" approach.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Stock Short Sellers Have Lost $2.6 Billion Since Bitcoin Bull Run Began]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208921</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208921/crypto-stock-short-sellers-lost-2-6-billion-since-bitcoin-bull-run-began"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T23:07:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Short sellers are playing with fire and getting burned as Bitcoin's boom boosts crypto stocks. Experts say it's about to get worse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To AI: Best AI Tools for Image Generation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208752</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208752/which-ai-art-generator-should-you-use-comparison-dalle-midjourney-stable-diffusion-sdxl-adobe-firefly-amazon-titan-leonardo"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T22:05:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Which AI image generator fits your needs? From Dall-E and MidJourney to Stable Diffusion, we've got a comprehensive guide to help you choose.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Buy BTC': Viral Leaked GTA 6 Game Trailer Shills Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208899</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208899/buy-btc-viral-leaked-gta-6-game-trailer-shills-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T21:20:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The much-anticipated Grand Theft Auto 6 trailer came with a Bitcoin-buying plug, thanks to an anonymous leaker.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JP Morgan CEO Jamie Dimon Says Feds Should 'Close Down' Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208890</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208890/jp-morgan-ceo-jamie-dimon-close-down-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T20:15:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JP Morgan CEO has again slammed crypto and Bitcoin, saying he'd "close it down" if he were in charge of making laws.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FaZe Clan Founder Banks Says Ethereum Is 'Large Percentage' of His Net Worth]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208876</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208876/faze-clan-founder-banks-says-ethereum-large-percentage-net-worth"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T19:12:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Richard "FaZe Banks" Bengtson took to Instagram to boast that he recently dropped $200,000 on altcoins like Pepe, among other claims.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Flips Tesla, Meta, and BTC Hater Buffett's Berkshire Hathaway]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208854</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208854/btc-flip-tesla-meta-bitcoin-hater-buffetts-berkshire-hathaway"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T18:25:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin now ranks among the top 7 most valuable traded assets in the world—topping a financial giant led by BTC skeptic Warren Buffett.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Is Surging—Is It Up Only From Here?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208844</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208844/bitcoin-surging-up-only-from-here"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T17:21:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Analysts say that Bitcoin could just continue to go up in price as institutions and excitement surround a spot Bitcoin ETF have caused a rally.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond Bard: Google Launches Gemini, a Multimodal AI to Challenge ChatGPT]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208845</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208845/beyond-bard-google-launches-gemini-a-multimodal-ai-to-challenge-chatgpt"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T16:58:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At first glance, Gemini demonstrates unprecedented capabilities in understanding and integrating text, image, audio, and video.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Gaming Platform Portal Adds Rockstar Co-Founder Amid Airdrop Frenzy]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208747</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208747/portal-foundation-adds-rockstar-games-cofounder-amid-airdrop-push"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Exclusive: One of the original minds behind the Grand Theft Auto franchise has joined Portal, a cross-platform gaming token project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Marks 10th Anniversary, Hits $0.10 For First Time in a Year]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208813</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208813/dogecoin-marks-10th-anniversary-hits-0-10-for-first-time-in-a-year"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T09:43:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dog-themed meme coin Dogecoin marked its 10th anniversary with a double-digit surge that carried its price to a yearly high over $0.10.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tech Titans Assemble: IBM and Meta Lead 50+ Organizations in New AI Alliance]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208762</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208762/tech-titans-assemble-ibm-and-meta-lead-50-organizations-in-new-ai-alliance"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T01:36:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tech giants form yet another coalition to champion open source AI innovation and development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GTA 6 Preview: Everything You Need to Know About the New Grand Theft Auto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154049</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154049/grand-theft-auto-6-release-date-rumors-leaks-news"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T00:44:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATE: The first Grand Theft Auto 6 trailer is officially live, confirming a number of the GTA leaks and rumors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Flying High: Why Bitcoin Fans Are Buzzing About Hitting $42,069]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208727</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208727/flying-high-why-bitcoin-fans-buzzing-hitting-42069"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T23:54:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin broke past the fabled meme number this week, sparking hopes that the cryptocurrency might soon ascend to the promised land of $69,420.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Wonderful Afterlife? AI Recreates Jimmy Stewart's Voice for Holiday Story]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208728</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208728/jimmy-stewart-ai-voice-recreation-calm-app-wonderful-life"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T23:11:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The distinctive vocals of the Hollywood legend have been brought back to narrate a new bedtime track in the Calm app.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Send a Selfie to See Porn? UK Ponders Ways to Age-Gate Adult Sites]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208719</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208719/uk-ofcom-age-gate-porn-ai-selfie-evaluation"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T21:56:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A European telecom regulator floats using AI to analyze selfies of web surfers to determine if they’re old enough to see stuff.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Is Talking to Bitcoin ETF Contenders—Here’s What It's Likely Saying]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208717</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208717/sec-talking-bitcoin-etf-contenders-what-its-saying"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T21:56:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What has the SEC been saying in discussions with Bitcoin ETF applicants? Recent changes in amended filings provide a few clues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Prime Is Giving Out Free Card Packs for NFT Game 'Gods Unchained']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208712</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208712/amazon-prime-giving-out-free-card-packs-nft-game-gods-unchained"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T21:38:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prime subscribers can now claim card packs for Immutable NFT game Gods Unchained, with six months of free items planned via Amazon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Delays Grayscale Ethereum ETF, Confirms Receipt of BlackRock ETH Fund]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208707</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208707/sec-pushes-grayscale-ethereum-etf-decision-into-2024"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T21:13:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale will have to wait until late January 2024 to learn the fate of its request to covert its Ethereum trust into an ETF.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Kawailani Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum NFT Creators Scramble to Secure Projects From Thirdweb Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208690</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208690/ethereum-nft-creators-scramble-secure-projects-thirdweb-exploit"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T20:34:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prominent Ethereum NFT marketplaces and project creators are taking steps to mitigate a serious smart contract issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[X.AI, Elon Musk's AI Play, Files for $1 Billion Equity Offering]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208687</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208687/1-billion-x-ai-elon-musk-security-offering-sec-filing"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T19:42:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Would-be investors need at least $2 million to participate, with nearly $135 million already sold.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Kawailani Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Director Jordan Bayne on the State of Film3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZLoEDkL9/director-jordan-bayne-on-the-state-of-film3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZLoEDkL9/director-jordan-bayne-on-the-state-of-film3"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T00:11:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the 2023 Film3 Summit, Jordan Bayne—director and founder of The Squad—spoke with Decrypt's Sander Lutz about how the Film3 world has progressed over the last year and what decentralized technologies can offer to creators that want to buck the Hollywood system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Questions With SCENE: Phil Mohun]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TwOjXfOR/5-questions-with-scene-phil-mohun</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TwOjXfOR/5-questions-with-scene-phil-mohun"/>
        <updated>2023-12-01T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bright Moments co-founder Phil Mohun joins 5 Questions With SCENE to recount some favorite moments from the road, including negotiating with Patagonian gauchos, falling in love with Tokyo, and gaining a newfound appreciation for shrooms chocolate bars.

Shot and edited by Vincent Roazzi Jr.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are NFTs Ever Coming Back?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qLmFpNKE/are-nfts-ever-coming-back</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qLmFpNKE/are-nfts-ever-coming-back"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T18:38:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this weeks episode we sit down with Cashtro from Arcade.xyz to discuss NFTs, shitcoins, what collections have held onto their floor prices, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Summit: Will Web3 Gaming Ever be Mainstream?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OvVWhGbW/web-summit-will-web3-gaming-ever-be-mainstream</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OvVWhGbW/web-summit-will-web3-gaming-ever-be-mainstream"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T19:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animoca Brands CEO Robby Yung, EndeavorXR CEO Amy Peck and Gamee co-founder CEO Bozena Rezab joined Decrypt's Stephen Graves on stage at Web Summit to talk about the future of Web3 gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Allie Eve Knox on Spankchain and the life of a Crypto Financial Dominatrix]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/16rVeg6o/allie-eve-knox-on-spankchain-and-the-life-of-a-crypto-financial-dominatrix</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/16rVeg6o/allie-eve-knox-on-spankchain-and-the-life-of-a-crypto-financial-dominatrix"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T21:20:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the first IRL episode of This Time Will Be Different!

In this week's episode, our host, Reza Jafery, is joined by Allie Eve Knox, the Spankchain Chief of Staff and FinDomme. 

They discuss
- How to sell feet pics
- If crypto is really as permissionless as it seems
- the intersections between crypto and sex work]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Questions With SCENE: Jeff Davis]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PChJu1R8/5-questions-with-scene-jeff-davis</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PChJu1R8/5-questions-with-scene-jeff-davis"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artist Jeff Davis joins 5 Questions with SCENE to answer burning questions about his artistic practice, the path that brought him to Art Blocks, and his quietly sophisticated DJ abilities.

Video shot and edited by Vincent Roazzi Jr.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Heatbit Founder Alex Busarov on the Bitcoin Miner That Heats Your Home]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DJuHqcGT/heatbit-founder-alex-busarov-on-the-bitcoin-miner-that-heats-your-home</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DJuHqcGT/heatbit-founder-alex-busarov-on-the-bitcoin-miner-that-heats-your-home"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T18:12:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt joined Heatbit founder Alex Busarov at Web Summit for a walkthrough of the firm's flagship product, a Bitcoin miner that acts as a domestic space heater—aimed at the casual user.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nym CEO Harry Halpin on Privacy, Decentralized VPNs and Tornado Cash]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/aLTtY2aq/nym-ceo-harry-halpin-on-privacy-decentralized-vpns-and-tornado-cash</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/aLTtY2aq/nym-ceo-harry-halpin-on-privacy-decentralized-vpns-and-tornado-cash"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T18:08:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The founder of privacy-preserving mixnet Nym sat down with Decrypt at Web Summit to talk about its new decentralized VPN, the Web3 privacy landscape and why "devs should be defended" in the wake of the Tornado Cash crackdown.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pat Felder - The worst is over [Macro Deep Dive Episode]]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MdcKPVo0/pat-felder-the-worst-is-over-macro-deep-dive-episode</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MdcKPVo0/pat-felder-the-worst-is-over-macro-deep-dive-episode"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T17:10:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the first Markets Edition of This Time Will Be Different! In this episode we dive into the current macroeconomic conditions around crypto and look at the data behind the price action. 


Reza sits down with Pat Felder, founder of Prismatic Capital to discuss the current macro environment, and to answer the question on everyone's mind-- is the bear market really over?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Sandbox Co-Founder Sebastien Borget: 'We're Already Integrating AI']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/HlARjhG1/the-sandbox-co-founder-sebastien-borget-were-already-integrating-ai</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/HlARjhG1/the-sandbox-co-founder-sebastien-borget-were-already-integrating-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T16:09:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt sat down with The Sandbox co-founder Sebastien Borget at Web Summit to talk about AI, the open metaverse and the creative challenges of interoperability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dacoco CEO Saro McKenna: How Alien Worlds is Creating an AI-Powered 'Lore DAO' with Kevin J Anderson]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QrQTrsjH/dacoco-ceo-saro-mckenna-how-alien-worlds-is-creating-an-ai-powered-lore-dao-with-kevin-j-anderson</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QrQTrsjH/dacoco-ceo-saro-mckenna-how-alien-worlds-is-creating-an-ai-powered-lore-dao-with-kevin-j-anderson"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T16:06:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt joined Dacoco CEO Sarojini McKenna at Web Summit 2023 to talk about Alien Worlds' new Lore DAO and its AI-powered collaboration with sci-fi author Kevin J Anderson.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avalon's Jeffrey Butler on Designing a Metaverse MMO That Lets Players Co-Create]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XDz9vsvT/avalons-jeffrey-butler-on-designing-a-metaverse-mmo-that-lets-players-co-create</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XDz9vsvT/avalons-jeffrey-butler-on-designing-a-metaverse-mmo-that-lets-players-co-create"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T00:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avalon Chief Product Officer Jeffrey Butler speaks with Decrypt reporter Jason Nelson and details his studio's new MMO game with interoperable assets—and how it will enable players to create and monetize their own content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Gen Z Is Different: OTK Chief Strategy Officer Talks Creator Economy Shift and Rise of Kick]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PieshbpH/how-gen-z-is-different-otk-chief-strategy-officer-talks-creator-economy-shift-and-rise-of-kick</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PieshbpH/how-gen-z-is-different-otk-chief-strategy-officer-talks-creator-economy-shift-and-rise-of-kick"/>
        <updated>2023-11-10T18:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One True King, an esports and gaming lifestyle brand and media company, was founded by creators like Asmongold and Mizkif. OTK's Chief Strategy Officer Zachary Diaz, who previously worked at TikTok and Twitch, shares with Decrypt's Kate Irwin about how the creator economy is changing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moisés Zamora on Videomart and Bucking the Hollywood System]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kyjQCle8/moises-zamora-on-videomart-and-bucking-the-hollywood-system</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kyjQCle8/moises-zamora-on-videomart-and-bucking-the-hollywood-system"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T17:11:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Selena: The Series" creator and co-showrunner Moisés Zamora joins Decrypt's Sander Lutz at the Film3 Summit 2023 to discuss why the Hollywood system is broken and why he founded the Videomart NFT digital film marketplace to give creators more power.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why OTK Is Making Video Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/1NCV4Fk0/why-otk-is-making-video-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/1NCV4Fk0/why-otk-is-making-video-games"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One True King (OTK) Chief Strategy Officer Zachary Diaz tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about OTK's long-term strategy and vision to become a content creator-powered media and video games company.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Questions With SCENE: LoVid]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/E8BZZBWX/5-questions-with-scene-lovid</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/E8BZZBWX/5-questions-with-scene-lovid"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T21:47:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artistic duo LoVid, aka Tali Hinkis and Kyle Lapidus, joins 5 Questions with SCENE to answer burning questions about art, lettuce, and the hellscape (in someone’s opinion) that is Miami.

Video shot and edited by Vincent Roazzi Jr.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Barney on DeFi, Privacy, and Vega]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/hgDzjboU/barney-on-defi-privacy-and-vega</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/hgDzjboU/barney-on-defi-privacy-and-vega"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T18:27:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week our host is joined by Barney the founder of Vega Protocol. 

They discuss the current state of DeFi, what's wrong with the apps being built today, whether or not privacy matters when its only applied to an L2, and most importantly-- which form of sales tax is the sexiest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>