<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-04-07T13:17:28.525Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-04-07T13:17:28.525Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 5 VR sports games]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18061576/Top-5-VR-sports-games</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18061576/Top-5-VR-sports-games"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T13:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Experience realistic sports gameplay with stunning graphics, from martial arts to football.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ordinals Are Good For Bitcoin, But More Standards Are Needed]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75200444fa</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/bitcoin-ordinals-need-standards"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T13:05:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ordinals are driving a Bitcoin popularity surge, but for that to continue the protocol will need to integrate more standards.
This is an opinion editorially by Danny Yang, founder of the Stanford Bitcoin Meetup, who has inscribed the OnChainMonkey NFT collection on Bitcoin.
In the last few years, NFTs have been the breakout application for Ethereum and other blockchains. While much of this mainstream user base did leave with the drop in NFT prices, many have stayed. But the initial surge in NFT interest drew most of these users to blockchain projects aside from Bitcoin, even though BTC is the largest cryptocurrency by market cap (which is twice the size of Ethereum’s) and it has the highest level of security and the most proven capacity as a store of value. Unsurprisingly, a protocol like …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Yang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Europe’s digital ID wallet — Easy for users or a data privacy nightmare?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18061577/Europes-digital-ID-wallet-Easy-for-users-or-a-data-privacy-nightmare</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18061577/Europes-digital-ID-wallet-Easy-for-users-or-a-data-privacy-nightmare"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T13:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[European Union lawmakers are planning an EU-wide digital identity wallet for access to essential services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here's how much is lost to crypto hacks and exploits in Q1 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18061543/Heres-how-much-is-lost-to-crypto-hacks-and-exploits-in-Q1-2023</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18061543/Heres-how-much-is-lost-to-crypto-hacks-and-exploits-in-Q1-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BNB Chain had the largest number of incidents in the quarter, while Ethereum had the biggest amount lost.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin trades steady following lower unemployment than expected in jobs data]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18061550/Bitcoin-trades-steady-following-lower-unemployment-than-expected-in-jobs-data</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18061550/Bitcoin-trades-steady-following-lower-unemployment-than-expected-in-jobs-data"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T12:54:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin held steady following a near miss on expected jobs added. On the release of employment data, the leading cryptocurrency recorded a 0.5% swing in the 13:30 (BST) 15-minute candle, topping out at $27,980. The U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics employment report showed 236,000 nonfarm jobs...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Adds 236K Jobs in March Versus Forecasts for 239K]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7520068ac9</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/04/07/us-adds-236k-jobs-in-march-versus-forecasts-for-239k/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T12:49:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin rose/fell to $XX,XXX in the minutes following the report.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen  Alpher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP price eyes 30% upside after key resistance area breaks]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18061544/XRP-price-eyes-30-upside-after-key-resistance-area-breaks</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18061544/XRP-price-eyes-30-upside-after-key-resistance-area-breaks"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T12:48:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More gains for XRP price appear likely due to a classic bullish continuation pattern alongside strong whale accumulation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Failure of Government Economic Policy with Dan Tubb]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18061584/The-Failure-of-Government-Economic-Policy-with-Dan-Tubb</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18061584/The-Failure-of-Government-Economic-Policy-with-Dan-Tubb"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T12:44:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SHOW NOTES:https://www.whatbitcoindid.com/podcast/the-failure-of-government-economic-policyDan Tubb is a podcaster and former venture capitalist. In this interview, we discuss the problems with fixing the sovereign debt problem in the context of broken media, broken politics and broken...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Technical Analysis: BTC, ETH Extend Consolidation, Ahead of Nonfarm Payrolls]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7520076fb9</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-ethereum-technical-analysis-btc-eth-extend-consolidation-ahead-of-nonfarm-payrolls/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T12:42:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin consolidated for a third consecutive session on Friday, hours before a much anticipated nonfarm payrolls (NFP) release. Many are expecting that payrolls will come in under the 240,000 expected sum, following recent disappointing labor data. Ethereum was also largely unchanged as of writing.
 
Bitcoin
 
Bitcoin (BTC) consolidated for a third consecutive session on Friday, as the global cryptocurrency market cap remains largely unchanged at the time of writing.
 
Following a high of $28,178.30 on Thursday, BTC/USD fell marginally lower in today’s session, hitting a bottom of $27,765.34.
 
Markets have mostly been muted following last week’s ten-month high, however a target of $30,000 still remains a short-term possibility.
 
 
Bitcoin chart by TradingView
 

 
 

 
From the chart, today’s action comes as the relative strength index (RSI) continues to hover close to a floor at 58.00
 
As of writing, the index is tracking at 58.37, with the 10-day (red) moving average now on the brink of a downwards cross with its 25-day (blue) counterpart.
 
Should today’s NFP beat expectations, resulting in a stronger U.S. Dollar, we could see this crossover take place, sending BTC lower.
 
 
Ethereum
 
Ethereum (ETH) was largely unchanged in today’s session, as the world’s second largest cryptocurrency remained near $1,850.
 
ETH/USD is trading at $1,854.27 at the time of writing, after falling to a low of $1,846.82 earlier in the day.
 
This comes just two days after ethereum rose to its strongest point since last August, climbing over $1,900 in the process.
 
 
Ethereum chart by TradingView
 

 
 

 
The decline came as ETH bulls were unable to prevent the RSI from moving below a support point at 60.00.
 
Currently, price strength is tracking around 58.67, with a floor of 57.00 a potential target, should momentum begin to decline.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
Do you expect a strong nonfarm payrolls report today? Leave your thoughts in the comments below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Adds 236K Jobs in March Versus Forecasts for 239K]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18061537/US-Adds-236K-Jobs-in-March-Versus-Forecasts-for-239K</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18061537/US-Adds-236K-Jobs-in-March-Versus-Forecasts-for-239K"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T12:38:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin rose/fell to $XX,XXX in the minutes following the report.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trading Titan Henrik Zeberg Reveals Key Ingredient Needed for Altcoin Season]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18061518/Trading-Titan-Henrik-Zeberg-Reveals-Key-Ingredient-Needed-for-Altcoin-Season</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18061518/Trading-Titan-Henrik-Zeberg-Reveals-Key-Ingredient-Needed-for-Altcoin-Season"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Altcoin season's missing ingredient revealed, macro expert Henrik Zeberg explains what's needed]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US presidential candidate Robert Kennedy says FedNow is first step to banning Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18061506/US-presidential-candidate-Robert-Kennedy-says-FedNow-is-first-step-to-banning-Bitcoin</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18061506/US-presidential-candidate-Robert-Kennedy-says-FedNow-is-first-step-to-banning-Bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T12:28:36.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sandbox (SAND) Loses Ground as Metaverse Hype Fizzles, More Price Drop Ahead?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18061514/Sandbox-SAND-Loses-Ground-as-Metaverse-Hype-Fizzles-More-Price-Drop-Ahead</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18061514/Sandbox-SAND-Loses-Ground-as-Metaverse-Hype-Fizzles-More-Price-Drop-Ahead"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T12:27:02.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin: US Presidential Contender Fears Crypto Ban Due To Fed’s CBDC Plans]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7520023e01</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/us-presidential-contender-fears-bitcoin-ban/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T12:21:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) may face the threat of being banned and seized by the US government if plans for a central bank digital currency (CBDC) come to fruition, warns Robert F. Kennedy Jr. on Twitter. 
 
Kennedy Jr.s’ tweets on the matter came as he filed documents with the US Federal Election Commission to run for office in 2024, with an official announcement expected on April 19 in Boston, Massachusetts. 
 
This raises the question: will the growing popularity of Bitcoin lead to its downfall?
 
 
Kennedy Jr. Warns Of CBDC’s Potential To Lead To ‘Financial Slavery, Political Tyranny’
 
The potential introduction of the Federal Reserve’s “FedNow” CBDC in July has raised concerns for the Democratic presidential hopeful, who sees it as a gateway to “financial slavery and political tyranny.” 
 
Kenned…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon (MATIC) Becomes Second-Largest Gaming Blockchain in March After Surge in Activity: DappRadar]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18061460/Polygon-MATIC-Becomes-Second-Largest-Gaming-Blockchain-in-March-After-Surge-in-Activity-DappRadar</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18061460/Polygon-MATIC-Becomes-Second-Largest-Gaming-Blockchain-in-March-After-Surge-in-Activity-DappRadar"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T11:45:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Layer-2 scaling solution Polygon (MATIC) is establishing a name in the gaming sector following impressive growth in daily unique active wallets (dUAW) last month. According to blockchain intelligence platform DappRadar, Polygon recorded 138,081 dUAWs in March marking an increase of 53% from the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Swiss State-Owned Banking Giant Postfinance to Offer Crypto Services]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75200f60f4</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/swiss-state-owned-banking-giant-postfinance-to-offer-crypto-services/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T11:42:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Postfinance, one of Switzerland’s largest retail banks, will offer customers access to major cryptocurrencies and related services. The state-owned financial institution will be using the banking platform developed by the Swiss-licensed digital asset bank Sygnum. 
 
Postfinance Partners With Sygnum to Provide Digital Asset Products and Services
 
The financial services unit of the national postal service of Switzerland, Postfinance, has joined forces with crypto bank Sygnum to offer a range of digital asset banking services. To achieve that, the bank will employ Sygnum’s B2B (business-to-business) banking platform.
 
The partnership enables the launch and expansion of regulated bank-grade products and services for digital assets, Sygnum said in an announcement published Wednesday. The Swit…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lubomir Tassev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Self-proclaimed Satoshi accuses Apple of violating copyright by putting Bitcoin white paper on MacBooks]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18061450/Self-proclaimed-Satoshi-accuses-Apple-of-violating-copyright-by-putting-Bitcoin-white-paper-on-MacBooks</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18061450/Self-proclaimed-Satoshi-accuses-Apple-of-violating-copyright-by-putting-Bitcoin-white-paper-on-MacBooks"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T11:36:38.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthony Scaramucci: This is the Beginning of a New Era for Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18061447/Anthony-Scaramucci-This-is-the-Beginning-of-a-New-Era-for-Bitcoin</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18061447/Anthony-Scaramucci-This-is-the-Beginning-of-a-New-Era-for-Bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthony Scaramucci, SkyBridge Capital's founder, predicts Bitcoin will hit $1 million by 2030. His firm bets on digital assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korea's ‘Malicious Cyber Activities’ Deeply Concerning, Say US, Japan, South Korea: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125683</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125683/north-koreas-malicious-cyber-activities-deeply-concerning-say-us-japan-south-korea-report"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T11:26:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[High-level diplomats have urged the global community to ensure the repatriation of all North Korean nationals working abroad.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do Kwon's Millions Are Not in South Korea, Prosecutors Say: Report]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e752009c4d2</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/04/07/do-kwons-millions-are-not-in-south-korea-prosecutors-say-report/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T11:25:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[South Korea requested the extradition of the Terraform Labs CEO after his recent arrest in Montenegro.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandali Handagama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do Kwon's Millions Are Not in South Korea, Prosecutors Say: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18061426/Do-Kwons-Millions-Are-Not-in-South-Korea-Prosecutors-Say-Report</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18061426/Do-Kwons-Millions-Are-Not-in-South-Korea-Prosecutors-Say-Report"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T11:16:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[South Korea requested the extradition of the Terraform Labs CEO after his recent arrest in Montenegro.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood Reaches $10M Settlement with State Securities Regulators for Failing Investors]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18061424/Robinhood-Reaches-10M-Settlement-with-State-Securities-Regulators-for-Failing-Investors</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18061424/Robinhood-Reaches-10M-Settlement-with-State-Securities-Regulators-for-Failing-Investors"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T11:15:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinspeaker Robinhood Reaches $10M Settlement with State Securities Regulators for Failing Investors Multifaceted trading platform Robinhood will pay the $10 million fine to DFPI following an investigation by NASAA. Robinhood Reaches $10M Settlement with State Securities Regulators for Failing Investors]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitget Features GoSleep (ZZZ) on Launchpad and Introduces Sunshine Pool]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75200bb324</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitget-features-gosleep-zzz-on-launchpad-and-introduces-sunshine-pool/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T11:10:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. Victoria, Seychelles 7 Apr 2023 – Bitget, the leading crypto derivatives exchange and copy trading platform, has announced a new round of launchpad listing featuring GoSleep (ZZZ), the leading Web3 sleep and healthy living reward app on Arbitrum. The launchpad tickets for ZZZ token will be allocated on Apr 17, with the deposit period starting on Apr 10. In this round of launchpad, Bitget has also introduced the sunshine pool, which is specially designed to provide fair opportunities for more participants to get allocations.
 
Bitget’s Launchpad was initially introduced in February 2022, and as of now, it has launched eight early-stage projects with a price increase of up to 14950% in the first week of their listing. Previously, Launchpad featured REVO, BBO, and HALO, offerin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Repayments From Mt. Gox Begin, Will It Affect The BTC Price?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7521f4ffb2</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-repayments-from-mt-gox-begin/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T11:01:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The rehabilitation trustee of the exchange Mt. Gox that went bankrupt in 2014, Nobuaki Kobayashi has published a new letter today regarding the repayments of the recovered Bitcoin. In it, Kobayashi informs that the deadline for creditors to submit their repayment information passed yesterday, April 6, 2023.
 
After several years of delays, the window thus opens for Bitcoin repayments, which are expected to be made by October 31, 2023. The letter also states that the rehabilitation trustee is currently making the necessary preparations for the repayments.
 
This includes, among other things, Kobayashi contacting banks, money transfer providers and cryptocurrency exchanges and custodians to clarify repayment arrangements:
 

[…] which include the confirmation of the selection and registratio…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rep. Emmer on Why He Believes Gary Gensler Is a ‘Bad-Faith Regulator’ - Ep. 478]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18061394/Rep-Emmer-on-Why-He-Believes-Gary-Gensler-Is-a-Bad-Faith-Regulator-Ep-478</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18061394/Rep-Emmer-on-Why-He-Believes-Gary-Gensler-Is-a-Bad-Faith-Regulator-Ep-478"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simply Sessions News Roundup | EP 1]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18054256/Simply-Sessions-News-Roundup-EP-1</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18054256/Simply-Sessions-News-Roundup-EP-1"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T10:59:25.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Repayments From Mt. Gox Begin, Will It Affect The BTC Price?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18061369/Bitcoin-Repayments-From-Mt-Gox-Begin-Will-It-Affect-The-BTC-Price</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18061369/Bitcoin-Repayments-From-Mt-Gox-Begin-Will-It-Affect-The-BTC-Price"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T10:55:19.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reddit Readies Third Round of NFT Avatars, But Is the Hype Over?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18061383/Reddit-Readies-Third-Round-of-NFT-Avatars-But-Is-the-Hype-Over</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18061383/Reddit-Readies-Third-Round-of-NFT-Avatars-But-Is-the-Hype-Over"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T10:49:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reddit is ready to release the third installment of its 'Collectible Avatars.' The GEN 3 NFTs will launch in the week of April 10.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Warning To Bitcoin Investors | The Reason Bitcoin Is Still In A Bear Market]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18061390/A-Warning-To-Bitcoin-Investors-The-Reason-Bitcoin-Is-Still-In-A-Bear-Market</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18061390/A-Warning-To-Bitcoin-Investors-The-Reason-Bitcoin-Is-Still-In-A-Bear-Market"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T10:49:51.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Head of Thailand’s Opposition Party Promises $300 Crypto Airdrop if Elected Prime Minister: Report]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7521fc3343</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/04/07/head-of-thailands-opposition-party-promises-300-crypto-airdrop-if-elected-prime-minister/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T10:08:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Local stakeholders call the move a “marketing gimmick” while others say its the most efficient way to mass distribute economic stimulus.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Which Crypto Transactions Are NOT Taxable? How To Minimize Your Crypto Taxes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125680</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/dont-overpay-your-crypto-taxes-decrypt-learn-article"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T10:07:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Doing your crypto taxes can be a lot less stressful if you know how to minimize your tax burden.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kade Garrett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former US President Donald Trump States China Is ‘Trying to Replace the Dollar as Number One Currency’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7521ffb5ed</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/former-us-president-donald-trump-states-china-is-trying-to-replace-the-dollar-as-number-one-currency/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T09:40:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former U.S. President Donald Trump has acknowledged the push that China is making to dethrone the dollar as a reserve currency. In a post published on Truth Social, Trump stated that if this comes to happen, it would be the biggest defeat in the history of the U.S. in the last 200 years.
Donald Trump Alerts About China’s Push Against the U.S. Dollar
Donald Trump, former president of the U.S. has recognized the recent moves that China and other countries including Russia and Saudi Arabia are taking to undermine the influence of the dollar in worked markets. In a post published in Truth Social, the social platform founded by Trump, he acknowledged these developments, stating:
China is trying to displace the U.S. dollar as the number one currency throughout the world. If this happens, and und…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The anti-crypto army is going to war]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7521f82b5a</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/the-anti-crypto-army-is-going-to-war/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T09:36:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto has often come across as apolitical. This is partly due to being seen as existing outside regular financial systems and, going back through crypto history, being outside regular systems really meant that, with early enthusiasts acquiring bitcoin peer-to-peer, sometimes even physically meeting up with sellers and paying in cash.
  
Such personal mechanisms don’t scale up to mass adoption, but they are bedded in the perception that Bitcoin, and crypto more widely, are separated from banking, financial services and, relatedly, from politics.
  
Times have changed though, and debate recently has centered on crypto’s access (or lack of access) to banking services and fiat on/off ramps. And, any perceived separation from politics is becoming a bygone chapter, as we increasingly see crypto…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam White</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood Faces $10.2M Penalty From Multiple U.S. States Over Technical Failures, Investor Harm]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7521e629a7</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/04/07/robinhood-faces-102m-penalty-from-multiple-us-states-over-technical-failures-investor-harm/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T08:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The settlement follows an investigation into Robinhood platform outages in March 2020 spearheaded by a regulators in seven states including California and Alabama.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandali Handagama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will The Swiss National Bank Buy Bitcoin? New Interview Causes A Stir]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7521ed8568</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-very-interesting-concept-swiss-snb/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T07:46:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Vice President of the Swiss National Bank (SNB) Martin Schlegel has caused a stir in the Bitcoin community with a new remark in a TV interview. Schlegel was asked to complete the sentences of the Swiss presenter who said, “I consider Bitcoin…”. And Schlegel added: “a very interesting concept.”
 
Even though this was his only statement regarding Bitcoin, it gives an interesting insight into the current view of the Swiss National Bank. The statement implies that the SNB is curious about the technology and the potential use of Bitcoin. However, it does not mean that it supports or opposes BTC.
 
Still, the statement is notable because a US Federal Reserve (Fed) or European Central Bank (ECB) could never admit that the number one cryptocurrency is an “interesting concept.” Instead, ECB Pre…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Luxury Brand Ralph Lauren Now Accepting Crypto Payments at Its New Miami Store]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7521ee2392</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/luxury-brand-ralph-lauren-now-accepting-crypto-payments-at-its-new-miami-store/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T07:41:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. luxury brand Ralph Lauren has said customers can now pay via crypto at its Miami Design District location. The store has also been designated the luxury brand’s focal point for Web3 promotions. Bitcoin, ethereum, and polygon are among the cryptocurrencies that are accepted at Ralph Lauren’s new store in Miami.
 
Miami Store Ralph Lauren’s Web3 Promotions Focal Point
 

 
United States luxury brand Ralph Lauren said on April 5 that it will accept crypto payments at its new store in Miami. According to a statement released by Bitpay, Ralph Lauren customers can now pay at this store using BTC, ETH, MATIC, and twelve other cryptocurrencies.
 

 
 
Introducing our new #RLMiami store, the first Ralph Lauren store to accept cryptocurrency as a form of payment.
 
In partnership with @BitP…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BYDFi Review: Turning Your Crypto Trading Dreams to a Reality]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7521eea6b7</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bydfi-review-turning-your-crypto-trading-dreams-to-a-reality/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T07:36:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Choosing a reliable and safe crypto trading platform can prove confusing for traders, especially with bad players and untrustworthy firms all over the market. Moreover, there are thousands of cryptocurrencies in the market, of which most exchanges support less than a hundred. As such, finding one with your favorite trading pairs on the right platform could be a hard nut to crack but not impossible.
 
So, if you’re searching for a reliable crypto trading platform for advanced trading services to achieve your financial goals, BYDFi is your go-to exchange.
 
What is BYDFi? 
BYDFi is a global cryptocurrency trading platform that offers an advanced range of crypto products and services. On the BYDFi platform, you can access services like crypto spots, derivatives, and copy trading. BYDFi has be…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Schiff on the Upcoming Gold Bull Market and Wall Street: ‘It Will Be Spectacular, Capitulation Will Be Epic’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7521d2fe8b</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/peter-schiff-on-the-upcoming-gold-bull-market-and-wall-street-it-will-be-spectacular-capitulation-will-be-epic/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T05:39:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Schiff, economist and known gold bug, believes that the price uptick that gold is currently experiencing will extend in the future, surprising stock traders. Schiff stated that gold stocks were the new tech stocks and that Wall Street’s indifference regarding these would lead to massive market capitulation.
Peter Schiff Warns of Gold Rally: ‘It’s Real’
Peter Schiff, the chief economist of Europac and gold permabull, believes that a gold bull market brewing will take the precious metal to even higher prices than it reached. Motivated by the recent breakout that took gold prices to break the $2,000 mark on April 4, Schiff stated:
Senior miners still need to rise by over 20% and juniors by over 25% to hit new 52-week highs. The divergence is due to negative sentiment. Investors still do…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Difficulty Reaches New All-Time High After Fourth Consecutive Increase]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7521c5328d</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-difficulty-reaches-new-all-time-high-after-fourth-consecutive-increase/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T03:49:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On April 6, 2023, Bitcoin’s difficulty rose 2.23% higher at block height 784,224, touching another all-time high. It’s the fourth consecutive difficulty increase on the Bitcoin network since Feb. 24, and the protocol’s current difficulty is 47.89 trillion, which is only 2.11 trillion away from reaching the 50 trillion range.
 
Bitcoin Difficulty Jumps 2.23% Higher
 
Bitcoin’s current difficulty of approximately 47.89 trillion is an all-time high, meaning it has never been harder for bitcoin miners to find blocks. The current Bitcoin protocol difficulty level mandates that miners execute roughly 47.89 trillion computations via a trial-and-error approach to discover a cryptographic hash value that fulfills the predetermined criteria for every appended block in the blockchain.
 
The difficult…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former BitMex CEO Arthur Hayes Calls His Maelstrom Capital a ‘Very Patient’ Fund]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7521c072b8</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/04/07/former-bitmex-ceo-arthur-hayes-calls-his-maelstrom-capital-a-very-patient-fund/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T03:12:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hayes wants Maelstrom Capital to outperform bitcoin and ether, which won’t be easy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 YouTuber CryptoStache: Gaming Will Be the Catalyst That Takes NFTs Mainstream]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Exb7eWKj/web3-youtuber-cryptostache-gaming-will-be-the-catalyst-that-takes-nfts-mainstream</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Exb7eWKj/web3-youtuber-cryptostache-gaming-will-be-the-catalyst-that-takes-nfts-mainstream"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T02:51:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 gaming YouTuber CryptoStache talks to Decrypt's Jason Nelson at Outer Edge LA about why Web3 gaming will bring NFTs mainstream, the partnerships that prove it's already happening, how gamers will change their tune on NFTs, and how the terminology is likely to change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fordefi Aims to Dramatically Simplify the Institutional Crypto Wallet]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/LGxyFJP5/fordefi-aims-to-dramatically-simplify-the-institutional-crypto-wallet</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/LGxyFJP5/fordefi-aims-to-dramatically-simplify-the-institutional-crypto-wallet"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T02:39:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Steve H., VP of sales from Fordefi, which raised $18 million in funding last year, tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson at Outer Edge LA how Fordefi uses multi-party computation to make signing transactions on an institutional crypto wallet much simpler—no seed phrase needed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Binance Asked to Provide More Information as Dubai Tightens Screws Against Crypto Entities]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7521c854d3</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/report-binance-asked-to-provide-more-information-as-dubai-tightens-screws-against-crypto-entities/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T01:40:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dubai’s Virtual Assets Regulatory Authority (VARA) has reportedly asked Binance to share more information about the crypto exchange’s ownership structure and its auditing procedures. According to reports, Dubai regulators are still keen on fostering innovation but without comprising the security of users’ funds. 
 
Binance Asked to Provide More Information
 
The collapse of the crypto exchange FTX prompted Dubai regulators to ask for more information from crypto license applicants such as Binance, a Bloomberg report has said. According to the April 5 report, officials from Dubai’s Virtual Assets Regulatory Authority (VARA) have in recent weeks told Binance, which already holds the minimal viable product license, to share more information concerning its ownership structure, governance, and …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Mover Asia: Bitcoin Is Flat, Ether in the Red, as a Long Weekend Begins]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7521c8b9ae</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/04/07/first-mover-asia-bitcoin-is-flat-ether-in-the-red-as-a-long-weekend-begins/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T01:36:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hayes wants Maelstrom Capital to outperform bitcoin and ether, which won’t be easy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Rubin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unreleased David Bowie Recording to Debut as Music NFT]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125653</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125653/unreleased-david-bowie-recording-debut-music-nft"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T23:28:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The never-before-heard version of Bowie's hit "Let’s Dance" will be sold via pay-what-you-want NFTs from Gala Music and benefit charity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Launches AI Tool That Can Identify, Separate Items in Pictures]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125660</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125660/meta-ai-artificial-intelligence-image-segmentation-segment-anything"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T23:09:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meta unveils "Segment Anything" AI image identification tool, but the scale of the dataset used by the social giant raises privacy concerns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Drops Sharply After Twitter Blue Bird Returns]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125649</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125649/dogecoin-drop-twitter-bird-returns"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T22:11:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Doge had a very short run as Twitter's new mascot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: Canadian Bitcoin Miner Hut 8 Is Heading West]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5AGD2ifd/gm-canadian-bitcoin-miner-hut-8-is-heading-west</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5AGD2ifd/gm-canadian-bitcoin-miner-hut-8-is-heading-west"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T21:40:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Toronto-based Bitcoin mining company Hut 8 recently announced a merger with U.S. Bitcoin Corp that will take it into Texas, Nebraska, and New York. Hut 8 CEO Jaime Leverton joined Dan Roberts and Stacy Elliott to talk expanding into the U.S., dealing with regulatory pushback post-FTX, why Texas is such a hotspot, and where she'd like to expand globally down the road (the climates may surprise you). Watch and make sure to subscribe to the gm podcast on Apple or Spotify.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT Picks Gold Over Bitcoin, Says Crypto Critic Peter Schiff]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125646</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125646/chatgpt-picks-gold-over-bitcoin-says-crypto-critic-peter-schiff"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T21:30:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT chooses to include gold, not Bitcoin, as part of its "recession-proof" portfolio.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lawyer Says He’s Called the FBI on Bitboy Over Threatening Emails, Calls and Tweets]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125630</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125630/lawyer-adam-moskowitz-fbi-bitboy-threatening-emails-calls"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T20:25:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After weeks of threatening messages, lawyer Adam Moskowitz says he fears that one of Bitboy’s followers might try to harm him and his family.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Treasury Says Crooks Prefer Fiat to Crypto in DeFi Risk Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125623</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125623/crooks-defi-crypto-fiat-treasury"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T18:50:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Treasury Department said in a Thursday report that criminals do indeed use DeFi tools and apps, but most criminal activity still opts for fiat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lawyers Claim Shaq Is Hiding From FTX Lawsuit, Seek Alternative Method to Serve Him]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125616</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125616/shaq-hiding-ftx-lawsuit-seek-alternative-method-serve"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T18:41:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shaquille O'Neal is a defendant in a lawsuit for promoting FTX, including Tom Brady and Larry David.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple's Hidden Bitcoin White Paper the Latest in a Long List of Easter Eggs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125612</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125612/apples-hidden-bitcoin-whitepaper-the-latest-in-a-long-list-of-easter-eggs"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T17:31:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The seminal document behind Bitcoin has been lurking in an innocuous file on Apple computers for years. Here's how to find it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Magic Eden Bitcoin NFT Launchpad Debuts as Ordinals Total Nears 1 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125599</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125599/magic-eden-bitcoin-nft-launchpad-ordinals"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T16:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Interest in Ordinals is going strong, and now NFT marketplace Magic Eden looks to further capitalize on the latest Bitcoin craze.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aragon’s New DAO Toolkit on Polygon Takes Aim at Voter Apathy]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125577</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125577/aragons-new-dao-toolkit-polygon-takes-aim-voter-apathy"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T14:10:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aragon’s recently launched tech stack is now live on Polygon, dropping costs for spinning up DAOs and taking aim at voter apathy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mutant Apes Take the Lead in Serum City, an ApeCoin-Powered Ethereum NFT Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125548</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125548/mutant-apes-take-lead-serum-city-apecoin-powered-ethereum-nft-game"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Novel Labs and Faraway are developing an independent city-building game that gives new life to Yuga Labs’ Mutant Ape Yacht Club NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Down 8% as Musk’s Twitter Hype Fades]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125588</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125588/dogecoin-down-twitter-hype-fades"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T13:27:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin has posted an intraday loss of roughly 8%, but it still has most of its Elon Musk-assisted gains over the last seven days.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Carolina County Mulls 1-Year Bitcoin Mining Moratorium]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125575</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125575/north-carolina-county-mulls-1-year-bitcoin-mining-moratorium"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T09:53:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 1-year moratorium on mining would give county officials more time to better establish clearer standards for the activity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Australia Financial Regulator Cancels Binance Derivatives Business License]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125572</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125572/financial-regulator-cancels-license-binances-derivatives-business-australia"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T08:57:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance requested the cancellation a day before Australia's securities regulator announced that it would end the license.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report Blasts Bitcoin Mining for Pollution—But Bitcoiners Aren’t Buying It]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125566</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125566/bitcoin-environmental-harm-report"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T01:08:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Environmental Working Group continues to rail against proof-of-work blockchains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Has Amazon Lost The AI Race?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125558</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125558/amazon-ai-artificial-intelligence-aws-accelerator"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T00:25:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite flagging demand for Alexa, experts say Amazon could still pull ahead of the pack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Bitcoin Stamps’ NFTs Are Gaining On Ordinals]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125556</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125556/bitcoin-stamps-nfts-are-gaining-on-ordinals"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T22:51:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The creator of the new protocol claims it is the “most permanent” means of inscribing data on the Bitcoin blockchain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Fears Grow as Germany, France, Sweden, and Canada Voice Concerns]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125540</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125540/ai-artificial-intelligence-national-bans-laws"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T22:33:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the wake of an outright ban of ChatGPT in Italy, governments are trying to balance innovation with protecting user privacy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Texas Still 'Very Open for Business' for Bitcoin Mining?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125545</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125545/is-texas-still-open-for-business-for-bitcoin-mining"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T22:11:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The state is a mining hot-spot, but a new bill limiting benefits got unanimous approval by a state Senate committee. Mining advocates are concerned.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Future of Paxful Bitcoin Exchange in Flux As Co-Founders Fight]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125527</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125527/founders-fight-paxful-bitcoin-exchange-future-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T21:54:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One wants to resume operation of the marketplace, the other is directing users to an alternative service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MobileCoin Exec Bob Lee Fatally Stabbed in San Francisco]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125516</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125516/bob-lee-mobilecoin-cash-app-death"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T18:44:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Cash App creator also led Google's Android team and helped combat the COVID-19 pandemic.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Reveals AI Tool to Help Brands Target Facebook, Instagram Users]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125512</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125512/meta-reveals-ai-tool-help-brands-target-facebook-instagram-users"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T18:28:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meta’s recent embrace of AI is only growing, with new plans for generative ads—and Meta’s CTO thinks AI will help power the metaverse, too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Cohen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy Buys More Bitcoin as Asset Nears Company’s Break Even Price]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125511</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125511/microstrategy-buys-more-bitcoin-break-even-price"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T18:20:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The software company is still buying up the cryptocurrency—which has soared in value since January.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Lollipop' NFT Racing Game From Filmmaker David Ayer Coming to Polygon]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125440</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125440/lollipop-nft-racing-game-from-filmmaker-david-ayer-coming-to-polygon"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T16:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feature.io tapped “The Fast and Furious” co-writer Ayer to write and produce the project, which is billed as an interactive media experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['District 9' Director Is Launching a Web3 Game—With a Dedicated Avalanche Subnet]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125447</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125447/filmmaker-neill-blomkamps-off-grid-game-dedicated-avalanche-subnet"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T15:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer Gunzilla Games and Neill Blomkamp will roll out the upcoming battle royale shooter via an Avalanche subnet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Batteries or Bitcoin: Is Mining the Best Use for ‘Excess’ Green Energy?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125482</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125482/batteries-bitcoin-is-mining-best-use-excess-green-energy"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T14:23:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin miners are quick to claim they're an asset to grids, while others suggest it’s not the best use of excess green energy. Which is it?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Krantz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinFLEX Founder Offers Bitcoin Evangelist Roger Ver ‘Olive Branch’ to Settle Alleged $84M Debt]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125501</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125501/coinflex-founder-offers-bitcoin-evangelist-roger-ver-olive-branch-settle-alleged-84m-debt"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T14:04:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CoinFLEX founder offered Ver and Blockchain.com’s CEO two years of free trading on OPNX should they settle their debts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Swiss Bank PostFinance to Roll Out Bitcoin, Ethereum Services for Clients]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125492</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125492/swiss-bank-postfinance-roll-out-bitcoin-ethereum-services-clients"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T10:34:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PostFinance is rolling out a range of crypto services through a new partnership with digital assets bank Sygnum.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum, LSD Tokens on the Rise Ahead of Next Week's Shanghai Upgrade]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125485</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125485/ethereum-lsd-tokens-rise-ahead-next-weeks-shapella-upgrade"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T09:49:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Ethereum’s next upgrade just around the corner, ETH and tokens powering liquid staking platforms are soaring.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tron Launches Dominica Metaverse Bound Token With Huobi]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=124671</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/124671/tron-launches-dominica-metaverse-bound-token-with-huobi"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T09:21:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The digital identity system lays the foundation for a metaverse “truly capable of servicing the global population.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Ethereum’s Shanghai Upgrade?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=120499</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-ethereums-shanghai-upgrade"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T08:56:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Shanghai fork will implement EIP-4895, which allows validators to withdraw ETH that have been staked since as long ago as December 2020.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Reiff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ultra’s New Web3 Gaming Marketplace Lets Users Resell Digital Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125471</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125471/ultras-new-web3-gaming-marketplace-lets-users-resell-digital-games"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T08:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gone are the days of digital games rotting in your Steam library—Ultra Games will let you sell them to other users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum’s ERC-4337 Standard: A Game-Changing, User-Friendly Innovation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125481</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/ethereums-erc-4337-standard-a-game-changing-user-friendly-innovation"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T07:46:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ERC-4337 standard enhances the functionality and user friendliness of Ethereum without requiring a change to the core blockchain protocol.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kade Garrett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free POAP? Not for Commercial Users of the Ethereum Attendance NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125462</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125462/paid-poap-proof-of-attendance-ethereum-nft"/>
        <updated>2023-04-04T23:22:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The "proof of attendance" badge provider says it will still waive fees for some projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Criminal’ Trump NFTs Rise as Former President Faces 34 Felony Charges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125450</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125450/criminal-trump-nfts-rise-as-former-president-faces-34-felony-charges"/>
        <updated>2023-04-04T22:55:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trump's own NFT trading cards are up—but so are these unauthorized knockoffs that show the former U.S. president locked up in prison.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFT Sales Near $2 Billion in March as Blur Dominates Market]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125444</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125444/nft-sales-near-2-billion-march-blur"/>
        <updated>2023-04-04T22:45:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March trading volume dips only slightly compared to February, but 69% of it came from a single marketplace.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Latin America’s Biggest Investment Bank Just Launched a Stablecoin on Polygon]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125420</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125420/latin-america-investment-bank-btg-pactual-stablecoin-polygon"/>
        <updated>2023-04-04T22:05:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brazil-based BTG Pactual today launched its BTG Dol stablecoin, a dollar-backed asset.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ralph Lauren Debuts In-Store Crypto Payments and NFT 'Gifts' in Miami]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125424</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125424/ralph-lauren-debuts-in-store-crypto-payments-amid-miami-focused-web3-push"/>
        <updated>2023-04-04T20:43:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fashion brand will use the Miami location to spearhead a push into the city's Web3 community with NFT-based activations experiences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: Kevin Owocki Wants to Regenerate DeFi]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/knbMLd17/gm-kevin-owocki-wants-to-regenerate-defi</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/knbMLd17/gm-kevin-owocki-wants-to-regenerate-defi"/>
        <updated>2023-04-01T14:23:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Move over, DeFi—ReFi is coming? Gitcoin founder Kevin Owocki has stepped away from DeFi grant-giving machine Gitcoin as it fully decentralizes and is now focused on regenerative finance (huh?) and ReFi incubator Supermodular. He aims to "regenerate the regenerators." He explained it all to Dan Roberts and Liam Kelly, and also talks DAO structure, crypto factions, NFT use cases, his book "Greenpilled," and much more. Watch and make sure to subscribe to the gm podcast on Apple or Spotify.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Aurory's Head of Production Left Ubisoft for Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PqJHF0N9/why-aurorys-head-of-production-left-ubisoft-for-web3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PqJHF0N9/why-aurorys-head-of-production-left-ubisoft-for-web3"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T21:24:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aurory executive producer and head of production Jonathan Campeau tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin at GDC about how the first-generation of Web3 games came out of DeFi and are now evolving.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['We Don't Really Do the Corporate Thing Very Well' Says Jason Brink on Gala Games Approach]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/EDzHoKrt/we-dont-really-do-the-corporate-thing-very-well-says-jason-brink-on-gala-games-approach</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/EDzHoKrt/we-dont-really-do-the-corporate-thing-very-well-says-jason-brink-on-gala-games-approach"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T21:14:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With roughly 50 video games in its pipeline, Gala Games is all-in on Web3. Gala's President of Blockchain Jason Brink told Decrypt's Kate Irwin at GDC about the studio's ethos and weighs in on the different approaches to Web3 gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: Coinbase's Top Lawyer Gets Real on SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mB7DMx7l/gm-coinbases-top-lawyer-gets-real-on-sec</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mB7DMx7l/gm-coinbases-top-lawyer-gets-real-on-sec"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T16:36:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paul Grewal is the Chief Legal Officer at Coinbase and a former U.S. magistrate judge in Northern California. He gave Dan Roberts and Stacy Elliott his candid takes on Sam Bankman-Fried and FTX, the SEC's crackdown on staking, the sanctioning of Tornado Cash, and more alpha on how Coinbase is approaching the current unfriendly US regulatory environment. Watch and make sure to subscribe to the gm podcast on Apple or Spotify.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Founder of Rotten Tomatoes Says Web3 Entertainment Isn’t Nearly Entertaining Enough Yet]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/ri2LLifZ/the-founder-of-rotten-tomatoes-says-web3-entertainment-isnt-nearly-entertaining-enough-yet</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/ri2LLifZ/the-founder-of-rotten-tomatoes-says-web3-entertainment-isnt-nearly-entertaining-enough-yet"/>
        <updated>2023-03-25T02:44:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rotten Tomatoes founder Patrick Lee, who has led companies at the intersection of technology and entertainment from Web1 to Web3, spoke to Decrypt's Sander Lutz at Outer Edge LA about the current state of decentralized gaming, film and television.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: How Gnosis Has Endured and Evolved]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Kxfs2Dmd/gm-how-gnosis-has-endured-and-evolved</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Kxfs2Dmd/gm-how-gnosis-has-endured-and-evolved"/>
        <updated>2023-03-24T20:58:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gnosis first launched in 2015 as a decentralized prediction market built on Ethereum. Now it's a DAO, a multi-sig wallet, a staking chain, and a vibrant community with its own GNO governance token. Co-founder and COO Friederike Ernst talked to Dan Roberts and Stacy Elliott about the careful evolution of Gnosis, decentralization impostors, account abstraction, DeFi UX failures, why Ethereum is the "Manhattan of crypto," and much more. Watch and make sure to subscribe to the gm podcast on Apple or Spotify.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Justin Aversano's Inspiration for Tarot-Themed NFT Photo Series 'Smoke and Mirrors']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/dkWNFMPb/justin-aversanos-inspiration-for-tarot-themed-nft-photo-series-smoke-and-mirrors</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/dkWNFMPb/justin-aversanos-inspiration-for-tarot-themed-nft-photo-series-smoke-and-mirrors"/>
        <updated>2023-03-24T20:03:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Justin Aversano, best known for his high-selling "Twin Flames" NFT photo series, joined Decrypt’s Andrew Hayward ahead of the upcoming L.A. exhibition for his new Ethereum NFT project "Smoke and Mirrors." He shared the wild inspiration behind the tarot-themed collection, and why—despite his growing profile—he opted not to exhibit at a major brand-name gallery.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Midnight Society’s Rob Bowling Talks Deadrop Launch and Working With Dr. Disrespect]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/yIc3fKH2/midnight-societys-rob-bowling-talks-deadrop-launch-and-working-with-dr-disrespect</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/yIc3fKH2/midnight-societys-rob-bowling-talks-deadrop-launch-and-working-with-dr-disrespect"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T21:28:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former "Call of Duty" developer Rob Bowling, now head of Midnight Society Studio, checked in with Decrypt's Kate Irwin at GDC and shared some behind-the-scenes statistics on how players are enjoying "Deadrop." The game saw 90,000 player hours over the weekend, with 97 minutes average play time per player, and their community size tripled in just a few days.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big Brands Get Serious About NFTs: Salesforce, VW, Panerai, Absolute Labs at NFT Paris]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/BHN8nxxH/big-brands-get-serious-about-nfts-salesforce-vw-panerai-absolute-labs-at-nft-paris</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/BHN8nxxH/big-brands-get-serious-about-nfts-salesforce-vw-panerai-absolute-labs-at-nft-paris"/>
        <updated>2023-03-16T14:57:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this panel from NFT Paris 2023 moderated by Decrypt's Dan Roberts, Web3 leads from some of the largest consumer and tech brands discuss their NFT strategies. Marc Mathieu of Salesforce, Tim Walther of VW Group, Eva Assayag of Panerai, and Samir Addamine of Absolute Labs joined the panel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFT Entertainment Revolution: Warner Bros, Orange Comet, CyberBrokers and NFT Now at NFT Paris]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/ZWr09Uou/nft-entertainment-revolution-warner-bros-orange-comet-cyberbrokers-and-nft-now-at-nft-paris</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/ZWr09Uou/nft-entertainment-revolution-warner-bros-orange-comet-cyberbrokers-and-nft-now-at-nft-paris"/>
        <updated>2023-03-16T14:49:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At NFT Paris 2023, Decrypt’s Stephen Graves moderated a discussion about NFTs and the entertainment industry with Warner Bros’ NFT head Josh Hackbarth, CyberBrokers founder Josie Bellini, NFT Now founder Matt Medved and Dave Broome, CEO of Orange Comet, which has produced NFTs for Anthony Hopkins and The Walking Dead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Step Inside the Armory of the NFT Collective 'Knights Who Say Nah']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/V6NGpw3i/step-inside-the-armory-of-the-nft-collective-knights-who-say-nah</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/V6NGpw3i/step-inside-the-armory-of-the-nft-collective-knights-who-say-nah"/>
        <updated>2023-03-15T20:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Knights Who Say Nah co-founder and project lead Nick Richey chats with Decrypt's Jason Nelson inside the group's armory of artifacts, shows off a historic Japanese tanto sword, and discusses why the preservation of historical artifacts is the best use case for NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Voltz Labs CEO: DeFi Innovation Is Moving Offshore Because of US Regulatory Severity]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/3fFVrd6t/voltz-labs-ceo-defi-innovation-is-moving-offshore-because-of-us-regulatory-severity</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/3fFVrd6t/voltz-labs-ceo-defi-innovation-is-moving-offshore-because-of-us-regulatory-severity"/>
        <updated>2023-03-09T18:13:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Voltz Labs Co-founder and CEO Simon Jones talks to Decrypt's Jason Nelson at ETH Denver about using DeFi for interest rate swaps, the unfriendly regulatory environment in the US right now, emerging economies becoming crypto hubs, and the "cartoonishly large" market opportunity for DeFi.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MoonPay CEO: Next Phase of NFT Adoption Will Come From 'Brands You Love in Your Everyday Life']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/AMqP6177/moonpay-ceo-next-phase-of-nft-adoption-will-come-from-brands-you-love-in-your-everyday-life</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/AMqP6177/moonpay-ceo-next-phase-of-nft-adoption-will-come-from-brands-you-love-in-your-everyday-life"/>
        <updated>2023-03-09T13:52:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MoonPay CEO Ivan Soto-Wright talked to Decrypt's Liam Kelly at NFT Paris about how NFTs are clearly not "waning," how MoonPay works with brands like Puma and Nike to manage their Web3 plays and smart contracts, and how NFTs and crypto will go mainstream when they can integrate in our daily lives—and his prediction that brands will drive that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>