<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-12-11T23:15:14.938Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-12-11T23:15:14.938Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google To Loosen Restrictions on Crypto Ads, Will Allow Promotion of ‘Cryptocurrency Coin Trusts’]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19102069/Google-To-Loosen-Restrictions-on-Crypto-Ads-Will-Allow-Promotion-of-Cryptocurrency-Coin-Trusts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19102069/Google-To-Loosen-Restrictions-on-Crypto-Ads-Will-Allow-Promotion-of-Cryptocurrency-Coin-Trusts"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T23:01:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has announced it’s updating its policy on allowing advertisements related to cryptocurrencies worldwide. According to a new update from the company, the search giant will update its policy on crypto in January 2024 to address the advertising rules for what it calls Cryptocurrency Coin...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk’s GROK AI Calls Dogecoin The ‘Ultimate Meme Coin’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748acfe1cf</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-ultimate-meme-coin/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T23:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Billionaire and SpaceX CEO Elon Musk announced his very own artificial intelligence (AI) chatbot and it seems he did not hesitate to somehow integrate his favorite cryptocurrency, Dogecoin, into it. As Grok’s popularity has grown, X (formerly Twitter) users have taken to the platform to ask the AI a series of interesting questions, one of those being the AI’s favorite cryptocurrency.
 
Grok Says AI Is Its Favorite Cryptocurrency
 
Dogecoin influencer @TOPDOGE007 took to X to share with their almost 90,000 followers a screenshot of an interesting response they got from the Grok AI. According to the screenshot posted, the influencer had asked the AI for their favorite cryptocurrency and the answer was Dogecoin.
 
 
The AI didn’t just give a single answer to the question though as it further …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Best Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk’s GROK AI Calls Dogecoin The ‘Ultimate Meme Coin’]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19102067/Elon-Musks-GROK-AI-Calls-Dogecoin-The-Ultimate-Meme-Coin</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19102067/Elon-Musks-GROK-AI-Calls-Dogecoin-The-Ultimate-Meme-Coin"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T23:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Billionaire and SpaceX CEO Elon Musk announced his very own artificial intelligence (AI) chatbot and it seems he did not hesitate to somehow integrate his favorite cryptocurrency, Dogecoin, into it. As Grok’s popularity has grown, X (formerly Twitter) users have taken to the platform to ask the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Vulnerability Discovered By A Developer Has Been Flagged By The US Government]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19102058/Bitcoin-Vulnerability-Discovered-By-A-Developer-Has-Been-Flagged-By-The-US-Government</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19102058/Bitcoin-Vulnerability-Discovered-By-A-Developer-Has-Been-Flagged-By-The-US-Government"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T23:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week, a Bitcoin developer Luke Dashjr raised alarm about a possible vulnerability in the network in relation to the Bitcoin Ordinals that could lead to a code exploit. After posting his findings to social media, Dashjr’s warnings were not taken seriously as community members believed it...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Controversial Bitcoin Ordinals-related bug added to U.S. National Vulnerability Database]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19102068/Controversial-Bitcoin-Ordinals-related-bug-added-to-US-National-Vulnerability-Database</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19102068/Controversial-Bitcoin-Ordinals-related-bug-added-to-US-National-Vulnerability-Database"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T23:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. National Vulnerability Database (NVD), a central repository for cybersecurity threats, has hosted a page concerning an alleged bug related to Bitcoin inscriptions as of Dec. 9. Inscriptions, a fundamental aspect of a Bitcoin feature known as Ordinals, allow for the creation of digital...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX debtors push back against $24B IRS claim]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19102048/FTX-debtors-push-back-against-24B-IRS-claim</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19102048/FTX-debtors-push-back-against-24B-IRS-claim"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T22:51:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“The only source of recovery is by taking recoveries away from victims,” FTX debtors warned]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[World Gold Council Anticipates Flat Performance In ‘Soft Landing’ Scenario]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748ac9cf71</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/world-gold-council-anticipates-flat-performance-in-soft-landing-scenario/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T22:42:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The World Gold Council (WGC) is anticipating a flat demand for the precious metal in the expected case of a “soft landing” scenario. However, the institution states that a recession is still not off the table, given that the U.S. Federal Reserve has managed only to pull off two soft landings in nine tightening cycles.
World Gold Council Examines Gold Demand in Various Scenarios
The World Gold Council (WGC) has released its 2024 Gold Outlook report, which examines the possible behavior of the gold markets for next year. According to the institution, the most likely scenario, expected by the markets due to the prediction of growth ahead, is a U.S. economy “soft landing,” forecasting that the Federal Reserve will be able to lower inflation without setting up a decline in the country’s economy.
Gold would not be favored in this scenario, as investors historically have favored bonds and stocks instead. However, a soft landing, albeit expected, is still not sure to happen. According to the report, a recession is still not off the table, given that seven of nine tightening cycles of the Fed have resulted in recession. The behavior of the labor market will be significant, as its situation has considerably worsened in recent months.
In this context, the WGC predicts a favorable outcome for gold investors, with markets taking a “flight to safety” approach. The report stated:
If a recession becomes a reality, weaker growth will help push inflation back towards central bank targets. Such an environment has historically created a positive environment for high-quality government bonds and gold.
In addition, the geopolitical events happening on the planet, including war, conflicts, elections, and above-trend gold purchases by central banks that have escalated historically during the last two years, might also boost gold’s performance as an investment asset in 2024.
How do you think gold will perform in 2024? Tell us in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's Going On With AVAX? Avalanche Bucks Crypto Pullback, Maintains Upward Momentum On Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19102043/Whats-Going-On-With-AVAX-Avalanche-Bucks-Crypto-Pullback-Maintains-Upward-Momentum-On-Monday</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19102043/Whats-Going-On-With-AVAX-Avalanche-Bucks-Crypto-Pullback-Maintains-Upward-Momentum-On-Monday"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T22:25:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite the broader crypto market seeing a downturn on Monday, Avalanche (CRYPTO: AVAX) emerged as the highest gainer in the top 20 cryptocurrencies, up over 6% in read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance faces serious allegations in SEC legal battle]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19102008/Binance-faces-serious-allegations-in-SEC-legal-battle</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19102008/Binance-faces-serious-allegations-in-SEC-legal-battle"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T22:22:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance, the world’s largest crypto exchange, and its former CEO, Changpeng Zhao, are embroiled in a legal tussle with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). The SEC’s latest court filings suggest that Binance and Zhao attempted to deliberately sidestep U.S. laws. This accusation...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Fund Sets Sights On Animoca Brands And Chainalysis In $500 Million Investment Drive]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748ab61324</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-fund-animoca-brands-chainalysis-500-invest/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T22:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent report by the Australian Financial Review, it has been revealed that Animoca Brands, a blockchain-based gaming business formerly listed on the Australian Securities Exchange (ASX), is among several cryptocurrency companies being targeted by a $500 million fund. 
 
The fund, known as C1 Fund, reportedly specializes in acquiring secondary shares at significant discounts of up to 80 percent.
 
Blockchain Gaming Giant Animoca Brands In Crosshairs Of C1 Fund
 
C1 Fund, founded by a group of former Coinbase lawyers and investors, has held discussions with several local venture firms, offering to purchase private holdings from investors at discounts ranging from 50 to 80 percent of their last valuation. 
 
Per the report, the fund’s strategy focuses on crypto companies with a minimum …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 3 Altcoins Under $5 #shorts]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19102002/Top-3-Altcoins-Under-5-shorts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19102002/Top-3-Altcoins-Under-5-shorts"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T22:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2024 Outlook for Bitcoin Regulation and Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19101999/2024-Outlook-for-Bitcoin-Regulation-and-Web3</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19101999/2024-Outlook-for-Bitcoin-Regulation-and-Web3"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T22:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Pakman is a Managing Partner at CoinFund, a blockchain & crypto-native investing firm. In this conversation, we talk about bitcoin, Web3, regulation, stablecoins, and what he is expecting in 2024 & beyond. Cal.com is leading the charge of scheduling platforms in the open-source sphere,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2024 crypto vision: Spot Bitcoin ETFs, interest rates, and a bull run]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19102009/2024-crypto-vision-Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-interest-rates-and-a-bull-run</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19102009/2024-crypto-vision-Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-interest-rates-and-a-bull-run"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T21:55:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto sphere, a domain often synonymous with volatility and unpredictability, is standing at a crossroads as we approach 2024. The central question captivating the minds of crypto enthusiasts and skeptics alike is: What’s next for this mercurial market? After a rollercoaster 2023, the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gods Unchained Rated 'Adults Only' for Play-to-Earn Elements, Booted From Epic Games Store]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209315</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209315/gods-unchained-rated-adults-only-play-earn-elements-booted-epic-games-store"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T21:54:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NFT game’s team is currently trying to appeal the ESRB rating to get back on Epic’s store.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gods Unchained Rated 'Adults Only' for Play-to-Earn Elements, Booted From Epic Games Store]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19101970/Gods-Unchained-Rated-Adults-Only-for-Play-to-Earn-Elements-Booted-From-Epic-Games-Store</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19101970/Gods-Unchained-Rated-Adults-Only-for-Play-to-Earn-Elements-Booted-From-Epic-Games-Store"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T21:54:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NFT game’s team is currently trying to appeal the ESRB rating to get back on Epic’s store.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Where pension funds stand today on crypto investments]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19101962/Where-pension-funds-stand-today-on-crypto-investments</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19101962/Where-pension-funds-stand-today-on-crypto-investments"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T21:52:39.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The UK is investigating the Microsoft and OpenAI partnership]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19101980/The-UK-is-investigating-the-Microsoft-and-OpenAI-partnership</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19101980/The-UK-is-investigating-the-Microsoft-and-OpenAI-partnership"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T21:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's Going On With Cardano? ADA's Dip Outpaces Losses In Bitcoin, Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19101961/Whats-Going-On-With-Cardano-ADAs-Dip-Outpaces-Losses-In-Bitcoin-Ethereum</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19101961/Whats-Going-On-With-Cardano-ADAs-Dip-Outpaces-Losses-In-Bitcoin-Ethereum"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T21:42:42.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Dips 7% to Near $40K; Pullback Will Be Short-Lived, Say Experts]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748ab02d87</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/12/11/bitcoin-dips-7-to-near-40k-pullback-will-be-short-lived-say-experts/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T21:42:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin endured its worst daily drawdowns in 4 months, dipping over 7% to nearly $40,000. $XRP, $LINK, $ADA declined 8%-10%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance to exit Russia and discontinue Ruble amid regulatory scrutiny]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19101954/Binance-to-exit-Russia-and-discontinue-Ruble-amid-regulatory-scrutiny</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19101954/Binance-to-exit-Russia-and-discontinue-Ruble-amid-regulatory-scrutiny"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T21:41:57.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Dips 7% to Near $40K; Pullback Will Be Short-Lived, Say Experts]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19101953/Bitcoin-Dips-7-to-Near-40K-Pullback-Will-Be-Short-Lived-Say-Experts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19101953/Bitcoin-Dips-7-to-Near-40K-Pullback-Will-Be-Short-Lived-Say-Experts"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T21:40:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin endured its worst daily drawdowns in 4 months, dipping over 7% to nearly $40,000. $XRP, $LINK, $ADA declined 8%-10%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance to End Ruble P2P Support as Part of Russia Exit]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19101922/Binance-to-End-Ruble-P2P-Support-as-Part-of-Russia-Exit</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19101922/Binance-to-End-Ruble-P2P-Support-as-Part-of-Russia-Exit"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T21:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance unveils plans to end Russian ruble support on its P2P trading platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Explaining Bitcoin’s ‘Flash Crash’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748ab0fbac</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/12/11/explaining-bitcoins-flash-crash/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T21:34:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cryptocurrency's volatility cuts both ways.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Kuhn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Crypto ‘Plan Remains Unchanged,’ Says Crypto Analysts]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19102003/The-Crypto-Plan-Remains-Unchanged-Says-Crypto-Analysts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19102003/The-Crypto-Plan-Remains-Unchanged-Says-Crypto-Analysts"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T21:33:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A slight retreat in Bitcoin’s price within the last 24 hours prompts crypto analysts to inform their extensive followers that it’s a regular part of the market flow, urging them to stick to the long-term plan. One analyst confidently asserts the ease of predicting the price pullback, while...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin and Ether lead crypto fund inflows as Europe adds $43 million]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19101923/Bitcoin-and-Ether-lead-crypto-fund-inflows-as-Europe-adds-43-million</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19101923/Bitcoin-and-Ether-lead-crypto-fund-inflows-as-Europe-adds-43-million"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T21:32:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to a recent report, digital asset investment products saw an 11th straight week of inflows totaling $43 million. However, the latest inflows represent a decline compared to prior weeks as some investors take a cautious stance amid recent price increases.Bitcoin remains investors'...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Lists SEAM Token as Airdrop and Liquidity Mining Program Begin]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19101921/Coinbase-Lists-SEAM-Token-as-Airdrop-and-Liquidity-Mining-Program-Begin</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19101921/Coinbase-Lists-SEAM-Token-as-Airdrop-and-Liquidity-Mining-Program-Begin"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T21:32:25.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin and Ethereum Dip 7% as Crypto Markets Cool]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209316</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209316/bitcoin-ethereum-dip-7-crypto-markets-cool"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T21:21:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There has now been $516 million worth of liquidations on crypto futures contracts in the past day.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Economist Steve Hanke Blasts Nobel Laureate Paul Krugman’s ‘Global Phenomenon’ Inflation Remark]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748ab3c069</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/economist-steve-hanke-blasts-nobel-laureate-paul-krugmans-global-phenomenon-inflation-remark/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T21:10:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Johns Hopkins University applied economics professor Steven Hanke has lambasted fellow economist and Nobel laureate Paul Krugman’s claim that inflation is a “global phenomenon.” Paul Krugman suggested that progressive U.S. citizens can still be convinced that the Biden administration has done well with the economy.
 
Krugman Accused of Spreading Disinformation
 
Steve Hanke, a professor of applied economics at Johns Hopkins University, has criticized fellow economist and Nobel laureate Paul Krugman for claiming that inflation is a “global phenomenon.” In a post on X (formerly Twitter), Hanke characterized Krugman’s latest op-ed article in the New York Times as another of the Nobel laureate’s disinformation pieces.
 
In his Dec. 7 installment, Krugman argues the case for Bidenomics, a term …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Prepares for Potential Bitcoin ETFs by Easing Crypto Ad Rules]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209317</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209317/google-prepares-potential-bitcoin-etfs-easing-crypto-ad-rules"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T20:48:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Online advertising giant Google will soon permit the promotion of "cryptocurrency coin trusts" amid expected Bitcoin ETF approvals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto’s Gainers and Losers: BTT and BONK Spike Amidst Overall Downturn]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748aa62140</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/cryptos-gainers-and-losers-btt-and-bonk-spike-amidst-overall-downturn/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T19:40:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past day, a considerable number of crypto assets have experienced a decline. However, looking at the seven-day performance, several of them have maintained a substantial increase. For example, bittorrent (BTT) has seen a significant surge of 188% in the last week, while bonk (BONK) has also recorded a 100% rise during the same period.
 
Market Watch: Identifying This Week’s Crypto Fortunes
 

 
Today’s markets have dipped, showing a nearly 5% decline across the spectrum, as per the latest figures on Monday, Dec. 11, 2023. Despite this downtrend, a significant number of cryptocurrencies have recorded impressive gains over the last week.
 

 
Leading the surge, BTT and BONK have escalated by 188% and 100% respectively. Other top performers include Avalanche (AVAX), with a 69.4% incr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s Uptrend Forecast: Expert Signals Market Triumph, Says ‘We’re About To Win’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748aa6355f</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-up-forecast-expert-signals-market-triumph/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T19:39:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samson Mow, the CEO of Jan3 and a recognized investor in Bitcoin, has recently expressed a confident outlook on the future of the cryptocurrency, suggesting that a significant victory for its supporters is “imminent.”
 
In a recent tweet, the CEO of Jan3 observed that several prominent accounts, which he broadly categorizes as “influential,” have been critical of BTC. Mow clarified that his definition of “influential” is wide and might even encompass “third-rate comedians.”
 
 
Despite this criticism, Mow’s interpretation of these events is optimistic, encapsulated in his statement, “Feels like we’re about to win.”
 
 
*Influential used loosely and may include third rate comedians.
 
— Samson Mow (@Excellion) December 11, 2023
 
His comments come at a pivotal moment for BTC, as it is going…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Senator Elizabeth Warren Introduces Bill To "Crack Down" on Bitcoin And Crypto]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748aa05ab6</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/markets/us-senator-elizabeth-warren-introduces-bill-to-crack-down-on-bitcoin-and-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T19:22:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, US Senator Elizabeth Warren introduced legislation to address her concerns surrounding the alleged misuse of digital currencies in illicit activities, citing money laundering, drug trafficking, sanctions evasion, and more.



The bill, supported by a coalition within the Banking Committee, marks a significant push for increased oversight and regulation within the Bitcoin and cryptocurrency sphere. Citing risks associated with cryptocurrencies, Senator Warren stressed that digital currencies are used as an avenue for criminal activities, and that must be addressed through stringent regulatory frameworks.
“The Treasury Department is making clear that we need new laws to crack down on crypto’s use in enabling terrorist groups, rogue nations, drug lords, ransomware gangs, and fraudsters…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nik Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance’s Market Share of Crypto Trading Tumbled to 30% in 2023]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748aa19b9e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/12/11/binances-market-share-of-crypto-trading-tumbled-to-30-in-2023/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T19:12:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The exchange has also witnessed a drop in its trading volume amidst the regulatory crackdown on the entity in the U.S.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lyllah Ledesma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FCA Slow to Take Crypto Enforcement Action, UK's Public Spending Watchdog Says]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748aac2267</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/12/11/fca-slow-to-take-crypto-enforcement-action-uks-public-spending-watchdog-says/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T18:52:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even when the financial regulator has the power to act, years can go by before it takes enforcement action, the U.K.'s National Audit Office said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camomile Shumba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analyst Predicts Cardano (ADA) Rise To $10 Amid Massive Network Activity]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748aaa0531</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/analyst-cardano-ada-rise-to-10/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T18:08:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano’s growth in the past two months has rolled over into the first 10 days of December. At the time of writing, Cardano is up by 48% since the beginning of the month. While the price has been on a steady increase, Cardano’s ecosystem has grown in adoption and on the backend of things.
 
In its latest Cardano weekly development report, the Cardano team detailed how developers are working on updates, while also showing an increase in project development on the ecosystem and token metrics. Considering the current state of its ecosystem, a recent prediction by crypto analyst Psyclops has noted Cardano (ADA) is ready to push to $10 in the next bull market. 
 
Analyst Psyclops Predicts Cardano Price Will Reach $10
 
Crypto analyst Psyclops noted in a social media post on X how Cardano’s ecos…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's 2023 Person of the Year: BlackRock CEO Larry Fink]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209308</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209308/decrypt-2023-person-of-the-year-blackrock-ceo-larry-fink"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T18:05:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[He wasn’t always so bullish and his evolving relationship with crypto—what this could mean for the market—is why he is Person of the Year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seamless Protocol Issues SEAM, Bags First Base-Blockchain Token Listing on Coinbase]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748a946586</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/12/11/seamless-protocol-issues-seam-bags-first-base-blockchain-token-listing-on-coinbase/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T17:51:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seamless previously operated the "OG Points" program, allowing thousands of users to earn points in their on-chain wallets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fed Observer Jim Grant Foresees Long-Term High Rates as FOMC Meeting Approaches]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748a960af7</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/fed-observer-jim-grant-foresees-long-term-high-rates-as-fomc-meeting-approaches/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T17:39:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Market participants, including both investors and traders, have their attention keenly set on the upcoming Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC) meeting, slated for Dec. 13, 2023. There is widespread speculation about whether Fed Chair Jerome Powell will continue to uphold the current elevated benchmark interest rate. Concurrently, Jim Grant, renowned for his four-decade-long work on Grant’s Interest Rate Observer, holds the conviction that interest rates will stay at a “higher for much, much, much, much longer” level.
 
Economic Expert Jim Grant Anticipates Persistent High Interest Rates Post-FOMC
 
Presently, the federal funds rate stands between 5.25% and 5.50%, reaching its highest point in 22 years. This benchmark rate, crucial for banks and other financial institutions for inter-lendi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Investors Eyeing Up Solana and Avalanche as Cash Flows Into Funds]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209302</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209302/investors-eyeing-up-solana-and-avalanche-as-cash-flows-into-funds"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T17:31:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Investors are largely interested in Bitcoin, but these two altcoins are grabbing attention.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Not Just Electricity And Water — Bitcoin Mines Use A Lot Of Air, Too]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748a97709a</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/technical/its-not-just-electricity-and-water-bitcoin-mines-use-a-lot-of-air-too"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T17:29:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This piece is an entirely and deeply serious parody. 
Bitcoin mines aren’t just thirsty, it turns out they’re starving for air, too. The air consumption tied to a single Bitcoin transaction, on average, could be enough for a DINK couple to breathe for an entire year, according to a new analysis by Andrew de Breeze. Bitcoin mines are essentially big data centers, which have become notorious for how much electricity and water they use, taking those resources directly away from human beings and mother nature.
But according to an analysis published today by sources familiar with the situation, Bitcoin’s air consumption footprint is growing even faster than it’s water consumption and is a key issue to watch as the price of Bitcoin is rallying.
The study was conducted by Andrew de Breeze, a PhD …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Gagnon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TradeWire: Leveraging AI to Revolutionize Data-Driven Trading]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748a911e9a</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/tradewire-leveraging-ai-data-trading-crypto/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T17:17:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the modern financial landscape, leveraging technology to gain an analytical edge has become essential for traders to keep pace with markets growing ever more efficiently. 
 
Hedge funds and prop trading firms invest heavily in high-frequency infrastructure and quantitative teams wielding sophisticated data science capabilities. Yet most mainstream retail traders still lack access to the kind of robust tools and predictive insights provided by artificial intelligence and machine learning.
 
TradeWire aims to change that status quo. This ambitious fintech startup seeks to “democratize” access to institutional-grade analytics to all market participants regardless of experience, account size or technical abilities.
 
After extensive testing and review over a multi-month beta period, TradeWi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No 'Surprise' Airdrop Coming for PIXEL Token, Says Pixels Game Founder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209294</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209294/no-surprise-airdrop-pixel-token-says-pixels-founder"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T17:06:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pixels has thousands of players and a PIXEL token is in the works—but the founder says they'll be "noisy as hell" about the launch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase, MicroStrategy, Marathon Stocks Buckle 5%-10% as Bitcoin Tumbles Below $42K]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748a935cef</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/12/11/coinbase-microstrategy-marathon-stocks-buckle-5-10-as-bitcoin-tumbles-below-42k/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T17:01:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A "flash crash" in thin trading Sunday evening, saw bitcoin's price plunge nearly 10% from the $44,000 level in the space of a few minutes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taiwan Completes Wholesale CBDC Technical Study, Central Bank Official Says]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748a9d686b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/12/11/taiwan-completes-wholesale-cbdc-technical-study-central-bank-official-says/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T16:48:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The central bank is now gathering feedback and improving a platform design, according to Deputy Governor Chu Mei-lie.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandali Handagama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Korea Financial Regulator Proposes Consumer Protection Rules for Crypto Users]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748a9d685d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/12/11/south-korea-financial-regulator-proposes-consumer-protection-rules-for-crypto-users/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T16:48:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The rules are scheduled to take affect on July 19 next year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camomile Shumba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Immutable Climbs 10% While Most Gaming Tokens Fall With Bitcoin and Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209283</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209283/immutable-rising-while-gaming-tokens-fall"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T16:41:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IMX is bucking the downward trend Monday following VanEck’s recent vote of confidence in crypto gaming platform Immutable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bears Strike Back: $333 Million Crypto Longs Squeezed]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748a9edc73</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-bears-strike-333-crypto-longs-squeezed/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T16:38:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data shows over $333 million cryptocurrency futures shorts have found liquidation in the past day after Bitcoin registered a plunge towards $42,000.
 
Cryptocurrency Market Sees Long Squeeze Following Bitcoin Plunge
 
Bitcoin and the cryptocurrency sector as a whole have gone through some sharp volatility in the past day and as is usually the case, this volatility has accompanied with it some shakeup for the futures side of the market.
 
As data from CoinGlass below shows, the sector has observed over $389 million in total liquidations over the past 24 hours.
 

 
 
“Liquidation” here naturally refers to the forced closure that any contract undergoes after it amasses losses of a specific degree (the exact value of which may be dependent on the derivative platform it’s open with).
 
 
The v…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$330 Million in Crypto Longs Liquidated as Bitcoin Tumbles Below $43,000]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209259</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209259/330-million-in-crypto-longs-liquidated-as-bitcoin-tumbles-below-43000"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T10:26:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin's upward march over the past month hit a bump in the road Monday morning, with the cryptocurrency's price slipping below $43,000.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt Media Inc. and Rug Radio Merge to Create Global Web3 Publishing Company]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209209</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209209/decrypt-rug-radio-merger-web3-publishing"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T20:07:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“This is an example of one plus one equalling three,” said Josh Quittner, who co-founded Decrypt in 2018.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week On Crypto Twitter: Good for Meme Coins, Bad for (Alleged) Crypto Criminals]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209211</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209211/this-week-on-crypto-twitter-good-for-meme-coins-bad-for-alleged-crypto-criminals"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T18:30:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto continued on the path of broad gains this week, creating a giddily optimistic online atmosphere.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pudgy Penguins Reveal 'Pudgy World' NFT Game Rollout Plans]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209174</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209174/pudgy-penguins-reveals-pudgy-world-nft-game-rollout-plans"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T02:31:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Pudgy Penguins NFT empire is expanding and will open the gates for its metaverse experience Pudgy World sometime in 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Bitcoin Rally Lends Meme Coins a Helping Hand]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209125</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209125/this-week-in-coins-bitcoin-rally-lends-meme-coins-a-helping-hand"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T16:33:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin continued to rally this week. And major altcoins—especially meme coins—blew up in value as a result.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Free Money': These Are the Hottest Airdrops Around Right Now]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209179</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209179/free-money-hottest-airdrops-around-right-now"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T14:01:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jito just dropped bags of tokens to Solana users, and Starknet, Portal, and Jupiter airdrops are on the horizon. Here’s what you need to know.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Undressing: Deepfake Nude Services Skyrocket in Popularity]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209181</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209181/ai-undressing-deepfake-nude-services-skyrocket-in-popularity"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T01:12:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Analytics firm Graphika says the amount of non-consensual intimate imagery online has grown 2,408% since January.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SOL Surges 13% as Solana NFTs Overtake Ethereum, BONK Up 26%]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209160</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209160/sol-surges-13-solana-nfts-overtake-ethereum-bonk-up-26"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T21:22:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana’s resurgence isn’t slowing, with SOL and Solana-based tokens still rising and NFT sales volume ruling the wider market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avail Hopes to Sell Hollywood on Using AI to Sort Through Scripts]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209135</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209135/ai-to-sort-summarize-movie-tv-scripts-avail"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T20:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The film and TV script summary platform says it can save time and effort with minimal AI hallucinations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI's Potential in Business Breakthroughs Is Overhyped, Says OpenAI COO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209143</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209143/ais-potential-in-business-breakthroughs-is-overhyped-says-openai-coo"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T20:10:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI won’t make you a millionaire, says Brad Lightcap, Sam Altman’s right hand man, calling the tech more of a “sidekick.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Says 'Not Your Keys, Not Your Wallet' in Butchered Attempt at Bitcoin Mantra]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209133</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209133/elon-musk-says-not-keys-not-wallet-butchered-bitcoin-mantra"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T19:47:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[World's richest man and alleged crypto fan Elon Musk took a swing at the classic Bitcoin "not your keys" mantra—and whiffed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Got $1 Million in Bitcoin or Tether? El Salvador Will Give You a 'Freedom Visa']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209122</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209122/el-salvador-passport-cough-up-1m-bitcoin-tether"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T19:06:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[El Salvador has announced a new “freedom visa” for rich people who want to live in the Central American nation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Prime Is Giving Out Free Items for NFT Game ‘Champions Ascension’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209121</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209121/amazon-prime-giving-out-free-items-nft-game-champions-ascension"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T18:57:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Got an Amazon Prime membership? You’ll be able to grab in-game items for NFT actioner Champions Ascension on PC for weeks to come.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Layer-2 Starknet Reveals STRK Token Airdrop]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209109</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209109/ethereum-layer-2-starknet-reveals-strk-token-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T18:01:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starknet, an Ethereum scaling network, is readying 1.8 billion STRK tokens between the airdrop and rebates, plus incentives for DeFi users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Dogecoin? The Original Meme Coin Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=5678</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/dogecoin-crypto-cryptocurrency-guide-how-to-buy-doge"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T17:50:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin is a peer-to-peer cryptocurrency based on a popular Internet meme. The token started off as a joke, but it's become a serious proposition.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward,Stephen Graves,Wendy Clack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Animoca Brands Boosts 'Mocaverse' Funding to $31.88 Million With Dapper, Polygon Onboard]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209096</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209096/animoca-brands-boosts-mocaverse-funding-31-88-million-dapper-polygon-onboard"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T17:27:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum NFT-based digital identity and loyalty platform Mocaverse will connect metaverse game worlds, apps, and other Web3 projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HODL: VanEck Bitcoin ETF Uses Laser-Eyed Lingo for Ticker]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209094</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209094/hodl-vaneck-bitcoin-etf-uses-laser-eyed-lingo-for-ticker"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T17:26:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fund manager is one of the biggest contenders in the spot Bitcoin ETF race.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Novel Wallet Is a Book That Hides Your Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209113</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209113/novel-wallet-is-a-book-that-hides-your-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T17:16:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This low-tech tome puts every possible passphrase word in print, providing a creative way to safely store your seed phrase.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Withdraws Abu Dhabi Investment Fund Licence Application]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209069</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209069/binance-withdraws-abu-dhabi-investment-fund-licence-application"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T12:30:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The license, which Binance voluntarily canceled, would have permitted the exchange to manage a collective investment fund in the country.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elizabeth Warren: Update Bank Secrecy Act to Address Crypto 'Threat']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209068</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209068/elizabeth-warren-update-bank-secrecy-act-to-address-crypto-threat"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T11:02:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Senator linked crypto to terrorist financing, drug trafficking, and North Korea's nuclear weapons programme.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Judge Bans Changpeng ‘CZ’ Zhao from Leaving the Country]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209060</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209060/us-judge-bans-changpeng-cz-zhao-from-leaving-the-country"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T02:51:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["The defendant has enormous wealth and property abroad," wrote Judge Richard Jones, "and no ties to the United States."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Early Bitcoin Ordinals Art Sells for Record $450,000]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209032</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209032/early-bitcoin-ordinals-art-sells-for-record-450000"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T02:21:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Honey Badger inscription number eight, created on Jan. 15, sold on Magic Eden on Thursday for 10.4 BTC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft May Be Working On an AI Edition of Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209025</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209025/microsoft-ai-windows-2024-germanium-copilot"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T02:06:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 Windows release is rumored to have AI in everything from its graphical user interface to its command line.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jito Airdrop Hands Out $225 Million to Solana Users]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209010</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209010/jito-airdrop-hands-out-225-million-solana-users"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T23:22:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana DeFi users are celebrating after Jito launched JTO, with 90 million tokens up for grabs for eligible users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INTERVIEW: Ember Sword CEO Says NFT Games Are More 'Transparent']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/M9OHCVpA/interview-ember-sword-ceo-says-nft-games-are-more-transparent</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/M9OHCVpA/interview-ember-sword-ceo-says-nft-games-are-more-transparent"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T21:58:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ember Sword CEO Mark Laursen shares why some big game studios "irk" him—and why he got into game development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Unveils Open-Source Path for AI Development on Its Silicon Chips]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209003</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209003/apple-ai-ml-development-mlx-silicon"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T21:07:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MLX speeds AI development on Apple hardware, connecting its users with the broader AI development community on other platforms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What the Bitcoin Halving Means for Investors]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208164</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208164/bitcoin-halving-what-it-means-investors"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T19:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The next Bitcoin halving takes place in April—but this time is different, insiders say. Here's what retail investors should know.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reebok Follows Nike Into Digital Fashion and Gaming, With an AI Twist]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208993</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208993/reebok-follows-nike-into-digital-wearables-gaming-with-ai-twist"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T19:31:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Footwear brand Reebok will debut an on-chain gaming experience next year that it promises will be “mind-bending.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meme Coins Dogecoin, SHIB Slip—But Solana's BONK Continues to Soar]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208973</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208973/meme-coin-dogecoin-shib-solana-bonk"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T18:38:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bullish traders are once again eyeing up risky assets for quick gains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ronin and Beam Gaming Tokens Surge, Outpacing Bitcoin and Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208986</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208986/ronin-beam-gaming-tokens-surge-outpacing-bitcoin-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T18:16:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gaming tokens remain hot, with RON and BEAM the biggest winners this week with huge double-digit weekly percentage jumps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gamers Can Now Livestream to Twitter via Streamlabs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208972</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208972/gamers-can-now-livestream-twitter-streamlabs"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T17:01:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Streamlabs’ new X feature allows gamers to go live on Twitter from a phone or computer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Director Jordan Bayne on the State of Film3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZLoEDkL9/director-jordan-bayne-on-the-state-of-film3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZLoEDkL9/director-jordan-bayne-on-the-state-of-film3"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T00:11:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the 2023 Film3 Summit, Jordan Bayne—director and founder of The Squad—spoke with Decrypt's Sander Lutz about how the Film3 world has progressed over the last year and what decentralized technologies can offer to creators that want to buck the Hollywood system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Questions With SCENE: Phil Mohun]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TwOjXfOR/5-questions-with-scene-phil-mohun</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TwOjXfOR/5-questions-with-scene-phil-mohun"/>
        <updated>2023-12-01T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bright Moments co-founder Phil Mohun joins 5 Questions With SCENE to recount some favorite moments from the road, including negotiating with Patagonian gauchos, falling in love with Tokyo, and gaining a newfound appreciation for shrooms chocolate bars.

Shot and edited by Vincent Roazzi Jr.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are NFTs Ever Coming Back?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qLmFpNKE/are-nfts-ever-coming-back</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qLmFpNKE/are-nfts-ever-coming-back"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T18:38:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this weeks episode we sit down with Cashtro from Arcade.xyz to discuss NFTs, shitcoins, what collections have held onto their floor prices, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Summit: Will Web3 Gaming Ever be Mainstream?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OvVWhGbW/web-summit-will-web3-gaming-ever-be-mainstream</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OvVWhGbW/web-summit-will-web3-gaming-ever-be-mainstream"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T19:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animoca Brands CEO Robby Yung, EndeavorXR CEO Amy Peck and Gamee co-founder CEO Bozena Rezab joined Decrypt's Stephen Graves on stage at Web Summit to talk about the future of Web3 gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Allie Eve Knox on Spankchain and the life of a Crypto Financial Dominatrix]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/16rVeg6o/allie-eve-knox-on-spankchain-and-the-life-of-a-crypto-financial-dominatrix</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/16rVeg6o/allie-eve-knox-on-spankchain-and-the-life-of-a-crypto-financial-dominatrix"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T21:20:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the first IRL episode of This Time Will Be Different!

In this week's episode, our host, Reza Jafery, is joined by Allie Eve Knox, the Spankchain Chief of Staff and FinDomme. 

They discuss
- How to sell feet pics
- If crypto is really as permissionless as it seems
- the intersections between crypto and sex work]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Questions With SCENE: Jeff Davis]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PChJu1R8/5-questions-with-scene-jeff-davis</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PChJu1R8/5-questions-with-scene-jeff-davis"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artist Jeff Davis joins 5 Questions with SCENE to answer burning questions about his artistic practice, the path that brought him to Art Blocks, and his quietly sophisticated DJ abilities.

Video shot and edited by Vincent Roazzi Jr.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Heatbit Founder Alex Busarov on the Bitcoin Miner That Heats Your Home]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DJuHqcGT/heatbit-founder-alex-busarov-on-the-bitcoin-miner-that-heats-your-home</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DJuHqcGT/heatbit-founder-alex-busarov-on-the-bitcoin-miner-that-heats-your-home"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T18:12:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt joined Heatbit founder Alex Busarov at Web Summit for a walkthrough of the firm's flagship product, a Bitcoin miner that acts as a domestic space heater—aimed at the casual user.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nym CEO Harry Halpin on Privacy, Decentralized VPNs and Tornado Cash]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/aLTtY2aq/nym-ceo-harry-halpin-on-privacy-decentralized-vpns-and-tornado-cash</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/aLTtY2aq/nym-ceo-harry-halpin-on-privacy-decentralized-vpns-and-tornado-cash"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T18:08:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The founder of privacy-preserving mixnet Nym sat down with Decrypt at Web Summit to talk about its new decentralized VPN, the Web3 privacy landscape and why "devs should be defended" in the wake of the Tornado Cash crackdown.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pat Felder - The worst is over [Macro Deep Dive Episode]]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MdcKPVo0/pat-felder-the-worst-is-over-macro-deep-dive-episode</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MdcKPVo0/pat-felder-the-worst-is-over-macro-deep-dive-episode"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T17:10:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the first Markets Edition of This Time Will Be Different! In this episode we dive into the current macroeconomic conditions around crypto and look at the data behind the price action. 


Reza sits down with Pat Felder, founder of Prismatic Capital to discuss the current macro environment, and to answer the question on everyone's mind-- is the bear market really over?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Sandbox Co-Founder Sebastien Borget: 'We're Already Integrating AI']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/HlARjhG1/the-sandbox-co-founder-sebastien-borget-were-already-integrating-ai</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/HlARjhG1/the-sandbox-co-founder-sebastien-borget-were-already-integrating-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T16:09:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt sat down with The Sandbox co-founder Sebastien Borget at Web Summit to talk about AI, the open metaverse and the creative challenges of interoperability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dacoco CEO Saro McKenna: How Alien Worlds is Creating an AI-Powered 'Lore DAO' with Kevin J Anderson]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QrQTrsjH/dacoco-ceo-saro-mckenna-how-alien-worlds-is-creating-an-ai-powered-lore-dao-with-kevin-j-anderson</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QrQTrsjH/dacoco-ceo-saro-mckenna-how-alien-worlds-is-creating-an-ai-powered-lore-dao-with-kevin-j-anderson"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T16:06:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt joined Dacoco CEO Sarojini McKenna at Web Summit 2023 to talk about Alien Worlds' new Lore DAO and its AI-powered collaboration with sci-fi author Kevin J Anderson.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avalon's Jeffrey Butler on Designing a Metaverse MMO That Lets Players Co-Create]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XDz9vsvT/avalons-jeffrey-butler-on-designing-a-metaverse-mmo-that-lets-players-co-create</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XDz9vsvT/avalons-jeffrey-butler-on-designing-a-metaverse-mmo-that-lets-players-co-create"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T00:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avalon Chief Product Officer Jeffrey Butler speaks with Decrypt reporter Jason Nelson and details his studio's new MMO game with interoperable assets—and how it will enable players to create and monetize their own content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>