<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-01-23T09:15:43.088Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-01-23T09:15:43.088Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTT Bucks Market Turmoil As FTX Estate Revealed To Be Behind GBTC Sales]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f02507e8</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/01/23/ftt-bucks-market-turmoil-as-ftx-estate-revealed-to-be-behind-gbtc-sales/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T09:13:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FTT was up 11% in the past 24 hours as the broader market tracked by CoinDesk 20 slumped 4%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Vanguard Said "No" to Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f0258047</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/why-vanguard-said-no-to-bitcoin/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T09:10:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After months of speculation and a frenzy of attention that crossed over from crypto Twitter to mainstream financial channels, those long-awaited spot BTC ETFs finally gained approval from the SEC earlier this month, and from there, were almost immediately up and running.
 There was the added last minute drama of the SEC having its X account compromised, resulting in a fake approval post going out a day early, an occurrence which will go down as yet another moment of disruptive madness in Bitcoin history, but in the end, the consensus was that we were in uncharted but inevitable territory; stepping across the chasm between a novel, volatile, and frequently misunderstood monetary technology, and the (ostensibly) risk-averse world of orthodox, mainstream finance.
 After all, with the investme…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam White</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pro-XRP Lawyer Deaton Unpacks Why Ethereum Received Its ‘Free Pass’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f0258a87</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/pro-xrp-lawyer-ethereum-free-pass/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T09:10:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a scathing critique of the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), renowned pro-XRP lawyer John E. Deaton has unleashed a broadside against what he perceives as systemic corruption, favoritism, and a glaring double standard in the regulatory oversight of cryptocurrencies. Deaton’s fiery response, articulated through via X, was triggered by a commentary from his colleague, James “MetaLawMan” Murphy, regarding the SEC’s recent hearings involving major crypto exchanges Coinbase and Binance.
 
Murphy’s initial observation pointed out a significant omission in the SEC’s narrative, “The SEC touted the benefits of the guidance it had given about how to analyze whether crypto tokens are securities. Yet, they omitted any mention of Bill Hinman’s invention of the ‘sufficiently decentralized’…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Web3 and Blockchain Focused VC Fund, Paper Ventures, Launched With Initial Capital of $25 Million]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f0262352</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/new-web3-and-blockchain-focused-vc-fund-paper-ventures-launched-with-initial-capital-of-25-million/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T09:05:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paper Ventures, a new blockchain venture capital (VC) fund focused on early-stage Web3 and blockchain projects, has been launched with an initial fund of $25 million. The fund, founded by experienced venture capitalists, will not only invest in outstanding projects but will help nurture them.
 
New Fund Backed by Leading Industry Figures
 
A new blockchain venture capital (VC) fund, Paper Ventures, has been launched with an initial fund of $25 million earmarked for investment in early-stage Web3 and blockchain projects. The fund was mobilized from traditional hedge funds, family offices, exchanges, founders, and high net worth (HNW) crypto OGs.
 
The VC, which claims to have the backing of some prominent industry figures, said it not only seeks to fund but also to nurture outstanding projects. According to a statement, Danish Chaudhry, Oliver Blakey, and Ivailo Jordanov are the founders of Paper Ventures. The three are experienced in investing in Web3 projects.
 
Some of the projects which the trio helped to secure early funding include Frax Finance, SEI, Polygon, Injective, Polkadot, Moonbeam and Cosmos.
 
 
Commenting on the launch of the fund, co-founder Blakey, a former poker pro, said:
 
“We are more than just investors. Our mission at Paper Ventures is to be at the very forefront of innovation, fostering groundbreaking ideas that redefine the boundaries of technology and finance. We believe in the transformative power of blockchain and are committed to supporting those who are as passionate about its potential as we are.”
 
Fellow co-founder Chaudhry expressed his delight and readiness to invest in not only groundbreaking ideas but also to do his part in elevating the brilliant minds behind them. Through Paper Ventures, the co-founders plan to avail their extensive industry experience and network, which can help provide the portfolio projects with the connections they need to succeed.
 
What are your thoughts on this story? Let us know what you think in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pro-XRP Lawyer Deaton Unpacks Why Ethereum Received Its ‘Free Pass’]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19196144/Pro-XRP-Lawyer-Deaton-Unpacks-Why-Ethereum-Received-Its-Free-Pass</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19196144/Pro-XRP-Lawyer-Deaton-Unpacks-Why-Ethereum-Received-Its-Free-Pass"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T09:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a scathing critique of the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), renowned pro-XRP lawyer John E. Deaton has unleashed a broadside against what he perceives as systemic corruption, favoritism, and a glaring double standard in the regulatory oversight of cryptocurrencies. Deaton’s fiery...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Animoca-backed Gamee confirms major exploit of token contracts]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19196110/Animoca-backed-Gamee-confirms-major-exploit-of-token-contracts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19196110/Animoca-backed-Gamee-confirms-major-exploit-of-token-contracts"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T08:50:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Gamee token fell 64% over the past 24 hours, with the exploiter converting the stolen tokens into ETH and MATIC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk addresses surge in flagged crypto accounts on X]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19196108/Elon-Musk-addresses-surge-in-flagged-crypto-accounts-on-X</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19196108/Elon-Musk-addresses-surge-in-flagged-crypto-accounts-on-X"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T08:49:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent development, X’s new owner, Elon Musk, has shed light on the surge of flagged accounts on the platform within the cryptocurrency community. This issue, identified as a result of an anti-spam bot’s error, has sparked concern among users and stakeholders in the digital currency space....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Payu Coin Looks To Bring Meme Coins Together In One, Ultimate Platform]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f020f467</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/payu-coin-looks-to-bring-meme-coins-together-in-one-ultimate-platform/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T08:46:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. Payu Coin ($PAYU) aims to become the premier platform bringing together meme coins on the Binance Smart Chain (BSC). Its strategic features set it apart in the competitive market which is often highly volatile and unpredictable with plenty of participants.
 
What Makes Payu Coin Stand Out?
 
Firstly, there is the efficiency of BSC. Payu Coin leverages the speed and cost-effectiveness of the Binance Smart Chain, ensuring rapid transactions and minimal fees, establishing it as a go-to platform for crypto enthusiasts.
 
Another standout characteristic when it comes to Payu Coin is the absence of tax deductions and transaction fees for buying and selling. This user-centric approach enhances the overall experience, making Payu Coin an advantageous choice for traders. Moreover, th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTT Bucks Market Turmoil As FTX Estate Revealed To Be Behind GBTC Sales]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19196113/FTT-Bucks-Market-Turmoil-As-FTX-Estate-Revealed-To-Be-Behind-GBTC-Sales</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19196113/FTT-Bucks-Market-Turmoil-As-FTX-Estate-Revealed-To-Be-Behind-GBTC-Sales"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T08:45:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FTT was up 11% in the past 24 hours as the broader market tracked by CoinDesk 20 slumped 4%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Vivek Wanted This:' Trump Pledges Yet Again To Reject CBDCs, Calls Them 'Dangerous Threat To Freedom']]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19196146/Vivek-Wanted-This-Trump-Pledges-Yet-Again-To-Reject-CBDCs-Calls-Them-Dangerous-Threat-To-Freedom</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19196146/Vivek-Wanted-This-Trump-Pledges-Yet-Again-To-Reject-CBDCs-Calls-Them-Dangerous-Threat-To-Freedom"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T08:40:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former President Donald Trump reiterated his opposition to the development of central bank digital currencies (CBDCs) during a rally in Laconia, New H read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin slips below $40K – Millions in longs get wiped out]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19196086/Bitcoin-slips-below-40K-Millions-in-longs-get-wiped-out</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19196086/Bitcoin-slips-below-40K-Millions-in-longs-get-wiped-out"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T08:30:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussions around Bitcoin dropped by 35% compared to the week prior to ETF approvals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Might Drop Another 10%, Here's What Happens After]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19196092/XRP-Might-Drop-Another-10-Heres-What-Happens-After</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19196092/XRP-Might-Drop-Another-10-Heres-What-Happens-After"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XRP's potential price drop may lead to something that many investors anticipated]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Korea's Popular Cryptocurrency Exchange Announced the Listing of a New Altcoin, There was a Rise in Price!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19196080/South-Koreas-Popular-Cryptocurrency-Exchange-Announced-the-Listing-of-a-New-Altcoin-There-was-a-Rise-in-Price</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19196080/South-Koreas-Popular-Cryptocurrency-Exchange-Announced-the-Listing-of-a-New-Altcoin-There-was-a-Rise-in-Price"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T08:27:06.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Frenzy: Burn Rate Soars 459%, Robinhood Adds 15B SHIB tokens]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19196083/Shiba-Inu-Frenzy-Burn-Rate-Soars-459-Robinhood-Adds-15B-SHIB-tokens</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19196083/Shiba-Inu-Frenzy-Burn-Rate-Soars-459-Robinhood-Adds-15B-SHIB-tokens"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T08:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use Unreal Engine 4 for VR development?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19196061/How-to-use-Unreal-Engine-4-for-VR-development</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19196061/How-to-use-Unreal-Engine-4-for-VR-development"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T08:22:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Craft immersive virtual worlds and VR games with the Unreal Engine 4 game development platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Bitcoin ETFs hold $27 billion in assets, Ali Martinez reports]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19196050/US-Bitcoin-ETFs-hold-27-billion-in-assets-Ali-Martinez-reports</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19196050/US-Bitcoin-ETFs-hold-27-billion-in-assets-Ali-Martinez-reports"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T08:19:39.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Exchange Binance Announced the Listing of 3 New Altcoin Trading Pairs!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19196036/Bitcoin-Exchange-Binance-Announced-the-Listing-of-3-New-Altcoin-Trading-Pairs</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19196036/Bitcoin-Exchange-Binance-Announced-the-Listing-of-3-New-Altcoin-Trading-Pairs"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T08:15:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency exchange Binance announced that it will list 3 new altcoin trading pairs on its platform. Continue Reading: Bitcoin Exchange Binance Announced the Listing of 3 New Altcoin Trading Pairs!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Goldman Sachs Executive Shares His Top 9 Tips for Successful Crypto Trading]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19196063/Former-Goldman-Sachs-Executive-Shares-His-Top-9-Tips-for-Successful-Crypto-Trading</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19196063/Former-Goldman-Sachs-Executive-Shares-His-Top-9-Tips-for-Successful-Crypto-Trading"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T08:15:02.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Reiterates Anti-CBDC Stance, Credits Vivek Ramaswamy for Policy Guidance]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f02dc434</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/01/23/trump-reiterates-anti-cbdc-stance-credits-vivek-ramaswamy-for-policy-guidance/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T08:10:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Republican frontrunner credited former candidate Vivek Ramaswamy for the policy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jim Cramer Cautious On Bitcoin: ETF Introduction Doesn’t Guarantee Recovery]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f02e02a6</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/jim-cramer-cautious-on-bitcoin-and-etf/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T08:09:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the dynamic landscape of cryptocurrencies, Bitcoin is currently traversing a terrain marked by uncertainty and divergent perspectives. Once a dominant force in the digital currency realm, Bitcoin is now experiencing a period of skepticism and reevaluation.
 
The initial surge in anticipation surrounding the introduction of Bitcoin Exchange-Traded Funds (ETFs) has waned, leading to a more cautious outlook, notably articulated by Wall Street figure Jim Cramer.
 
 
Cramer Not Comfy About Short-Term Trajectory Of Bitcoin
 
Cramer, the host of CNBC’s “Mad Money” who is usually known for his market optimism, has raised concerns about the leading coin’s short-term prospects. He attributes this shift in sentiment to Bitcoin’s inability to sustain its rapid pre-ETF price surge, suggesting that t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s When Bitcoin ETFs Could Drive BTC Price to Greater Heights, According to Macro Guru Lyn Alden]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19196030/Heres-When-Bitcoin-ETFs-Could-Drive-BTC-Price-to-Greater-Heights-According-to-Macro-Guru-Lyn-Alden</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19196030/Heres-When-Bitcoin-ETFs-Could-Drive-BTC-Price-to-Greater-Heights-According-to-Macro-Guru-Lyn-Alden"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T08:04:57.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pressure mounts on Meta as Congress demands transparency]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19196051/Pressure-mounts-on-Meta-as-Congress-demands-transparency</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19196051/Pressure-mounts-on-Meta-as-Congress-demands-transparency"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T08:02:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The United States House Financial Services Committee has intensified its scrutiny of Meta, the parent company of Facebook, over its cryptocurrency and blockchain-related plans. This comes as Meta currently has five active trademark applications related to cryptocurrencies and blockchain...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jim Cramer Cautious On Bitcoin: ETF Introduction Doesn’t Guarantee Recovery]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19196019/Jim-Cramer-Cautious-On-Bitcoin-ETF-Introduction-Doesnt-Guarantee-Recovery</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19196019/Jim-Cramer-Cautious-On-Bitcoin-ETF-Introduction-Doesnt-Guarantee-Recovery"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T08:02:11.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Massive 200,000 Bitcoin (BTC) Dump Expected in 60 Days: Mt. Gox Update]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19196032/Massive-200000-Bitcoin-BTC-Dump-Expected-in-60-Days-Mt-Gox-Update</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19196032/Massive-200000-Bitcoin-BTC-Dump-Expected-in-60-Days-Mt-Gox-Update"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T08:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to choose a safe casino zonder Cruks?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19196022/How-to-choose-a-safe-casino-zonder-Cruks</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19196022/How-to-choose-a-safe-casino-zonder-Cruks"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Reiterates Anti-CBDC Stance, Credits Vivek Ramaswamy for Policy Guidance]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19196021/Trump-Reiterates-Anti-CBDC-Stance-Credits-Vivek-Ramaswamy-for-Policy-Guidance</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19196021/Trump-Reiterates-Anti-CBDC-Stance-Credits-Vivek-Ramaswamy-for-Policy-Guidance"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T07:58:21.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Development That Excites Victims of Bankrupt Crypto Exchanges: 'The Exchange Sent a Confirmation E-Mail to Its Users!']]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19196015/Development-That-Excites-Victims-of-Bankrupt-Crypto-Exchanges-The-Exchange-Sent-a-Confirmation-E-Mail-to-Its-Users</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19196015/Development-That-Excites-Victims-of-Bankrupt-Crypto-Exchanges-The-Exchange-Sent-a-Confirmation-E-Mail-to-Its-Users"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T07:56:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Users on Reddit reported that the bankrupt Bitcoin exchange has begun the process of compensating its creditors. Continue Reading: Development That Excites Victims of Bankrupt Crypto Exchanges: 'The Exchange Sent a Confirmation E-Mail to Its Users!']]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brad Mills Reflects on Bitcoin ‘Season 2’ — A New Era of Monetary and Platform Coexistence]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f0152d67</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/brad-mills-reflects-on-bitcoin-season-2-a-new-era-of-monetary-and-platform-coexistence/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T07:13:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brad Mills discusses the Bitcoin “Season 2” narrative, a phase that signifies a coexistence and rivalry between the traditional monetary maximalists and the newly emerging platform maximalists.
 
Brad Mills Discusses the Rise of Platform Maximalism in ‘Season 2’
 
In a thought-provoking post on X, Brad Mills, a notable figure in the Bitcoin community, delves into the evolving dynamics of Bitcoin’s ecosystem, specifically something referred to as “Season 2.” Brad Mills is known for his early involvement, expertise, and advocacy for bitcoin as well as a founder of multiple crypto startups.
 
Season 2 refers to, in Mills’s own words, “the split of the monetary maximalist activist Bitcoiners from the platform maximalist entrepreneur Bitcoiners.” Mills, initially skeptical of the Season 2 conce…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Sencil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Abra Settles with Texas Regulator, Will Open Withdrawals for 12,000 Customers]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f0157e60</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/abra-settles-with-texas-regulator-will-open-withdrawals-for-12000-customers/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T07:11:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto lender Abra has entered into a settlement with the Texas State Securities Board, agreeing to return the frozen funds of the customers. According to yesterday’s (Monday) announcement, the company currently holds about $13.6 million in crypto assets for roughly 12,000 investors.
Withdrawals Will Start
Under the settlement terms, Abra clients with a balance of more than $10 will receive a notification detailing the withdrawal procedure. They will have a seven-day window to make the withdrawals. For the unclaimed proceeds, the company will convert them to US dollars and send checks to the investors in Texas. Abra must complete the other stipulations under the settlement agreement within 30 days.
“Our agency recognizes that financial losses can have a devastating impact on retirement…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arnab Shome</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Sheds Nearly $1 Billion In Grayscale Bitcoin ETF: Is This The End Of The BTC Sell-Off Saga?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f015c92a</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ftx-sheds-nearly-1-billion-in-grayscale-bitcoin-etf/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T07:08:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FTX, a now-defunct crypto exchange, has reportedly sold off its stake in Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC). Recent reports indicate that FTX liquidated approximately 22 million shares, valued at nearly $1 billion, effectively reducing its GBTC ownership to zero.
 
This massive sale emerges after GBTC’s transformation into a spot exchange-traded fund (ETF), marking a pivotal moment in the defunct crypto exchange’s strategic maneuvers.
 
Grayscale’s conversion of its Bitcoin trust into a spot ETF, which now stands as the world’s largest Bitcoin ETF with assets exceeding $28.6 billion, was a landmark event in the crypto sphere.
 
 
This significant shift followed Grayscale’s victory against the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), allowing the conversion last year. However, this transiti…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Unphased by China's Stimulus Plan]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f0122d42</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/01/23/bitcoin-unphased-by-chinas-stimulus-plan/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T06:34:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong's Hang Seng Index and the CSI 300 both responded to Beijing's plan to reboot China's domestic stock market, but bitcoin remains in the red.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Sanctions Imposed By These 3 Countries In Joint Effort Against Hamas-Linked Networks]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f01d6292</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-sanctions-imposed-by-these-3-countries/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T06:07:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The United States Department of the Treasury’s Office of Foreign Assets Control (OFAC) has announced a new round of sanctions targeting networks and facilitators involved in crypto transactions linked to the terrorist group Hamas. 
 
The move comes in response to Hamas’ alleged continued efforts to exploit various financial transfer mechanisms, including cryptocurrencies, to fund their terrorist activities.
 
Sanctions On Crypto Networks Linked To Hamas
 
Under Secretary of the Treasury for Terrorism and Financial Intelligence, Brian E. Nelson emphasized that Hamas has been using crypto assets and other means to channel funds to support its illicit operations. 
 
The US Treasury, in collaboration with its allies and partners, is committed to leveraging its authorities to target Hamas, its …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Howell Predicts Continued Surge in Global Liquidity Benefiting Stocks, Gold, and Crypto]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f01bb07b</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/michael-howell-predicts-continued-surge-in-global-liquidity-benefiting-stocks-gold-and-crypto/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T05:10:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crossborder Capital’s Michael Howell, a veteran in global finance, offered a liquidity-based view on the current state of the economy. He challenged the prevailing narrative of monetary tightening with evidence of a rise in liquidity, which in turn should uplift stocks, gold, and cryptocurrencies.
 
Michael Howell of Crossborder Capital Focused on Rising Global Liquidity and Its Market Impact
 
Michael Howell is the founder and CEO of Crossborder Capital, a London-based FCA registered, independent research and investment company with over $1 billion assets under management. Previously he was Head of Research for Baring Securities and Research Director of Solomon Brothers. With a deep understanding of international finance and economics, Howell has become a prominent figure in analyzing glo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Sencil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX’s Trading Arm Drops Lawsuit Against Grayscale]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f00447b1</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ftxs-trading-arm-drops-lawsuit-against-grayscale/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T05:04:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After crypto exchange FTX and its trading arm Alameda Research filed for bankruptcy in November 2022, the failed company has been attempting to recover assets to refund its creditors. In a new development, the FTX affiliate has decided to drop its lawsuit against Digital asset manager Grayscale voluntarily.
 
 
An Attempt To “Recover Hundreds Of Millions Of Dollars”
 
According to a report from Reuters, Alameda Research has decided to drop the lawsuit against Grayscale this Monday, as a court filing showed.
 
In March 2023, Alameda filed a lawsuit in a Court in Delaware against Grayscale, its parent company Digital Currency Group, Inc. (DCG), and the CEOs of both companies, Michael Sonnenshein and Barry Silbert.
 
In this lawsuit, they accused the digital asset manager of abusing “their co…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rubmar Garcia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale Selling: CryptoQuant CEO Unveils On-Chain Discrepancy]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f0024344</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/grayscale-selling-cryptoquant-disclosures-on-chain/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T04:05:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CryptoQuant CEO has explained there is a delay between when Grayscale made Bitcoin outflows and when they made a disclosure.
 
Grayscale Has Made Some Bitcoin Outflows That Are Yet To Be Disclosed
 
A few days ago, CryptoQuant founder and CEO Ki Young Ju revealed a discrepancy between on-chain data and the off-chain disclosures made by the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC).
 
Here are the charts that the analyst had shared in the X post:
 

 
 
The left chart shows the data for the Bitcoin fund holdings of GBTC as disclosed by Grayscale, while the right one reveals the actual reserve of the ETF by tracking the on-chain addresses associated with it.
 
 
When Ju shared these charts, the left chart showed around 581,276 BTC in the GBTC reserve, while the right displayed about 561,700 BTC. The an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Abra to Open Withdrawals After Settling with Texas Regulators]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f00d7094</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/01/23/abra-to-open-withdrawals-after-settling-with-texas-regulators/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T03:35:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tk]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Napolitano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China Pushes Metaverse Standardization Group to Establish the Rules of the Yuanverse]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f00ffbd7</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/china-pushes-metaverse-standardization-group-to-establish-the-rules-of-the-yuanverse/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T03:09:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The government of China has announced the creation of a metaverse standardization working group to establish different rules to govern the Chinese Yuanverse platform. The standardization group will be integrated by Chinese universities, government institutions, and companies like Tencent, Huawei, Baidu, Netease, and Sense Time.
China Announces Metaverse Standardization Group
The Chinese government aims to create standards for metaverse platforms. In a circular released on January 19, the Ministry of Industry and Information Technology of China (MIIT) communicated the formation of the Metaverse Standardization Working Group, which will aim to establish rules for the organization of metaverse platforms and the development of the Yuanverse, a national metaverse platform.
The standardization g…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Bitcoin Paradigm: How BTC Surpasses Traditional Finance, According To Expert]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f00898a9</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-paradigm-btc-surpasses-traditional-finance/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T03:02:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samson Mow, former Chief Strategy Officer at Blockstream and the CEO of Jan3, recently shared an insight into Bitcoin’s impact on modern financial technology.
 
1000x Superiority Over Traditional Finance
 
In a bold statement on X, Mow proclaimed that Bitcoin represents a “quantum” leap in monetary technology, surpassing traditional financial systems by “1,000.” The CEO of Jan3 emphasized that BTC is not merely an “incremental improvement” over existing monetary systems like gold or the US dollar.
 
Instead, Mow asserted that Bitcoin’s emergence marks a pivotal shift, “revolutionizing” how society perceives and interacts with money. Mow described BTC as a “step change” in the global financial system.
 
As indicated in the shared screenshot from a dictionary, this signifies a “sudden and di…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Resurrecting Dead Loved Ones with AI Is Already a Thing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213802</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213802/thanabots-eternal-you-project-december-ai-dead-people"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T02:20:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A documentary premiering at Sundance Film Festival follows the sometimes heartwarming, sometimes harrowing world of ”thanabots.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Fund Exodus: Higher-Cost Issuers Lose $2.9 Billion As Spot Bitcoin ETFs Attract Massive Inflows]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f1f1a524</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-fund-exodus-bitcoin-etfs-attract-inflows/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T01:32:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recent report by CoinShares revealed that higher-cost crypto fund issuers in the United States have experienced a significant outflow of $2.9 billion since the new spot Bitcoin ETFs hit the market.
 
Growing Dominance Of Bitcoin ETFs
 
Per the report, while experiencing minor outflows of $21 million last week, digital asset investment products showed significantly high trading volumes amounting to $11.8 billion. 
 
This surge in trading activity underscores the growing dominance of exchange-traded products (ETPs) and highlights their significant impact on the overall market.
 
Incumbent higher-cost issuers in the United States bore the brunt of the outflows, with $2.9 billion exiting their funds. In contrast, as seen in the chart below, newly issued Bitcoin ETFs garnered $4.13 billion in…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Asks Judge to Deny SEC’s New Discovery Requests Concerning XRP]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f1fc0d28</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ripple-asks-judge-to-deny-secs-new-discovery-requests-concerning-xrp/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T01:08:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Labs has opposed the requests by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) for post-compliant discovery concerning XRP. Ripple argued that the regulator’s requests are “untimely” and “the SEC has failed to justify each of its requests on the merits.” Moreover, the crypto firm stated that “the information the SEC seeks has no bearing on the court’s remedies determination.”
 
SEC Seeks More Information From Ripple Regarding XRP
 

 
In response to the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission’s motion to compel certain post-compliant discovery regarding XRP, Ripple Labs sent a letter to Judge Sarah Netburn on Friday, firmly opposing the SEC’s requests.
 

 
The SEC wants Ripple to produce audited financial statements for 2022 and 2023 as well as all post-complaint contracts for …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Pokémon With Guns’: Why Gamers Can’t Stop Talking About Palworld]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213791</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213791/pokemon-with-guns-why-gamers-cant-stop-talking-about-palworld"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T00:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Palworld is gaming’s hottest new thing, with huge sales and sizable controversy to match for the Pokémon-esque indie game. Here’s why.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Ordinals 'Quantum Cat' Sells for Over $250K at Sotheby's]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213779</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213779/bitcoin-ordinals-quantum-cat-sells-for-over-250k-at-sothebys"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T23:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The “Genesis Cat” Bitcoin art by FAR fetched 6.31 BTC at Sotheby's, with the wider Ordinals sale bringing in nearly $1.1 million in total.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Business or Pleasure: Nvidia's CEO Visits China For the First Time in Years]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213768</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213768/nvidia-ceo-goes-to-china-jensen-huang-taiwan"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T23:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jensen Huang hadn’t been to China in four years, but visited Taiwan for the fourth time in one year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kaspersky Warns of Mac Exploit Targeting Bitcoin and Exodus Wallets]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213754</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213754/macos-bitcoin-wallet-malware-exploit-kapersky"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T22:46:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cybersecurity firm says hackers show "unusual creativity" in building the macOS malware, affecting both Intel and Apple Silicon devices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Air Ball: NBA Star Dwight Howard's Avalanche NFTs Are a Huge Miss]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213736</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213736/air-ball-nba-star-dwight-howard-avalanche-nfts-huge-miss"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T22:05:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Negative buzz around Dwight Howard's collection, Ballers, was so bad that Ava Labs distanced itself from the collection on Sunday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alameda Research Drops Grayscale Lawsuit, Sparking Share Redemption Rush]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213748</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213748/alameda-research-drops-grayscale-lawsuit-sparking-share-redemption-rush"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T21:46:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The likely reason? The ability to sell Grayscale’s Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) tokens.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Someone Airdropped 21K Ordinals to Bitcoin Users as Part of Mysterious Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213720</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213720/someone-just-airdropped-21000-ordinals-to-bitcoin-collectors-and-its-part-of-a-mysterious-game"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T21:11:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The buzzy but anonymous ‘Runecoin’ airdrop is unrelated to Ordinals’ Runes, raising scam concerns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Falls Below $40,000 as Grayscale Unwind Continues]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213721</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213721/bitcoin-falls-below-40000-grayscale"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T20:21:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Market watchers point to the flood of cash exiting Grayscale's Bitcoin ETF.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Pumps Amid Speculation Over Twitter Payments]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213702</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213702/dogecoin-pumps-amid-speculation-over-twitter-payments"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T17:58:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twitter hasn't confirmed anything about using Dogecoin for payments, but that's not stopping traders from buying the rumor.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETFs Have Gained $4 Billion—But Other Crypto Funds Are Waning]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213679</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213679/bitcoin-etfs-have-gained-4-billion-but-other-crypto-funds-are-waning"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T16:47:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Investors are fast putting money into Bitcoin ETFs—at the expense of other types of crypto funds, a report says.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gaming Tokens Plunge as Bitcoin Nears $40K—But Ronin Is On Fire]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213686</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213686/gaming-tokens-plunge-bitcoin-nears-40k-ronin-on-fire"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T16:30:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ronin’s RON token nearly hit a two-year high Sunday amid Pixels airdrop hype, but most major gaming tokens are down today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum DeFi Gets ‘Gasless' Trading With New 0x API]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213582</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213582/ethereum-defi-gasless-trading-0x-api"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T16:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The newest addition to 0x’s selection of trading APIs allows builders to use "gasless" swaps in their decentralized applications on Ethereum.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Proof of Stake? How it Differs From Proof of Work]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=5733</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/proof-of-work-vs-proof-of-stake"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T12:50:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Proof of stake is a consensus protocol that locks up crypto to secure the network. It's less energy-intensive than Bitcoin's proof of work mechanism.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Benson,Matt Hussey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Slips Below $41,000 as Sell-Off Continues]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213668</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213668/bitcoin-slips-below-41000-as-sell-off-continues"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T12:38:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price of Bitcoin has continued to slide following the approval of multiple spot Bitcoin ETFs earlier in the month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Labs Files for Chapter 11 Bankrupty in Delaware]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213662</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213662/terraform-labs-files-for-chapter-11-bankrupty-in-delaware"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T10:46:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The firm said that the bankruptcy filing would enable it "to execute on its business plan while navigating ongoing legal proceedings."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week on Crypto Twitter: Wall Street, Republican Candidates Embrace Crypto Ethos]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213609</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213609/this-week-on-crypto-twitter-wall-street-republican-candidates-embrace-crypto-ethos"/>
        <updated>2024-01-21T11:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recent moves appear to have cemented Trump’s status as the most attractive presidential candidate for crypto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Oasys? The Gaming Blockchain With Ubisoft and Sega Onboard]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213499</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-oasys-gaming-blockchain-ubisoft-sega-onboard"/>
        <updated>2024-01-20T19:49:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oasys wants to be a crypto gaming destination for the biggest developers. Here’s how it works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk’s xAI Raises $500 Million: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213614</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213614/elon-musks-xai-raises-500-million-report"/>
        <updated>2024-01-20T16:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AI start-up is eyeing an up to $20 billion valuation, according to Bloomberg.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Despite ETF Hype, Bitcoin and Ethereum Plunge Hard]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213494</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213494/this-week-in-coins-despite-etf-hype-bitcoin-and-ethereum-plunge-hard"/>
        <updated>2024-01-20T11:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin has taken a big hit over the past seven days following the launch of long-awaited spot Bitcoin ETFs on Wall Street.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Church Allegedly Issued Crypto Token Backed by Nothing But God's Word]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213592</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213592/church-allegedly-issued-crypto-token-backed-nothing-but-gods-word"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T23:21:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Colorado couple had their assets frozen by a state judge after making millions on a cryptocurrency they say they created at God’s command.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale Is Sending Bitcoin to Coinbase in $500 Million Clips—Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213564</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213564/grayscale-sending-bitcoin-coinbase-500-million-why"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T21:57:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cash continues to flow out from Grayscale's Bitcoin ETF, while other funds see gains. Here's what's going on.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Ubisoft, Xbox, and Blizzard Are Using AI to Make Next-Generation Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147436</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147436/ai-game-development-ubisoft-roblox-blizzard"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T21:53:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATED: Final Fantasy maker Square Enix says it used AI tools for its big new game, plus Ubisoft is tapping Nvidia's gaming tech for NPCs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Coinbase Win Dismissal of SEC Lawsuit? Legal Experts Weigh In]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213566</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213566/will-coinbase-win-dismissal-sec-lawsuit-legal-experts-weigh-in"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T21:27:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lawyers were impressed by Coinbase's oral arguments, and say full dismissal of the SEC's suit is a realistic possibility.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brazil Stock Exchange to Open After Hours Trading, Give Bitcoin a Boost]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213568</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213568/brazil-stock-exchange-to-open-after-hours-trading-give-bitcoin-a-boost"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T21:10:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin was the only asset besides the country’s own Ibovespa index approved for late night trading sessions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Game On: The Hottest Upcoming Gaming Token Airdrops]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211029</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211029/game-on-hottest-upcoming-gaming-token-airdrops"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T20:26:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATED: Gaming airdrops are heating up, with Nifty Island, Nyan Heroes, and Apeiron revealing plans after the buzzy XAI token launch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘You Can See the Demand Out There for Bitcoin’: Franklin Templeton CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213537</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213537/you-can-see-the-demand-out-there-for-bitcoin-franklin-templeton-ceo"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T19:21:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The global asset manager’s Bitcoin ETF is the latest in blockchain-related investment opportunities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ronin Gaming Wallet Now Supports Ethereum, Polygon, and BNB Chain]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213540</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213540/ronin-gaming-wallet-now-supports-ethereum-polygon-bnb-chain"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T19:06:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ronin’s mobile wallet for iOS and Android will see a new security feature as well as a refreshed design that lets users view more data about their crypto and NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nintendo Switch 2 Preview: Everything You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197793</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197793/nintendo-switch-2-rumors-leaks-latest-news"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T18:13:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATED: Hundreds of developers admit in a major industry survey that they're working on Nintendo Switch 2 games. Here's everything we know so far.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saga Expands Airdrop Rewards to Solana, Polygon, and Avalanche Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213528</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213528/saga-expands-airdrop-rewards-solana-polygon-avalanche-games"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T18:08:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Upcoming gaming network Saga is bringing its play-to-airdrop push to games like Parallel, Shrapnel, and Gas Hero on other chains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana, Avalanche Tumble as Bitcoin Slides Towards $40,000]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213511</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213511/solana-avalanche-tumble-bitcoin-slides-towards-40000"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T17:34:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin is down bad—but major altcoins like Solana, Avalanche, and Cardano are also experiencing a brutal selloff.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Dips Into Bitcoin Ordinals as His NFT Ambitions Fizzle]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213478</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213478/trump-is-doing-bitcoin-ordinals-as-he-tries-to-revive-flailing-nft-drop"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T12:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 presidential hopeful’s latest project involves 200 NFTs inscribed on the Bitcoin blockchain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Punts Fidelty Spot Ethereum ETF Decision to March]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213480</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213480/sec-punts-fidelty-spot-ethereum-etf-decision-to-march"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T11:04:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC has stated it needs "sufficient time to consider the proposed rule change and the issues raised therein."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Crime Down 29% in 2023: Chainalysis Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213470</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213470/crypto-crime-down-29-percent-in-2023-chainalysis-report"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T01:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FTX tipped the scales in the amount of illicit cryptocurrency reported after the conviction of Sam Bankman-Fried.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Nifty Island' Is Already Better Than Most NFT Sandbox Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213423</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213423/nifty-island-already-better-most-nft-sandbox-games"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T23:24:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PREVIEW: Our first hands-on playtest of Nifty Island’s public beta was surprisingly addicting, allowing tons of room for imagination.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Someone 'Microwaved' a Solana Saga Phone—Now Degens Are Buying Meme NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213457</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213457/someone-microwaved-solana-saga-phone-now-degens-buying-meme-nfts"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T23:06:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s one less Solana Saga in the world after a viral experiment... but 3,333 more NFTs commemorating it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Is Coming for Gold's Global Market, Says Cathie Wood]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213442</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213442/bitcoin-is-coming-for-golds-global-market-says-cathie-wood"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T22:45:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ARK Invest CEO says financial investors should go with crypto over the precious metal, and tech investors should stick with software.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former OpenSea Exec Argues NFT Insider Trading Conviction Violated Law]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213440</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213440/former-opensea-exec-argues-nft-insider-trading-conviction-violated-law"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T22:21:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nathaniel Chastain was convicted last year for profiting off of information he was privy to as an executive at NFT marketplace OpenSea.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are you the one being farmed? w/ Frisson]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/i3sesrao/are-you-the-one-being-farmed-w-frisson</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/i3sesrao/are-you-the-one-being-farmed-w-frisson"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T18:38:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reza is joined by Frisson from Tallyx.xyz

They reflect on:
- building in the bear market
- the points system meta
- will zoomers care about decentralization]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Look Touch Own': OONA Discusses Her Performance Art Exhibition]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/79jpGlCe/look-touch-own-oona-discusses-her-performance-art-exhibition</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/79jpGlCe/look-touch-own-oona-discusses-her-performance-art-exhibition"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T16:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Conceptual artist OONA joins moderator Raina Marie to discuss "Look Touch Own," her performance art exhibition featuring her own former breast implants, which have been tokenized. This conversation was recorded at Rug Radio's R Haus event at Art Basel Miami in December 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Genius Marketing by Genius Marketers: How Crypto Builders Can Reach the Masses]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/YiQgzWJW/genius-marketing-by-genius-marketers-how-crypto-builders-can-reach-the-masses</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/YiQgzWJW/genius-marketing-by-genius-marketers-how-crypto-builders-can-reach-the-masses"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rug Radio founder Farokh Sarmad moderates a conversation between 9dcc founder and CEO Gmoney and Serotonin founder and CEO Amanda Cassatt about the challenges and opportunities in Web3 marketing and how they're navigating the ever-evolving space. Recorded at Rug Radio's R Haus event at Art Basel Miami in December 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generative Art Across Mediums: Artists Discuss the Evolving Space]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/GK3aN0zo/generative-art-across-mediums-artists-discuss-the-evolving-space</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/GK3aN0zo/generative-art-across-mediums-artists-discuss-the-evolving-space"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T02:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this panel discussion from Rug Radio's R Haus at Art Basel Miami 2023, Sofia Garcia, Ismail Tazi, Emily Edelman, and Aleksandra Art discuss the expanding generative art space—and why "generative" doesn't necessarily have to mean digital.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The AI Coin to Rule Them All with Mike Grantis]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rkYpU8TJ/the-ai-coin-to-rule-them-all-with-mike-grantis</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rkYpU8TJ/the-ai-coin-to-rule-them-all-with-mike-grantis"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T18:46:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reza is joined by Mike Grantis from Contango Digital to discuss
- The AI coin to rule them all
- The Solana Ecosystem 
- What's next for Solana airdrops]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conversation With Snowfro: Bringing 'Chromie Squiggle' #8107 to the Physical Space]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/DcrU04gG/conversation-with-snowfro-bringing-chromie-squiggle-8107-to-the-physical-space</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/DcrU04gG/conversation-with-snowfro-bringing-chromie-squiggle-8107-to-the-physical-space"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Art Blocks founder and CEO and "Chromie Squiggle" project creator Erick "snowfro" Calderon spoke with Benny Redbeard Gross at Rug Radio's R Haus event at Art Basel 2023, to discuss how and why "Chromie Squiggle" NFT #8107 was given a special edition print run in collaboration with Avant Arte.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don't Underestimate Mobile Gaming: Qualcomm's Matthew Grossman]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/34Oil4Qu/dont-underestimate-mobile-gaming-qualcomms-matthew-grossman</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/34Oil4Qu/dont-underestimate-mobile-gaming-qualcomms-matthew-grossman"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Qualcomm product marketing manager Matthew Grossman tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin why mobile esports is exploding in popularity around the world—and dispels some of the misconceptions around mobile gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF: This Is the 'Calm Before the Storm', Says ETF Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/VOX04ytt/bitcoin-etf-this-is-the-calm-before-the-storm-says-etf-analyst</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/VOX04ytt/bitcoin-etf-this-is-the-calm-before-the-storm-says-etf-analyst"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T20:20:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bloomberg Senior ETF Analyst Eric Balchunas joins Farokh Sarmad, Michael Anderson, and Ovie Faruq on the FOMO Hour to share the latest intel on the looming approval for a spot Bitcoin ETF, what might happen when the very different worlds of TradFi and crypto collide, and his insights on “Genslish,” the unique and strategic language of SEC chair Gary Gensler.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Losing 1500 BTC on Mt Gox and the Problem with Women in Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/EfNuNu8a/losing-1500-btc-on-mt-gox-and-the-problem-with-women-in-web3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/EfNuNu8a/losing-1500-btc-on-mt-gox-and-the-problem-with-women-in-web3"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T19:02:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week our host is joined by Brooke Lacey! 

They discuss:  
- Making and losing generational wealth
- Trauma Bond
- Women in Web3
- The Problem with WAGMI]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ESL Faceit Group Exploring Blockchain 'Opportunistically,' Says Exec]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/yvrs4lBx/esl-faceit-group-exploring-blockchain-opportunistically-says-exec</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/yvrs4lBx/esl-faceit-group-exploring-blockchain-opportunistically-says-exec"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T02:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Braithwaite—ESL Faceit Group's VP of Game Ecosystems, Mobile, and Snapdragon Pro Series—shares the esports firm's approach to blockchain technology with GG's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>