<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-05-07T05:17:17.759Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-05-07T05:17:17.759Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ore wins Solana hackathon despite disrupting Solana’s network in April]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19465509/Ore-wins-Solana-hackathon-despite-disrupting-Solanas-network-in-April</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19465509/Ore-wins-Solana-hackathon-despite-disrupting-Solanas-network-in-April"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T05:06:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A sudden rise in Ore mining transactions was one of the main culprits behind Solana’s April congestion issue where up to 70% of non-vote transactions were being rejected.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale Bitcoin Trust Sees First Inflows In 3 Months, Hong Kong ETF Market Gains Traction]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7428c3342e</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/grayscale-bitcoin-trust-first-inflows-in-3-months/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T05:02:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC), the world’s largest cryptocurrency investment vehicle, has experienced a notable influx of investor funds for the first time since the January approval of US spot Bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs). 
 
Grayscale Bitcoin Trust Bounces Back With Inflows
 
Data compiled by Bloomberg reveals that on May 3, Grayscale’s Bitcoin Trust received approximately $63 million in net inflows. This comes after net outflows totaling around $17.4 billion since the trust’s conversion. 
 
The outflows experienced in the past were partially linked to bankruptcies in the crypto industry, as defunct companies sought to repay their creditors by withdrawing funds from the trust. 
 
 
However, Grayscale’s position as the largest spot Bitcoin ETF in terms of assets under management …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitget’s Blockchain4Youth Celebrates 1st Anniversary, Educated Over 6,000 Participants Worldwide]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7428c36cbd</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitgets-blockchain4youth-celebrates-1st-anniversary-educated-over-6000-participants-worldwide/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T05:01:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitget, a leading crypto exchange and web3 company, announces the first anniversary of its Blockchain4Youth program and launches recap videos of the program. The initiative celebrated a year of driving Web 3.0 adoption among the youth, staying true to Bitget’s core principles of innovation, education, and empowerment. Bitget envisions a more equitable future driven by […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale Bitcoin Trust Sees First Inflows In 3 Months, Hong Kong ETF Market Gains Traction]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19465500/Grayscale-Bitcoin-Trust-Sees-First-Inflows-In-3-Months-Hong-Kong-ETF-Market-Gains-Traction</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19465500/Grayscale-Bitcoin-Trust-Sees-First-Inflows-In-3-Months-Hong-Kong-ETF-Market-Gains-Traction"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T05:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC), the world’s largest cryptocurrency investment vehicle, has experienced a notable influx of investor funds for the first time since the January approval of US spot Bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs). Grayscale Bitcoin Trust Bounces Back With Inflows Data compiled...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin's Transaction Fees Dominate Income As App Development Thrives, Says Analyst — A Boom For Industry With Dwindling Block Subsidies?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19465508/Bitcoins-Transaction-Fees-Dominate-Income-As-App-Development-Thrives-Says-Analyst-A-Boom-For-Industry-With-Dwindling-Block-Subsidies</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19465508/Bitcoins-Transaction-Fees-Dominate-Income-As-App-Development-Thrives-Says-Analyst-A-Boom-For-Industry-With-Dwindling-Block-Subsidies"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T04:53:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fees charged for processing transactions on the Bitcoin (CRYPTO: BTC) network have been on the rise in the last two years, providing a more sustainable source of income for a sector whose margins are narrowing. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tom Brady grilled on FTX ties in Netflix roast — ‘He fucked those people’]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19465478/Tom-Brady-grilled-on-FTX-ties-in-Netflix-roast-He-fucked-those-people</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19465478/Tom-Brady-grilled-on-FTX-ties-in-Netflix-roast-He-fucked-those-people"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T04:40:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tom Brady copped heat from comedians for his role in partnering with the now-defunct crypto exchange FTX.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Australia Tax Office Sets Sights On Crypto Exchanges’ Client Data, Bank Details]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19465483/Australia-Tax-Office-Sets-Sights-On-Crypto-Exchanges-Client-Data-Bank-Details</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19465483/Australia-Tax-Office-Sets-Sights-On-Crypto-Exchanges-Client-Data-Bank-Details"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T04:40:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Australian Tax Office is demanding annual transaction details from crypto exchanges in a move to tackle potential tax evasion. This crackdown aims to ensure investors correctly report their crypto gains and pay any capital gains taxes owed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ‘as strong as ever’ with record high 200-day moving average]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19465441/Bitcoin-as-strong-as-ever-with-record-high-200-day-moving-average</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19465441/Bitcoin-as-strong-as-ever-with-record-high-200-day-moving-average"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T04:21:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The long-term Bitcoin trend indicators, the 200-day and 200-week moving average, are at the highest-ever levels with Anthony Pompliano saying BTC is “as strong as ever.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu’s layer 3 blockchain set to power up blockchain real-world utility: Cypher Capital Chairman]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19465428/Shiba-Inus-layer-3-blockchain-set-to-power-up-blockchain-real-world-utility-Cypher-Capital-Chairman</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19465428/Shiba-Inus-layer-3-blockchain-set-to-power-up-blockchain-real-world-utility-Cypher-Capital-Chairman"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T04:06:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite a shaky 2022 and a challenging 2023, Shiba Inu has remained dedicated to its vision of building a comprehensive crypto ecosystem.Following the development of its metaverse and layer 2 chain, Shiba Inu is now ramping up efforts for its new privacy-centric layer 3 blockchain. Last month,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Enters A Long-Term Bullish Rally, Here’s The Roadmap And Target]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7428c9febd</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-long-term-bullish-rally/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T04:04:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin has now presumably entered a long-term bullish rally that could send its price higher from here, according to one crypto analyst. This comes after the price had crashed below $0.13, before a swift recovery brought it back above $0.16. So what is driving this current bull rally?
 
Dogecoin Ready For Long-Term Bullish Rally
 
Crypto analyst Behdark, on the TradingView website, shared an interesting analysis that has caught the eye of Dogecoin community members. The crypto analyst identified that the meme coin has now entered a bullish rally, with reasons to back up why this is so.
 
 
Behdark explained that the Dogecoin price has formed strong support just above $0.1, and this has helped to bounce the coin back up in the event of a crash. The demand at this level is what ensures tha…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Enters A Long-Term Bullish Rally, Here’s The Roadmap And Target]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19465418/Dogecoin-Enters-A-Long-Term-Bullish-Rally-Heres-The-Roadmap-And-Target</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19465418/Dogecoin-Enters-A-Long-Term-Bullish-Rally-Heres-The-Roadmap-And-Target"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T04:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin has now presumably entered a long-term bullish rally that could send its price higher from here, according to one crypto analyst. This comes after the price had crashed below $0.13, before a swift recovery brought it back above $0.16. So what is driving this current bull rally? Dogecoin...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More Ethereum whales exit the market – Are they giving up?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19465416/More-Ethereum-whales-exit-the-market-Are-they-giving-up</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19465416/More-Ethereum-whales-exit-the-market-Are-they-giving-up"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T04:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum is seeing small gains as its largest holders show signs of losing faith, unimpressed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Delays Spot Ethereum ETFs while Bitcoin ETFs Draw Institutional Interest]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19465467/SEC-Delays-Spot-Ethereum-ETFs-while-Bitcoin-ETFs-Draw-Institutional-Interest</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19465467/SEC-Delays-Spot-Ethereum-ETFs-while-Bitcoin-ETFs-Draw-Institutional-Interest"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T03:57:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has once again delayed its decision on highly-anticipated Ethereum exchange-traded funds (ETFs). This postponement marks another chapter in the complex interplay between regulatory actions and market dynamics in the crypto sector....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More Airdrop Claims AGAIN!! (And NFT Minting ALPHA Update)]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19465419/More-Airdrop-Claims-AGAIN-And-NFT-Minting-ALPHA-Update</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19465419/More-Airdrop-Claims-AGAIN-And-NFT-Minting-ALPHA-Update"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T03:57:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tabi Voyager II: https://tabi.lol/Masa Finance: https://app.masa.finance/Legend of Arcadia NFT Genesis Mint: https://mint.legendofarcadia.io/Tabi Invite Code (FCFS):x9ZRjzoZaEtGU0AX4ugq5RxAIKu0jofAlObSQPQ4sI9Wj3SzdYqpaoGJiIPfHHm5DH0znWPiKweMAbImR2is7Yc3vkSAhIxrO4Td🌼 GET $30,000 in rewards on...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CFTC Chairman Says Expect Regulators to Crack Down on More Crypto Firms]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19465423/CFTC-Chairman-Says-Expect-Regulators-to-Crack-Down-on-More-Crypto-Firms</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19465423/CFTC-Chairman-Says-Expect-Regulators-to-Crack-Down-on-More-Crypto-Firms"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T03:41:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Commodity Futures Trading Commission chairman Rostin Behnam said cryptocurrency firms can expect to see more enforcement action from U.S. regulators in the next 6 to 24 months as retail interest in the asset class increases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI and Web 3.0 – a Risky Convergence of Technologies]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19465399/AI-and-Web-30-a-Risky-Convergence-of-Technologies</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19465399/AI-and-Web-30-a-Risky-Convergence-of-Technologies"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T03:40:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The advent of strong AI, or AGI, no longer seems like something coming out of a sci-fi book – it’s increasingly becoming our reality. Naturally, this trending topic has influenced the Web 3.0 space, prompting companies and investors to focus on AI integration. Remember the initial crypto boom...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Investment Firm Franklin Templeton Believes Solana Will Become the Third Largest Crypto Asset]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7428b52faa</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/investment-firm-franklin-templeton-believes-solana-will-become-the-third-largest-crypto-asset/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T03:33:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Franklin Templeton, a leading investment firm with over $1.5 trillion in assets under management (AUM), believes Solana has the potential to become the third-largest cryptocurrency in the market. The firm praised the resilience of the project, its continued airdrops, and the work developers have undertaken to fix the network’s recent congestion issues. Franklin Templeton: There […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lbank Now The 2nd Crypto Exchange To Confirm It Will List New Bitcoin Rival, Mollars Token]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19465422/Lbank-Now-The-2nd-Crypto-Exchange-To-Confirm-It-Will-List-New-Bitcoin-Rival-Mollars-Token</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19465422/Lbank-Now-The-2nd-Crypto-Exchange-To-Confirm-It-Will-List-New-Bitcoin-Rival-Mollars-Token"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T03:31:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new Bitcoin rival, Mollars (MOLLARS), continues to gain ground before its official listing on public crypto exchanges. A second crypto exchange, “LBank,” announced Monday that it will list the new store-of-value crypto asset after the token presale closes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Supply Shock: Exchange Inflow Trend Lowest Since 2015]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7428b04d13</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-supply-shock-exchange-inflow-lowest-2015/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T03:03:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data shows the Bitcoin exchange inflow trend has been at its lowest in almost a decade recently, a sign that may be bullish for the asset.
 
Bitcoin Exchange Inflows Have Been On The Decline Recently
 
As pointed out by CryptoQuant author Axel Adler Jr in a post on X, the BTC exchange inflows have been heading down for a while now. The “exchange inflow” is an on-chain indicator that keeps track of the total amount of Bitcoin the investors deposit to wallets attached to centralized exchanges.
 
 
When this metric’s value is high, it means that holders are transferring a large number of coins to these platforms right now. As one of the main reasons why investors might deposit coins in the exchanges’ custody is for selling purposes, this kind of trend can be bearish for the asset.
 
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Supply Shock: Exchange Inflow Trend Lowest Since 2015]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19465374/Bitcoin-Supply-Shock-Exchange-Inflow-Trend-Lowest-Since-2015</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19465374/Bitcoin-Supply-Shock-Exchange-Inflow-Trend-Lowest-Since-2015"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T03:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data shows the Bitcoin exchange inflow trend has been at its lowest in almost a decade recently, a sign that may be bullish for the asset. Bitcoin Exchange Inflows Have Been On The Decline Recently As pointed out by CryptoQuant author Axel Adler Jr in a post on X, the BTC exchange...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4.85m French Crypto Holders ‘Fail to Declare Their Holdings’ as Gov’t ‘Takes Aim’ at Offenders]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19465387/485m-French-Crypto-Holders-Fail-to-Declare-Their-Holdings-as-Govt-Takes-Aim-at-Offenders</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19465387/485m-French-Crypto-Holders-Fail-to-Declare-Their-Holdings-as-Govt-Takes-Aim-at-Offenders"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T03:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Only a small fraction of French crypto holders have declared their coins to the state, a report claimed – with the government set to take action.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amsterdam Halving Party 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19465384/Amsterdam-Halving-Party-2024</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19465384/Amsterdam-Halving-Party-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T02:59:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s a wrap! On Friday, April 19th, we celebrated an unique event at the Posthoornkerk in Amsterdam, where more than 315 Bitcoiners and captains of industry gathered for this sold-out occasion! 🧡Together with friends from Satoshi Radio , @BNRCryptocast, Web3 Pioniers podcast, and Bitcoin Alpha,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Meets Bitcoin-Supporting President Javier Milei Again: 'I Recommend Investing In Argentina']]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19465376/Elon-Musk-Meets-Bitcoin-Supporting-President-Javier-Milei-Again-I-Recommend-Investing-In-Argentina</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19465376/Elon-Musk-Meets-Bitcoin-Supporting-President-Javier-Milei-Again-I-Recommend-Investing-In-Argentina"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T02:56:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla and SpaceX CEO Elon Musk and Argentina president Javier Milei met on the sidelines of the 27th annual Milken Institute Global Conference on Monday, their second meeting in less than a month. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Congressman calls SEC Chair Gary Gensler “rouge regulator”]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19465325/US-Congressman-calls-SEC-Chair-Gary-Gensler-rouge-regulator</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19465325/US-Congressman-calls-SEC-Chair-Gary-Gensler-rouge-regulator"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T02:12:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Rose, US Representative serving Tennessee's Sixth Congressional District, is strongly critical of the US Securities and Exchange Commissions (SEC) actions against Robinhood. The Congressman called the SEC and its Chair, Gary Gensler rouge regulators in a recent post on X.According to him,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This State-Owned German Bank Enters Crypto With New Blockchain-Based Digital Bond]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7428be30c0</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/german-bank-enters-crypto-blockchain-digital-bond/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T02:04:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[German state-owned development bank Kreditanstalt für Wiederaufbau (KfW) is gearing up to issue its first blockchain-based digital bond, marking a significant milestone in adopting crypto technology within the financial sector. 
 
According to a recent report by Bloomberg, KfW has already successfully issued a digital bond as a central register security in compliance with the German Electronic Securities Act (eWpG). The bank is preparing to take the next step by offering a blockchain-based bond to attract a wide range of investors.
 
Streamlined Crypto Bond Offering
 
Treasurer Tim Armbruster expressed optimism about digitalization’s advantages in terms of increased efficiency and scalability. Recognizing these potential benefits, KfW aims to leverage blockchain technology to streamline an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana NFTs revive, beat Polygon: What about Ethereum NFTs?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19465318/Solana-NFTs-revive-beat-Polygon-What-about-Ethereum-NFTs</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19465318/Solana-NFTs-revive-beat-Polygon-What-about-Ethereum-NFTs"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T02:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana NFTs outshines Polygon, but Ethereum remains the top player.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash Prepares Adaptive Blocksize Limit Upgrade, Commits to Network Scaling]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7428b85550</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-cash-prepares-adaptive-blocksize-limit-upgrade-commits-to-network-scaling/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T01:42:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash, the usability-focused Bitcoin hard fork, is preparing to perform a blockchain-wide upgrade slated to happen on May 15th. The upgrade implements the adaptive blocksize limit algorithm, allowing the network to adapt to future increases in demand without having direct input from actors, avoiding the opportunity for social attacks. Bitcoin Cash to Include Adaptative […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano Founder Considers Partnership With Bitcoin Cash – What Is It About?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7428a4213b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/cardano-partnership-bitcoin-cash/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T01:02:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano’s (ADA) founder, Charles Hoskinson, recently raised the possibility of Cardano partnering with Bitcoin Cash. He noted how significant this partnership could be for Bitcoin Cash as it would put it ahead of networks like Bitcoin. 
 
What Cardano’s Potential Partnership With Bitcoin Cash Is About
 
Hoskinson conducted a “hypothetical poll” on his X (formerly Twitter) platform, asking his followers if they would like to see Bitcoin Cash become a Cardano “partnerchain.” He noted that this partnership would upgrade Bitcoin Cash with “Useful Proof of Work Leios, NiPoPoWs, and Ergo tech.”
 
 
Hoskinson further claimed that the partnership would make Bitcoin Cash the “fastest and most useful proof of work chain (PoW) ever built.” At the time of writing, over 13,000 people have voted on the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple's AI Ambitions Emerge Ahead of iPad Event]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229615</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229615/apple-ai-strategy-siri-xcode-music"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T00:46:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Between Tuesday's iPad event and WWDC, AI is expected to play a part in nearly every corner of the Apple ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Clearer Regulations? Australian Watchdog Wins First Crypto Non-Cash Payment Case]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7428ac399f</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/clearer-regulations-australian-watchdog-wins-first-crypto-non-cash-payment-case/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T23:40:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recent reports revealed that the Australian Securities and Investment Commission (ASIC) was granted its first victory on a non-cash payment case involving cryptocurrencies. Per the documents, an Australian court ruled partially in favor of the watchdog’s lawsuit against BPS Financial Pty Ltd (BPS).
 
 
“Qoin Scheme” Earns $26 Million In Sales
 
In 2022, ASIC initiated civil penalty procedures against BPS for alleged “misleading, false or deceptive” advertising and engaging in unlicensed operations with a non-cash payment facility involving a crypto asset token.
 
The Australian regulator claimed that the Qoin Facility was a “non-cash payment facility” established by the company in 2020. The “Qoin scheme” included the Qoin tokens, the Qoin Wallet, and a distributed digital ledger implemente…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rubmar Garcia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analysts Stand Firm on $150K Bitcoin Price Forecast Citing ‘a Healthy Cycle’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7428ae6d6d</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/analysts-stand-firm-on-150k-bitcoin-price-forecast-citing-a-healthy-cycle/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T23:19:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Global asset management firm Alliance Bernstein’s analysts have reaffirmed their bullish outlook on bitcoin, predicting a rise to $150,000 by 2025. They view the recent price correction as a healthy cleanup of market excesses. Additionally, they highlighted the market’s strength, citing significant inflows into spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) and encouraging signs for increased corporate […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Ethereum Game ‘Fantasy Top’ Is Taking Over Crypto Twitter]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229595</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229595/why-ethereum-game-fantasy-top-taking-over-crypto-twitter"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T23:06:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fantasy Top is like fantasy football, but with crypto influencers. The Blast game is the hot new thing amid a cooling crypto market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Wallet Maker Exodus Jumping Up to New York Stock Exchange]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229589</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229589/bitcoin-wallet-exodus-nyse-exod-listing"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T22:36:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Exodus says it is the only U.S. company that will have its EXOD common stock tokenized on the blockchain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk’s Tesla Adds Dogecoin Payments On Its Website, Is X Next?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742896afe1</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/tesla-dogecoin-payments-x/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T22:03:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla, an American multinational automotive and clean energy company led by billionaire entrepreneur, Elon Musk, has announced that it will now accept Dogecoin (DOGE) as a form of payment on certain products in the Tesla shop. 
 
This move comes as an exciting development for Tesla and the broader crypto community as it marks another pivotal instance where major corporations embrace meme-based cryptocurrencies. Additionally, it also raises speculations about whether Musk’s other ventures, particularly X Payments, could follow suit and adopt Dogecoin. 
 
Tesla Integrates Dogecoin As A Payment Method
 
Tesla has integrated Dogecoin into its payments system, allowing users to purchase merchandise when they opt for Dogecoin-eligible products. The automotive company made the announcement on its…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale's Ethereum Fund Discount Steadies as ETF Deadline Looms]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229584</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229584/grayscale-ethereum-ethe-fund-discount"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T21:50:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale hopes to convert its Ethereum Trust to a spot ETH ETF, and current investors see opportunity in the uncertainty.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Is Down, But These Analysts Still Think BTC Hits $150K This Year]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229582</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229582/bitcoin-150000-price-doubling-18-months-bernstein"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T21:32:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AllianceBernstein join Standard Chartered analysts in seeing the price of BTC more than doubling in the next 18 months.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Warren Buffett Sees No Alternative to US Dollar as Reserve Currency — Berkshire Holding $188 Billion in Cash]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742892f732</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/warren-buffett-sees-no-alternative-to-us-dollar-as-reserve-currency-berkshire-holding-188-billion-in-cash/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T21:26:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Warren Buffett, chairman and CEO of Berkshire Hathaway, asserts that there is currently no viable alternative to the U.S. dollar as the world’s reserve currency, suggesting that U.S. debt will remain acceptable “for a very long time.” Berkshire currently sits on a cash pile of $188 billion, which Buffett views as “quite attractive.” Insights From […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Slips to $63K as Crypto Market Faces More U.S. Regulatory Pressure]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742893ffce</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/05/06/bitcoin-slips-to-63k-as-crypto-market-faces-more-us-regulatory-pressure/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T21:18:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite the recent bounce, the correction isn't over, said one technical analyst, expecting bitcoin to fall to the low-mid $50,000 area before rallying to new all-time highs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visa Claims Most Stablecoin Data Is ‘Noise’—Here’s What Their Data Shows]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74289dfc44</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/visa-claims-most-crypto-stablecoin-data-is-noise/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T21:01:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So far, the role of stablecoins in global transactions has become a focal point of discussions just as the crypto markets continue to go mainstream. However, with mounting concerns over the reliability of available data, Visa, a long-standing leader in financial services, has stepped forward to clarify the landscape.
 
Under the guidance of Cuy Sheffield, Visa’s Head of Crypto, the company recently launched an Onchain Analytics Dashboard aimed at cutting through the “noise” and providing a more accurate reflection of stablecoin activities, as highlighted by the report.
 
 
Decoding The Noise In Crypto Stablecoin Transactions
 
The introduction of this dashboard is Visa’s response to the prevalent issue of “misleading data” surrounding stablecoin usage. Despite their growing popularity, dis…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DIY Multisig vs. Collaborative Custody Multisig]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74289eb5f9</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/technical/diy-multisig-vs-collaborative-custody-multisig"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T20:56:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Originally published on Unchained.com.
Unchained is the official US Collaborative Custody partner of Bitcoin Magazine and an integral sponsor of related content published through Bitcoin Magazine. For more information on services offered, custody products, and the relationship between Unchained and Bitcoin Magazine, please visit our website. 
 
                         
                         
                        Visit unchained.bitcoinmagazine.com for resources and special offers to upgrade your bitcoin security. 
                     
                    
Once someone decides that they want to hold bitcoin in self-custody, they will soon discover that hardware wallets are the most secure tools for managing bitcoin keys. The next question becomes whether to use a singlesig wallet or…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Unchained</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two Big Bitcoin Catalysts Could Drive MicroStrategy Stock Gains, TD Cowen Says]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74289877fa</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/05/06/two-big-bitcoin-catalysts-could-drive-microstrategy-stock-gains-td-cowen-says/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T20:41:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin has significant upside potential this month thanks to two big catalysts and Michael Saylor's MicroStrategy (MSTR) stock could surge, too, on its way toward getting "meaningfully higher" by the end of the year, TD Cowen analyst Lance Vitanza said in a note Monday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC Can’t Stop Suing Crypto Companies]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742884db1a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2024/05/06/the-sec-cant-stop-suing-crypto-companies/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T20:05:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood apparently made strenuous efforts to comply with the agency, even applying to become a special purpose crypto broker-dealer. The SEC is likely to sue for alleged securities violations in any case.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Kuhn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Litecoin Whales Buy Big Despite Bearish Price: Rebound Incoming?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74288521f3</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/litecoin-whales-buy-bearish-price-rebound-incoming/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T20:03:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data suggests Litecoin whales have participated in buying recently despite the fact that the asset’s price has been finding struggle.
 
Litecoin Whales Accumulated 100,000 LTC Recently
 
As pointed out by an X user using data from the on-chain analytics firm Santiment, the LTC whales have recently bought while the cryptocurrency’s price has declined.
 
The indicator of relevance here is the “Supply Distribution,” which tells us about the total amount of Litecoin that the different wallet groups in the market are holding right now.
 
 
Addresses or investors are divided into these cohorts based on the number of coins they are carrying in their balance currently. The 1-10 coins group, for instance, includes holders owning at least 1 and at most 10 LTC.
 
In the context of the curren…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Long-Term Bitcoin Investors Have Returned To HODLing: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229577</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229577/bitcoin-long-term-btc-holders-grow"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T20:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin whales eagerly bought the latest dip, and long-term investors are now patiently awaiting the next leg up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoins Under Scrutiny: Study Reveals 90% Non-User Transactions]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742880f7b0</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/stablecoins-under-scrutiny-study-reveals-90-non-user-transactions/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T19:31:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over 90% of stablecoin transactions do not originate  
from real users, a recent study by Visa and Allium Labs revealed. These  
findings raise questions about the potential of stablecoins revolutionizing the  
payment sector despite the optimism from industry leaders and the overall positive market  
sentiment. 
 Stablecoin Potential in Payments
Out of a staggering $2.65 trillion in total stablecoin transactions in the past 30 days, a mere $265 billion is attributed to "organic  
payments activity," highlighting the prevalence of non-user transactions.  
This data was highlighted in a dashboard aimed at analyzing stablecoin  
transactions to differentiate between authentic user activity and artificial  
volume.
This revelation challenges the narrative that  
stablecoins, tethered to asset…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETFs Are Back? $378 Million In Gains Marks Best Day In Over a Month]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229553</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229553/bitcoin-spot-etf-inflows-across-the-board-gbtc-turns-green"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T19:30:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every fund flipped green on Friday, as more traditional investors hold on to their BTC-based shares.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Developers Target Ease of Crypto Wallets With 'EIP-3074']]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7428814024</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2024/05/06/ethereum-developers-target-ease-of-crypto-wallets-with-eip-3074/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T19:29:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EIP-3074 has drawn both support and concern from the Ethereum community, a code change that is supposed to improve the user experience with wallets on the blockchain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Margaux Nijkerk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana's Dogwifhat Pumps as Bonk, Dogecoin and Other Meme Coins Lose Ground]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229555</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229555/meme-coin-wif-bonk-doge-pepe"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T19:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WIF is the only meme coin in the top 100 posting gains amid a broader crypto dip. Other popular meme coins are struggling to maintain momentum.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mixers Pull Out of the US Amid Regulatory Heat]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229543</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229543/bitcoin-coin-mixers-shut-americans-out"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T18:48:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Privacy preserving crypto services are shutting down or shutting out American users as U.S. agencies turn up the pressure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Whale Moves $44 Million After a Decade—Here's How Much It Gained]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229534</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229534/bitcoin-whale-moves-44-million-after-decade-how-much-gained"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T17:09:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An unidentified Bitcoin whale just moved 687 BTC after it sat for more than a decade. Here's how much the value increased during that span.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Price Jumps Nearly 5% as Bitcoin, Ethereum Lag Behind]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229533</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229533/solana-price-jumps-bitcoin-ethereum-lag-behind"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T16:13:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana is the biggest gainer in the top 10 cryptocurrencies on an otherwise quiet Monday morning, as Bitcoin and Ethereum tick down.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[90% of Ethereum, Tron, Solana Stablecoin Transactions Are ‘Inorgranic Activity’, Visa Says]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229515</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229515/stablecoin-transactions-inorganic-bots-ethereum-tron-solana"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T16:02:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smart contracts, not humans, are driving nearly all stablecoin arbitrage, liquidity provision, and market making.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood Crypto Says SEC Has 'Weak' Case in Response to Wells Notice]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229516</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229516/robinhood-crypto-sec-wells-notice"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T13:31:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company said it's looking forward to showing "just how weak any case against Robinhood Crypto would be on both the facts and the law."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott,André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Sees Modest Gains as Network Processes Its 1 Billionth Transaction]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229504</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229504/bitcoin-sees-modest-gains-as-network-processes-its-1-billionth-transaction"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T12:05:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The world's oldest and largest cryptocurrency just celebrated a birthday of sorts: Its network has processed more than 1 billion transactions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Ordinals Size Record Broken Again—How Much Bigger Can They Get?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229421</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229421/bitcoin-block-size-record-broken-again-how-much-bigger"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T18:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The largest-ever Bitcoin file was just inscribed, as an Ordinals asset broke the two-month-old size record. Can it be broken again?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Crypto Games: Supercell's Investment, Saga Airdrop, 'Parallel' Adds Expansion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229459</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229459/this-week-crypto-games-supercell-investment-saga-airdrop-parallel-expansion"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T16:53:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Catch up on this week’s biggest crypto and NFT gaming news and find some weekend reads in our latest roundup.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week on Crypto Twitter: Ethereum, CZ, and Roger Ver in US Government Crosshairs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229391</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229391/this-week-on-crypto-twitter-ethereum-cz-roger-ver-government-wrath"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T16:19:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CZ got sentenced, Ver got arrested, and Ethereum has been secretly considered a regulated security since April 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biggest Video Games Releasing in May 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229400</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229400/biggest-video-games-releasing-may-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-05-04T15:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's a busy month of sequels as Senua's Saga: Hellblade II, Homeworld 3, and World of Goo 2 lead May 2024's video game releases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Frederiksen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moonbirds Copyright Controversy Exposes Flaws in Crypto's IP Obsession]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229373</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229373/moonbirds-copyright-controversy-exposes-flaws-in-cryptos-ip-obsession"/>
        <updated>2024-05-04T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most NFT brands think ‘IP’ is the future. But as a Moonbirds announcement revealed this week, does anyone actually understand what that means?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Bitcoin Battered But Rebounds As Meme Coin Mania Abides]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229314</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229314/this-week-in-coins-bitcoin-battered-but-rebounds-as-meme-coin-mania-abides"/>
        <updated>2024-05-04T10:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From Bitcoin's mid-week plunge to the prurient LIVEMOM pump, it was a wild seven days in crypto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI Could Challenge Google and Perplexity With AI-Powered Search: Reports]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229381</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229381/search-chatgpt-openai-web-google-perplexity"/>
        <updated>2024-05-04T00:29:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The leader in AI could dethrone the leader in search, with web sleuths uncovering signs of a search tool linked to ChatGPT.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale Bitcoin ETF Snaps Losing Streak, Pulls In $63 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229415</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229415/grayscale-bitcoin-etf-snaps-losing-streak-pulls-in-63-million"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T22:32:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After 80 days of outflows, the battered long-standing Bitcoin fund grew by $63 million.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Kawailani Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Most Dogecoin Holders Didn't Buy the Elon Musk Top]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229375</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229375/most-dogecoin-holders-didnt-buy-elon-musk-top"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T20:49:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A strong majority of Dogecoin holders are currently in the green, even at prices well below Elon Musk-led highs in 2021.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Game ‘Nyan Heroes’ Returning With Expanded Play-to-Airdrop Rewards]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229370</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229370/solana-game-nyan-heroes-returning-expanded-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T19:54:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cats-in-mechs shooter Nyan Heroes will bring its servers back online next week as the second play-to-airdrop season kicks off.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy Orange: Everything You Need to Know About Decentralized ID on Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229320</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229320/what-is-microstrategy-orange-decentralized-identity-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T18:47:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The largest institutional holder of Bitcoin is getting into decentralized identity. But how does MicroStrategy Orange work?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[As Bitcoin Pumps, These Altcoins Are Doing Even Better]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229325</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229325/bitcoin-altcoin-ordi-ton-bonk"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T18:21:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While Bitcoin is up 4.62% in the last 24 hours, ORDI, TON, and BONK are outperforming the market leader with impressive gains. Here's a closer look at their recent performance and potential price movements.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Time to Buy? MicroStrategy Stock Premium Shrinks After Bitcoin Pullback]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229323</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229323/microstrategy-mstr-btc-premium-shrinks"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T18:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MSTR still trades much higher than the value of the Bitcoin behind it, but one analyst believes fundamentals aren’t important for investors right now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saga Reveals First ‘Power-Level Over 9,000’ Airdrop With $10 Million in Tokens]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229319</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229319/saga-power-level-over-9000-airdrop-10-million-tokens"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T17:50:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gaming-heavy layer-1 network Saga is serving up more SAGA rewards as it prepares to tee up airdrops from 100+ partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jack Dorsey's Block Will Reinvest 10% of Bitcoin Profits Into BTC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229317</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229317/jack-dorsey-block-reinvest-10-percent-bitcoin-profits-btc"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T17:35:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After selling $2.7 billion worth of Bitcoin in Q1 2024, Jack Dorsey's Block unveiled a plan to reinvest Bitcoin-related profits into the coin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Rebound Smashes $100 Million in Crypto Shorts]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229313</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229313/bitcoin-price-rebound-smashes-100-million-crypto-shorts"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T16:44:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin is back up again—and as a result, traders betting on a dip in the asset's price have had their positions liquidated.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Leaps Over $61K Following US Unemployment Data]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229310</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229310/bitcoin-price-leaps-over-61k-following-us-unemployment-data"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T14:30:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a government employment report was published, showing unemployment is higher than expected, Bitcoin leaped over $61k.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Billionaire Arthur Hayes Predicts Market Bottom Is In, 'Slow Grind Higher']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229288</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229288/bitcoin-billionaire-arthur-hayes-predicts-market-bottom-is-in-slow-grind-higher"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T13:33:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin has hit its bottom, BTC billionaire Arthur Hayes argued. And now, he predicts markets will see "a slow grind higher."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Week in Polkadot: JAM Pushes Toward ‘Original Concept’ of World Computer: Gavin Wood]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229293</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229293/the-week-in-polkadot-jam-pushes-toward-original-concept-of-world-computer-gavin-wood"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T13:09:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Polkadot founder Gavin Wood sat down for an hour-long podcast to answer questions about the network’s JAM upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will McCurdy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Asked AI to Predict Kentucky Derby Winners—Here Are Its Picks]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229239</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229239/ai-picks-kentucky-derby-horse-race-winners-horsegpt"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We built an AI agent and fed it bales of race horse statistics. Our HorseGPT slate matched human expert predictions well.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friend.tech Community in Uproar Amid Token and V2 Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229273</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229273/friend-tech-community-in-uproar-amid-token-and-v2-launch"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T11:43:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Community members are upset after web3 social media platform, Friend.tech, fumbles its token and V2 launch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Do A Little With Mike Demarais]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ajrh0oiK/we-do-a-little-with-mike-demarais</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ajrh0oiK/we-do-a-little-with-mike-demarais"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T15:11:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mike dropped knowledge bombs from years of building in the trenches alongside some deep cuts on the early Williamsburg crypto mafia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eth Rally Fails]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Gj7TMrbP/eth-rally-fails</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Gj7TMrbP/eth-rally-fails"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T12:45:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto falls, ETH/BTC rally again marks mini sell-off. Yen carry-trade implosion linked to worries. ETH gas fees hit 6-month lows. 3rd straight week of institutional outflows. Slowing BTC ETF flows are just a pause: Bernstein. BTC now on track for 5 red weeks in a row. BTC may have topped, could hit $35k: Brandt. ETFs may become big sellers: Bianco. Consensys list 4 reasons ETH isn’t a security. Rumours continue to grow of EigenLayer airdrop. Perp DEX volumes continue fall, GMX underperforms. Wallets begin to block US users after Samourai case. WLD in reported partnership talks with OpenAI. Large unlocks this week for SUI, PYTH & MEME.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Sasha Stiles’ Experiential, AI-Infused NFT Drop with Bang & Olufsen]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/6Vi2IgYj/inside-sasha-stiles-experiential-ai-infused-nft-drop-with-bang-olufsen</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/6Vi2IgYj/inside-sasha-stiles-experiential-ai-infused-nft-drop-with-bang-olufsen"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T22:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At a launch party for the collection in New York’s SoHo neighborhood, the artist broke down her latest art experiment, “Four Core Texts,” with Decrypt’s Sander Lutz.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interview: How 'Notcoin' Will Evolve After the NOT Token Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PprnGP14/interview-how-notcoin-will-evolve-after-the-not-token-launch</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PprnGP14/interview-how-notcoin-will-evolve-after-the-not-token-launch"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Open Builders founder Sasha Plotvinov speaks with Decrypt's Sander Lutz at Token 2049 Dubai about how he envisions Notcoin's expansion and evolution after the token drop—into something akin to the "Netflix of social, viral games."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Magic Runes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IGWg0R64/magic-runes</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IGWg0R64/magic-runes"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T13:59:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC stables at $66k, liquidations in narrow range. BTC funding again turns negative in bullish sign. ETFs net inflow after Grayscale moves to lower fees. BTC demand 5x vs supply post-halving: Bitfinex. SOL congestion issue now largely solved. Two SEC lawyers resign after ‘gross abuse of power’. Ripple fights to lower $2bn SEC fine. SAFE trades at $2.8bn FDV after OKX lists. MANEKI hits $150m on first day, China memes pump. Memecoins are ‘black hole you can’t ignore’. DeGods up 20%, may switch back to SOL. Magic Eden launches Runes platform ahead of time.  Louis Vuitton gifts Pharrell jacket to NFT holders. Melania Trump launches necklace with SOL NFTs. Hoodie Punk trades for $620K.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Luxury Watches, Designer Shoes Will Soon Trade Like NFTs: Arianee CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/CSNQG2md/luxury-watches-designer-shoes-will-soon-trade-like-nfts-arianee-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/CSNQG2md/luxury-watches-designer-shoes-will-soon-trade-like-nfts-arianee-ceo"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arianee CEO Pierre-Nicolas Hurstel sat down with Rug Radio founder Farokh and Decrypt’s Sander Lutz at NFT Paris to discuss everything from the future of on-chain luxury to the secret hack to finding the best restaurants in France.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notcoin's Co-Creator Explains the Game's Token Delay—And When to Expect NOT Now]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/7Zx33xo5/notcoins-co-creator-explains-the-games-token-delayand-when-to-expect-not-now</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/7Zx33xo5/notcoins-co-creator-explains-the-games-token-delayand-when-to-expect-not-now"/>
        <updated>2024-04-22T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Notcoin co-creator Sasha Plotvinov spoke with Decrypt's Sander Lutz at Token 2049 Dubai to discuss why the NOT token launch was pushed back from the original 4/20 target, when to expect the listing, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TON’s Justin Hyun Breaks Down The Importance of USDT Coming to Telegram]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ODQI6ACA/tons-justin-hyun-breaks-down-the-importance-of-usdt-coming-to-telegram</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ODQI6ACA/tons-justin-hyun-breaks-down-the-importance-of-usdt-coming-to-telegram"/>
        <updated>2024-04-19T10:14:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Token 2049 in Dubai, The Open Network’s director of investments sat down with Decrypt’s Sander Lutz to discuss what he sees as the game-changing integration of USDT onto TON, and his plans for getting Telegram’s 900 million users to start using crypto in the immediate future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Influencer Ansem Explains His Meme Coin Thesis and Why He’s Bullish on Bitcoin Runes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/u9DHFoK0/crypto-influencer-ansem-explains-his-meme-coin-thesis-and-why-hes-bullish-on-bitcoin-runes</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/u9DHFoK0/crypto-influencer-ansem-explains-his-meme-coin-thesis-and-why-hes-bullish-on-bitcoin-runes"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T21:56:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ansem, the crypto trader who's amassed a sizable following on the back of meme coin Dogwifhat (WIF) and other calls, chats with Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz at Token 2049 Dubai about his meme coin thesis, why he's bullish on Bitcoin Runes, and what he sees ahead for the crypto markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Sander Lutz Braves the Dubai Floods for a Crypto Conference]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/mtjVHGa3/decrypts-sander-lutz-braves-the-dubai-floods-for-a-crypto-conference</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/mtjVHGa3/decrypts-sander-lutz-braves-the-dubai-floods-for-a-crypto-conference"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T21:33:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz reports from Dubai amid a historic storm that flooded the famed city, trudging through the streets to complete his essential task: Attending the Token 2049 crypto conference.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gold Beats Its All Time High]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/6ULgUKVk/gold-beats-its-all-time-high</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/6ULgUKVk/gold-beats-its-all-time-high"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T09:53:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) maintains its trend of reaching higher lows amidst choppy market conditions. Exchange-traded funds (ETFs) witness another influx of $125 million. There's anticipation of Hong Kong approving ETFs for both Bitcoin and Ethereum (ETH) come Monday. Notable institutional investor BlackRock shows interest in Bitcoin. Recent filings reveal increased Bitcoin purchases by banks. A Bitcoin-friendly political party secures victory in the South Korean election. Analyst Kang predicts Bitcoin could surge to $80-100k by May. Meanwhile, Ethereum sees accumulation by stablecoin whales on the rise. A new Ethereum Improvement Proposal (EIP) aims to streamline signing requests. Solana (SOL) experiences a resurgence in activity, reaching yearly highs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NASA’s Next Deep Space Mission Won’t Use Artificial Intelligence]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/0WGP33Rp/nasas-next-deep-space-mission-wont-use-artificial-intelligence</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/0WGP33Rp/nasas-next-deep-space-mission-wont-use-artificial-intelligence"/>
        <updated>2024-04-13T18:42:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Thursday, Decrypt Media visited NASA's Jet Propulsion Laboratory in Pasadena, CA to meet with the Engineering team behind the Europa Clipper before its launch to Jupiter's Europa moon in October.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Do A Little with Weesh]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LnaOT9bF/we-do-a-little-with-weesh</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LnaOT9bF/we-do-a-little-with-weesh"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T07:46:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week’s episode, we did a little something different. We took the man who is usually behind the camera and put him in front of it. We sat down with our producer Weesh to dive into how in fell in love with art and became a collector, how he met Andy and fun childhood memories together, his biggest wins in crypto, and so much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside VanEck’s Crypto Takeover of the New York Stock Exchange]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9YAY4wGD/inside-vanecks-crypto-takeover-of-the-new-york-stock-exchange</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9YAY4wGD/inside-vanecks-crypto-takeover-of-the-new-york-stock-exchange"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T14:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worlds collide as Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz heads to the floor of the NYSE to witness a special closing bell ceremony hosted by VanEck in honor of Web3. Featuring Choose Rich Nick, VanEck Head of Web3 Matt Bartlett, and more!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wormhole Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9SNiIVfU/wormhole-wednesday</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9SNiIVfU/wormhole-wednesday"/>
        <updated>2024-04-07T17:42:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC hits $64.5K then rebounds, SOL outperforms. Government sends $2B BTC to Coinbase to sell. Funding rates stay low after sweep lower. ETFs see small inflow, Ark outflow more than GBTC. Wormhole W launches at $15B FDV. BTC ‘inflection point’ if it follows rates or gold. Gold & BTC very correlated for the last year. Expect slower ETF volume this month: Bloomberg. BTC 2x and 3x levered ETFs launch yesterday. BTC ETFs now half the size of gold.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>