<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-06-13T07:13:57.785Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-06-13T07:13:57.785Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘100xs’ Possible for Crypto Now That Doubt Plagues Markets: Investor Who Called Market Bottom]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18562215/100xs-Possible-for-Crypto-Now-That-Doubt-Plagues-Markets-Investor-Who-Called-Market-Bottom</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18562215/100xs-Possible-for-Crypto-Now-That-Doubt-Plagues-Markets-Investor-Who-Called-Market-Bottom"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T07:04:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A venture capitalist who correctly called the 2022 crypto bottom isn’t fazed by the ongoing turmoil in the digital asset markets. Chris Burniske, a partner at the venture capital firm Placeholder, tells his 261,000 Twitter followers that crypto is at a stage where people are doubting its future...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GCEX and Hex Trust Bolster Partnership to Broaden Staking Services]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7578f5902f</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/gcex-and-hex-trust-bolster-partnership-to-broaden-staking-services/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T07:02:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GCEX, a  
digital prime brokerage, has expanded its partnership with Hex Trust, an  
institutional custodian for cryptocurrencies. The announcement follows the companies'  
initial venture into staking services in April 2023.
Now, their  
relationship  includes an expansion in staking services, offering a broader  
portfolio of assets to brokers, hedge funds, professional traders and fund  
managers.
Hex Trust and GCEX Expand  
Partnership
According  
to the press release, GCEX will introduce nine additional assets for staking to  
its institutional and professional clients. The new offering includes Apecoin,  
Flare and Ethereum. Moreover, GC Exchange A/S has hinted at augmenting  
the list in response to growing client demands.
"Our  
bond with Hex Trust, our custody partner for more tha…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Damian Chmiel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tokenized US Treasury bills are entering emerging markets]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18562017/Tokenized-US-Treasury-bills-are-entering-emerging-markets</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18562017/Tokenized-US-Treasury-bills-are-entering-emerging-markets"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Users can withdrawal deposits after waiting for five days]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon unveils plan to build network of ZK-based Layer 2 chains]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18562029/Polygon-unveils-plan-to-build-network-of-ZK-based-Layer-2-chains</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18562029/Polygon-unveils-plan-to-build-network-of-ZK-based-Layer-2-chains"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T06:54:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon 2.0 will provide a multi-chain network of ZK-powered Layer 2 chains that can securely interact with each other.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Next 24 Hours Will Be Critical For Crypto – Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7578f716f8</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/next-24-hours-will-be-critical-for-crypto/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T06:50:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The next 24 hours are extremely critical for the entire crypto industry for several reasons. Besides the macroeconomic events this week, they also have the potential to massively influence prices on the crypto market.
 
Today, Tuesday, June 13th, the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) will take the center stage no less than four times. But perhaps the event with the greatest potential impact is the alleged unsealing of the SEC’s internal Hinman documents in the Ripple case.
 
The Hinman documents could shed light on Ethereum’s (ETH) previous classification as a non-security, which is now being challenged by SEC Chairman Gary Gensler. Right at the beginning of the legal dispute with Ripple, the SEC had already requested the Hinman documents to be declared invalid.
 
In June 2018, t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong: The SEC Told Us ‘Everything Other Than Bitcoin Is a Security’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7578f06ec7</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/coinbase-ceo-brian-armstrong-the-sec-told-us-everything-other-than-bitcoin-is-a-security/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T06:38:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brian Armstrong, CEO of Coinbase, the largest U.S.-based cryptocurrency exchange, explained how negotiations reached a standstill with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). In a recent interview with the Wall Street Journal, Armstrong detailed the changes in how the SEC approached securities regulation and how the exchange has tried to work with regulators since day one.
Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong on SEC Enforcement Actions: ‘Something Shifted About a Year Ago’
Brian Armstrong, the CEO of Coinbase, one of the largest U.S.-based cryptocurrency exchanges, explained the company’s journey before reaching a standstill in negotiations with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).
In a recent interview with the Wall Street Journal (WSJ), Armstrong detailed the changes in …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sygnum Inches Closure to Get Singapore's Payment Institution License]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7578f10bbf</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/sygnum-inches-closure-to-get-singapores-payment-institution-license/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T06:33:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Singapore subsidiary of Sygnum, a digital asset bank, has become the latest to obtain in-principal approval for a Major Payment Institution Licence (MPIL) from the Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS).  

Sygnum Gains In-Principal Singapore License  

The in-principal license was awarded to Sygnum Singapore, thus putting it closer to becoming a regulated crypto brokerage service. Once the full license is obtained, the company can offer a range of crypto services, including digital payment token services, along with cross-border and domestic money transfer services.  

"This in-principle approval of our Major Payment Institution Licence by the MAS is a milestone in our strategic growth plans for Sygnum Singapore and South-East Asia," said Gerald Goh, Sygnum Co-Founder and CEO Singapore…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arnab Shome</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP (XRP/USD) Price Analysis for 13 June 2023: A ‘STRONG BUY’ Suggested by Technical Indicators and Moving Averages]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18561665/XRP-XRPUSD-Price-Analysis-for-13-June-2023-A-STRONG-BUY-Suggested-by-Technical-Indicators-and-Moving-Averages</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18561665/XRP-XRPUSD-Price-Analysis-for-13-June-2023-A-STRONG-BUY-Suggested-by-Technical-Indicators-and-Moving-Averages"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T06:27:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction This report provides a comprehensive analysis of XRP’s price dynamics on Binance, covering technical indicators, moving averages, and pivot points. While the analysis provides valuable insights into the potential price trends, it is crucial for traders and investors to conduct...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried's Bahamas Litigation May Take ‘Months or Years,’ His Counsel Says]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18561428/Sam-Bankman-Frieds-Bahamas-Litigation-May-Take-Months-or-Years-His-Counsel-Says</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18561428/Sam-Bankman-Frieds-Bahamas-Litigation-May-Take-Months-or-Years-His-Counsel-Says"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T06:23:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The FTX founder’s lawyers argue that a new Supreme Court judgment shows that he has not committed fraud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Police Warn of a Rise in Digital Yuan-themed Scams]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18561100/Chinese-Police-Warn-of-a-Rise-in-Digital-Yuan-themed-Scams</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18561100/Chinese-Police-Warn-of-a-Rise-in-Digital-Yuan-themed-Scams"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese police have warned there has been an increase in digital yuan-themed scams, as the nation’s CBDC rollout gathers pace. Per the state-run news outlet CCTV (via Xinhua), officers in Shandong Province claimed they had seen a rise in digital yuan-themed “fraud.” They said one recent scam had...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple CEO Hints at Crucial Information in Pending Hinman Documents]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18561240/Ripple-CEO-Hints-at-Crucial-Information-in-Pending-Hinman-Documents</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18561240/Ripple-CEO-Hints-at-Crucial-Information-in-Pending-Hinman-Documents"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T05:59:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse suggests crucial insights lie within the pending "Hinman documents" release]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Next 24 Hours Will Be Critical For Crypto – Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18560920/Next-24-Hours-Will-Be-Critical-For-Crypto-Heres-Why</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18560920/Next-24-Hours-Will-Be-Critical-For-Crypto-Heres-Why"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T05:55:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The next 24 hours are extremely critical for the entire crypto industry for several reasons. Besides the macroeconomic events this week, they also have the potential to massively influence prices on the crypto market. Today, Tuesday, June 13th, the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC)...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[eToro US Disallows New Positions in $MATIC, $ALGO, and $MANA Amid SEC’s War on Exchanges]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18560943/eToro-US-Disallows-New-Positions-in-MATIC-ALGO-and-MANA-Amid-SECs-War-on-Exchanges</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18560943/eToro-US-Disallows-New-Positions-in-MATIC-ALGO-and-MANA-Amid-SECs-War-on-Exchanges"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T05:50:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On June 12, 2023, eToro US announced significant changes to its cryptocurrency offering for US customers in response to the rapidly evolving regulatory landscape. eToro, a social trading and multi-asset brokerage company, is renowned for its platform that enables users to observe, copy, and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance criminal indictment may already be filed under seal, former SEC chief says]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18560390/Binance-criminal-indictment-may-already-be-filed-under-seal-former-SEC-chief-says</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18560390/Binance-criminal-indictment-may-already-be-filed-under-seal-former-SEC-chief-says"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T05:20:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Reed Stark argues that the U.S. DOJ will file — or has already filed under seal — a Binance-related criminal indictment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘All of the SEC’s claims fail’ — Binance.US rebuts motion to freeze funds]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18560357/All-of-the-SECs-claims-fail-BinanceUS-rebuts-motion-to-freeze-funds</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18560357/All-of-the-SECs-claims-fail-BinanceUS-rebuts-motion-to-freeze-funds"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T05:15:22.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC’s Gensler says BTC, ETH ‘not securities’ in a newly surfaced video]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18560337/SECs-Gensler-says-BTC-ETH-not-securities-in-a-newly-surfaced-video</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18560337/SECs-Gensler-says-BTC-ETH-not-securities-in-a-newly-surfaced-video"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T04:57:27.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Etoro to Delist ALGO, MANA, DASH, and MATIC for US Customers Amid ‘Evolving Regulatory Landscape’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7578e58b01</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/etoro-to-delist-algo-mana-dash-and-matic-for-us-customers-amid-evolving-regulatory-landscape/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T04:37:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The social trading and investment company Etoro declared on Monday that starting July 12, 2023, U.S. customers would be unable to initiate new trades for ALGO, MANA, DASH, and MATIC. The company cited the “rapidly evolving regulatory landscape” as the reason behind the delistings.
 
Etoro Reveals Plans to Delist 4 Crypto Assets
 

 
Based in Tel Aviv, Israel, Etoro’s trading and investing platform specified that as of July 12, 2023, American customers will be barred from trading four distinct cryptocurrencies. The organization claimed that it has devised a system for its team to assess crypto assets in response to the ever-shifting regulatory climate.
 

 
“Due to recent developments, we will be making some changes to our crypto offering for U.S. customers,” Etoro said on Monday. “From 6:0…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jump Trading seeks to move Terra class action suit to California]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18560310/Jump-Trading-seeks-to-move-Terra-class-action-suit-to-California</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18560310/Jump-Trading-seeks-to-move-Terra-class-action-suit-to-California"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T04:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Atomic Wallet hackers turn to OFAC-sanctioned Garantex: Elliptic]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18560286/Atomic-Wallet-hackers-turn-to-OFAC-sanctioned-Garantex-Elliptic</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18560286/Atomic-Wallet-hackers-turn-to-OFAC-sanctioned-Garantex-Elliptic"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T04:01:12.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Volatility Incoming: Breaking Down This Week’s Major Macro Events]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7578e213e0</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-volatility-breaking-macro-events-cpi-ppi-fed/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T03:50:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week in the crypto market is shaping up to be one of the most significant in terms of macroeconomic events. These unfolding developments will not only have a ripple effect on cryptocurrencies, but also on stocks, the dollar, and every other asset class. Let’s break down these crucial events and why they matter to crypto enthusiasts and investors.
 
The Macro Economic Calendar And Its Impact On Crypto
 
All week long, the crypto market will be exposed to the impact of a series of macro events, ranging from inflation metrics to a Fed rate decision, to the unsealing of the “Hinman documents” which have the potential to change the outcome of the Ripple v. SEC case.
 
The rollercoaster week ahead on the regulatory front kicks off with the release of the Hinman documents, which could potent…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tony &amp;quot;The Bull&amp;quot;</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Volatility Incoming: Breaking Down This Week’s Major Macro Events]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18560269/Crypto-Volatility-Incoming-Breaking-Down-This-Weeks-Major-Macro-Events</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18560269/Crypto-Volatility-Incoming-Breaking-Down-This-Weeks-Major-Macro-Events"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T03:45:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week in the crypto market is shaping up to be one of the most significant in terms of macroeconomic events. These unfolding developments will not only have a ripple effect on cryptocurrencies, but also on stocks, the dollar, and every other asset class. Let’s break down these crucial events...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance.US says SEC’s motion to freeze exchange’s assets may end its operations]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18560270/BinanceUS-says-SECs-motion-to-freeze-exchanges-assets-may-end-its-operations</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18560270/BinanceUS-says-SECs-motion-to-freeze-exchanges-assets-may-end-its-operations"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T03:45:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The operations of cryptocurrency trading platform Binance.US, “would quickly grind to a halt” if a court rules in favor of an SEC request last week to freeze the firm’s assets, the company said Monday in a court filing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$ADA: Cardano’s Hoskinson Sees SEC’s Lawsuit Against Binance as a Step Towards Control, US CBDC]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18560242/ADA-Cardanos-Hoskinson-Sees-SECs-Lawsuit-Against-Binance-as-a-Step-Towards-Control-US-CBDC</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18560242/ADA-Cardanos-Hoskinson-Sees-SECs-Lawsuit-Against-Binance-as-a-Step-Towards-Control-US-CBDC"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T03:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano ($ADA) creator Charles Hoskinson has, in the face of a sweeping legal action by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) against Binance, offered his interpretation of the situation, where he asserted the lawsuit is part of a larger effort to regulate the digital assets...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OUR ROOMMATES ARE NBA CHAMPS! 

Congrats, @nuggets!

#GoAvsGo #BringItIn]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18560766/OUR-ROOMMATES-ARE-NBA-CHAMPS-Congrats-nuggets-GoAvsGo-BringItIn</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18560766/OUR-ROOMMATES-ARE-NBA-CHAMPS-Congrats-nuggets-GoAvsGo-BringItIn"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T03:02:29.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC has spoken: The future of finance is not in America]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18560235/The-SEC-has-spoken-The-future-of-finance-is-not-in-America</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18560235/The-SEC-has-spoken-The-future-of-finance-is-not-in-America"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T03:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC’s one-two punch of Coinbase and Binance couldn’t have come at a better time for Hong Kong and Singapore, as US crypto firms look to shift to friendlier shores, writes Hamilton Keats of Krayon Digital.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Lawyers Push Back Against US SEC Claims That Binance.US Customer Assets Are at Risk]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18560234/Binance-Lawyers-Push-Back-Against-US-SEC-Claims-That-BinanceUS-Customer-Assets-Are-at-Risk</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18560234/Binance-Lawyers-Push-Back-Against-US-SEC-Claims-That-BinanceUS-Customer-Assets-Are-at-Risk"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T03:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Republican Congressman Seeks to Oust SEC Chair Gensler With SEC Stabilization Act]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7578e9291a</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/republican-congressman-seeks-to-oust-sec-chair-gensler-with-sec-stabilization-act/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T02:33:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Warren Davidson, the Republican congressman who first introduced the legislation in mid-April, has filed the SEC Stabilization Act to remove Gary Gensler, the current chair of the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). Davidson insists the act aims to safeguard U.S. capital markets “from a tyrannical chairman.”
 
Legislation Filed to Remove SEC Chair Gensler in Effort to Safeguard U.S. Capital Markets
 

 
Several Republican lawmakers have openly criticized SEC chairman Gary Gensler for his performance in leading the federal securities regulatory division. Among them is congressman Warren Davidson (R-OH), who recently announced his intention to introduce legislation to remove Gensler from his position. Less than two months later, Davidson filed the SEC Stabilization Act and shared …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Mover Asia: Binance's Exchange Flow Flips Positive; Bitcoin Trades Flat]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7578e9ff0c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/06/13/first-mover-asia-binances-exchange-flow-flips-positive-bitcoin-trades-flat/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T02:23:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ALSO: The co-founder of crypto security firm De.Fi called the price stabilization of crypto assets that plummeted after SEC lawsuits against Binance and Coinbase "mean regression."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds, James Rubin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Dithers Below $26K as Investors Eye CPI Data, FOMC Rate Hike Decision]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7578e9ff04</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/06/12/bitcoin-dithers-below-26k-as-investors-eye-cpi-data-fomc-rate-hike-decision/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T02:23:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The largest cryptocurrency held its perch where it spent much of the previous three days.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Rubin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Metaverse Beauty Week Aims to Showcase the Branding Potential of the Metaverse]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144327</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144327/metaverse-beauty-week-aims-showcase-branding-potential-metaverse"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T02:03:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Immersive games and events across Decentraland, Spatial, and Roblox this week will invite users to experience cosmetic brands in new ways.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Fights Back Against SEC Lawsuit Over Alleged Securities Violations]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144334</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144334/binance-fights-back-against-sec-lawsuit-over-securities-law"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T01:56:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cryptocurrency exchange filed more than 20 motions and declarations late Monday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Richi Sunak’s £100 Million Plan to Make the UK an AI Hub]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144318</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144318/richi-sunaks-100-million-plan-to-make-the-uk-an-ai-hub"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T01:35:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Prime Minister wants early access to OpenAI and Google’s new LLMs “for safety purposes.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Ordinals Hype Lures Meme Token Traders Into Wallet Drainer Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144320</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144320/bitcoin-ordinals-hype-lures-meme-token-traders-wallet-drainer-attack"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T01:18:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A convincing-looking BRC-20 token mint on Friday apparently swiped some $63,000 worth of Bitcoin from unsuspecting traders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[a16z Expands To London Citing Favorable Crypto Regulatory Environment]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7578d1d684</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/a16z-expands-to-london-citing-favorable-crypto-regulatory-environment/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T00:53:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Andreessen Horowitz, the name behind venture capitalist firm a16z, is going international with a new crypto office in London. The new move from the venture capital company adds to the number of crypto-related firms in the US looking for a favorable environment outside the country.
 
 
 
a16z Cites US Regulatory Unclarity As A Push For Its International Move
 
On June 11, Andreessen Horowitz (a16z) announced that its first international office would kick off in London later this year. 
 
The founder and managing partner of a16z crypto, Chris Dixion, explained the importance of regulatory clarity in building decentralized blockchain startups. He stated that the US crypto regulatory pressure is part of the reasons for a16z expansion into the UK. 
 
According to the executive, decentralization…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Dambel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFT Market Sees 20% Drop in Weekly Sales After a Few Weeks of Gains]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7578d80896</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/nft-market-sees-20-drop-in-weekly-sales-after-a-few-weeks-of-gains/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T23:42:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After several weeks of consecutive gains, sales of non-fungible tokens (NFTs) have slumped 20.44% this week compared to the previous week. According to seven-day statistics, NFT sales totaled $152.96 million last week, with $84 million in sales originating from the Ethereum blockchain.
 
This Week’s NFT Sales Follow Crypto Market’s Nosedive
 

 
Sales of non-fungible tokens (NFTs) have nosedived more than 20% over the past seven days compared to the previous week. The decline follows several consecutive weeks of gains, during which Bitcoin (BTC)-based NFTs gained significant prominence. In the last seven days, NFT sales totaled $152.96 million, and the number of NFT buyers decreased by 63.59%. Ethereum-based NFT sales accounted for $84 million, representing 54.91% of the market share among…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC’s DeFi Rulemaking Do-Over Falls Short]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7578d9b903</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/06/12/secs-defi-rulemaking-do-over-falls-short/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T23:23:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An attempt at classifying decentralized, open-source protocols as regulated exchanges is a "gussied up ban on blockchain in the U.S.," ConsenSys lawyer Bill Hughes writes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Hughes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another Solo Bitcoin Miner Hits the Jackpot for $160,000]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144309</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144309/another-solo-bitcoin-miner-hits-the-jackpot-for-160000"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T23:06:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Beating one-to-5,500 odds, the miner solved a block by renting six-year-old hardware.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto-Friendly Congressmen Draft Bill to Reform SEC, Fire Gary Gensler]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144280</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144280/congressmen-draft-bill-to-fire-gary-gensler"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T23:03:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The congressman aims to decentralize the structure of the SEC, and free the agency from its "tyrannical Chairman."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse Says Hinman Documents Are “Well Worth the Wait”]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7578c43c94</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ripple-ceo-brad-garlinghouse-hinman-documents/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T22:55:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a new tweet, Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse claims that the highly anticipated “Hinman documents” were “well worth the wait,” hinting at their potential significance in the ongoing legal battle between Ripple and the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).
 
With the documents expected to be unsealed this week, here is a recap of what we’ve been waiting on and why it’s such an important moment in the crypto market.
 
The Ripple Effect Of The Hinman Docs
 
Named after William Hinman, the former Director of the Division of Corporation Finance at the SEC, the “Hinman documents” are speculated to provide insight into the SEC’s stance on cryptocurrency regulation. In 2018, Hinman made a groundbreaking statement, asserting that Bitcoin and Ethereum were not securities under US law due to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tony &amp;quot;The Bull&amp;quot;</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Court Dismisses BitGo’s Lawsuit Against Galaxy Digital]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7578c0545b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/u-s-court-dismisses-bitgos-lawsuit-against-galaxy-digital"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T22:12:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A U.S. court has dismissed the lawsuit filed by BitGo against Galaxy Digital in relation to a failed merger previously agreed to in 2021.
In the company’s response to the terminated merger agreement, BitGo had alleged that Galaxy Digital failed to uphold their end of the bargain, saying the company “intends to hold Galaxy Digital legally responsible for its improper decision to terminate the merger agreement,” with a lawyer representing the company adding that “Either Galaxy owes BitGo a $100 million termination fee as promised or it has been acting in bad faith and faces damages of that much or more.”
At the time of termination, Galaxy Digital cited BitGo's failure to deliver audited financial statements for 2021 that complied with the requirements of the agreement. According to court documents released June 9, this was a “valid basis” for the decision to end the merger, and it effectively voided the termination fee.
“We’re pleased with the court’s decision to dismiss BitGo’s claims,” A statement made by Galaxy Digital on Twitter read. “Now is the time for all of us to work together and focus on the task at hand: Upgrading the global financial system in a manner that promotes innovation and protects investors and consumers alike.”
Just last week, it was announced that BitGo reached a preliminary agreement to acquire its primary U.S. competitor, Prime Trust. Although the details of that merger have not yet been made public, the industry had widely speculated in recent days that Prime Trust faced financial troubles. As such, the agreement has been seen as a relatively good thing, avoiding what many thought may be a coming failure of another large firm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BtcCasey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Argentina’s Bitcoin Community Created The World’s Largest Human Bitcoin Logo]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7578c05457</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/argentinas-bitcoin-community-created-the-worlds-largest-human-bitcoin-logo"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T22:12:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last Saturday, over 500 people gathered in the Argentine Polo Field to create the largest human ₿ in the world in celebration of the 10th anniversary of NGO Bitcoin Argentina. The event aimed to showcase the technology's ability to mobilize people in defense of monetary freedom, privacy, and other values of the cryptocurrency ecosystem. The human ₿, sitting at a massive 40 meters, became the world's largest bitcoin symbol. Jimena Vallone, director of Bitcoin Argentina, expressed hopes that this would be the first of many attempts to break the record.
 
         
         
         
        Photo credits: @BitcoinAR 
    
The event was captured by drones, documenting the scale of the gathering both day and night. Attendees also enjoyed activities such as a Kahoot game, with winners receivin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BtcCasey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fire Gary Gensler: Lawmaker Takes Stand Against SEC Chairman’s Crypto Agenda]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7578c1e95e</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/lawmaker-takes-stand-against-sec-crypto-agenda/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T21:55:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lawmakers in the United States are taking a stand against the recent crackdown on the crypto industry by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). Congressman Warren Davidson has been particularly vocal in his criticism of SEC Chairman Gary Gensler and has called for his removal.
 
 
“Time For Real Reform”, Good For Crypto?
 
In a recent statement, Congressman Davidson claimed that he believes the SEC’s actions against the crypto industry are unjust and that the U.S. capital markets must be protected from a “tyrannical” chairman. He has introduced the SEC Stabilization Act, which aims to restructure the agency and remove Gary Gensler as its chair.
 
The Act proposes replacing the current single-chairman leadership structure with a six-commissioner body to ensure a more balanced and div…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[eToro to Halt Polygon, Algorand, Decentraland, and Dash Purchases for US Customers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144294</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144294/etoro-to-halt-polygon-alogrand-decentraland-and-dash-purchases-for-us-customers"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T21:42:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The move follows a similar pull-back from stock and crypto trading app Robinhood.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC's Temporary Restraining Order Would 'Effectively End' Binance.US Business, Company Claims]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7578c36a10</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/06/12/secs-temporary-restraining-order-would-effectively-end-binanceus-business-company-claims/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T21:40:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Monday effort to freeze Binance.US's funds is a "draconian and unduly burdensome" move, the U.S. affiliate of the global crypto exchange argued Monday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reddit’s Crypto Communities Go Dark In Support of Protest Against API Changes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144290</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144290/reddits-crypto-communities-go-dark-in-support-of-protest-against-api-changes"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T21:23:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Twitter, meanwhile, carried on as usual.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance US Lawyers Up, Braces for Looming Federal Charges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144291</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144291/binance-us-lawyers-up-braces-for-looming-federal-charges"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T21:18:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The American arm of the exchange giant is arming itself with top talent—including an ex-SEC attorney.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BLUR Underperforms CoinDesk Market Index Ahead of $62M Token Unlock]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7578cfcc86</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/06/12/blur-underperforms-coindesk-market-index-ahead-of-62m-token-unlock/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T20:58:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Huge increase in supply could hurt BLUR’s price. The token has also fallen after SEC labeled other tokens as securities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sage D. Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Over 100 Physical Attacks Against Bitcoin Holders And Infrastructure Recorded Since 2014]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7578c80514</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/physical-attacks-bitcoin-holders-infrastructure/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T20:56:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There have been at least 100 physical attacks against Bitcoin holders or infrastructure facilitating BTC transactions, a recent list documenting all recorded attacks on June 12 shows. The list records all known physical attacks on BTC holders or facilities, including crypto ATMs, as early as 2014.
 
Over 100 Recorded Physical Attacks Against Bitcoin Holders
 
The list published on GitHub, a public code repository, and shared by Bitcoin supporter Jameson Lopp, the chief technical officer of Casa, shows that the first recorded attack on BTC was in 2014 when Hal Finney fell victim. Finney was one the first supporters of Bitcoin who was also in touch with Satoshi Nakamoto, the mysterious founder of the cryptocurrency.
 
 
According to circulated news on that day, Finney was “SWATed” after mont…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dalmas Ngetich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UN Warns of AI-Generated Deepfakes Fueling Hate and Misinformation Online]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144281</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144281/un-united-nations-ai-deepfakes-hate-misinformation"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T20:48:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The United Nations expressed particular concern over the role of AI-generated deepfakes in conflict zones.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sturdy Finance Falls Victim to Exploit, Losing 442 ETH in Latest Defi Hack]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7578c9ca1b</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/sturdy-finance-falls-victim-to-exploit-losing-442-eth-in-latest-defi-hack/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T20:39:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized finance (defi) platform Sturdy Finance was exploited on Sunday evening, losing 442 ether to an attacker. The team behind the project stated that it is aware of the reported exploit and paused markets at 10:19 p.m. ET.
 
442 Ethereum Worth Over $766K Siphoned From Sturdy Protocol
 

 
The defi community has experienced another hack, with the Sturdy Finance protocol suffering a loss of 442 ETH, equivalent to an estimated $766,900, according to a summary by Blocksec, a smart contract auditing security team. The issue was also discovered by the blockchain intelligence firm Peckshield at 9:28 p.m. ET.
 

 
 
Hi @SturdyFinance, you may want to take a look:  https://t.co/XiJppu6Ww3
 
The issue seems to be related to the price manipulation
 
— PeckShield Inc. (@peckshield) June 12, 2…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Learning From AI is The Beginning of the End for AI Models]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144271</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144271/ai-learning-from-ai-is-the-beginning-of-the-end-for-ai-models"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T20:11:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The generative AI machine is so ravenous for content, it may consume more AI-generated material.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance US Market Shrinks 78% in Just 7 Days After SEC Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144266</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144266/binance-us-market-shrinks-after-sec-lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T19:55:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Liquidity on Binance's American exchange has dropped since its regulatory woes began last week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Suspends a Dozen Ethereum, BNB Token Trading Pairs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144255</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144255/binance-suspends-ethereum-bnb-busd-trading-pairs"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T18:42:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance ended trading for more than a dozen pairs including its native BNB token, the defunct Binance USD (BUSD) stablecoin, and five involving ETH.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Standard Crypto VC Co-Founder on NFTs and Their Stigma in Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/bmtrrLio/standard-crypto-vc-co-founder-on-nfts-and-their-stigma-in-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/bmtrrLio/standard-crypto-vc-co-founder-on-nfts-and-their-stigma-in-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T18:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alok Vasudev is a co-founder of venture capital firm Standard Crypto. In an interview with Decrypt's Kate Irwin, he shares his thoughts on NFT marketing, NFT utility in gaming, and the stigma that pervades the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Investors Have Pulled $417M Out of Crypto Funds in Two Months]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144251</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144251/investors-have-pulled-417m-out-of-crypto-funds-in-two-months"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T18:11:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Currently there is no end in sight to interest rates rises," James Butterfill, head of research at CoinShares, writes in the new report.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linda Dounia's IN/Visible NFT Exhibition Highlights Black Artists, AI's ‘Skewed’ Lens]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144222</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144222/linda-dounias-in-visible-nft-exhibition-highlights-black-artists-ais-skewed-lens"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T17:01:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The exhibition on Feral File explores “the biases of AI, the biases of the internet, and the biases inherent in Western art history.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BitGo’s Lawsuit Against Galaxy Digital Over $1.2B Merger Dismissed]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144210</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144210/bitgos-lawsuit-against-galaxy-digital-over-1-2b-merger-dismissed"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T14:04:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Galaxy said it was “pleased” at the dismissal of the $100m lawsuit, after the merger between the companies was called off last year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alys Key</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is a Decentralized Autonomous Organization (DAO)?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=5728</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/decentralized-autonomous-organization-dao"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T12:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DAOs use smart contracts and governance tokens to enable participants to make consensus decisions on how the organization's resources are allocated.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Hussey,Adriana Hamacher,Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Launch a DAO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=103949</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/how-to-launch-decentralized-autonomous-organization-dao"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T12:26:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here's a beginner's guide to the tools and apps you need to start a Decentralized Autonomous Organization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ‘Antifragile’ to Regulatory Pressures: Blockstream CEO Adam Back]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144193</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144193/bitcoin-antifragile-to-regulatory-pressures-blockstream-ceo-adam-back"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T12:01:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Blockstream co-founder told Decrypt that the U.S. crypto crackdown won’t have far-reaching consequences for Bitcoin traders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi Lending Protocol Sturdy Finance Hit By Exploit, Over $750K Drained]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144188</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144188/defi-lending-protocol-sturdy-finance-hit-by-exploit-over-750k-drained"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T11:09:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The DeFi platform’s team is trying to communicate with the attackers as its stolen ETH is moved through Tornado Cash.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lummis Renews Commitment to US Crypto Regulation: ‘The Fight is Far From Over’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144182</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144182/lummis-renews-commitment-to-us-crypto-regulation-the-fight-is-far-from-over"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T10:24:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Senator said to ‘stay tuned’ for more on her efforts to establish a regulatory framework for the crypto sector in the U.S.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alys Key</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thirdweb Plots Web3 Gaming Push With Ex-Facebook Exec Hire]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144131</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144131/thirdweb-plots-web3-gaming-tools-push-ex-facebook-exec-hire"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T04:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The infrastructure firm has added Atif Khan to lead its gaming charge, and recently created the game Web3 Warriors on Base.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Farren</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Winklevoss Twins Say 'War On Crypto' Will Hurt Democrats]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144172</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144172/winklevoss-twins-say-war-on-crypto-will-hurt-democrats"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T00:26:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The billionaire co-founders of Gemini say that “crypto has already won the hearts and minds of Millennials and GenZ."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Andreessen Horowitz Opening Crypto Office in London]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144159</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144159/andreessen-horowitz-a16z-crypto-expanding-london-uk"/>
        <updated>2023-06-11T23:43:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Citing "a clear regulatory regime" in the UK, a16z crypto sets up shop outside the United States.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gensyn AI Secures $43M for Decentralized Machine Learning Led by a16z]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144068</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144068/gensyn-ai-secures-43m-for-decentralized-machine-learning-led-by-a16z"/>
        <updated>2023-06-11T23:02:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The UK-based startup aims to democratize machine learning and AI development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana, Cardano, Polygon Push Back Against SEC 'Security' Label]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144124</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144124/solana-cardano-polygon-push-back-against-sec-security-label"/>
        <updated>2023-06-11T22:03:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Although all disagreed, each organization tied to the trio of tokens show varying levels of conviction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Algorand and Flow Crash to All-Time Lows Following SEC Lawsuits]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144119</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144119/algorand-flow-all-time-lows-sec-lawsuits"/>
        <updated>2023-06-11T19:41:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prices for a number of altcoins fell after they were namechecked by the Securities and Exchange Commission.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week on Crypto Twitter: Outrage Over the SEC Crypto Crackdown]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144099</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144099/this-week-on-crypto-twitter-outrage-over-sec-crypto-crackdown"/>
        <updated>2023-06-11T17:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Between bombshell lawsuits against two crypto titans and talk of a weekend Bitcoin dump, it's been a wild ride.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Court Finds a 'DAO Is a Person,' Owes $643,542 in Shutdown Order]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144075</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144075/court-finds-a-dao-is-a-person-owes-643542-in-shutdown-order"/>
        <updated>2023-06-10T23:02:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CFTC touts the "wake-up call to anyone who believes they can circumvent the law by adopting a DAO structure."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Picking and Choosing Tokens to Prosecute Is 'Pretty Unfair,' Says Former SEC Cyber Chief]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144085</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144085/picking-and-choosing-tokens-to-prosecute-is-pretty-unfair-says-former-sec-cyber-chief"/>
        <updated>2023-06-10T21:45:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robert Cohen says the SEC's selective enforcement is having a "real impact on real people and real businesses.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Foodmasku Dishes Out Edible Masks on Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144033</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144033/foodmasku-food-mask-proof-of-eat-nft"/>
        <updated>2023-06-10T20:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The multimedia artist has embraced the blockchain as a means to safeguard his work and explore the intersection of technology and humanity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Market Crashes as SEC Slams Binance and Coinbase]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144061</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144061/this-week-in-coins-market-crashes-as-sec-slams-binance-and-coinbase"/>
        <updated>2023-06-10T17:41:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was a relentless week of enforcement actions by the SEC against crypto’s major players.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Worldwide Tax Standard Includes Cryptocurrencies and CBDCs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144050</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144050/new-worldwide-tax-standard-includes-cryptocurrencies-and-cbdcs"/>
        <updated>2023-06-10T09:08:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new set of rules from the OECD also takes aim at reducing tax evasion executed using cryptocurrencies and blockchain technologies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Toxic Cocktail': EU Watchdog Calls Out Instagram, TikTok for Enabling Crypto Scams]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144028</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144028/toxic-cocktail-eu-watchdog-calls-out-instagram-tiktok-enabling-crypto-scams"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T21:53:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leading social media networks have been targeted by the BEUC for allegedly allowing misleading cryptocurrency ads.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generative AI Will Have 'Enormous Impact' on Business, Execs Admit—But Not Right Away]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144011</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144011/generative-ai-enormous-impact-business-execs-admit-not-right-away"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T21:30:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Corporate executives are optimistic about the benefits of generative AI, according to a KPMG study, but it'll take time to implement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Bankrupt FTX Wants to Keep its List of Customers Private]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144001</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144001/why-bankrupt-ftx-wants-keep-list-customers-private"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T20:57:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A partner at investment bank Perella Weinberg said that revealing customer names would hurt FTX's ongoing sales process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet PassGPT, the AI Trained on Millions of Leaked Passwords]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144004</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144004/meet-passgpt-ai-trained-millions-leaked-passwords"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T20:48:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It shares a name with a past April Fool's gag, but this PassGPT is no joke—and the AI model could help develop more secure passwords.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Minecraft Still Hasn't Officially Banned NFTs—But It's Coming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143996</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143996/minecraft-still-hasnt-officially-banned-nfts-but-coming"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T19:31:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nearly a year after making the announcement, Microsoft shares an update about Minecraft’s intended NFT ban.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ava Labs Launches Avalanche Arcad3 to Help Game Studios Enter Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143978</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143978/ava-labs-launches-avalanche-arcad3-help-game-studios-enter-web3"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T18:46:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche Arcad3 is connecting traditional game publishers with crypto firms to help bring legacy IP into the fledgling Web3 gaming space.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ava Labs Announces Avalanche Arcad3 for Game Developers at 3XP]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XPHp9r4j/ava-labs-announces-avalanche-arcad3-for-game-developers-at-3xp</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XPHp9r4j/ava-labs-announces-avalanche-arcad3-for-game-developers-at-3xp"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T15:21:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ava Labs Head of Gaming Ed Chang shares news with Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the crypto firm's latest push to help traditional game developers break into blockchain gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Like a Middle Finger to Western Culture’: YuYu Unpacks Inspiration Behind NFT Expo GAG]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Vuoplr6a/like-a-middle-finger-to-western-culture-yuyu-unpacks-inspiration-behind-nft-expo-gag</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Vuoplr6a/like-a-middle-finger-to-western-culture-yuyu-unpacks-inspiration-behind-nft-expo-gag"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T13:33:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At this year’s NFC Lisbon, multimedia artist and photographer YuLiang "YuYu" Liu broke down how themes from traditional painting and BDSM informed his latest NFT exhibition called “GAG.” He also shared exclusively with Decrypt a yet-to-be-launched drop for fans of his work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘We’ve Never Seen Anything Like This in VR’, Says The Sandbox COO on Apple’s Vision Pro Headset]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/GQ29RaHw/weve-never-seen-anything-like-this-in-vr-says-the-sandbox-coo-on-apples-vision-pro-headset</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/GQ29RaHw/weve-never-seen-anything-like-this-in-vr-says-the-sandbox-coo-on-apples-vision-pro-headset"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T13:33:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Sandbox COO Sebastien Borget told Decrypt at this year’s NFC Lisbon that despite the high price point, Apple’s new VR headset is nonetheless “groundbreaking.” And though the tech giant never used the term “metaverse” in its reveal, Borget is sure that the technology will be key in growing participation in various digital worlds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Gala Safe? Gala Games Head of Blockchain on GALA, Crypto, and SEC Regulatory Turmoil]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5bcrE8nL/is-gala-safe-gala-games-head-of-blockchain-on-gala-crypto-and-sec-regulatory-turmoil</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5bcrE8nL/is-gala-safe-gala-games-head-of-blockchain-on-gala-crypto-and-sec-regulatory-turmoil"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T15:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gala Games President of Blockchain shares his thoughts on the GALA token upgrade and the latest SEC turmoil with Decrypt's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Artists Adopting NFTs Has Been ‘Really Market Dependent’, Says NFT Club Berlin’s Rebekka Revel]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/QKlIVlj3/artists-adopting-nfts-has-been-really-market-dependent-says-nft-club-berlins-rebekka-revel</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/QKlIVlj3/artists-adopting-nfts-has-been-really-market-dependent-says-nft-club-berlins-rebekka-revel"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T15:07:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Getting non-crypto artists to make the leap into Web3 comes in ebbs and flows according to the market’s bear and bull waves, says co-founder of NFT Club Berlin and Superteam Germany Rebekka Revel. But she’s hoping to change that by changing the narrative around digital collectibles, regardless of the market, one word at a time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big Brands Exploring Web3 to ‘Scale Up Their Superfan Base’: SuperDuper Co-founder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/he6UzJwz/big-brands-exploring-web3-to-scale-up-their-superfan-base-superduper-co-founder</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/he6UzJwz/big-brands-exploring-web3-to-scale-up-their-superfan-base-superduper-co-founder"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T14:49:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Co-founder and co-CEO of Web3 media brand SuperDuper Dom Smith says big brands are eager to enter the space—they just don’t know how. Still, they all maintain a thesis of turning their communities into “super fans” that generate value for users as well as a firm’s bottom line.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How 1 Simple Question Kickstarted Performance Artist Foodmasku's Plunge Into NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/w86DMn3p/how-1-simple-question-kickstarted-performance-artist-foodmaskus-plunge-into-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/w86DMn3p/how-1-simple-question-kickstarted-performance-artist-foodmaskus-plunge-into-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T10:10:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As his food mask creations went viral on the Internet during the COVID lockdowns, reposted on TikTok and Instagram without his consent, he soon asked: "How do I protect my digital files?" Performance artist Foodmasku describes at this year's NFC Lisbon how that simple question spiraled into a minting collection after collection of his edible works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arianee CEO Pegs Wine and Spirits as Next 'Exciting' Industry to Make Web3 Leap]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Bo2NeG9Z/arianee-ceo-pegs-wine-and-spirits-as-next-exciting-industry-to-make-web3-leap</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Bo2NeG9Z/arianee-ceo-pegs-wine-and-spirits-as-next-exciting-industry-to-make-web3-leap"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T09:28:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CEO and co-founder of Arianee Pierre Nicolas Hurstel unpacks the wide spectrum of digital collectibles from 10,000 PFP collections to access passes for exclusive events. And with an unannounced big brand soon joining, Hurstel revealed at NFC Lisbon which kind of NFTs big brands are moving towards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why 'Words With Friends' Creator Paul Bettner is 'Allergic' to Pay-to-Win NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JkfOleb4/why-words-with-friends-creator-paul-bettner-is-allergic-to-pay-to-win-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JkfOleb4/why-words-with-friends-creator-paul-bettner-is-allergic-to-pay-to-win-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T20:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Words With Friends and Wildcard creator Paul Bettner tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about his perspective on what to do when NFTs become in-game characters and assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitch Co-Founder Justin Kan: 18 Months is 'Several Decades' in Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rKVvsPFb/twitch-co-founder-justin-kan-18-months-is-several-decades-in-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rKVvsPFb/twitch-co-founder-justin-kan-18-months-is-several-decades-in-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fractal and Twitch co-founder Justin Kan gives Decrypt's Kate Irwin an update on all things Fractal and his perspective on blockchain technology in gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Playing for Money in Web3 Games Not 'Durable,' Says Fractal's Justin Kan]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MQG3SaBM/playing-for-money-in-web3-games-not-durable-says-fractals-justin-kan</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MQG3SaBM/playing-for-money-in-web3-games-not-durable-says-fractals-justin-kan"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twitch and Fractal co-founder Justin Kan and Fractal co-founder Dan Borstelmann share their perspectives on Web3 gaming's changing landscape with Decrypt's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Cyber Cafe to Web3: How Everquest Dev Jeffrey Butler Got Into Game Development]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/hRlI4WXe/from-cyber-cafe-to-web3-how-everquest-dev-jeffrey-butler-got-into-game-development</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/hRlI4WXe/from-cyber-cafe-to-web3-how-everquest-dev-jeffrey-butler-got-into-game-development"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T14:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everquest developer turned Avalon Chief Product Officer Jeffrey Butler tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how he got into game development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Machines Arena Game Preview: Is This the Next Overwatch?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/tT0qWy4s/the-machines-arena-game-preview-is-this-the-next-overwatch</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/tT0qWy4s/the-machines-arena-game-preview-is-this-the-next-overwatch"/>
        <updated>2023-06-02T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt contributor Ryan S. Gladwin shares an inside look at The Machines Arena, an upcoming top-down 4v4 shooter from Directive Games that will offer NFTs minted on Ethereum sidechain network Ronin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You 'Have' to Be on Mobile: InfiniGods Cofounders on Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/l3KBurz4/you-have-to-be-on-mobile-infinigods-cofounders-on-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/l3KBurz4/you-have-to-be-on-mobile-infinigods-cofounders-on-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[InfiniGods developers Damon Gura and Owen O’Donoghue share their stance on why mobile gaming is essential to Web3 adoption and general success in the video games industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Chaos of 2022 'Didn't Damage Technology Underlying the Industry': X Ventures Co-Founder Matthias Reiser]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PDArXOkZ/crypto-chaos-of-2022-didnt-damage-technology-underlying-the-industry-x-ventures-co-founder-matthias-reiser</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PDArXOkZ/crypto-chaos-of-2022-didnt-damage-technology-underlying-the-industry-x-ventures-co-founder-matthias-reiser"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T13:13:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ahead of this month's Proof of Talk event in Paris on June 14 and June 15, X Ventures co-founder and the event's co-organizer Dr. Matthias Reiser said nothing's changed for those with a "long-term view" of the industry. Still, events like the collapse of Terra and FTX in 20222 have certainly damaged investors' trust in crypto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tron's Justin Sun Thinks Hong Kong Will Be a Big Fiat Onramp for Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/agBnfg7Z/trons-justin-sun-thinks-hong-kong-will-be-a-big-fiat-onramp-for-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/agBnfg7Z/trons-justin-sun-thinks-hong-kong-will-be-a-big-fiat-onramp-for-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T12:19:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Justin Sun, Tron founder and advisor to crypto exchange Huobi, talks to Decrypt's Liam Kelly and Stacy Elliott about the impact of Hong Kong allowing residents to trade crypto, complications of restricting access based on location, and how AI will change the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NVIDIA's AI Push Could Change Gaming Forever]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/79ArMuzj/nvidias-ai-push-could-change-gaming-forever</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/79ArMuzj/nvidias-ai-push-could-change-gaming-forever"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T14:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Computer tech firm NVIDIA profited off the crypto mining industry. Now, it's looking to artificial intelligence—and its stock price is soaring.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why InfiniGods Laughs at 'AAA' Web3 Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/WzdrzXOY/why-infinigods-laughs-at-aaa-web3-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/WzdrzXOY/why-infinigods-laughs-at-aaa-web3-games"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The InfiniGods founders share their approach to game development and offer a critique of games that call themselves "AAA."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Make it Fast, Make it Friendly: Jerome de Tychey Unpacks Key Themes at This Year's EthCC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yNyunUz4/make-it-fast-make-it-friendly-jerome-de-tychey-unpacks-key-themes-at-this-years-ethcc</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yNyunUz4/make-it-fast-make-it-friendly-jerome-de-tychey-unpacks-key-themes-at-this-years-ethcc"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T15:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After six years running, EthCC is back, this time in Paris from July 17 to July 20. Decrypt sat down with the brains behind one of Ethereum’s longest-running events Jerome de Tychey to get an inside look into what’s on the agenda this year, several unannounced guests, and the rollout of at least one “secret” DeFi project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>