<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-09-30T15:13:10.139Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-09-30T15:13:10.139Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Garlinghouse Baits XRP Community Ahead of Celebratory Event]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18939297/Garlinghouse-Baits-XRP-Community-Ahead-of-Celebratory-Event</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18939297/Garlinghouse-Baits-XRP-Community-Ahead-of-Celebratory-Event"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T15:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple's CEO, Brad Garlinghouse, recently revealed his unwavering commitment to XRP through an unexpected gesture.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitwise joins growing list of Ethereum ETF managers]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18939296/Bitwise-joins-growing-list-of-Ethereum-ETF-managers</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18939296/Bitwise-joins-growing-list-of-Ethereum-ETF-managers"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T15:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitwise Asset Management announced the launch of two Ethereum-themed exchange-traded funds (ETFs), joining the growing list of asset managers looking to create Ethereum-based futures products after the SEC greenlit them. The two funds will be called the Bitwise Ethereum Strategy ETF (AETH) and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Price Predictions: The Ultra Bullish To The Most Bearish]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18939294/XRP-Price-Predictions-The-Ultra-Bullish-To-The-Most-Bearish</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18939294/XRP-Price-Predictions-The-Ultra-Bullish-To-The-Most-Bearish"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T15:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The future XRP price is one topic that has been keenly debated since Judge Analisa Torres’ ruling in favor of Ripple against the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), with many crypto analysts chiming in on the token’s future trajectory. Some have stated that XRP could go as high as...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI forecasts Dogecoin price for the end of 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18939278/AI-forecasts-Dogecoin-price-for-the-end-of-2023</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18939278/AI-forecasts-Dogecoin-price-for-the-end-of-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T15:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite the extended bear market, Dogecoin (DOGE) has been able to keep its position among the 10-largest cryptocurrencies by market … Continued]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chainlink (LINK) Displays Interesting Q3 Growth Trends: See What Data Says]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18939284/Chainlink-LINK-Displays-Interesting-Q3-Growth-Trends-See-What-Data-Says</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18939284/Chainlink-LINK-Displays-Interesting-Q3-Growth-Trends-See-What-Data-Says"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T14:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chainlink has printed its second consecutive quarterly growth amid expanding utility embrace]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fornite Developer Cuts 16% of Workforce Amid Metaverse Revenue Shortfall]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18939260/Fornite-Developer-Cuts-16-of-Workforce-Amid-Metaverse-Revenue-Shortfall</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18939260/Fornite-Developer-Cuts-16-of-Workforce-Amid-Metaverse-Revenue-Shortfall"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T14:35:07.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Could Benefit if an Economic Recession Hits, Says Fidelity Investments Macro Analyst – Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18939259/Bitcoin-Could-Benefit-if-an-Economic-Recession-Hits-Says-Fidelity-Investments-Macro-Analyst-Heres-Why</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18939259/Bitcoin-Could-Benefit-if-an-Economic-Recession-Hits-Says-Fidelity-Investments-Macro-Analyst-Heres-Why"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T14:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fidelity Investments’ global macro director Jurrien Timmer says that a recession could spark a big rally for Bitcoin (BTC). Timmer tells his 167,000 followers on the social media platform X that current high-interest rates need to decline for Bitcoin to put up big gains. “What will keep driving...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s behind GMX’s rising V2 traction?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18939252/Whats-behind-GMXs-rising-V2-traction</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18939252/Whats-behind-GMXs-rising-V2-traction"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T14:30:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following the launch of GMX quests, the leading decentralized exchange has recorded a new daily all-time high for network activity on its V2 iteration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chainlink Labs Co-Founder Sergey Nazarov: Only Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Chainlink Achieve True Decentralization]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18939255/Chainlink-Labs-Co-Founder-Sergey-Nazarov-Only-Bitcoin-Ethereum-and-Chainlink-Achieve-True-Decentralization</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18939255/Chainlink-Labs-Co-Founder-Sergey-Nazarov-Only-Bitcoin-Ethereum-and-Chainlink-Achieve-True-Decentralization"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T14:29:29.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Ethereum Can Appeal to Institutional Investors: Fidelity]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18939238/How-Ethereum-Can-Appeal-to-Institutional-Investors-Fidelity</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18939238/How-Ethereum-Can-Appeal-to-Institutional-Investors-Fidelity"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T14:26:10.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu's Shibarium Approaches Major Achievement: Details]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18939242/Shiba-Inus-Shibarium-Approaches-Major-Achievement-Details</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18939242/Shiba-Inus-Shibarium-Approaches-Major-Achievement-Details"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T14:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$415 Million FTX Hacker Moves ETH Exploited From The Exchange]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18939248/415-Million-FTX-Hacker-Moves-ETH-Exploited-From-The-Exchange</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18939248/415-Million-FTX-Hacker-Moves-ETH-Exploited-From-The-Exchange"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T14:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biggest Movers: LINK Races to 2-Month High, SOL Extends Gains]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b8a456c4</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/biggest-movers-link-races-to-2-month-high-sol-extends-gains/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T14:08:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chainlink rose for a fourth straight day to start the weekend, as the price surged by as much as 7% in today’s session. The move pushed the token to a two-month high, breaking out of a key resistance level in the process. Solana extended recent gains on Saturday. 
 
Chainlink (LINK)
 
Chainlink (LINK) rose by as much as 7% in today’s session, as the token climbed to a two-month peak.
 
LINK/USD raced to an intraday high of $8.21 to start the weekend, which comes a day after falling to a low of $7.69.
 
As a result of the rally, chainlink climbed to its highest level since July 22, when the price peaked at $8.37.
 
 
From the chart, it appears that the move occurred after bulls orchestrated a breakout of a ceiling at $8.10.
 
This gain also pushed the relative strength index (RSI) into the overbought region, with a current reading of 74.28.
 
Bears may see this as an opportunity to trigger a price reversal, with a ceiling of 75.00 as a potential entry point.
 
 
Solana (SOL)
 
Solana (SOL) remained above the $20.00 level on Saturday, as the token neared a key price point.
 
Following a low of $20.06 on Friday, SOL/USD jumped to a high of $20.42 earlier in the weekend’s session.
 
This saw the cryptocurrency near a ceiling of $20.50, with bulls so far unable to force a breakout beyond this level.
 
 
Earlier gains have since edged lower as a result, with solana now trading at $20.30, with the RSI under a resistance point of its own at 56.00.
 
Price strength now sits at 55.96, with a floor of 53.00 a possible target for bears, in the event momentum continues to weaken this weekend.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
Will solana fall under $20.00 in the coming days? Let us know your thoughts in the comments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum ETFs Saga: Former CFTC Officer Reveals Unexpected Effects of SEC Loss]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18939220/Ethereum-ETFs-Saga-Former-CFTC-Officer-Reveals-Unexpected-Effects-of-SEC-Loss</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18939220/Ethereum-ETFs-Saga-Former-CFTC-Officer-Reveals-Unexpected-Effects-of-SEC-Loss"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T14:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CFTC veteran Mike Selig, one of most influential blockchain lawyers, is sure that Grayscale legal win is crucial for spot ETFs progress]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain Expert Explains Why He Holds XRP]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18939218/Blockchain-Expert-Explains-Why-He-Holds-XRP</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18939218/Blockchain-Expert-Explains-Why-He-Holds-XRP"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T14:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Watch THIS If You Use Stablecoins!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18939234/Watch-THIS-If-You-Use-Stablecoins</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18939234/Watch-THIS-If-You-Use-Stablecoins"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T14:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried’s Lawyer Opposes Prosecutors’ Proposed Jury Questions]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b8a5df1f</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/sam-bankman-fried-lawyer-opposes-prosecutors/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T13:52:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The legal counsel representing Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF), the former boss of the now-defunct FTX exchange, has raised some questions about the government’s proposed queries during jury selection. The FTX co-founder faces a six-week trial, which will commence with a jury selection process on October 3, 2023.
 
The prosecutors and the defense counsel submitted their questions for jury selection on September 11. As Bitcoinist reported, the prosecutors challenged Sam Bankman-Fried’s proposed questions, calling it “unnecessarily intrusive.”
 
Sam Bankman-Fried’s Lawyer Accuses Government Of Prejudice
 
According to a court filing on Friday, September 29, Bankman-Fried’s attorney, Mark Cohen, argued that the questions proposed by the United States for jury selection contain bias that could result …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Opeyemi Sule</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Future ETFs: VanEck to Donate 10% Profit to Protocol Guild for 10 Years]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18939195/Ethereum-Future-ETFs-VanEck-to-Donate-10-Profit-to-Protocol-Guild-for-10-Years</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18939195/Ethereum-Future-ETFs-VanEck-to-Donate-10-Profit-to-Protocol-Guild-for-10-Years"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Years Taken: Bitcoin Icon Ross Ulbricht Is Still In Jail, Still Seeking Justice]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b8a79956</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/10-years-bitcoin-silk-road-ross-ulbricht-jail-justice"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T13:34:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It has officially been a decade since Ross Ulbricht, the man behind the popular online marketplace Silk Road, was sentenced to life in prison without the possibility of parole. His crime: enabling free people to freely trade.
In the years since, his case has been a lightning rod for debates about internet freedom, drug policy, and the criminal justice system, leaving a lasting impact on the Bitcoin and cryptocurrency community. 
As the years roll by, Ulbricht remains in prison, still seeking justice for what he believes was an unfair sentence.
In 2014, Ulbricht was arrested and accused of running Silk Road, a clandestine online marketplace that allowed users to buy and sell a wide range of goods, including drugs, using Bitcoin as the primary currency. His arrest was a pivotal moment in the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reed Macdonald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unusual Activity Spike in Trading Volumes of 5 Altcoins on South Korean Exchanges]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18939183/Unusual-Activity-Spike-in-Trading-Volumes-of-5-Altcoins-on-South-Korean-Exchanges</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18939183/Unusual-Activity-Spike-in-Trading-Volumes-of-5-Altcoins-on-South-Korean-Exchanges"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T13:34:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There were unusual increases in the transaction volumes of some altcoins on Upbit, South Korea's largest cryptocurrency exchange. Continue Reading: Unusual Activity Spike in Trading Volumes of 5 Altcoins on South Korean Exchanges]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. dollar lost 99.5% of its value against Bitcoin in the last 10 years]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18939167/US-dollar-lost-995-of-its-value-against-Bitcoin-in-the-last-10-years</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18939167/US-dollar-lost-995-of-its-value-against-Bitcoin-in-the-last-10-years"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T13:27:58.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biggest Video Games Releasing in October 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199403</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199403/biggest-video-games-releasing-october-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From Assassin's Creed Mirage to Spider-Man 2 and Super Mario Bros. Wonder, these are the can't-miss video game launches in October.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biggest Video Games Releasing in October 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18939128/Biggest-Video-Games-Releasing-in-October-2023</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18939128/Biggest-Video-Games-Releasing-in-October-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI tech boom: Is the artificial intelligence market already saturated?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18939127/AI-tech-boom-Is-the-artificial-intelligence-market-already-saturated</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18939127/AI-tech-boom-Is-the-artificial-intelligence-market-already-saturated"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T13:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Technical Analysis: Profit Takers Swoop in to Send BTC, ETH Lower]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b8a92a37</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-ethereum-technical-analysis-profit-takers-swoop-in-to-send-btc-eth-lower/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T11:57:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin consolidated to start the weekend, as traders moved to secure gains following recent highs in the market. The global market cap was largely unchanged on Saturday, trading 0.06% lower at the time of writing. Ethereum also declined, after a one-month high on Friday.
 
Bitcoin
 
Bitcoin retreated from a ten-day high on Saturday, as bulls opted to secure profits from recent gains.
 
BTC/USD slipped to a low of $26,721.76 earlier in the day, which comes less than 24-hours after peaking at $27,075.94.
 
The move comes as bulls were unable to sustain a recent breakout above a ceiling at the $27,100 level.
 
 
Zooming into the chart, a failed break of the 58.00 resistance level on the relative strength index (RSI), also contributed to the downturn.
 
At the time of writing this, price strength is now tracking at 56.24, which is marginally above a ceiling of 55.00.
 
Bulls will likely make another run towards $27,000 this weekend, despite today’s price consolidation.
 
 
Ethereum
 
Ethereum (ETH) has been on a bull run this week, climbing to a one-month high during Friday’s session.
 
These gains have since been erased, with ETH/USD falling to a low of $1,657.68 earlier in the day, after hitting a high of $1,681.79 the day before.
 
The move has pushed the 10-day (red) moving average on the cusp with a crossover with its 25-day (blue) counterpart.
 
 
Although momentum is firmly bullish, a ceiling of 61.00 on the RSI could act as a hurdle for traders looking to take ETH towards $1,700.
 
Currently, the index is tracking at 60.01, with ethereum hovering slightly below the $1,680 price region.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
Is today’s consolidation solely due to profit-taking? Leave your thoughts in the comments below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Counting The Loot: $3 Million Stolen In ‘Kraken’ Crypto Con – Details]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b8a995a9</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/3-million-stolen-in-kraken-crypto-con/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T11:53:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The surge in online scams has drawn heightened regulatory attention towards the crypto industry. A recent case serves as a vivid reminder of the risks involved, where a Connecticut resident became a victim of a significant scam, losing more than $3 million to individuals falsely purporting to be associated with Kraken, a well-known cryptocurrency exchange.
 
The victim, who remains unnamed, was based in Westport and followed advice to transfer funds out of a retirement account, intending to reinvest the money in an account supposedly linked to Kraken. However, their decision led to more than $3 million swiftly disappearing into crypto wallets they could not access.
 
 
Recovery Of Stolen Crypto Funds
 
Fortunately, the victim sought help from law enforcement, and local detectives, collabor…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yuna Rin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rising Rates Gives New Life to Interest-Bearing Stablecoins]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199327</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199327/rising-rates-gives-new-life-interest-bearing-stablecoins"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T11:01:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rising interest rates ain't all bad, as many decentralized stablecoin issuers are turning to real-world assets to generate new yield.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paypal Selects Crypto.com as ‘Preferred Exchange’ for PYUSD Stablecoin]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b890f392</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/paypal-selects-crypto-com-as-preferred-exchange-for-pyusd-stablecoin/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T10:36:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paypal has chosen Crypto.com as the “preferred exchange” for its recently launched stablecoin issued by the blockchain company Paxos. The partnership with the trading platform seeks to prop the U.S. dollar-pegged cryptocurrency which has already listed the coin and provides liquidity for its market.
 
Crypto.com Joins Payments Giant Paypal and Fintech Firm Paxos to ‘Further Enable Paypal USD’
 
Crypto.com announced a partnership with Paypal that aims to establish the digital assets exchange as the preferred trading platform for the online payment provider’s new paypal usd (PYUSD) stablecoin. In a press release, the crypto firm highlighted it has already listed the new currency and is currently the exchange with the deepest liquidity for its trading pairs.
 
Paypal introduced the stablecoin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lubomir Tassev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Millions in Ether Tied to FTX Account Drainer on The Move]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b892c437</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/09/30/millions-in-ether-tied-to-ftx-account-drainer-on-the-move/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T10:18:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FTX was hacked in November 2022, hours after the global crypto empire declared bankruptcy and its founder Sam Bankman-Fried stepped down from running the company.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa, Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Vs. SEC: Paradigm Files An Amicus Brief, Accuses SEC Of Regulatory Overreach]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b89d1894</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/paradigm-amicus-accuses-sec-of-regulatory-overreach/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T09:54:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto research firm Paradigm has filed an amicus brief in the ongoing court case between the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and Binance, its US affiliate – Binance.US – and the exchange’s global CEO Changpeng “CZ” Chao.
 
Back in June, the US top securities watchdog launched a lawsuit against the defendants, accusing them of operating unlicensed exchanges, broker-dealers, and clearing agencies among 13 charges.
 
In a statement released on September 29, Paradigm, who claims to have zero interest or investment in the defendants, has taken a stance against the SEC, accusing the commission of governmental overreach.
 
 
SEC Wants To Change The Law, Paradigm Says
 
According to Paradigm, the SEC is attempting to bypass the rulemaking process and rewrite the law, utilizing the “di…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Semilore Faleti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Israel Land Authority Examines Real Estate Tokenization Applications]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b899ed79</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/israel-land-authority-examines-real-estate-tokenization-applications/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T09:03:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Israel Land Authority has called for blockchain experts to determine the different applications of distributed ledger technology in real estate. Implementing this technology could ostensibly present several advantages compared to traditional real estate transactions, which are qualified by Israeli media as being “time-consuming” and having high operational fees.
Israel Examines Blockchain Real Estate Opportunities
Israel is mulling the application of blockchain tech in the real estate sector. According to Israeli media, the national Land Authority has called for blockchain experts to examine the various applications of blockchain in the real estate sector, and how it might benefit from such implementations.
Some of the applications that the Israeli Land Authority believes blockchain te…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JPEX Scam: Hong Kong Cops Nab 4 More People Linked To Crypto Exchange]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b8802a27</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/jpex-scam-hong-kong-cops-nab-4-more/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T07:55:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Friday, officials in Hong Kong and Macao said that they had arrested four more people with ties to the cryptocurrency exchange JPEX, which is accused of bilking over 2,400 users out of about $200 million.
 
The overall number of detentions has now reached 18 after these arrests, which the authorities have described as involving those “relatively close” to the core of the issue.
 
 
Police in Hong Kong announced the arrest of two individuals on Friday, one of whom had been using paper shredders and laundry bleach to destroy papers.
 
Inquiry Into JPEX Operations
 
The most recent police investigation resulted in the seizure of cash and gold totaling approximately $9 million Hong Kong dollars ($1.15 million) from three separate apartments.
 
Following increased regulatory monitoring of JP…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hashgraph Association in Blockchain Adoption Drive Partnership With Tunisia-Based Dar Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b88145b8</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/hashgraph-association-in-blockchain-adoption-drive-partnership-with-tunisia-based-dar-blockchain/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T07:43:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Hashgraph Association and Dar Blockchain recently said they will be working “to nurture projects, facilitate growth, and profoundly shape the Middle East and North Africa (MENA) technology landscape.” The two entities said they hope to achieve the set objectives via meetups, hackathons, and university groups.
 
Shaping the MENA Region Technology Landscape
 
The Hashgraph Association, a non-profit organisation promoting the use and adoption of the Hedera network, recently said it had entered into a partnership with the Tunisia-based Dar Blockchain. Through this collaboration, Hashgraph Association and Dar Blockchain said they hope “to nurture projects, facilitate growth, and profoundly shape the Middle East and North Africa (MENA) technology landscape.”
 
According to a press statement,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Buenos Aires to Bring Blockchain-Based Digital ID to Millions of Citizens]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b88a1668</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/buenos-aires-to-bring-blockchain-based-digital-id-to-millions-of-citizens/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T06:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The city of Buenos Aires has announced that it will roll out a blockchain-based, privacy-focused digital ID wallet starting in October. The Quarkid project, previously known as Tangoid, will allow its users to download a “self-sovereign” wallet to hold their birth and marriage certificates, with more digital documents to be added later this year.
Buenos Aires to Roll Out Blockchain-Based ID Program
The City of Buenos Aires government announced the deployment of a digital, blockchain-based “self-sovereign” ID project for its citizens. The wallet, called Quarkid, formerly known as Tangoid and scheduled to be operating by last January, will supposedly allow its users to exert full ownership of their data, granting only trusted and permissioned third parties access.
The Quarkid wallet will use…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried Trial: A Colossal Legal Showdown Starts Next Week]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b8734dfe</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/sam-bankman-fried-trial-a-colossal-legal-showdown-starts-next-week/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T04:08:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A calendar has been set for the upcoming trial of United States v. Bankman-Fried, with jury selection beginning October 3, 2023. The FTX founder, Sam Bankman-Fried, was denied temporary release from prison but will be allowed to use an “air-gapped,” internet-disabled laptop for note-taking in the courtroom. In the coming month and a half, the public will likely hear testimonies from FTX senior personnel such as Zixiao (Gary) Wang, Caroline Ellison, Nishad Singh, and Ryan Salame.
 
The Bankman-Fried Trial Kickoff
 
Next week, the co-founder and former FTX CEO Sam Bankman-Fried is set to face trial following charges leveled by the U.S. government. The litany of accusations against him includes wire fraud conspiracy, wire fraud, commodities fraud conspiracy, securities fraud conspiracy, and m…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOJ's Proposed Jury Questions 'Risks Tainting' Bankman-Fried's Panel, Defense Says]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b87f7e3f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/09/30/dojs-proposed-jury-questions-risks-tainting-bankman-frieds-panel-defense-says/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T03:13:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried's attorneys objected to some of the U.S. Department of Justice's proposed voir dire questions in a late Friday filing, saying they may miss potential juror bias or otherwise lead to jurors making assumptions about the case.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Delays Decisions on More Bitcoin ETFs Including That of Blackrock]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b8642c13</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/sec-delays-decisions-on-more-bitcoin-etfs-including-that-of-blackrock/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T02:09:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has postponed its decisions on the spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) proposed by several companies. The delays of the applications of financial powerhouse Blackrock, asset manager Valkyrie and others come ahead of an expected government shutdown that would affect the SEC.
 
U.S. Securities Regulator Pushes Back Verdicts on Multiple Bitcoin ETF Applications
 
The future of a number of attempts to issue spot bitcoin ETFs in the United States remains unclear after the country’s regulatory body overseeing the securities market delayed its decisions again. The move concerns the high-profile application of investment giant Blackrock as well as those of Valkyrie, Bitwise, and Invesco, according to filings on Thursday.
 
The development follows…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lubomir Tassev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GMX Paid A Hefty Prize Because Of This Flaw]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b862232d</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/gmx-paid-a-hefty-prize-because-of-this-flaw/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T00:50:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GMX, a decentralized exchange, awarded Collider Research a $1 million bug bounty in 2022. This payout was in recognition of their discovery of a critical bug in GMX’s smart contracts that directly affected how the protocol tracks outstanding debt.
 
The Bug Affecting GMX And GLP
 
GMX has not provided more information on how the bug was patched and when. However, the DEX operator said the bug negatively impacted GMX v1 liquidity providers (LPs) as the code led to inaccuracies in quotes related to “the fair value of tokens.” Specifically, the bug affected the Global Liquidity Pool (GLP), causing it to deviate from its fair value. 
 
Since GMX supports up to 50X leverage, a system tracks debt borrowed by traders and how it is repaid. It is smart contract-driven, and the trader enters into de…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dalmas Ngetich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Representative Introduces Legislation to Mandate Reporting of Off-Chain Crypto Transactions to the CFTC]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b86d2c02</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/us-representative-introduces-legislation-to-mandate-reporting-of-off-chain-crypto-transactions-to-the-cftc/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T00:10:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Virginia’s Democratic representative Don Beyer has ushered in a fresh bill mandating the documentation of off-chain transactions and over-the-counter (OTC) crypto engagements by cryptocurrency exchanges, to be catalogued in a repository under the purview of the U.S. Commodity Futures Trading Commission.
 
New Legislation Targets Off-Chain Transfers in Crypto Industry
 
Representative Don Beyer (D-VA), has unveiled a new legislative piece reportedly aimed at safeguarding stakeholders in the digital assets arena. Titled the “Off-Chain Digital Commodity Transaction Reporting Act,” this bill mandates “trading platforms to report all transactions to a repository registered with the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC).”
 
Beyer posits that crypto trading platforms bear the responsibility…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Analyst Says COMP Price Will Reach $66 If This Happens]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b86ee35b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-analyst-comp-price-66/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T23:49:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week has seen the COMP price put on one of the most impressive rallies amid the bear market. The price recovery has seen the digital asset gain more than 22% over a 7-day period, cementing its position as a top gainer. But even with such an already significant gain, one analyst believes that the rally is far from over.
 
COMP Price Chart Shows Promise
 
In the analysis that presents one of the most bullish scenarios so far for the COMP price, a pseudonymous analyst who goes by MyCryptoParadise on TradingView has put forward that the altcoin could still rise another 50% from here.
 
 
The chart shared by the analyst points to a double bottom that was marked between August and September. At the end of this double bottom lies incredible promise for the COMP price, making a rise to $66 po…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Best Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Scam Alert: CFTC Launches Lawsuit Against Mosaic Exchange]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b854209c</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-scam-cftc-lawsuit-against-mosaic-exchange/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T22:48:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a significant move targeting the crypto industry, the US Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) has filed a civil enforcement action against Mosaic Exchange Limited, a Pennsylvania limited liability company, and its owner and Chief Executive Officer, Sean Michael.
 
The complaint alleges that the defendants operated a fraudulent digital asset commodity scheme, deceiving investors and misappropriating customer funds.
 
Alleged Fraudulent Crypto Scheme
 
According to the complaint, the defendants fraudulently solicited and induced 17 individuals from the United States and other countries to invest hundreds of thousands of dollars’ worth of Bitcoin (BTC) and other funds. 
 
These funds were supposed to be traded on behalf of the customers in Bitcoin and other crypto assets. However, t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Traders Eye Bullish Silver Lining in Looming US Government Shutdown, Says Analyst]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b8577f17</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-traders-eye-bullish-silver-lining-in-looming-us-government-shutdown-says-analyst/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T22:12:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Numerous reports foretell an imminent U.S. government shutdown, given the anticipated failure of a spending bill to secure passage by Saturday evening — a measure meant to sustain operations till mid-November. On the cusp of this shutdown, bitcoin (BTC) has been on an ascent, catching the eye of many. Coinshares analyst Luke Nolan notes a buoyant sentiment among some traders, who view the government’s looming closure with a favorable lens.
 
Bitcoin Rides the Wave of Uncertainty as U.S. Braces for Government Shutdown
 

 
The U.S. government could shut down this weekend if Democrats and Republican policymakers can’t come to an agreement on spending. Currently, there’s a bill on the table that aims to extend the government’s pay until mid-November, but a number of Republicans and Kevin McCa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoin Legislation Looms Despite Threat of Government Shutdown]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199523</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199523/stablecoin-legislation-government-shutdown"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T22:05:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Things are complicated right now,” Congressman Patrick McHenry told Circle’s Chief Strategy Officer and Head of Global Policy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Galaxy and Invesco Join Growing Ethereum ETF Race]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199379</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199379/galaxy-invesco-join-growing-ethereum-etf-race"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T21:46:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Galaxy and Invesco added their names to the Ethereum spot ETF field on Friday, even as worry of a government shutdown and SEC delays loom.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quantum Leap: Researchers Achieve Major Milestone for Reliable Quantum Computers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199380</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199380/quantum-leap-researchers-achieve-major-milestone-for-reliable-quantum-computers"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T19:44:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers discovered a way to bring the industry closer to more reliable, powerful quantum computers less prone to errors or inaccuracies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's Stopping Fortnite and Call of Duty From Using the Same Items? It's Not Just NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199378</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199378/whats-stopping-fortnite-call-duty-using-same-items-not-just-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T19:28:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Will the video game industry open up and play nice? These are the hurdles left to overcome to enable interoperable items at scale.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terra's Do Kwon Admits to Faking Trading Volume in Leaked Chat: Court Docs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199375</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199375/terras-do-kwon-admits-to-faking-trading-volume-in-leaked-chat-court-docs"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T19:15:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["I won't tell if you won't," Terra's Do Kwon said, according to SEC documents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['There Are No Real Standards': Ready Player Me CEO Timmu Tõke on Building for an Open Gaming Ecosystem]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TH3KEAI0/there-are-no-real-standards-ready-player-me-ceo-timmu-tke-on-building-for-an-open-gaming-ecosystem</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TH3KEAI0/there-are-no-real-standards-ready-player-me-ceo-timmu-tke-on-building-for-an-open-gaming-ecosystem"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T17:29:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Timmu Tõke, co-founder and CEO of Ready Player Me, joins Decrypt contributor Ryan Gladwin to discuss the startup's approach to powering avatars that are interoperable across games and metaverse platforms—and what's needed to convince the industry to adopt standards and open up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoins Aren't Securities, Says Circle in SEC Lawsuits Against Binance]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199356</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199356/stablecoins-arent-securities-says-circle-in-sec-lawsuits-against-binance"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T16:03:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neither BUSD nor USDC is a security, Circle argued—but was careful to say it's not picking sides in the case.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Is Giving Away Free Gaming NFTs—Here's How to Claim]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151872</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151872/amazon-giving-away-free-gaming-nfts-how-claim"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T15:59:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATE: A new Mojo Melee champion NFT is now available for Amazon Prime subscribers, along with non-NFT items in Web3 game My Pet Hooligan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Arrows Capital Co-Founder Su Zhu Arrested in Singapore]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199354</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199354/three-arrows-capital-co-founder-su-zhu-arrested-in-singapore"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T15:47:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Su Zhu will serve a four-month sentence behind bars for not complying with court orders during 3AC's bankruptcy process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How On-Chain Attestations Unlock Blockchain’s Most Valuable Use Cases]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199326</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199326/how-on-chain-attestations-unlock-blockchains-most-valuable-use-cases"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T15:27:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KYC alone won’t cut it—to open up real world use cases for crypto, on-chain attestations are the solution for identity verification.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Graeme Moore</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$3 Billion in Bitcoin Options Expire Today—What Will That Do to BTC's Price?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199339</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199339/3-billion-bitcoin-options-expire-september-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T15:23:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Analysts say there's no sign that the expiring options will cause big swings in BTC's price.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Sam Bankman-Fried Ended Up in Jail]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199249</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199249/how-sam-bankman-fried-ended-up-in-jail"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T15:22:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Super Bowl streaming with a VPN and witness tampering concerns eventually led Sam Bankman-Fried back to jail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get Paid to Train AI? There’s a New Cryptocurrency for That]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199332</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199332/get-paid-train-ai-theres-new-cryptocurrency-that"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T13:31:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ta-Da will soon offer a native token for data contributions, introducing a new model for training artificial intelligence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenTrade Launches Tokenized Treasury Bills on Protocol Developed by Circle]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199291</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199291/opentrade-launches-tokenized-treasury-bills-on-protocol-developed-by-circle"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T12:59:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For every tokenized t-bill an investor purchases, OpenTrade will be buy an actual treasury bill and provide an on-chain identifier it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Market Flips Green Amid Ethereum Futures ETF Approval, Dollar Weakness]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199324</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199324/crypto-market-flips-green-amid-ethereum-futures-etf-approval-dollar-weakness"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T12:05:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With October around the corner, Bitcoin and Ethereum appear to be returning to better form.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ann Hirsch's 'Sacra Famiglia' Puts a Surreal AI Spin on Suburbia]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199099</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199099/ann-hirschs-sacra-famiglia-puts-surreal-ai-spin-suburbia"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T11:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artist Ann Hirsch's new web-browsing haunt "Sacra Famiglia" twists up family photos with the bizarre flourishes of generative AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cosmos Product Lead Says Ethereum Layer-2s Are Not the ‘Holy Grail’ of Scaling]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199312</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199312/cosmos-product-lead-says-ethereum-layer-2s-holy-grail-scaling"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T10:58:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Layer-2 networks are all the rage at the moment, but with user funds splintering across networks, the tech comes with its downsides.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[French Authorities Raid NVIDIA Offices Over Suspicions of Anti-Competitive Practices: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199310</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199310/french-authorities-raid-nvidia-offices-over-suspicions-anti-competitive-practices"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T10:46:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[French authorities have raided NVIDIA's offices in Paris and Nice as part of a wider probe into the firm's competitive practices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Real-World Passions Will Onboard the Next Wave of Crypto Adopters]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199155</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199155/real-world-passions-will-onboard-the-next-wave-of-crypto-adopters"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T09:34:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IRL experiences are key to on-chain identity and onboarding new users to the Web3 space, says MintPass founder Sam Simmons.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Delays Decision on Four Spot Bitcoin ETF Filings Ahead of Government Shutdown]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199305</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199305/sec-punts-four-spot-bitcoin-etf-filing-ahead-government-shutdown"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T09:15:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC's latest move is the second round of delays on the various spot Bitcoin ETF applications filed this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Musée d’Orsay Embraces NFTs in Push to Reach New Audiences]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199278</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199278/musee-dorsay-embraces-nfts-push-reach-new-audiences"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T06:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The French art museum announced a partnership with the Tezos Foundation that will bring its collections into conversation with on-chain digital artists and blockchain-backed experiences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Republican FCC Commissioner Calls Renewed Net Neutrality Push 'Unlawful']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199253</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199253/republican-fcc-commissioner-calls-renewed-net-neutrality-push-unlawful"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T00:31:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Digital rights group the Electronic Frontier Foundation praised the FCC’s move, emphasizing fair treatment of all data and warning against ISPs becoming gatekeepers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xbox Chat Was Used to Share Insider Trading Secrets, Says SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199252</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199252/xbox-chat-used-share-insider-trading-secrets-says-sec"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T00:16:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. regulator alleged that participants of an insider trading scheme used Xbox audio chat to share info, netting thousands in profits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Like We Were Talking in Person': Zuckerberg’s Metaverse Is Coming to Life]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199263</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199263/metaverse-zuckerberg-lex-fridman-future-ai-ultra-realistic-avatars"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T23:18:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mark Zuckerberg and Lex Fridman did a podcast on AI entirely in the metaverse—and we’ve come a long way from Meta’s legless avatars.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain Is 'Only Way' Forward for Gaming, Says Shrapnel Studio Head]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/fhoy7Z8f/blockchain-is-only-way-forward-for-gaming-says-shrapnel-studio-head</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/fhoy7Z8f/blockchain-is-only-way-forward-for-gaming-says-shrapnel-studio-head"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T21:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shrapnel Studio Head Don Norbury tells Kate Irwin the reasons why the upcoming first-person shooter game will offer a wide range of NFTs. He also reveals team-based gameplay plans and shares how game maps have already changed this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fortress CEO Responds to Ripple Backing Out of Acquisition]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199250</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199250/fortress-ceo-responds-to-ripple-backing-out-of-acquisition"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T21:13:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fortress CEO Scott Purcell said Ripple wants to stick with its current B2B focus.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Epic Games Is Jacking Up the Price of Fortnite V-Bucks]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199236</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199236/epic-games-jacking-up-price-fortnite-v-bucks"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T19:59:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alongside layoffs, Epic Games is also raising the price of Fortnite’s in-game currency, citing inflation and currency shifts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These Paris Fashion Week Outfits Transform Under Ultraviolet Light]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199218</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199218/anrealage-paris-fashion-week-outfits-transform-under-ultraviolet-light"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T19:13:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anrealage delivered a head-turning runway at Paris Fashion Week, spotlighting designer Kunihiko Morinaga's latest color-changing outfits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephanie Hirschmiller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gemini Calls Description of $218 Million Genesis Withdrawal ‘Pure Fantasy’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199204</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199204/gemini-calls-description-of-218-million-genesis-withdrawal-pure-fantasy"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T18:08:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gemini described the withdrawal as an attempt to bulk up Gemini Earn’s liquidity reserves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried Trial: All the Names You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=198989</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/198989/sam-bankman-fried-trial-all-the-names-you-need-to-know"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T17:39:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These are the big players you should know before tuning into Sam Bankman-Fried's trial next week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fortnite Maker Epic Games Cuts 830 Staff as CEO Calls Layoffs 'Only Way']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199202</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199202/fortnite-maker-epic-games-cuts-830-staff-ceo-calls-layoffs-only-way"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T17:19:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Epic CEO Tim Sweeney said the Fortnite studio is going through “a major structural change” due to tighter margins and new revenue models.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Futures ETF to Begin Trading as Rumors Swirl of Accelerated SEC Approvals]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199178</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199178/ethereum-futures-etf-to-begin-trading-as-rumors-swirl-of-accelerated-sec-approvals"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T16:36:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first launch of an Ethereum ETF in the United States appears imminent, but VanEck didn't provide a specific date.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IYK Raises $16.8 Million to Power Token-Enabled Fashion With NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199165</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199165/iyk-raises-16-8-million-power-token-enabled-fashion-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T16:01:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After working with Adidas, 9dcc, and more, IYK has launched a self-serve platform for creating NFC-chipped products.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Are Crypto Futures, Coinbase's Latest Offering?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=41419</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-are-bitcoin-futures-how-do-they-work"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T14:37:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Futures contracts have a long and storied history—but for Bitcoin traders, they’ve unlocked new strategies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Stevens,Scott Chipolina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Rolls Out Futures Trading for Retail Crypto Traders Globally]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199098</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199098/coinbase-rolls-out-futures-trading-retail-crypto-traders-globally"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T13:53:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto exchange has set its sights on global expansion amid ongoing legal challenges from the SEC in the U.S.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Chief Says Former Russia Unit CommEx 'Does Not Service US or EU Users']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199093</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199093/binance-chief-says-former-russia-unit-commex-does-not-service-us-eu-users"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T11:24:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As part of the recent sale, Binance CEO said that “a few ex-Binance CIS team members” may join the CommEx team.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Extends Deadline for Ark Invest, VanEck Spot Ethereum ETF Filings]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199090</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199090/sec-extends-deadline-ark-invest-vaneck-spot-ethereum-etf-filings"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T10:21:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Though VanEck and Ark Invest have been hit with delays, a futures-based ETF could see approval by next week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Price for Your Money? Liberty, Security, and CBDCs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=198753</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/198753/what-price-for-your-money-liberty-security-and-cbdcs"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T10:12:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CBDCs promise to energise economic growth through greater efficiency and security—at the cost of enshrining fiat’s dominance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Dob</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Social Media Sentiment Is Key to Crypto Price Discovery]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/981TBppa/social-media-sentiment-is-key-to-crypto-price-discovery</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/981TBppa/social-media-sentiment-is-key-to-crypto-price-discovery"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T23:47:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sacha Ghebali, Director of Strategy and Business Development at The TIE, says social media sentiment remains a key factor in price movements for major cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin and Ethereum. However, he notes that sentiment has turned more negative lately amid regulatory uncertainty. Ghebali believes events like the Ripple lawsuit ruling significantly impacted sentiment and prices. André Beganski interviewed him at Messari Mainnet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[500Altcoins discusses DeFi Summer and the Dubai Crypto Scene - This Time Will Be Different - Episode 2]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cI7p8AK3/500altcoins-discusses-defi-summer-and-the-dubai-crypto-scene-this-time-will-be-different-episode-2</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cI7p8AK3/500altcoins-discusses-defi-summer-and-the-dubai-crypto-scene-this-time-will-be-different-episode-2"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our host Reza Jafery is joined by Gareth Fenney aka 500Altcoins. They discuss the glory days of DeFi Summer and whether or not its a smart move for builders in the crypto space to relocate to Dubai.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralize Derivatives Trading with Custom Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/lfmwAjB9/decentralize-derivatives-trading-with-custom-blockchain</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/lfmwAjB9/decentralize-derivatives-trading-with-custom-blockchain"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T10:37:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Gogel of dYdX discusses how the decentralized exchange is building a custom blockchain to fully decentralize derivatives trading. He explained how the new dYdX chain will allow validators to run order books in memory, enabling decentralized order matching at scale. This shift aims to increase security and transparency for traders while maintaining the performance of centralized exchanges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[India's 1% Crypto Tax Has Been a Nightmare for High-Frequency Traders, Says Shardeum CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/fxygwLvH/indias-1-crypto-tax-has-been-a-nightmare-for-high-frequency-traders-says-shardeum-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/fxygwLvH/indias-1-crypto-tax-has-been-a-nightmare-for-high-frequency-traders-says-shardeum-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As India figures out its regulatory approach to the crypto industry, one thing is clear to Shardeum co-founder Nischal Shetty: “If you're a high-frequency trader, you can't afford to lose a percentage every time you sell,” he told Decrypt's Andre Beganski at Messari Mainnet in New York. “That's something that's caused a lot of issues.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Newly Partnered with Visa, Solana Focuses on Reliability]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/MZoxvulr/newly-partnered-with-visa-solana-focuses-on-reliability</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/MZoxvulr/newly-partnered-with-visa-solana-focuses-on-reliability"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana has improved network reliability through upgrades like Quick and local fee markets. It recently partnered with Visa to allow settling transactions in USDC on Solana. This could enable merchants to receive instant payments and save on credit card processing fees. Stacy Elliott spoke with Austin Federa, Head of Strategy for the Solana Foundation, at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Accounting Challenges and Opportunities]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/0Sezz6pZ/crypto-accounting-challenges-and-opportunities</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/0Sezz6pZ/crypto-accounting-challenges-and-opportunities"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As crypto matures, accounting and tax regulations are evolving. Amy Kalnoki of Bitwave explains how her company helps crypto companies properly account for digital assets. She notes the importance of flexibility as new crypto assets emerge and regulations change. Stacy Elliott interviewed her at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Most Crypto Users Don't Trust Themselves to Keep Their Seed Phrase Safe: Ledger CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/0kYf2Qed/most-crypto-users-dont-trust-themselves-to-keep-their-seed-phrase-safe-ledger-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/0kYf2Qed/most-crypto-users-dont-trust-themselves-to-keep-their-seed-phrase-safe-ledger-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Stacy Elliott sat down with Ledger CEO Pascal Gauthier to discuss crypto custody post-FTX, and the hardware wallet manufacturer's controversial Ledger Recover service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Base as a 'Bridge, Not an Island']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/oZPr7bzY/base-as-a-bridge-not-an-island</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/oZPr7bzY/base-as-a-bridge-not-an-island"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase's Jesse Pollak, creator of layer-2 blockchain Base, says the launch of the network has exceeded expectations, even if plans changed along the way. He believes Arbitrum One will help bring billions onto blockchain by enabling seamless user experiences. Stacy Elliott interviewed him at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Explosive Growth Ahead for Enterprise Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/xXOrNbX9/explosive-growth-ahead-for-enterprise-blockchain</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/xXOrNbX9/explosive-growth-ahead-for-enterprise-blockchain"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paul Brody drives Ernst & Young (EY) initiatives and investments in blockchain technology across consulting, audit, and tax business lines. He says enterprise blockchain adoption is nearing an inflection point. Brody believes blockchains will one day handle 40 billion transactions daily across industries like automotive and pharma. Stacy Elliott interviewed him at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Developer-Friendly zkRollup to Scale Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/OvAFgxTd/building-a-developer-friendly-zkrollup-to-scale-ethereum</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/OvAFgxTd/building-a-developer-friendly-zkrollup-to-scale-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daniel Helm, head of Developer Relations at Scroll, discussess how they are building a zkRollup to scale Ethereum transactions and lower fees. He explained their focus on creating a seamless developer experience by maintaining Ethereum's ethos and tooling. Scroll aims to launch their mainnet soon, providing more scalable blockspace for Ethereum developers. Stacy Elliott of Decrypt interviewed him at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Regulation Threatens U.S. Dominance of Financial Markets, Says CoinRoutes CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/CrpvzFjL/regulation-threatens-us-dominance-of-financial-markets-says-coinroutes-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/CrpvzFjL/regulation-threatens-us-dominance-of-financial-markets-says-coinroutes-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dave Weisberger, Co-Founder and CEO of CoinRoutes, argued that excessive regulation in the U.S. threatens to undermine the country's long-standing dominance in global financial markets. He warned that other countries are embracing blockchain and crypto to build more efficient digital markets, which could cause the US to lose its competitive edge and trillions in GDP. Weisberger said CoinRoutes is now focusing more on expanding internationally due to restrictive policies in the U.S. He was interviewed by André Beganski of Decrypt at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin's Narrative Is Shifting Towards Layer-2 Solutions]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/axArPRp3/bitcoins-narrative-is-shifting-towards-layer-2-solutions</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/axArPRp3/bitcoins-narrative-is-shifting-towards-layer-2-solutions"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rich Rines, original Core DAO contributor and former Coinbase engineer, discusses how the narrative around Bitcoin is shifting in 2023. While Bitcoin remains digital gold, new layer 2 solutions are emerging to unlock more utility and value from the huge amounts of capital stored in Bitcoin. He says these innovations can benefit Bitcoin holders while keeping Bitcoin maximalists happy by building outside the base layer. André Beganski interviewed him at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Need to Start Thinking About How we Make Crypto Easy to Use: Robinhood Crypto General Manager]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PLZ0FpdC/we-need-to-start-thinking-about-how-we-make-crypto-easy-to-use-robinhood-crypto-general-manager</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PLZ0FpdC/we-need-to-start-thinking-about-how-we-make-crypto-easy-to-use-robinhood-crypto-general-manager"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Stacy Elliott sat down with Robinhood Crypto general manager Johann Kerbrat at Messari Mainnet 2023, to talk about the trading platform's crypto wallet, onboarding new users through simplicity, and keeping platform fees sustainable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On-Chain Gaming Poised for Mass Adoption]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/6ZryETKh/on-chain-gaming-poised-for-mass-adoption</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/6ZryETKh/on-chain-gaming-poised-for-mass-adoption"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T02:23:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jack O'Holleran is CEO and co-founder of SKALE Labs. He explains how on-chain gaming is ready for the mainstream after overcoming early challenges like high fees and poor user experience. Companies can now build blockchain games that look and feel like traditional games, and scalability improvements allow games to support hundreds of millions of players without performance issues. He was interviewed by André Beganski at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Blockchains Boom Creates Opportunity and Challenges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/7Ys4Rxay/new-blockchains-boom-creates-opportunity-and-challenges</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/7Ys4Rxay/new-blockchains-boom-creates-opportunity-and-challenges"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T02:07:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Billy Sebell of the XDC Foundation discussed the proliferation of new layer-1 and layer-2 blockchain solutions. While this expands possibilities, he noted projects must still attract users amidst growing competition. Sebell highlighted the benefits of targeting niche use cases and bringing real-world assets on-chain via tokenization. He was interviewed by André Beganski of Decrypt at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accessible Self-Custody for Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/kA1Bqu4H/accessible-self-custody-for-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/kA1Bqu4H/accessible-self-custody-for-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T00:52:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dave Lemke is the CFO & CCO at Giddy, creators of a crypto wallet with decentralized private key security. He explains how their solution allows self-custody while still being recoverable. He highlighted increasing demand for self-custody after the FTX collapse. Lemke also touched on upcoming US crypto regulations and Getty's roadmap to simplify staking and other complex processes. Stacy Elliott interviewed him at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defi Education Fund Advocates for Responsible Crypto Regulation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/xD0CzPUF/defi-education-fund-advocates-for-responsible-crypto-regulation</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/xD0CzPUF/defi-education-fund-advocates-for-responsible-crypto-regulation"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T00:32:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amanda Tuminelli of the Defi Education Fund discusses the need for sensible crypto regulation. She says regulators should work with the industry to understand how protocols work before proposing expansive rules that could stifle innovation. Stacy Elliott of Decrypt interviewed her at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Train Your Own AI-Powered Fighter? Inside AI Arena]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qTBh0ayt/train-your-own-ai-powered-fighter-inside-ai-arena</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qTBh0ayt/train-your-own-ai-powered-fighter-inside-ai-arena"/>
        <updated>2023-09-25T20:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is AI Arena? Decrypt's Kate Irwin dives into the upcoming video game in an interview with the game's founders, AI Arena CEO Brandon Da Silva and COO Wei Xie.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>