<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-07-29T08:16:17.857Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-07-29T08:16:17.857Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[European AI Regulations Spark Debate]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18804139/European-AI-Regulations-Spark-Debate</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18804139/European-AI-Regulations-Spark-Debate"/>
        <updated>2023-07-29T08:10:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The European Commission’s proposal for the Artificial Intelligence Act (AI Act) has undergone extensive negotiations...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Japan Blockchain Association requests crypto tax revision: CoinPost]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18804138/Japan-Blockchain-Association-requests-crypto-tax-revision-CoinPost</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18804138/Japan-Blockchain-Association-requests-crypto-tax-revision-CoinPost"/>
        <updated>2023-07-29T08:04:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JBA claimed that its review of the current tax system indicates that the growth of web3 business in Japan is hindered.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prominent Analyst Claims The Bear Market Is Nearing An End In This Altcoin Group!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18804122/Prominent-Analyst-Claims-The-Bear-Market-Is-Nearing-An-End-In-This-Altcoin-Group</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18804122/Prominent-Analyst-Claims-The-Bear-Market-Is-Nearing-An-End-In-This-Altcoin-Group"/>
        <updated>2023-07-29T07:52:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The founder of the crypto analysis company said in his statement that the bear market in an altcoin group is about to end. Continue Reading: Prominent Analyst Claims The Bear Market Is Nearing An End In This Altcoin Group!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$XRP: Japanese Financial Giant Plans to Use Ripple’s XRP-Powered ODL Product for Remittances]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18804117/XRP-Japanese-Financial-Giant-Plans-to-Use-Ripples-XRP-Powered-ODL-Product-for-Remittances</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18804117/XRP-Japanese-Financial-Giant-Plans-to-Use-Ripples-XRP-Powered-ODL-Product-for-Remittances"/>
        <updated>2023-07-29T07:50:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent webinar, SBI VC Trade, the cryptocurrency exchange arm of Japan’s financial giant SBI Group, reportedly unveiled its plans for Ripple’s On-Demand Liquidity (ODL) product in Japan. The company intends to use XRP for cross-border payments. According to an article by Albert Brown for...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin Under The Lens: French Regulator Suspects Dubious Data Handling Practices]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756415f0c2</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/worldcoin-under-the-lens-french-regulator/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-29T07:45:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin, the brainchild of ChatGPT founder Sam Altman, is being examined by European regulators because of concerns about the legality of its biometric data collection tactics. The French privacy authority, CNIL, has expressed worries about the project, claiming that gathering and storing biometric data is questionable.
 
Furthermore, CNIL is not comfortable about the conditions under which such sensitive information is handled. The British data regulator has also launched inquiries into the project.
 
 
Worldcoin: Rapid Adoption And Initial Launch Success
 
Since its launch on June 24, the project has required users to provide iris scans in exchange for a digital ID and, in some countries, free cryptocurrency. The project’s website boasts about signing up 2.1 million individuals, with m…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yuna Rin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin Under The Lens: French Regulator Suspects Dubious Data Handling Practices]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18804108/Worldcoin-Under-The-Lens-French-Regulator-Suspects-Dubious-Data-Handling-Practices</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18804108/Worldcoin-Under-The-Lens-French-Regulator-Suspects-Dubious-Data-Handling-Practices"/>
        <updated>2023-07-29T07:40:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin, the brainchild of ChatGPT founder Sam Altman, is being examined by European regulators because of concerns about the legality of its biometric data collection tactics. The French privacy authority, CNIL, has expressed worries about the project, claiming that gathering and storing...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$SHIB and $DOGE Shine: Santiment’s Bullish Observations in a Week of Crypto Movements]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18804104/SHIB-and-DOGE-Shine-Santiments-Bullish-Observations-in-a-Week-of-Crypto-Movements</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18804104/SHIB-and-DOGE-Shine-Santiments-Bullish-Observations-in-a-Week-of-Crypto-Movements"/>
        <updated>2023-07-29T07:26:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The past week has been a rollercoaster ride of intriguing developments. Let’s take a chronological journey through the insights the crypto analytics firm, Santiment provided. On July 25, 2023, Santiment noted a significant Dogecoin (DOGE) milestone. The meme coin had seen a price surge of 25%...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Prices Dip as U.S. Economic Data Fails to Spark Rally]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18804098/Bitcoin-Prices-Dip-as-US-Economic-Data-Fails-to-Spark-Rally</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18804098/Bitcoin-Prices-Dip-as-US-Economic-Data-Fails-to-Spark-Rally"/>
        <updated>2023-07-29T07:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) experienced a pullback on July 27, erasing the gains from the previous day,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin Adoption Said to Be Accelerating; Sam Altman States ‘One Person Getting Verified Every 8 Seconds’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7564106d37</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/worldcoin-adoption-said-to-be-accelerating-sam-altman-states-one-person-getting-verified-every-8-seconds/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-29T07:13:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin, the digital ID passport and universal basic income project, is allegedly rising in popularity, with thousands of people said to be signing up and registering. According to Sam Altman, co-founder of the project, one person is currently verified by the iris scanning devices — the “Orb” — every 8 seconds. However, some data could call these claims into question. 
Worldcoin Operations Allegedly Ramping Up, One Person Getting Verified Every 8 Seconds
Worldcoin, a project that aims to become a digital decentralized ID that will serve to deploy a Universal Basic Income (UBI) system with Sybil protections, is seeing more interest from potential users, according to statements from its team.
The project launched officially on July 24 after more than three years of development, and it is c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Indian Supreme Court pushing Union government for clear crypto regulation: report]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18804090/Indian-Supreme-Court-pushing-Union-government-for-clear-crypto-regulation-report</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18804090/Indian-Supreme-Court-pushing-Union-government-for-clear-crypto-regulation-report"/>
        <updated>2023-07-29T07:12:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[India's Supreme Court has directed the government to record whether it intends to establish a federal agency to investigate crypto cases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Could Explode by Up to 1,556% in an AI-Powered Economy, Says Arthur Hayes – Here’s the Timeline]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18804086/Ethereum-Could-Explode-by-Up-to-1556-in-an-AI-Powered-Economy-Says-Arthur-Hayes-Heres-the-Timeline</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18804086/Ethereum-Could-Explode-by-Up-to-1556-in-an-AI-Powered-Economy-Says-Arthur-Hayes-Heres-the-Timeline"/>
        <updated>2023-07-29T07:04:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BitMEX co-founder Arthur Hayes says the price of Ethereum (ETH) stands to benefit immensely from artificial intelligence (AI) technology. Painting a scenario where AI applications create decentralized autonomous organizations (DAOs) in order to execute smart contracts, Hayes says in a new blog...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried surrenders Caroline Ellison’s personal writings to court]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18804082/Sam-Bankman-Fried-surrenders-Caroline-Ellisons-personal-writings-to-court</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18804082/Sam-Bankman-Fried-surrenders-Caroline-Ellisons-personal-writings-to-court"/>
        <updated>2023-07-29T07:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried’s legal team has provided the court with documents previously shown to news reporters, according to a July 27 filing. Bankman-Fried, who served as the CEO of FTX until its collapse, recently communicated with The New York Times. He provided the news outlet with the private...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US banking advocacy group supports Sen. Warren’s reintroduced crypto bill]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18804062/US-banking-advocacy-group-supports-Sen-Warrens-reintroduced-crypto-bill</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18804062/US-banking-advocacy-group-supports-Sen-Warrens-reintroduced-crypto-bill"/>
        <updated>2023-07-29T06:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to the Bank Policy Institute, the inclusion of digital assets in the anti-money laundering framework is essential to safeguard the United States' financial system and protect the nation from illicit finance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC, Binance unite against Eeon’s lawsuit intervention]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18804063/SEC-Binance-unite-against-Eeons-lawsuit-intervention</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18804063/SEC-Binance-unite-against-Eeons-lawsuit-intervention"/>
        <updated>2023-07-29T06:42:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. SEC claims that Eeon has a history of repeatedly unsuccessfully representing itself in court cases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US lawmakers share concerns Apple’s App Store is stifling blockchain innovation]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18804052/US-lawmakers-share-concerns-Apples-App-Store-is-stifling-blockchain-innovation</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18804052/US-lawmakers-share-concerns-Apples-App-Store-is-stifling-blockchain-innovation"/>
        <updated>2023-07-29T06:25:21.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Traders’ Interest In XRP Remains Solid Despite Price Retreat, Data Shows]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18804042/Traders-Interest-In-XRP-Remains-Solid-Despite-Price-Retreat-Data-Shows</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18804042/Traders-Interest-In-XRP-Remains-Solid-Despite-Price-Retreat-Data-Shows"/>
        <updated>2023-07-29T06:05:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The enduring allure of XRP, despite market volatility, may be evidence of its continued relevance, as it has continued to attract the interest of traders and investors equally. Even as the dust settles after Ripple’s recent victory jubilation, the cryptocurrency market remains keen on XRP....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arkham Intel: Unveiling the World’s First On-Chain Intelligence Exchange Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18804073/Arkham-Intel-Unveiling-the-Worlds-First-On-Chain-Intelligence-Exchange-Platform</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18804073/Arkham-Intel-Unveiling-the-Worlds-First-On-Chain-Intelligence-Exchange-Platform"/>
        <updated>2023-07-29T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This groundbreaking platform allows individuals to anonymously buy and sell information about the owners of specific blockchain wallet addresses]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitget and CoinTracking partnership simplifies calculation of crypto taxes]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18804072/Bitget-and-CoinTracking-partnership-simplifies-calculation-of-crypto-taxes</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18804072/Bitget-and-CoinTracking-partnership-simplifies-calculation-of-crypto-taxes"/>
        <updated>2023-07-29T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This partnership aims to simplify the tax experience for users around the world]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin trading: the optimal times for an hourly bar-based trend following strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18804070/Bitcoin-trading-the-optimal-times-for-an-hourly-bar-based-trend-following-strategy</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18804070/Bitcoin-trading-the-optimal-times-for-an-hourly-bar-based-trend-following-strategy"/>
        <updated>2023-07-29T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Specifically, we are going to look for the best time within the session to make trend following trades]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. National Debt Skyrockets: Economic Security at Stake, Warns Cato Institute]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18804039/US-National-Debt-Skyrockets-Economic-Security-at-Stake-Warns-Cato-Institute</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18804039/US-National-Debt-Skyrockets-Economic-Security-at-Stake-Warns-Cato-Institute"/>
        <updated>2023-07-29T05:58:39.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russian President Vladimir Putin Criticizes the ‘Use of the Dollar as a Political Weapon’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75641f11c1</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/russian-president-vladimir-putin-criticizes-the-use-of-the-dollar-as-a-political-weapon/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-29T05:40:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Russian President Vladimir Putin has railed against using the dollar as a political weapon in a meeting with the New Development Bank’s president, Dilma Rousseff. Putin stated that this weaponization and the recent developments in global finance complicated the institution’s growth to help third-world countries facing difficult conditions.
Russian President Vladimir Putin Talks Dollar Weaponization in Recent Meeting
Russian President Vladimir Putin referred to the weaponization of the dollar and its effects on the global economy in a recent meeting with Dilma Rousseff, president of the New Development Bank (NDB) — also known as the BRICS bank — during the second Russia-Africa Summit held in Saint Petersburg. Putin explained this weaponization complicated Rousseff’s task of growing and deve…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Tron maintain its bullish streak in Q3?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18804022/Will-Tron-maintain-its-bullish-streak-in-Q3</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18804022/Will-Tron-maintain-its-bullish-streak-in-Q3"/>
        <updated>2023-07-29T05:30:42.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale Calls on SEC to Approve All Spot Bitcoin ETFs Simultaneously]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18804016/Grayscale-Calls-on-SEC-to-Approve-All-Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-Simultaneously</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18804016/Grayscale-Calls-on-SEC-to-Approve-All-Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-Simultaneously"/>
        <updated>2023-07-29T05:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peru Tightens Crypto Laws, Mandates Exchanges To Comply With AML Regulations]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75641aeb46</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/peru-tightens-crypto-laws-mandates-exchanges-to-comply-with-aml-regulations/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-29T04:45:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a move to address growing concerns over money laundering and terrorist financing associated with cryptocurrencies, the Presidency of Peru has issued a new decree. The decree mandates that all cryptocurrency exchanges operating within the country must comply with anti-money laundering (AML) regulations. This development marks a significant step in the Peruvian government’s efforts to regulate the cryptocurrency ecosystem and safeguard its financial system from illicit activities.
 
Related Reading: Crypto.com Pushes Ahead Of Binance With Registration Approval In The Netherlands
 
Mandatory Disclosure Of Crypto Holdings For Service Providers 
 
According to the decree, virtual asset service providers, which include both individuals and companies operating within Peru, are now required to …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olowoporoku Adeniyi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US State of Minnesota Okays Crypto Donations to Political Campaign Committees]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7564075a0e</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/us-state-of-minnesota-okays-crypto-donations-to-political-campaign-committees/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-29T03:39:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Minnesota has become one of the few U.S. states to permit crypto donations to political campaign committees. However, according to the state’s new rules, crypto donations must be converted to U.S. dollars within five days. In the event of price changes within the five-day grace period, these must be shown separately in campaign finance reports.
 
Converting Crypto Donations to Dollars
 
The U.S. state of Minnesota has become one of the first states in the country to okay crypto donations to political campaign committees. Under the state’s new rules, which took effect in July 2023, recipients of crypto donations are nevertheless required to convert these to U.S. dollars within five days.
 
According to a report by Axios, the crypto contributions must be valued at the digital assets’ respect…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Lawmakers Advance ‘FIT for the 21st Century Act’ to Establish Crypto Framework]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75640f4818</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/us-lawmakers-advance-fit-for-the-21st-century-act-to-establish-crypto-framework/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-29T01:35:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. lawmakers have advanced the Financial Innovation and Technology (FIT) for the 21st Century Act that establishes a regulatory framework for the crypto market. “Our bill establishes clear principles to ensure financial security and certainty as digital asset developers continue to innovate,” a lawmaker explained.
 
FIT for the 21st Century Act Advances
 
U.S. lawmakers have advanced the Financial Innovation and Technology (FIT) for the 21st Century Act (H.R. 4763). On Wednesday, the House Financial Services Committee passed the bill, followed by the House Committee on Agriculture approving it on Thursday. The FIT for the 21st Century Act establishes a digital asset framework to provide regulatory certainty to the crypto market.
 
Reps. French Hill (R-AR), chairman of the Subcommittee on…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why These 3 Mid Cap Crypto Could Provide A Unique Opportunity For Short-Term Gains]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7565f6b22b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/3-mid-cap-crypto-could-provide-a-unique-opportunity/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T23:45:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the crypto market currently experiencing a bear trend, it has presented a good opportunity for investors to get into digital assets at a low price. However, not all coins offer the same level of opportunity, especially given their recent performance. So here are three mid-cap tokens that have the potential to provide the most upside in the short term.
 
Toncoin (TON) 
Toncoin (TON) is the brainchild of the founders of Telegram Nikolai and Pavel Durov, before they gifted the project to the community. Due to its close ties with Telegram, which is currently one of the largest messaging apps in the world, it has enjoyed a lot of success as it is very popular among the millions of users of Telegram.
 
 
TON has done especially well in the year 2023 with its numerous open-source projects. H…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Best Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bankruptcy Tussle Between Crypto Firms FTX and Genesis Nears Resolution]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7565f6f26f</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bankruptcy-tussle-between-crypto-firms-ftx-and-genesis-nears-resolution/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T23:41:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The long-standing legal feud between FTX Trading and Genesis Global Holdco is taking a turn towards resolution. The two parties have reached an initial agreement, in principle, following bankruptcy protection disputes that have made industry headlines. An official letter to the bankruptcy judge representing their cases has affirmed the intent of the firms to put their settlement into motion.
 
FTX, Genesis Engage in Crypto Bankruptcy Settlement
 
The saga, rooted in the insolvency of FTX Trading, began when the company claimed that Genesis, a crypto lending platform, owed them a sum of nearly $2 billion. This claim could have considerably slowed down Genesis’ court procedures. Now, with the letter to the presiding judge dated July 27, 2023, the path to settlement seems more tangible, promi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried's Attempts to Influence Witnesses Show He Must Be Jailed Before Trial: DOJ]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7565f7852b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/07/28/sam-bankman-frieds-attempts-to-influence-witnesses-show-he-must-be-jailed-before-trial-doj/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T23:33:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried's repeated efforts to contact witnesses and influence their testimony shows that "no combination of conditions will reasonably assure the safety of the community," prosecutors said in a written filing calling for his bond to be revoked.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ATPBot Launches the Easiest Automated Crypto Trading Bot for Investors]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7565f1ea7b</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/atpbot-launches-the-easiest-automated-crypto-trading-bot-for-investors/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T23:01:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. ATPBot, the renowned leader in quantitative trading strategy development, proudly introduces its revolutionary auto trading bot to the cryptocurrency market. This cutting-edge bot boasts a user-friendly interface and a proven set of features, designed to cater to both novice and seasoned traders alike.
 
ATPBot leverages the power of artificial intelligence to create and implement winning quantitative trading strategies. Supported by rigorously tested and proven methods, the bot offers meticulous backtest data, instilling investors with confidence in their trading endeavors.
 
The auto trading bot simplifies the complex trading landscape into just three steps: Connect, Select, Run! By connecting to a crypto exchange API, users can effortlessly choose a strategy and set the i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[69% of Meme Coin Investors Buy for Fun — Study Delves Into Investor Sentiments on Meme Coins]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7565f881e3</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/69-of-meme-coin-investors-buy-for-fun-study-delves-into-investor-sentiments-on-meme-coins/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T21:40:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study conducted in May 2023 sought to uncover insights, perspectives, and outlooks on meme coins from crypto investors around the world. The online survey of 1,503 participants aimed to gauge meme coins’ potential in the cryptocurrency market. It revealed several findings about investor sentiments, behaviors, and perceptions surrounding these unique digital assets.
 
Meme Coins: Gamble or Investment?
 
The study by chainplay.gg titled “State of Meme Coin” revealed a divide between investors who have purchased meme coins (63.9%) and those avoiding them (36.1%). Of the investors purchasing meme coins, a majority (69%) do it for fun. Yet, 79% still perceive them as long-term investments with the potential for profit, even though 70% suspect most meme coins are fraudulent. Additionally, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Hopes to Recharge Lagging Horizon Worlds Metaverse With New In-House Game Studio]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7565fbb7d4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/web3/2023/07/28/meta-hopes-to-recharge-lagging-horizon-worlds-metaverse-with-new-in-house-game-studio/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T21:05:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The struggling platform reported losses of $3.7 billion in the second quarter, though CEO Mark Zuckerberg remains "fully committed" to the metaverse and AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rosie Perper</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arbitrum DAO’s First Grants Programs Take Shape]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7565e616f6</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/07/28/arbitrum-daos-first-grants-programs-take-shape/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T20:39:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two governance proposals are collectively requesting nearly $5 million worth of ARB tokens to launch grants programs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sage D. Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[France Joins the UK to Question Sam Altman’s Worldcoin]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7565e7c86f</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/france-joins-the-uk-to-question-sam-altmans-worldcoin/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T20:20:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Days after  
the UK’s data regulator disclosed plans to inquire about Worldcoin,  
France’s privacy watchdog today (Friday) also confirmed that it is investigating the  
project. Worldcoin, a project created by Sam Altman, OpenAI’s CEO, requires  
users to scan their irises in exchange for digital currencies and free  
cryptocurrency. 
Worldcoin Raises Concern
The  
project’s token, the Worldcoin (WLD), went live on Binance on Monday, listing against  
Bitcoin and Tether, Finance Magnates reported. The token was created  
by Tools for Humanity, a company based in San Francisco and Berlin. 
The firm creates for users an account  
dubbed World ID after their identities are registered using an orb-shaped scanner. Furthermore, Worldcoin, which recently raised $115 million  
from a funding roun…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Solomon Oladipupo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Regulation Or Overreach? SEC’s Warning Draws Mixed Reactions]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7565e34443</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/peirce-slams-secs-move-to-target-crypto-auditors/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T19:44:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has issued a dire warning to accounting firms conducting audits in the crypto asset space.
 
In a statement released on July 27, SEC Chief Accountant Paul Munter expressed concerns about the potential for misleading information to be presented to investors through non-audit work, which he argued is not as rigorous or comprehensive as a financial statement audit. 
 
Munter warned accounting firms of the potential for legal liability if their clients make misleading statements about the nature of their services, which could lead to potential anti-fraud violations under federal securities laws.
 
SEC Warns Accounting Firms Of Hazards In Crypto Industry
 
The statement highlighted the hazards associated with accounting firms’ increasing engagemen…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin’s Launch Propels Optimism to Record-Breaking Daily Transaction Volume]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7565e3f822</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/worldcoins-launch-propels-optimism-to-record-breaking-daily-transaction-volume/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T19:37:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the recent launch of Worldcoin’s token, worldcoin (WLD), Optimism has experienced a surge in daily transactions, reaching an all-time high on July 27. Data reveals that 944,000 Optimism transactions were processed on Thursday, with WLD transfers closing in on 1 million.
 
WLD Token Arrival Spurs Transaction Surge on Optimism: New Milestone Reached
 
The Ethereum layer two (L2) network, Optimism, is reaping the benefits from Worldcoin’s (WLD) debut as the token integrated with the L2 blockchain before its introduction. As of 11:03 a.m. Eastern Time on Friday, archived records show that 285,527 distinct addresses possess WLD, and thus far, WLD has recorded 887,482 transactions. As a result, Optimism’s daily transfers have soared to new levels.
 
For example, according to Dune Analytics …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No, Sam Bankman-Fried Is Not Being Bailed Out By Democrats]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7565ec5d12</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/07/28/no-sam-bankman-fried-is-not-being-bailed-out-by-democrats/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T19:33:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Republican candidate Vivek Rameswamy is rightly furious over dropped campaign finance charges. But the charges are likely to return after a procedural adjustment - and claims of corruption do more harm than good.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Z. Morris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried Maybe Hasn’t Escaped Campaign Finance Charges]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7565ee7e77</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/07/28/sam-bankman-fried-maybe-hasnt-escaped-campaign-finance-charges/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T19:12:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prosecutors just withdrew a campaign finance charge ahead of Sam Bankman-Fried’s criminal trial this October. That doesn’t mean the U.S. Department of Justice is letting the FTX founder off on alleged criminal conduct, however – and campaign finance charges could still be tried later.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘We’re Compute Cowboys’: Gideon Powell on the Pioneer Spirit Driving Bitcoin Mining]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7565e8a76b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/07/28/were-compute-cowboys-gideon-powell-on-the-pioneer-spirit-driving-bitcoin-mining/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T18:51:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An interview with the CEO of Cholla Inc., an oil & gas exploration company that’s investing in bitcoin mining.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Kuhn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aliens Exist. And They Use Cryptocurrency]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7565e8a845</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/07/28/aliens-exist-and-they-use-cryptocurrency/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T18:51:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few thoughts on government lies, the purpose of crypto and where technology can take us following a congressional hearing on inexplicable aerial phenomena.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Kuhn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Com2uS Is Going "Full Speed" on Crypto Gaming: Kyu Lee]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pYMZRoYy/com2us-is-going-full-speed-on-crypto-gaming-kyu-lee</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pYMZRoYy/com2us-is-going-full-speed-on-crypto-gaming-kyu-lee"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kyu Lee is the President of game studio Com2uS USA. In an interview, he shares the studio's approach to Web3 and crypto gaming with Decrypt GG's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Discord Game with AI and Blockchain: 'Alchemy: Battle for Ankhos' Creative Lead Alex Finden]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mF18GHGo/building-a-discord-game-with-ai-and-blockchain-alchemy-battle-for-ankhos-creative-lead-alex-finden</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mF18GHGo/building-a-discord-game-with-ai-and-blockchain-alchemy-battle-for-ankhos-creative-lead-alex-finden"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T21:55:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Jason Nelson interviews Alchemy: Battle for Ankhos Creative Director Alex Finden at the Solana PlayGG event in San Diego, California.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Big Respect Between Ethereum and Cosmos Developer Communities': dYdX Foundation CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/XU5MbCGE/big-respect-between-ethereum-and-cosmos-developer-communities-dydx-foundation-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/XU5MbCGE/big-respect-between-ethereum-and-cosmos-developer-communities-dydx-foundation-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T13:24:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CEO of the dYdX Foundation Charles d'Haussy unpacks the decision behind moving one of the largest decentralized exchange protocol's over to its very own chain built on Cosmos. A key driver, he told Decrypt at this year's EthCC event, was that instead of launching on a rollup or another layer-1, launching a fully customized chain will allow dYdX to fine tune the network for its product's needs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Staking Solution Lido 'Had Perfect Product Market Fit' at Launch, Says DAO's Biz Dev Contributor]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/fUHhelhV/ethereum-staking-solution-lido-had-perfect-product-market-fit-at-launch-says-daos-biz-dev-contributor</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/fUHhelhV/ethereum-staking-solution-lido-had-perfect-product-market-fit-at-launch-says-daos-biz-dev-contributor"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T08:43:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marin Tvrdić, a business development contributor to the Lido DAO, sat down with Decrypt during this year's EthCC to break down how the liquid staking protocol has managed such a massive lead, how it plans to keep that lead, and the protocol's new dual-governance tokenomics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's Going to Stop All the DeFi Hacks? 'Standards,' Says OpenZepplin Security Architect]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/aYNuFdAi/whats-going-to-stop-all-the-defi-hacks-standards-says-openzepplin-security-architect</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/aYNuFdAi/whats-going-to-stop-all-the-defi-hacks-standards-says-openzepplin-security-architect"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T08:04:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenZeppelin's security solutions architect Michael Lewellen sat down with Decrypt to discuss how the industry can become a little safer for users at this year's EthCC Paris. The key? Introducing security standards across the industry so folks know what an audit actually means and where risks lie, be it bad faith actors or poor implementation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Ev.io' Game Review: Earn Solana While Blasting Enemies]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/2ZmkuhL2/evio-game-review-earn-solana-while-blasting-enemies</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/2ZmkuhL2/evio-game-review-earn-solana-while-blasting-enemies"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T22:21:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ev.io is a web-based first-person shooter that's free to play, but lets NFT holders earn in-game currency that can be redeemed for Solana (SOL). Decrypt contributor Ryan Gladwin shares his review of the fun throwback to Quake-style blasting, albeit with a modern crypto twist.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Moving Fast and Breaking Things Isn't the Web3 Ethos': MetaMask Product Lead]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/l1EbLgl3/moving-fast-and-breaking-things-isnt-the-web3-ethos-metamask-product-lead</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/l1EbLgl3/moving-fast-and-breaking-things-isnt-the-web3-ethos-metamask-product-lead"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T15:45:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Account abstraction this, smart wallets that. Discussions at EthCC Paris about improving user experience have pointed at industry leader MetaMask as an example of what not to do. But that may soon change, with a host of updates and optimizations coming to crypto's number one wallet, said its product lead Alex Jupiter. It still may take some time, though, before these changes take effect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling Smart Wallets on Starknet 'Was The Winning Combination', Says Argent Co-Founder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/gnBsxw4D/scaling-smart-wallets-on-starknet-was-the-winning-combination-says-argent-co-founder</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/gnBsxw4D/scaling-smart-wallets-on-starknet-was-the-winning-combination-says-argent-co-founder"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T07:35:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Argent co-founder Julien Niset told Decrypt at EthCC Paris that he wants to make crypto wallets disappear. Or at least how they're currently conceived. From clunky seed phrases to a stiff user experience, Argent hopes to make using crypto a little less intimidating and a whole lot more fun.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Mighty Action Heroes' Open Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/litL6kKs/inside-mighty-action-heroes-open-beta</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/litL6kKs/inside-mighty-action-heroes-open-beta"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T18:23:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mighty Action Heroes is the flagship blockchain title from Mighty Bear Games. But is the browser-based battle royale shooter worth checking out? Decrypt's Kate Irwin offers her thoughts and a first look at the upcoming game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dr. Disrespect's 'Deadrop': Early Access Gameplay From Snapshot VI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/8l21EHoa/dr-disrespects-deadrop-early-access-gameplay-from-snapshot-vi</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/8l21EHoa/dr-disrespects-deadrop-early-access-gameplay-from-snapshot-vi"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T18:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin playtests Dr. Disrespect and Midnight Society's first-person shooter Deadrop and shares the latest game updates, as well as her opinions on the game in development. Currently, Deadrop offers Polygon Founders Pass NFTs with no other crypto plans revealed just yet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['More and More' Game Publishers Will Embrace NFTs: Mythical Games CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/wBWogSkl/more-and-more-game-publishers-will-embrace-nfts-mythical-games-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/wBWogSkl/more-and-more-game-publishers-will-embrace-nfts-mythical-games-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T22:28:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the wake of EA Sports and Fortnite creator Epic Games embracing Nike's NFT platform, Mythical Games CEO John Linden tells Decrypt's Andrew Hayward how quickly he expects to see more major traditional game publishers enter the blockchain space and how quickly the industry will scale.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gran Saga Unlimited Early Access: Inside the Anime MMORPG on Aptos]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JeFWMVwo/gran-saga-unlimited-early-access-inside-the-anime-mmorpg-on-aptos</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JeFWMVwo/gran-saga-unlimited-early-access-inside-the-anime-mmorpg-on-aptos"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T21:46:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin plays Gran Saga: Unlimited's second community playtest, reports her findings, and offers her opinion and insights on the upcoming game, which will offer optional Aptos NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[100 Thieves' Moe Says Blockchain Games Will 'Eventually' Be Accepted by Livestreamers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/xHhh62ID/100-thieves-moe-says-blockchain-games-will-eventually-be-accepted-by-livestreamers</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/xHhh62ID/100-thieves-moe-says-blockchain-games-will-eventually-be-accepted-by-livestreamers"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T16:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[100 Thieves content creator and gamer Moe also goes by "Yassuo" online after his favorite League of Legends character. Decrypt's Kate Irwin asks him about 100 Thieves' future crypto plans and whether Moe thinks creators like xQc and Pokimane might ever come around to blockchain games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Games of the Future Are Going to Be Different," Says Splinterlands Cofounder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/sQv6zcil/games-of-the-future-are-going-to-be-different-says-splinterlands-cofounder</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/sQv6zcil/games-of-the-future-are-going-to-be-different-says-splinterlands-cofounder"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T20:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Splinterlands Cofounder Matt Rosen tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about how the game has evolved over its five-year history and why he doesn't listen to the FUD around crypto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Champions Ascension: Like 'For Honor' with NFTs?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/gvM9ajww/inside-champions-ascension-like-for-honor-with-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/gvM9ajww/inside-champions-ascension-like-for-honor-with-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T22:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plai Labs Marketing Director Payton Kaleiwahea tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about player response to the combat game Champions Ascension in development, which offers arena combat, raid bosses, AI landscape features, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Activision VP Michael Lee: Gaming Is Crypto's 'Killer App']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/M9ulXrb3/ex-activision-vp-michael-lee-gaming-is-cryptos-killer-app</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/M9ulXrb3/ex-activision-vp-michael-lee-gaming-is-cryptos-killer-app"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Activision Vice President Michael Lee is now the SVP of Growth at Matter Labs. At the 3XP gaming conference, Lee sat down with Decrypt's Kate Irwin to discuss crypto gaming and give his predictions for the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Behind the Scenes with AMGI Studios and My Pet Hooligan]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/eQ71oapI/behind-the-scenes-with-amgi-studios-and-my-pet-hooligan</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/eQ71oapI/behind-the-scenes-with-amgi-studios-and-my-pet-hooligan"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T21:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin goes to Burbank, California for a behind-the-scenes tour of AMGI Studios, the developers of upcoming game My Pet Hooligan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Legend of Arcadia Chose Sui Over EVM Chains]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/H6JSRJIk/why-legend-of-arcadia-chose-sui-over-evm-chains</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/H6JSRJIk/why-legend-of-arcadia-chose-sui-over-evm-chains"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T21:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Legend of Arcadia Executive Producer Andy Lee tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the game and why they switched from EVM to new protocol Sui.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>