<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-09-07T03:14:32.809Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-09-07T03:14:32.809Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum, Dogecoin Stagnant Amid Dollar's Unnerving Rise — Analyst Tells Investors 'Just Survive This Month' And Then Things Will Be Fine]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18885332/Bitcoin-Ethereum-Dogecoin-Stagnant-Amid-Dollars-Unnerving-Rise-Analyst-Tells-Investors-Just-Survive-This-Month-And-Then-Things-Will-Be-Fine</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18885332/Bitcoin-Ethereum-Dogecoin-Stagnant-Amid-Dollars-Unnerving-Rise-Analyst-Tells-Investors-Just-Survive-This-Month-And-Then-Things-Will-Be-Fine"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T02:51:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum and Dogecoin were seen largely flat on Tuesday evening as the global cryptocurrency market cap inched up 0.4% to $1.04 trillion at the time of publishing. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bulls Continues To Struggle, Here’s Why Upsides Could Be Limited]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18885316/Bitcoin-Bulls-Continues-To-Struggle-Heres-Why-Upsides-Could-Be-Limited</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18885316/Bitcoin-Bulls-Continues-To-Struggle-Heres-Why-Upsides-Could-Be-Limited"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T02:48:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin price is still consolidating above $25,500. BTC might attempt an upside correction, but upsides might be limited above the $26,200 resistance. Bitcoin is still trading in a range above the $25,500 support zone. The price is trading below $26,000 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google To Update Crypto Advertising Policy, These NFT Games Are Big Winners]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18885309/Google-To-Update-Crypto-Advertising-Policy-These-NFT-Games-Are-Big-Winners</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18885309/Google-To-Update-Crypto-Advertising-Policy-These-NFT-Games-Are-Big-Winners"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T02:30:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google, the world’s most popular search engine and tech company, plans to update its cryptocurrency advertisement policy in September 2023. The tech giant intends to clarify “the scope and requirements for the advertisement of blockchain-based games involving non-fungible tokens (NFTs).”...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No bounce for Ether after Ark Invest files for first US spot Ether ETF]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18885286/No-bounce-for-Ether-after-Ark-Invest-files-for-first-US-spot-Ether-ETF</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18885286/No-bounce-for-Ether-after-Ark-Invest-files-for-first-US-spot-Ether-ETF"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T02:08:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin traded flat Wednesday morning in Asia below the resistance level of US$26,000. Ether also traded flat, hovering around US$1,600.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Whales Buy Over $400 Million Worth of $ETH in One Day as Crypto Market Dips]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18885285/Ethereum-Whales-Buy-Over-400-Million-Worth-of-ETH-in-One-Day-as-Crypto-Market-Dips</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18885285/Ethereum-Whales-Buy-Over-400-Million-Worth-of-ETH-in-One-Day-as-Crypto-Market-Dips"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T01:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VanEck, ARK filings ‘officially’ start clock for spot Ethereum ETFs: Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18885275/VanEck-ARK-filings-officially-start-clock-for-spot-Ethereum-ETFs-Analyst</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18885275/VanEck-ARK-filings-officially-start-clock-for-spot-Ethereum-ETFs-Analyst"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T01:54:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bloomberg ETF analyst James Seyffart expects more spot Ethereum ETFs to be filed in the coming days.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Schiff Says US Can’t Afford to Decouple From China — Warns of Dollar Collapse]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754fe68716</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/peter-schiff-says-us-cant-afford-to-decouple-from-china-warns-of-dollar-collapse/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T01:35:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Economist Peter Schiff has warned that the U.S. cannot afford to decouple from China. “Our entire standard of living rests on the support of China,” he stressed, adding that “If we lose that support, it’s going to collapse.” He also predicted the collapse of the U.S. dollar as the USD loses its world’s reserve currency status.
 
Peter Schiff on US-China Decoupling, Dollar Collapse
 
Economist and gold bug Peter Schiff discussed various economic topics, including the relationship between the U.S. and China, in an interview with NTD News last week.
 
Commenting on the recent statement by Commerce Secretary Gina Raimondo stating that “Decoupling is neither in our economic or national security goals,” Schiff stressed:
 

We can’t afford to decouple because you have to recognize that China is b…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum: Is this the right time to stake ETH?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18885264/Ethereum-Is-this-the-right-time-to-stake-ETH</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18885264/Ethereum-Is-this-the-right-time-to-stake-ETH"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T01:30:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since Ethereum's move to PoS, many validators have hopped on the staking train. But does staking ETH now sound like a good decision?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Whales Buy $425M In ETH Inside 24 Hours, Rebound Soon?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754fe00cd2</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-whales-buy-425m-eth-inside-24-rebound/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T01:19:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data shows the Ethereum whales have recently gone on a $425 million shopping spree, a sign that could be positive for the asset.
 
Ethereum Whales Have Participated In Accumulation Recently
 
As pointed out by analyst Ali in a post on X, the ETH whales have made some big purchases recently. The relevant indicator here is the “ETH Supply Distribution,” which tracks the total supply amount each investor group holds.
 
Investors or addresses are divided into these groups based on the total number of tokens they carry in their balance. For instance, the 1 to 10 coins cohort includes all investors holding at least 1 and at most 10 ETH.
 
In the context of the current discussion, the group of interest is that of the whales. The wallet range of these humongous holders can be assumed to b…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hououin Kyouma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nayib Bukele has the HIGHEST approval rating in the world!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18885252/Nayib-Bukele-has-the-HIGHEST-approval-rating-in-the-world</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18885252/Nayib-Bukele-has-the-HIGHEST-approval-rating-in-the-world"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T01:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maybe he is a good reason to move to El Salvador? Let us know in the comments below!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Whales Buy $425M In ETH Inside 24 Hours, Rebound Soon?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18885241/Ethereum-Whales-Buy-425M-In-ETH-Inside-24-Hours-Rebound-Soon</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18885241/Ethereum-Whales-Buy-425M-In-ETH-Inside-24-Hours-Rebound-Soon"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T01:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data shows the Ethereum whales have recently gone on a $425 million shopping spree, a sign that could be positive for the asset. Ethereum Whales Have Participated In Accumulation Recently As pointed out by analyst Ali in a post on X, the ETH whales have made some big purchases recently....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Korean finance giant links up with Polygon Labs on tokenized securities]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18885234/Korean-finance-giant-links-up-with-Polygon-Labs-on-tokenized-securities</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18885234/Korean-finance-giant-links-up-with-Polygon-Labs-on-tokenized-securities"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T01:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mirae Asset Securities looks to advance tokenization within finance, and South Korea, through a partnership with the Ethereum scaling architecture builder]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Standards Board Approves Long-Sought Change in Crypto Accounting Rules]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155244</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155244/bitcoin-digital-assets-accounting-standards-gaap-fasb-sec"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T00:58:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new rules on how digital assets are reflected in business financial reporting will not include NFTs or wrapped tokens.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt AI, Edited by Ryan Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Only 2 Altcoins Crypto Investors Need BEFORE 2025 Bull Run]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18885232/The-Only-2-Altcoins-Crypto-Investors-Need-BEFORE-2025-Bull-Run</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18885232/The-Only-2-Altcoins-Crypto-Investors-Need-BEFORE-2025-Bull-Run"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T00:30:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DescriptionManage Your Crypto Portfolio with Regular Updates and Top Insights for only $15/ month.Hot WEB3 Trends | Undervalued Crypto Gems | Daily Portfolio StrategySign up here:Youtube: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCGyqEtcGQQtXyUwvcy7Gmyg/joinPatreon: patreon.com/altcoinbuzz⏱️...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum whales bulk up on ETH holdings – What for?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18885216/Ethereum-whales-bulk-up-on-ETH-holdings-What-for</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18885216/Ethereum-whales-bulk-up-on-ETH-holdings-What-for"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T00:30:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Although demand for ETH has grown in the last week, its price remains in a narrow range, as poor sentiments continue to build up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Co-Founder Declares Biden’s Crypto Stance ‘A Really Bad Call’]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18885233/Ripple-Co-Founder-Declares-Bidens-Crypto-Stance-A-Really-Bad-Call</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18885233/Ripple-Co-Founder-Declares-Bidens-Crypto-Stance-A-Really-Bad-Call"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T00:21:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Larsen, co-founder of Ripple, has criticized United States President Joe Biden for his stance against crypto, which he believes hinders the nation’s innovation. Larsen believes that the US no longer leads the global blockchain industry. Biden’s Stringent Crypto Policies Are Holding Back...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Introduces Crypto Loan Service For US Institutions]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754fed6999</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/coinbase-introduces-crypto-loan-for-us-institutions/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T00:19:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prominent crypto exchange Coinbase has launched a crypto lending service targeted at institutional investors in the United States.  According to a Tuesday report by Bloomberg, the largest American exchange seeks to fill the void created by the collapse of crypto lending firms such as BlockFi, Genesis Global, Celsius, etc. 
 
 
Coinbase Lending Service Opens With Massive Investment 
 
Based on Bloomberg’s report, the Coinbase lending program is off to a good start, attracting $57 million in investment from Coinbase customers. This information was revealed in a US Securities and Exchange Commission filing. 
 
The Coinbase lending service allows institutional clients to lend funds – in the form of crypto assets – to exchange. 
 
These assets are collateralized by other digital assets, with a …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Semilore Faleti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s What’s Behind XRP’s Price Decline After SEC Lawsuit Victory, According to Analytics Firm Kaiko]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18885176/Heres-Whats-Behind-XRPs-Price-Decline-After-SEC-Lawsuit-Victory-According-to-Analytics-Firm-Kaiko</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18885176/Heres-Whats-Behind-XRPs-Price-Decline-After-SEC-Lawsuit-Victory-According-to-Analytics-Firm-Kaiko"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T00:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Digital asset research firm Kaiko finds that data from crypto exchanges suggests large traders in the US drove buying demand of XRP after Ripple won a partial court victory over the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) in July. In a new analysis, Kaiko notes that the Korean exchange...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Used for International Remittances in Key Asian Markets]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18885182/XRP-Used-for-International-Remittances-in-Key-Asian-Markets</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18885182/XRP-Used-for-International-Remittances-in-Key-Asian-Markets"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Major Japanese financial services company SBI Holdings is embracing XRP for international remittances between Japan and key Asian markets through its subsidiary SBI Remit. Starting this month, SBI Remit will use the crypto asset XRP to facilitate low-cost settlements for remittances to bank...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin And Crypto Giving Us The Best Chance To Get Rich]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18885202/BITCOIN-AND-CRYPTO-GIVING-US-THE-BEST-CHANCE-TO-GET-RICH</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18885202/BITCOIN-AND-CRYPTO-GIVING-US-THE-BEST-CHANCE-TO-GET-RICH"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T23:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[🔥 Activate NordVPN FOR JUST $3 PER MONTH and get access to Threat Protection: https://nordvpn.com/ellio#nft #ethereum #defi #blockchain #crypto #cryptocurrency #bitcoin #btc #eth #news #protocols #sidechain #altcoin #nftmarketplace #opensea #cryptoart #protocol #altcoins #nonfungibletoken #dao...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analyst Predicts SEC Will Approve First Spot Bitcoin ETF by Mid-March Next Year]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754fe8b463</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/analyst-predicts-sec-will-approve-first-spot-bitcoin-etf-by-mid-march-next-year/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T23:43:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Asset management firm Bernstein has predicted that the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) will approve its first spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) between mid-October and mid-March next year. The firm’s analyst believes that “the crypto ETF opportunity won’t just stop at bitcoin but will extend into multiple crypto assets.”
 
Bernstein’s Spot Bitcoin ETF Prediction
 
Gautam Chhugani, managing director and senior analyst of Global Digital Assets at asset management firm Bernstein, has predicted that the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) will approve its first bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) by mid-March next year.
 
He explained in a note on Monday that the court ruling in favor of crypto asset manager Grayscale Investments last week regarding the firm’s prop…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why PEPE might no longer be a whale favorite]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18885164/Why-PEPE-might-no-longer-be-a-whale-favorite</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18885164/Why-PEPE-might-no-longer-be-a-whale-favorite"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T23:30:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Significant whale activity has sparked concerns over PEPE's future, with large holders selling at a loss, creating market uncertainty.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MetaMask Users Targeted in Cryptocurrency Scam Using Government Website URLs]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18885158/MetaMask-Users-Targeted-in-Cryptocurrency-Scam-Using-Government-Website-URLs</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18885158/MetaMask-Users-Targeted-in-Cryptocurrency-Scam-Using-Government-Website-URLs"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T23:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scammers are capitalizing on MetaMask users in the crypto space through the use of government-owned...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance CEO Announces Exit of Key Executives in Russia Amid Growing FUD]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18885152/Binance-CEO-Announces-Exit-of-Key-Executives-in-Russia-Amid-Growing-FUD</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18885152/Binance-CEO-Announces-Exit-of-Key-Executives-in-Russia-Amid-Growing-FUD"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T23:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Changpeng Zhao announced the departure of key executives in its Russian branch. The two top executives, Gleb Kostarev and Vladimir Smerkis, made the announcements today. The departures have raised fears and speculations that Binance might exit Russia. Founder and CEO of Binance Changpeng...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Coinbase execs raise $8 million for fresh take on crypto lending]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18885146/Former-Coinbase-execs-raise-8-million-for-fresh-take-on-crypto-lending</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18885146/Former-Coinbase-execs-raise-8-million-for-fresh-take-on-crypto-lending"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T23:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trident Digital Group, founded by former Coinbase executives, raised $8 million for its “next generation” crypto lending business.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Power: Over 88,000 Millionaires Build Their Wealth Through Crypto – Study]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754fd0fb0c</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-power-over-88000-millionaires/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T22:18:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto world now boasts a staggering 88,200 crypto-millionaires scattered across the globe, according to the latest Crypto Wealth Report. This burgeoning class of wealth holders has seen their fortunes swell thanks to the ever-expanding digital asset universe. 
 
Astonishingly, half of these newly minted millionaires have pinned their financial dreams on Bitcoin (BTC), the world’s largest and most popular cryptocurrency.
 
The report, which delved deep into the crypto landscape, also uncovered intriguing statistics about the upper echelons of crypto wealth. Among the 182 individuals who wielded more than $100 million worth of crypto assets, a significant 78 were devout Bitcoiners. 
 
Further emphasizing Bitcoin’s sway, the report revealed that six out of the 22 crypto traders who had a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Genesis Hits Parent Company DCG With $600 Million Lawsuits]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155213</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155213/genesis-global-digital-currency-group-lawsuits-600-million-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T22:06:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The legal actions come a day after Genesis Global Trading said it would shutter its crypto spot trading operations in September.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reddit Kicks Off Football Season With NFTs of Every NFL Team]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155226</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155226/reddit-kicks-off-football-season-nfts-every-nfl-team"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T22:04:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Online discussion platform Reddit released a wave of collectible avatars Wednesday to commemorate the NFL's 32 teams as kickoff closes in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cboe's BZX Exchange Files to Launch Ark 21Shares, VanEck Spot Ether ETFs]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754fd3e0df</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/09/06/cboe-bzx-exchange-files-to-launch-ark-21shares-vaneck-spot-ether-etfs/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T21:50:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cboe's BZX exchange filed the first documents in a bid to offer the first spot ether exchange-traded funds in the U.S.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Little-Changed at $25.7K After Newsy and Volatile Session]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754fd3e0ca</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/09/06/bitcoin-little-changed-at-257k-after-newsy-and-volatile-session/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T21:50:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Broader crypto markets were modestly lower late on Wednesday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen  Alpher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s 21 Million Supply Cap: Immutable Truth or Future Flexibility?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754fdd0522</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoins-21-million-supply-cap-immutable-truth-or-future-flexibility/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T21:40:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, the crypto community is abuzz with discussions about Bitcoin’s 21 million supply cap and the potential for its alteration. On September 4, in a social media exchange, software developer and Bitcoin Core contributor Peter Todd expressed his belief that in “10-20 years the idea of a hard fork to add a small tail emission may not be so controversial any more.” Todd’s remarks ignited a flurry of reactions from crypto aficionados who took issue with his statement.
 
Rethinking Bitcoin’s 21 Million: A Controversial Crypto Conversation
 
Many firmly hold that Bitcoin’s 21 million supply cap is unchangeable, yet recent chatter suggests otherwise. A discussion ignited on the social media platform X (previously known as Twitter) when Cake Group’s CEO, Dr. Julian Hosp, penned an X post dec…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rookie Vs Veteran: Coinbase’s Month-Old ‘Base’ Surpasses Cardano TVL, A Closer Look]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754fdf8b6e</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/coinbase-month-old-base-surpasses-cardano-tvl/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T21:18:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Total Value Locked (TVL), one of the metrics used to know the robustness of a blockchain in the decentralized finance (DeFi) sector, has recently been put at the forefront to compare Coinbase’s newcomer second-layer blockchain Base, and Cardano, a veteran in the crypto scene.
 
For perspective, Cardano has been part of the blockchain ecosystem since 2017. It has had years to establish its foothold, earn its reputation, and attract investments. While Base, on the other hand, which is barely a month old, is now reportedly surpassing Cardano’s TVL by a notable margin.
 
 
 
 
Base Vs. Cardano: By The Numbers
 
On September 4th, Parul Gujral, a decentralized finance (DeFi) enthusiast, shed light on the matter. Gujral noticed that Base’s TVL is already three times that of Cardano’s. Gujral pres…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celsius Network Files 'Adversary Complaint' Against EquitiesFirst to Recover Assets]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754fdf93fd</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/09/06/celsius-network-files-adversary-complaint-against-equitiesfirst-to-recover-assets/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T21:17:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EquitiesFirst, a private lender, owed Celsius $439 million of assets as of July 2022.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried’s Motion for Pretrial Release Goes Before 3-Judge Panel]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754fd92214</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/09/06/sam-bankman-frieds-motion-for-pretrial-release-goes-before-3-judge-panel/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T21:04:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former FTX CEO Sam Bankman-Fried is trying to win back his freedom – at least temporarily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tornado Cash Co-Founder Pleads Innocence Amidst Money Laundering and Hacking Scandal]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754fdbf773</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/tornado-cash-co-founder-pleads-innocence-amidst-money-laundering-and-hacking-scandal/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T20:39:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On the 6th of September, 2023, the Inner City Press (ICP) delivered an account of the legal proceedings involving Roman Storm, one of the co-creators behind the ethereum (ETH) mixing protocol, Tornado Cash. In the courtroom drama that unfolded, Storm resolutely declared his innocence by pleading not guilty to the charges levied against him. 
 
Tornado Cash Co-Creator Roman Storm Denies Money Laundering Charges
 
As August drew to a close, the federal indictment of Roman Storm and his fellow co-founder, Roman Semenov, sent shockwaves through the cryptocurrency world. They faced charges that ranged from money laundering conspiracy to violating sanctions laws, all the way to operating an unlicensed money-transmitting enterprise. While Roman Storm was present in the courtroom, Semenov remained…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto ETF Showdown: Can Other Players Outrun The Bitcoin Fund?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754fc66d1b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-can-other-players-outrun-bitcoin-fund/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T20:18:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The quest for crypto exchange-traded funds (ETFs) remains at the forefront of industry discussions as the cryptocurrency market continues to capture the attention of investors and institutions alike. 
 
Several major players, including BlackRock and Fidelity, have eagerly awaited a ruling from the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) regarding their proposed spot bitcoin funds. 
 
However, the regulator announced last week that it required more time to evaluate seven such proposals, leaving the industry in suspense.
 
 
Spot Bitcoin ETFs In Regulatory Limbo
 
Despite the anticipation surrounding spot Bitcoin ETFs, the SEC’s decision to delay its ruling has created uncertainty. While industry experts speculate on the potential approval of these funds, other crypto investment products…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celsius CEO Alex Mashinsky’s Assets Frozen amid Ongoing Legal Battle]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754fc6bc78</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/former-celsius-ceo-alex-mashinskys-assets-frozen-amid-ongoing-legal-battle/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T20:15:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The assets of former Celsius CEO Alex Mashinsky have been  
ordered frozen by the court as he faces mounting legal battles related to the  
collapse of the crypto lending platform. This development comes in the wake of  
his arrest in July and subsequent release on a USD $40 million bond.
Mashinsky, who is also  
the Co-Founder of Celsius, has denied any wrongdoing. He is accused of  
securities fraud and manipulating the company’s CEL token. The assets allegedly  
frozen include corporate bank accounts and valuable property in Austin, Texas.
Mashinsky’s Legal Team  
Terms Allegations as Baseless
On August 16, New York  
Judge Jed Rakoff issued an order prohibiting financial institutions from  
selling assets in various Goldman Sachs bank accounts held in the name of Koala  
LLC, a company…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Despite the Hype, Crypto AI Tokens Have Been Languishing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155217</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155217/despite-the-hype-crypto-ai-tokens-have-been-languishing"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T20:09:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AI-inspired token category, including Fetch.ai and Worldcoin, has seen its market cap go from $170 million to $60 million in just a few months.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Open-Source ‘Falcon’ AI Language Model Overtakes Meta and Google]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155209</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155209/falcon-large-language-model-llm-ai-training-data-set"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T19:58:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meta's massive, 70-billion parameter LLaMA 2 has been outflanked by the newly released 180-billion parameter Falcon Large Language Model.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arkham Intelligence Identifies Grayscale’s $16 Billion Onchain Bitcoin Holdings]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754fc2adf9</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/arkham-intelligence-identifies-grayscales-16-billion-onchain-bitcoin-holdings/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T19:40:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arkham Intelligence, a leading crypto analytics firm, unveiled on Wednesday its findings on Grayscale’s Bitcoin Trust onchain holdings. This revelation comes just six days after Arkham shed light on the fund manager’s onchain ethereum assets.
 
Unmasking Grayscale’s Bitcoin Trust: Arkham Intelligence Exposes $16 Billion Onchain Bitcoin Assets
 
The crypto analytics startup, Arkham Intelligence, has pinpointed and tagged Grayscale’s bitcoin reserves. In a post on X (previously known as Twitter), Arkham highlighted a Grayscale X post, which was shared in the aftermath of FTX’s downfall and the rising trend of proof-of-reserve audits. Grayscale had assured that Coinbase securely held its BTC, yet the onchain addresses remained undisclosed.
 
On Wednesday, Arkham elaborated that Grayscale stan…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BREAKING: ARK Invest Files For First Ethereum Spot ETF]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754fcd6707</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/breaking-ark-files-for-the-first-ethereum-spot-etf/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T19:17:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Per a document filed with the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), hedge fund Ark Invest filed for the first Ethereum spot Exchange Traded Fund (ETF) in the US. This new filing has directly impacted the ETH price as the ETF narrative gains further influence in the crypto market.
 
 
ARK Gets Ahead Of The Curve: Ethereum Spot ETF Filing To Trigger Domino Effect?
 
According to the document file with the SEC, the financial product will trade on the Cboe BZX Exchange and track the ETH price on the spot market as displayed by the Chicago Mercantile Exchange (CME). Ark has listed Benchmarks as their Index manager and is sponsored by 21Shares.
 
Furthermore, Ark selected crypto exchange Coinbase as their ETH custodian, similar to its Bitcoin spot ETF application. The company will hold th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reynaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Genesis Global Capital Files for Over $600M in Unpaid DCG Loans: Court Docs]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754fcd8e2e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/09/06/genesis-global-capital-files-for-over-600m-in-unpaid-dcg-loans-court-docs/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T19:15:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Genesis Global Capital, a subsidiary of Digital Currency Group, filed in court for DCG to repay outstanding loans in excess of $600 million on Wednesday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cathie Wood's Ark Invest, 21Shares Apply for First Spot Ethereum ETF]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155204</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155204/cathie-woods-ark-invest-21shares-apply-for-first-spot-ethereum-etf"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T19:12:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dubbed the ARK 21Shares Ethereum ETF, the application resembles those for spot Bitcoin ETFs that were recently delayed by the SEC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FASB Says Crypto Assets Should Be Marked at Current Values]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754fcfff47</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/09/06/fasb-says-crypto-assets-should-be-marked-at-current-values/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T18:55:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first U.S. accounting rule specifically for cryptocurrency will say that companies must use a fair-value approach that would demand certain digital assets be measured at what they would trade for in the markets, according to the Financial Accounting Standards Board (FASB).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cathy Wood's ARK Invest Files for First Spot Ether ETF]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754fc9b1a4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/09/06/cathy-woods-ark-invest-files-for-first-spot-ether-etf/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T18:41:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ark 21Shares Ethereum ETF is the first attempt to list such a fund in the U.S. that directly invests in ETH, the second largest cryptocurrency by market capitalization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ice Cold: Feds Freeze Celsius Founder Alex Mashinsky's Assets]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155163</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155163/feds-freeze-former-celsius-ceo-alex-mashinskys-assets"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T18:37:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The alleged conman is facing a number of criminal and civil charges following the collapse of Celsius last year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Protocol: Ethereum Learns of Potential Defector as ‘Supreme Court’ Mooted]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754fca9bb8</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/09/06/ethereum-learns-of-potential-defector-as-supreme-court-mooted/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T18:34:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is a blockchain “sequencer?” Here’s why you need to know]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bradley Keoun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Changes Policy to Allow NFT Game Ads—With Some Limits]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155185</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155185/google-changes-policy-allow-nft-game-ads-some-limits"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T18:14:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google's updated advertising policy permits NFT games, but titles that offer wagering or staking require a gambling certification.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visa Payments Will Rely on 'Multiple Blockchains', Says Head of Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155182</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155182/visa-payments-will-rely-on-multiple-blockchains-says-head-of-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T18:12:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cuy Sheffield’s post referenced skepticism attached to an early internet, when slow, chirping modems were the norm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Racing Legend Michael Andretti Bets on AI With $200 Million Zapata Merger]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155181</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155181/racing-legend-michael-andretti-bets-ai-200-million-zapata-merger"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T17:58:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IndyCar icon Michael Andretti's SPAC has agreed to merge with startup Zapata AI, which is already helping his racing teams on the track.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Cohen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Justin Bieber Producer Is Selling Royalties for the Song 'Company' as NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155164</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155164/justin-bieber-producer-selling-royalties-song-company-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T17:13:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to own a small share of streaming royalty rights for a Justin Bieber hit? AnotherBlock is set to serve them up via NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ali Shutler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Most Anticipated Crypto and NFT Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=15221</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/15221/most-anticipated-crypto-games"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T16:16:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATED: Lavish titles like Parallel and Deadrop are poised to redefine blockchain gaming. Here's what to watch for in 2023 and beyond.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward,Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Social Network Rep is Taking GalaChain Beyond Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152396</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152396/social-network-rep-is-taking-galachain-beyond-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T15:51:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rep’s novel location-based platform will integrate with Gala’s gaming, music and film platforms in innovative, social ways.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elspeth Taylor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Star Wars Outlaws: Everything You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155149</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155149/star-wars-outlaws-everything-you-need-to-know"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T15:03:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The sci-fi franchise takes its first step into open-world adventure with thief Kay Vess and her creature companion Nix in Star Wars Outlaws.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is the Bitcoin Fear and Greed Index?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155091</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-the-bitcoin-fear-and-greed-index"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T14:09:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Primarily, the Index is used to reveal the opportunity in the market. Traders can buy Bitcoin when fearful investors sell at a low price and later sell for a much higher price when the Index denotes greed, or high demand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melanie Kramer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TON Foundation Announces Registration as Swiss Non-Profit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155138</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155138/ton-foundation-announces-registration-as-swiss-non-profit"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T13:14:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The foundation that develops and manages the TON blockchain after it spun off from Telegram has found a new home in Switzerland.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aspen Launches With Tools to Help NFT Creators Reclaim Royalties]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155121</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155121/aspen-launches-tools-help-nft-creators-reclaim-royalties"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T13:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Monax Labs has debuted a tool suite that helps creators reclaim unpaid NFT royalty fees by restricting access to perks and utility.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lucy Harley-McKeown</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Marathon Digital's Bitcoin Production Drops 9% in August Due to Texas Heat]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155120</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155120/marathon-digitals-bitcoin-production-drops-9-in-august-due-to-texas-heat"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T12:41:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The mining firm blamed extreme weather conditions in the Lone Star State for the decrease in Bitcoin production in August.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global Crypto Wealth Study Reveals 6 Bitcoin Billionaires and 88,000 Crypto Millionaires]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155113</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155113/global-crypto-wealth-study-reveals-6-bitcoin-billionaires-and-88000-crypto-millionaires"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T12:31:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Henley & Partners' Crypto Adoption Index tracks the sector’s new elite and the growth and potential of the digital economy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Circle Joins Forces with Legend Trading to Broaden International Reach of USDC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155043</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155043/circle-legend-trading-usdc-stablecoin-latin-america-asia-pacific"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T12:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Legend Trading serves over 800 institutions, processes more than $1 billion a month, and aims to bring USDC to its clients.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried's Lawyers Question Former FTX Founder’s Ability to Prepare for Trial]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155101</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155101/sam-bankman-frieds-lawyers-question-former-ftx-founders-ability-to-prepare-for-trial"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T10:13:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried is currently confined at the Metropolitan Detention Center, preparing for a trial scheduled for early October.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PUBG Developers Unveil Cosmos-Based Settlus Blockchain for USDC Settlements]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155092</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155092/pubg-developers-unveil-settlus-a-cosmos-based-blockchain-for-usdc-settlements"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T09:42:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Krafton, the developer behind popular battle royale title PUBG: Battlegrounds, has joined the Cosmos with new layer-1 blockchain Settlus.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Boosts AI Efficiency With a ‘Heavy Metal Quartet’ of Compilers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155066</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155066/microsoft-ai-compilers-heavy-metal"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T07:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft's Rammer, Roller, Welder and Grinder promise to make AI developments faster, beter, and more powerful]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Story Protocol Launches IP Ownership Network with $54 Million in Funding]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155052</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155052/story-protocol-launches-ip-ownership-network-with-54-million-in-funding"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T04:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Andreessen Horowitz invested in a startup that uses blockchain tech to address problems heightened by artificial intelligence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase-Incubated Base Suffers Outage, Team Says 'No Funds Are at Risk']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155083</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155083/coinbase-incubated-base-suffers-outage-team-says-no-funds-are-at-risk"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T00:30:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The outage prompted dozens of comparisons to other blockchain solutions and their relative stability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale Prods SEC to Approve Bitcoin Spot ETF After Court Victory]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155076</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155076/grayscale-prods-sec-to-approve-bitcoin-spot-etf-after-court-victory"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T23:33:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lawyers for the investment firm call out inconsistent treatment of Bitcoin trusts and futures in the protracted debate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt AI, Edited by Ryan Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MrBeast-Promoted 'Creator League' Postponed After Gamers Bail Amid NFT Backlash]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155041</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155041/mrbeast-promoted-creator-league-postponed-after-gamers-bail-amid-nft-pushback"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T23:05:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Influencers in the gaming league say they were misled about the blockchain aspect. Now eFuse is pausing the program and laying off staff.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Mino Games is Using Artificial Intelligence]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/SrT1Afj7/how-mino-games-is-using-artificial-intelligence</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/SrT1Afj7/how-mino-games-is-using-artificial-intelligence"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T22:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mino Games CEO Sasha McKinnon tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about how the studio's upcoming game Dimensionals will use real-time AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MetaMask Introduces Bank and PayPal Cash-Out Options]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155039</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155039/metamask-sell-transfer-withdraw-cash-out-paypal"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T21:11:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Ensuring a way for users to enter and exit crypto freely is important," the company said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gitcoin Co-Founder Kevin Owocki Says His Return Won't Make Him Center of the Network]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155031</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155031/gitcoin-co-founder-kevin-owocki-says-his-return-wont-make-him-center-of-the-network"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T20:34:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“To be clear, I’m not dictating. I’m bottoms-up gathering intelligence and helping them synthesize their roadmap together," he told Decrypt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bored Ape Creator Giving Away Bitcoin in Ordinals Puzzle Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155022</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155022/bored-ape-creator-giving-away-bitcoin-ordinals-puzzle-game"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T20:09:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yuga Labs has launched a 13-week puzzle-solving competition around its TwelveFold Ordinals, with Bitcoin prizes available for players.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Epic Games Embraces AI In Games, In Break With Steam]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155023</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155023/epic-games-embraces-ai-in-games-in-break-with-steam"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T18:49:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The two leading online game stores are split over artificial intelligence, setting the stage for a showdown.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visa Promises Faster Credit Card Payments With USDC on Solana]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155014</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155014/visa-faster-credit-card-payments-usdc-solana"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T17:40:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The payments giant doesn’t seem to be slowing down with its crypto ambitions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Pixel Pioneer': Christie's to Auction Keith Haring Digital Art as NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155006</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155006/pixel-pioneer-christies-auction-keith-haring-digital-art-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T17:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Keith Haring's 1987 artwork created on a Commodore Amiga has been minted on Ethereum and will be auctioned by Christie's.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephanie Hirschmiller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Watch-and-Earn Platform Myco Reveals Community Film Funding Program]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154941</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154941/watch-and-earn-platform-myco-reveals-community-film-funding-program"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Mycolab program will provide 65% of the funding for selected film projects that can raise the first 35% from the community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Future Ethereum Upgrades Could Allow Full Nodes to Run on Mobile Phones: Vitalik Buterin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154990</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154990/future-ethereum-upgrades-could-allow-full-nodes-to-run-on-mobile-phones-vitalik-buterin"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T12:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Planned Ethereum upgrades including stateless clients will help to decentralize the network, said its co-founder at Korea Blockchain Week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sorare Launches AR-Equipped 3D Digital Football Player Cards]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154975</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154975/sorare-launches-ar-equipped-3d-digital-football-player-cards"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T10:53:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The launch of Sorare's upgraded collectibles comes alongside a global scavenger hunt offering the winner a “once-in-a-lifetime” trip.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Korean Banking Giant Partners With BitGo, Opens Doors To Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154970</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154970/south-korean-banking-giant-partners-with-bitgo-opens-doors-to-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T10:13:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KEB Hana Bank’s partnership with the crypto custodian ties one of the largest financial groups in the country to the digital asset space.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ECB Exec Takes Aim At PayPal's Stablecoin, Praises Digital Euro]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154966</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154966/ecb-exec-takes-aim-at-paypals-stablecoin-praises-digital-euro"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T09:46:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[European Central Bank executive Fabio Panetta warned of the risks associated with private stablecoins, while making the case for CBDCs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Casio Dropping Free NFTs to 'Co-Create' Virtual G-Shock Watches]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154905</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154905/casio-dropping-free-nfts-co-create-virtual-g-shock-watches"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T01:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The G-Shock watch brand is coming to the metaverse via Polygon NFTs—and Casio wants to cultivate a community of collaborators.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephanie Hirschmiller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI Plugs ChatGPT Into Canva to Sharpen Its Competitive Edge in AI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154923</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154923/chatgpt-canva-plugin-openai-design-tool"/>
        <updated>2023-09-04T19:54:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now ChatGPT Plus users can "talk" to Canva directly from OpenAI's bot, making their workflow easier.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INTERVIEW: How Will Aurory Use NFTs and Crypto?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qv3VwNmM/interview-how-will-aurory-use-nfts-and-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qv3VwNmM/interview-how-will-aurory-use-nfts-and-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T15:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Natoli, Aurory's Head of Marketing and Business Development, tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how the Aurory games will use NFTs and crypto and shares the studio's broader stance on the tech.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Cloud's James Tromans on the Intersection of AI and Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OeD4uoLj/google-clouds-james-tromans-on-the-intersection-of-ai-and-web3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OeD4uoLj/google-clouds-james-tromans-on-the-intersection-of-ai-and-web3"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google's Global Head of Google Cloud for Web3 James Tromans sat down with Decrypt's Jason Nelson to discuss how AI can help Web3 companies come to market faster and the real value of Web3 tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastering NFT Trading - Degen U]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/HQGt1Vrq/mastering-nft-trading-degen-u</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/HQGt1Vrq/mastering-nft-trading-degen-u"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T07:08:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Take Degen U's new course, Mastering NFT Trading, and earn an on-chain certificate. A top instructor will help you identify trends, seize the right moment to trade, weed out scams—and have fun while doing it!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Space Nation CEO on Working With 'Independence Day' Director Roland Emmerich]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LpznLhtx/space-nation-ceo-on-working-with-independence-day-director-roland-emmerich</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LpznLhtx/space-nation-ceo-on-working-with-independence-day-director-roland-emmerich"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T17:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jerome Wu, CEO of Space Nation, tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the upcoming Space Nation Online game in development and shares details on Space Nation Cofounder Roland Emmerich's role in the project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GAME REVIEW: Champions Arena from Gala Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qUE1RlDx/game-review-champions-arena-from-gala-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qUE1RlDx/game-review-champions-arena-from-gala-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Champions Arena is a turn-based fantasy RPG from Gala Games, where characters can become NFTs and crypto can be used to purchase gems, one of the game's synthetic currencies. Decrypt's Kate Irwin takes us inside the game for her thoughts on the fun, mobile-first title.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apex Legends Voice Actor Ben Prendergast on the Future of Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/X3RKdsaG/apex-legends-voice-actor-ben-prendergast-on-the-future-of-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/X3RKdsaG/apex-legends-voice-actor-ben-prendergast-on-the-future-of-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T18:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Voice actor Ben Prendergast, who's voiced characters in games like Apex Legends and God of War Ragnarok, shares his opinions on the tech space's history of "bubbles" and whether blockchain gaming has a future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The future of AI Stardom and Robotics with SingularityNET COO Janet Adams and Desdemona]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yVQaZI71/the-future-of-ai-stardom-and-robotics-with-singularitynet-coo-janet-adams-and-desdemona</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yVQaZI71/the-future-of-ai-stardom-and-robotics-with-singularitynet-coo-janet-adams-and-desdemona"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T16:45:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this interview, SingularityNET COO Janet Adams explains the intricate details that went into creating the Desdemona robot AI from Hanson Robotics and future plans for the AI Diva.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto a 'No-Brainer' for Video Games, Says Mino Games CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rdynom8C/crypto-a-no-brainer-for-video-games-says-mino-games-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rdynom8C/crypto-a-no-brainer-for-video-games-says-mino-games-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T18:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mino Games CEO Sasha MacKinnon, developer of the upcoming Dimensionals game, tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the studio's approach to digital collectibles.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Wagner's 'Controversial Take' on Crypto in Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tc2nKeqA/michael-wagners-controversial-take-on-crypto-in-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tc2nKeqA/michael-wagners-controversial-take-on-crypto-in-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T16:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Solana's PlayGG, Star Atlas CEO Michael Wagner shares his "controversial take" on crypto in games, shares the challenges of developing the upcoming scifi game, and how crypto's volatility has changed his perspective with Decrypt's Jason Nelson.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interview: Angelic CEO on Building the Sci-Fi RPG on Solana and Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/uCzW3K7P/interview-angelic-ceo-on-building-the-sci-fi-rpg-on-solana-and-ethereum</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/uCzW3K7P/interview-angelic-ceo-on-building-the-sci-fi-rpg-on-solana-and-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T15:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Angelic is a sci-fi roleplay game in development that will be free-to-play and offer optional, opt-in crypto features on Solana and Ethereum and a governance token. Metaverse Game Studios CEO and Founder Erkan Bayol tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how he sees AAA traditional games as Angelic's main competitors and shares his vision for the game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apex Legends Voice Actor on AI's Impact on Video Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IOIrmb0N/apex-legends-voice-actor-on-ais-impact-on-video-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IOIrmb0N/apex-legends-voice-actor-on-ais-impact-on-video-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T17:28:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ben Prendergast is an actor who has voiced characters like Apex Legends' Fuse, God of War Ragnarok's Tyr, and Patroclus in Hades. But as debates swirl around the use of artificial intelligence in entertainment in light of the SAG-AFTRA and WGA strikes, Prendergast gives Decrypt's Kate Irwin his honest take on the potential use of AI actors in games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Star Atlas CEO on Developing an MMO Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/WQCaahmH/star-atlas-ceo-on-developing-an-mmo-game</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/WQCaahmH/star-atlas-ceo-on-developing-an-mmo-game"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T13:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Jason Nelson speaks with Star Atlas Founder and CEO Michael Wagner about the MMO game's approach to development, marketing, and blockchain integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aurory's Origin Story: How JRPGs Inspired the Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/O0S201TB/aurorys-origin-story-how-jrpgs-inspired-the-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/O0S201TB/aurorys-origin-story-how-jrpgs-inspired-the-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T16:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Jason Nelson talks to Aurory's Head of Marketing and Business Development Michael Natoli about the origins of the Aurory crypto games at the Solana PlayGG event.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Parallel TCG: Inside the Sci-Fi Card Game’s Closed Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/q8YVWJh4/parallel-tcg-inside-the-sci-fi-card-games-closed-beta</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/q8YVWJh4/parallel-tcg-inside-the-sci-fi-card-games-closed-beta"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T15:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin goes hands-on with Parallel’s closed beta on Windows PC to find out what sets it apart from other crypto card-battlers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 Games Need to Compete with All Games, Says Solana Foundation GM]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ud9wTd4s/web3-games-need-to-compete-with-all-games-says-solana-foundation-gm</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ud9wTd4s/web3-games-need-to-compete-with-all-games-says-solana-foundation-gm"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T19:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Foundation's General Manager of Games Johnny Lee tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about Solana's PlayGG conference and shares his take on crypto gaming and the "play-to-earn" concept.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>