<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-10-11T14:14:49.267Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-10-11T14:14:49.267Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Standard Chartered’s Research Predicts Ethereum to Hit $8K by 2026 and Eyes $35K Long-Term]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b182da31</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/standard-chartereds-research-predicts-ethereum-to-hit-8k-by-2026-and-eyes-35k-long-term/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T14:05:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum might soar to $8,000 by 2026, suggests a fresh investors memo penned by Standard Chartered’s lead on forex and crypto research. Geoffrey Kendrick, alongside his analytical squad at the bank, pinpointed Ethereum’s stronghold in smart contracts, gaming, and tokenization as the driving forces behind its projected price surge.
 
A New Era for Ethereum? Standard Chartered’s Latest Price Prediction
 
After the financial behemoth’s prior forecast of bitcoin (BTC) potentially hitting $50K by year-end and surging to $120K in 2024, Geoffrey Kendrick and his team at Standard Chartered are back with a new report, this time spotlighting ethereum (ETH).
 
In his recent analysis, Kendrick underscores Ethereum’s “unrivaled command” across diverse realms of decentralized finance (defi), token gene…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon Faces Cost Challenge in ApeCoin DAO ETH L2 Pitch]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18962135/Polygon-Faces-Cost-Challenge-in-ApeCoin-DAO-ETH-L2-Pitch</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18962135/Polygon-Faces-Cost-Challenge-in-ApeCoin-DAO-ETH-L2-Pitch"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T14:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon Labs' effort to convince ApeCoin DAO to transition to an Ethereum Layer 2 faces a cost hurdle.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance's Innovative STP Feature: Keeping Self-Trades in Check]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b1837e6c</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/news/binances-innovative-stp-feature-keeping-self-trades-in-check/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T14:02:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance  
is taking steps to enhance its user experience by introducing a  
self-transaction prevention (STP) function to prevent unnecessary trading fees  
associated with unintentional self-trades. The full rollout of this function  
for all spot and margin trading users is scheduled for October 26, as announced  
on the company's blog on October 11.
Binance's Solution to  
Self-Trades: Unveiling the STP Function
With  
the integration of STP, Binance will introduce the "expire maker" mode  
as the default setting for all trading pairs and orders on its spot and margin  
trading platforms. 
This  
feature will help users identify orders that have expired due to the STP  
function, allowing them to review these transactions via the Binance official  
website, Binance App, and Binance Desk…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tareq Sikder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Immutable partners with AWS to shape the future of gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18962129/Immutable-partners-with-AWS-to-shape-the-future-of-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18962129/Immutable-partners-with-AWS-to-shape-the-future-of-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T14:01:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways Immutable has partnered with Amazon Web Service in a bid to push its gaming ecosystem higher. The blockchain firm is set to gain access to a vast pipeline of game studio leads and support, Immutable partners with AWS Blockchain firm Immutable announced via X (formerly Twitter) on...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Could See A Steep Decline If It Closes Below This Level]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18962136/Ethereum-Could-See-A-Steep-Decline-If-It-Closes-Below-This-Level</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18962136/Ethereum-Could-See-A-Steep-Decline-If-It-Closes-Below-This-Level"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T14:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data suggests an Ethereum close under the $1,530 level could lead to a significant drawdown for the cryptocurrency. Ethereum Support Levels Below $1,530 Are Very Thin Currently In a new post on X, analyst Ali has discussed what the support and resistance levels of Ethereum are looking...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LIVE: Caroline Ellison Starts Day 2 of Testimony Against Sam Bankman-Fried]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b183cbfd</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/10/11/live-caroline-ellison-starts-day-2-of-testimony-against-sam-bankman-fried/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T13:59:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Alameda Research CEO Caroline Ellison retook the stand on Wednesday, after testifying that her former boss and boyfriend, Sam Bankman-Fried, had directed many of FTX's now-public missteps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Bank Xapo Snags European Broker License, Will Offer Stocks Like Apple]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18962128/Crypto-Bank-Xapo-Snags-European-Broker-License-Will-Offer-Stocks-Like-Apple</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18962128/Crypto-Bank-Xapo-Snags-European-Broker-License-Will-Offer-Stocks-Like-Apple"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T13:58:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Markets in Financial Instruments Directive (MiFID) license will soon allow the firm to offer S&P 500 stocks. In addition, Xapo, which has always been bitcoin-only, plans to add Ethereum’s ETH.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Giants Binance, Coinbase Now Operate Under New UK Regulations]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18962114/Crypto-Giants-Binance-Coinbase-Now-Operate-Under-New-UK-Regulations</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18962114/Crypto-Giants-Binance-Coinbase-Now-Operate-Under-New-UK-Regulations"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T13:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The largest crypto exchange, Binance, alongside the leading US-based exchange, Coinbase, now operates a trading platform for U.K. residents under the new regulations in the country. CryptoBusy, a renowned Bitcoin analyst in the crypto community, first drew the attention of crypto enthusiasts to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ESMA says DeFi can bring greater financial inclusion, but warns of volatility risks]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18962105/ESMA-says-DeFi-can-bring-greater-financial-inclusion-but-warns-of-volatility-risks</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18962105/ESMA-says-DeFi-can-bring-greater-financial-inclusion-but-warns-of-volatility-risks"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T13:57:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The regulator said that DeFi doesn’t pose a risk to financial stability, due to its small size, but said it needs to be monitored in the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano Founder Says ETHGate Is Not Corruption, Just Favouritism]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b18cf503</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/cardano-founder-ethgate-just-favouritism/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T13:52:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a revealing AMA session, Cardano founder, Charles Hoskinson, weighed in on the much-debated drafts of William Hinman’s controversial speech on Ethereum. Addressing the burning issue, he stated, “It’s certainly a value getting these Hinman emails and these other things because they can perhaps expose the thought process the SEC has and you can definitely show that there was unequal application of law. That’s fine. But none of that activity presupposes corruption, just favoritism.”
 
Controversy Surrounding Hinman Docs
 
Ripple Labs thrust Hinman’s documents into the limelight this June after enduring a prolonged legal feud with the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). The papers provided a meticulous account of the events that prefaced Hinman’s declaration that Bitcoin and Ethere…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano Founder Says ETHGate Is Not Corruption, Just Favouritism]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18962085/Cardano-Founder-Says-ETHGate-Is-Not-Corruption-Just-Favouritism</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18962085/Cardano-Founder-Says-ETHGate-Is-Not-Corruption-Just-Favouritism"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T13:45:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a revealing AMA session, Cardano founder, Charles Hoskinson, weighed in on the much-debated drafts of William Hinman’s controversial speech on Ethereum. Addressing the burning issue, he stated, “It’s certainly a value getting these Hinman emails and these other things because they can perhaps...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin price uptrend could be in trouble; Here’s why]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18962094/Bitcoin-price-uptrend-could-be-in-trouble-Heres-why</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18962094/Bitcoin-price-uptrend-could-be-in-trouble-Heres-why"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T13:44:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) has been trading above the 50 Exponential Moving Average (EMA) since September 28 in both the daily and … Continued]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EU Markets Regulator Warns of DeFi’s ‘Serious Risks’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b18e46f2</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/10/11/eu-markets-regulator-warns-of-defis-serious-risks/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T13:43:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ESMA, responsible for rulemaking under the bloc’s landmark new crypto law MiCA, is worried about new forms of market manipulation when there’s no central counterparty]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack Schickler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lido's Arbitrum Proposal Splits Community Over Grant Size, Centralization Concerns]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200999</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200999/lidos-arbitrum-proposal-splits-community-over-grant-size-centralization-concerns"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T13:43:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lido Finance's $4 million ARB grant proposal on Snapshot has become a battleground over the project's purported centralization concerns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lido's Arbitrum Proposal Splits Community Over Grant Size, Centralization Concerns]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18962091/Lidos-Arbitrum-Proposal-Splits-Community-Over-Grant-Size-Centralization-Concerns</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18962091/Lidos-Arbitrum-Proposal-Splits-Community-Over-Grant-Size-Centralization-Concerns"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T13:43:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lido Finance's $4 million ARB grant proposal on Snapshot has become a battleground over the project's purported centralization concerns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LIVE: Caroline Ellison Starts Day 2 of Testimony Against Sam Bankman-Fried]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18962098/LIVE-Caroline-Ellison-Starts-Day-2-of-Testimony-Against-Sam-Bankman-Fried</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18962098/LIVE-Caroline-Ellison-Starts-Day-2-of-Testimony-Against-Sam-Bankman-Fried"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T13:42:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Alameda Research CEO Caroline Ellison retook the stand on Wednesday, after testifying that her former boss and boyfriend, Sam Bankman-Fried, had directed many of FTX's now-public missteps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 Thousand Dollar Ethereum Prediction from Standard Chartered! Here is History!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18962097/8-Thousand-Dollar-Ethereum-Prediction-from-Standard-Chartered-Here-is-History</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18962097/8-Thousand-Dollar-Ethereum-Prediction-from-Standard-Chartered-Here-is-History"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T13:42:07.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitfinex Parent Company iFinex Considers $150 Million Share Buyback]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b18eaa91</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/bitfinex-parent-company-ifinex-considers-150-million-share-buyback/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T13:42:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The owner of crypto exchange Bitfinex, iFinex Inc.,  
is considering a share buyback offer of $150 million. This initiative aims to  
provide relief to the investors, who were originally compensated with BFX  
tokens after Bitfinex suffered a substantial hack in 2016.  
According to a report by Bloomberg, this proposal is  
equivalent to 9% of iFinex's outstanding capital and places the company at a  
valuation of $1.7 billion. The offer targets shareholders who obtained iFinex's  
stock as part of a swap arrangement with the investment platform BnkToTheFuture  
in 2016. 
Bitfinex Navigates Control and Compliance
Additionally, the proposed share buyback is driven  
by a desire to have more control over the company's operations, especially with  
the increasing regulatory scrutiny in the cr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sinterklaas: On Belief, Chocolate Coinage, and Grownups Still Asleep]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b18ee0e0</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/sinterklaas-on-belief-chocolate-coinage-and-grownups-still-asleep"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T13:40:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well, well, well. It’s that time of year again in the Netherlands. Not just to celebrate the second Bitcoin Conference in Amsterdam, but also the arrival by steamboat of our red caped Saint, the Holy Man himself, patron of boats, sailors, and little children: Sinterklaas. Yes, he’s the bringer of gifts in the shoes of Dutch kids and swaps a carrot or drawing for a gold ribboned package of your deepest desire. He’s the original boss, Santa's precursor (too bad Murica), and my red pill incarnate.

 Back at primary school, when I still ‘believed’, it was Micky, a kid from class, who burst my magical bubble. He was a funny boy and used to play tricks on everybody. For instance, he’d ask you coke or sprite, and whatever your response, he’d twist your wrist so badly you’d experience the ‘fizz’. …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin Graffiti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US CPI Data and Binance vs. SEC Hearings: What to Expect]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18962065/US-CPI-Data-and-Binance-vs-SEC-Hearings-What-to-Expect</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18962065/US-CPI-Data-and-Binance-vs-SEC-Hearings-What-to-Expect"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T13:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Does Circle Bridging to Polygon Mean for USDC Users?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18962055/What-Does-Circle-Bridging-to-Polygon-Mean-for-USDC-Users</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18962055/What-Does-Circle-Bridging-to-Polygon-Mean-for-USDC-Users"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T13:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Circle's groundbreaking move to mint USD Coin (USDC) natively on Polygon promises a revolution in seamless, cost-effective blockchain transactions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is the Bitcoin Halving? How Bitcoin's Supply is Limited.]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=17757</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-the-bitcoin-halving"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T13:34:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every four years, the amount of Bitcoin awarded to miners is halved, an event known as the Bitcoin halving.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Hussey,Ki Chong Tran,Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Moves Lower Following PPI Data; XDC Network Becomes Top Loser]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18962087/Bitcoin-Moves-Lower-Following-PPI-Data-XDC-Network-Becomes-Top-Loser</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18962087/Bitcoin-Moves-Lower-Following-PPI-Data-XDC-Network-Becomes-Top-Loser"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T13:32:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (CRYPTO: BTC) moved lower, with the cryptocurrency prices trading below the $27,200 level on Wednesday. Ethereum (CRYPTO: ETH), also edged lower, trading below the key $1,600 mark this morning. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building the Global Financial System with David Marcus]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18962066/Building-the-Global-Financial-System-with-David-Marcus</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18962066/Building-the-Global-Financial-System-with-David-Marcus"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T13:32:01.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miners Unload 20,000 BTC In A Week, Apple-Backed Right To Repair Is Now A Law In California - Top Headlines Today While US Was Sleeping]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18962088/Bitcoin-Miners-Unload-20000-BTC-In-A-Week-Apple-Backed-Right-To-Repair-Is-Now-A-Law-In-California-Top-Headlines-Today-While-US-Was-Sleeping</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18962088/Bitcoin-Miners-Unload-20000-BTC-In-A-Week-Apple-Backed-Right-To-Repair-Is-Now-A-Law-In-California-Top-Headlines-Today-While-US-Was-Sleeping"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T13:31:28.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This is how Bitcoin must perform to sustain its mining industry]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18962048/This-is-how-Bitcoin-must-perform-to-sustain-its-mining-industry</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18962048/This-is-how-Bitcoin-must-perform-to-sustain-its-mining-industry"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T13:30:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As per recent data, the cost to mine Bitcoin was nearly $24,000. But BTC’s price must rise above $40,000 after 2024's halving for miners to earn profits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[io.net to launch first GPU-enabled decentralized computing network for AI]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18962017/ionet-to-launch-first-GPU-enabled-decentralized-computing-network-for-AI</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18962017/ionet-to-launch-first-GPU-enabled-decentralized-computing-network-for-AI"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T13:30:13.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond crypto: Zero-knowledge proofs show potential from voting to finance]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18962050/Beyond-crypto-Zero-knowledge-proofs-show-potential-from-voting-to-finance</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18962050/Beyond-crypto-Zero-knowledge-proofs-show-potential-from-voting-to-finance"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An emerging cryptographic technology may provide help with two gaping 21st-century needs: Privacy and truth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRPL AMM: These XRP Liquidity Pools Would Be 'Fascinating to Watch']]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18962022/XRPL-AMM-These-XRP-Liquidity-Pools-Would-Be-Fascinating-to-Watch</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18962022/XRPL-AMM-These-XRP-Liquidity-Pools-Would-Be-Fascinating-to-Watch"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tornado Cash Trading Volumes Nosedived 90% After U.S. Sanctions]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b18afcdb</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/10/11/tornado-cash-trading-volumes-nosedived-90-after-us-sanctions/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T13:13:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While North Korean hackers have mostly moved to other Bitcoin mixers, some illicit use of Tornado Cash continues, a report from TRM Labs says.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Prime Broker Membrane Labs Raises $20M From Brevan Howard, Point72 and Jane Street]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b18afcbc</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/10/11/crypto-prime-broker-membrane-labs-raises-20m-from-brevan-howard-point72-and-jane-street/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T13:13:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Membrane Labs, a cryptocurrency-focused trading and lending platform, has raised $20 million in a Series A funding round, with participation from big names like Brevan Howard Digital and Point72 Ventures. The capital will be used to help build the type of grown-up trading infrastructure the crypto space needs in order to avoid further disasters.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Mover Americas: JPMorgan Goes Live With First Blockchain-Based Collateral Settlement]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b17769a6</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/10/11/first-mover-americas-jpmorgan-goes-live-with-first-blockchain-based-collateral-settlement/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T12:44:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest price moves in bitcoin (BTC) and crypto markets in context for Oct. 11, 2023. First Mover is CoinDesk’s daily newsletter that contextualizes the latest actions in the crypto markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lyllah Ledesma, Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Technical Analysis: BTC Hits 10-Day Low, Caroline Ellison Confirms Fraud on Behalf of SBF]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b17136eb</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-ethereum-technical-analysis-btc-hits-10-day-low-caroline-ellison-confirms-fraud-on-behalf-of-sbf/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T12:33:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin slipped to a ten-day low in today’s session, as the trial of Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF) continues. Caroline Ellison, the former CEO of Alameda Research, alleged that she committed fraud at the behest of SBF. Markets also declined ahead of the upcoming U.S. Producer Price Index, which is a key gauge of inflation.
 
Bitcoin
 
Bitcoin (BTC) moved lower for a fourth straight day, with many traders keeping one eye on the SBF proceedings.
 
Ellison stated that, “I sent balance sheets at the direction of Sam that made Alameda’s balances look less risky to investors.”
 
Following a high of $27,605.82 on Tuesday, BTC/USD dropped to an intraday low of $27,017.64 earlier in today’s session.
 
 
Bitcoin chart by TradingView
 

 
 

 
This plunge pushed the world’s largest cryptocurrency to its weakest point since the start of October.
 
Looking at the chart, the move resulted in bitcoin briefly falling below a floor at $27,100, prior to bulls reentering the market.
 
The relative strength index (RSI) also fell below a support point of its own at 53.00, and is currently tracking at 51.67.
 
BTC has since rebounded from its earlier low, and is currently trading at $27,292.17.
 
 
Ethereum
 
Ethereum (ETH) returned above a key support point of $1,565, after price broke out of this level earlier in the day.
 
ETH/USD edged to a low of $1,551.68 earlier in the day, before bouncing back and hitting its current price of $1,575.39.
 
Despite the rally, this remains lower than Tuesday’s peak at $1,587.56, and keeps ethereum near a one-month low.
 
 
Ethereum chart by TradingView
 

 
 

 
As a result of the recent sell-off, the 10-day (red) moving average has now crossed with its 25-day (blue) counterpart.
 
Should this crossover continue to mature in a downtrend, there is a good chance that ETH will soon fall below $1,500.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
Could there be further downward pressure in ethereum this week? Leave your thoughts in the comments below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[X Takes Center Stage in Web3 Marketing for Crypto Projects]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b17f5bd1</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/x-takes-center-stage-in-web3-marketing-for-crypto-projects/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T11:53:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you want to build a successful Web3 marketing campaign? Or maybe you’re just wondering what fuels the success of crypto projects in the bustling realm of Web3 marketing. Well, then you better start with X.
 If you're an entrepreneur, or a marketer, or even just a casual enthusiast in the blockchain space, you're likely familiar with the buzz around the social media platform formerly known as Twitter. But, what exactly makes it so pivotal to effective Web3 marketing? Let's dive right into the heart of the matter.
The Core of a Vibrant Web3 Community
It’s crystal clear that a thriving community is the heart and soul of any crypto project. But, it poses a logistical challenge that has baffled legions of entrepreneurs, tossing a proverbial wrench into the most solid business blueprints. So,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Haldorsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What The Recent Spike In Shiba Inu Exchange Inflow Means For SHIB’s Price]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b17fa2ae</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/spike-in-shiba-inu-inflow/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T11:51:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The future of SHIB’s price has been caught in a whirlwind of uncertainty in recent times, even as the updates continue to spring regarding the Shiba Inu community. Crypto exchanges witnessed a recent inflow of SHIB tokens this week, indicating a significant price action could be on the horizon for the popular meme coin. 
 
Shiba Inu Bearish Sentiment
 
All data points to Shiba Inu in a current bearish sentiment, and the recent inflows into crypto exchanges aren’t helping matters. According to IntoTheBlock, indicators and on-chain signals point to a bearish sentiment, with only 8% of holders making money at a current price.
 
 

 
 
Data compiled by on-chain analytics platform CryptoQuant has shown a similar market behavior as investors seem to be moving their holdings to exchanges for sell…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong Monetary Authority Advances e-HKD Tests, Mbridge Project]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b17a791a</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/hong-kong-monetary-authority-advances-e-hkd-tests-mbridge-project/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T11:32:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Hong Kong Monetary Authority (HKMA) has recently completed a series of tests regarding the programmability of the e-HKD, the proposed Hong Kong central bank digital currency (CBDC). While still in its initial phases, the e-HKD presents “interesting” use cases, HKMA CEO Eddie Yue stressed. He also revealed that the Mbridge project aims to have a minimum viable product for mid-2024.
Hong Kong Monetary Authority Advances e-HKD Research
The Hong Kong Monetary Authority (HKMA) has recently offered new insight into the different tests conducted with the e-HKD, a proposed central bank digital currency (CBDC). Eddie Yue, CEO of the HKMA, revealed that these tests focused on the programmable function of the e-HKD, allowing the issuer to establish certain limits in which the digital currency can…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitter Thread Suggests Sam Bankman-Fried Mulled Shutting Alameda Months Before FTX Collapse]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200985</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200985/twitter-thread-suggests-sam-bankman-fried-mulled-shutting-alameda-months-before-ftx-collapse"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T11:13:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Per a Twitter thread draft, Bankman-Fried called Alameda Research “It was one of my largest successes–and then, briefly, largest failures."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. State Regulators Intervene in Coinbase’s Unregistered Securities Case]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b165d899</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/10/11/us-state-regulators-intervene-in-coinbases-unregistered-securities-case/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T11:09:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amicus briefs filed to support the SEC argue crypto is insignificant, only used for speculation, and captured by existing investor-protection rules]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack Schickler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Is Fundamentally Different From Other Cryptocurrencies: Fidelity Digital Assets]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b160f392</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/10/11/bitcoin-is-fundamentally-different-from-other-cryptocurrencies-fidelity-digital-assets/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T10:49:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto’s technological breakthrough was not as a superior payment method but as a superior form of money, the report said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Canny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bored Bitcoin Analysts Point to McRib Meme for Bullish Return]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200966</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200966/bored-bitcoin-analysts-point-mcrib-meme-bullish-return"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T10:25:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The McRib is back and analysts are busy trying to pin Bitcoin and stock performances to the McDonald’s sandwich relaunch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitmain Halts Employee Salaries Amid Financial Woes, Report]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b16eb01f</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitmain-halts-employee-salaries-amid-financial-woes-report/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T10:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mining hardware manufacturer Bitmain has temporarily suspended salary payments to its employees, a media report has revealed. News of the move comes along with information suggesting that the crypto giant is experiencing financial difficulties with poor results from its operations.
 
Antminer Maker Bitmain Reportedly Delays Salaries and Bonuses
 
Bitmain, a major producer of bitcoin mining devices, has halted salaries and other incentives, according to inside sources quoted by Chinese media. In a notice reportedly confirmed by employees, Bitmain said its September cash flow has not turned positive.
 
The company was worried in particular about the orders for new mining machines, the report detailed, and decided to postpone some employee payments for September until later in October, depend…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lubomir Tassev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cyprus Plans to Crackdown Unregulated Firms with Hefty Fines and Imprisonment]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b16ed468</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/cyprus-plans-to-crackdown-unregulated-firms-with-hefty-fines-and-imprisonment/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T10:09:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The financial market regulator in Cyprus is considering the introduction of a severe monetary penalty of up to €350,000, imprisonment of up to five years, or both for cryptocurrency service providers who failed to register with relevant authorities, Cyprus Mail reported.
Crackdown on Non-Compliant Crypto Firms
Although there is no official confirmation yet from the Cyprus Securities and Exchange Commission (CySEC), it is planning to impose stringent penalties after the submission of a proposed legislative amendment to the 'Prevention and Suppression of Money Laundering Law', which seeks to align the Cypriot rules with global standards set by the Financial Action Task Force (FATF).
The proposal specified that the Cypriot companies dealing with crypto assets must register with CySEC. The rul…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arnab Shome</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ellison Was CEO But SBF Was Still Boss at Alameda, Her Testimony Suggests]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b1681773</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/10/11/ellison-was-ceo-but-sbf-was-still-boss-at-alameda-her-testimony-suggests/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T10:01:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The testimony of Caroline Ellison, the former business, romantic – and by her estimation, criminal – partner of Sam Bankman-Fried, whom she identified upon prosecutors’ request – began in the vaguest of ways.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Nelson, Sam Kessler, Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HODLers Stash BTC Worth $1.35B Each Month, Onchain Data Show]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b1681753</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/10/11/hodlers-stash-btc-worth-135b-each-month-onchain-data-show/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T10:01:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The continued accumulation shows tightening supply and a widespread reluctance to transact, according to Glassnode.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon and Immutable Want to Make it Easier to Launch Crypto Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200895</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200895/immutable-amazon-web-services-team-up-help-blockchain-games-scale"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T22:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto firm Immutable has joined Amazon Web Services' ISV Accelerate Program to develop blockchain gaming infrastructure solutions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BAPE Bets on Virtual Pet Nostalgia With Tamagotchi Streetwear Collab]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200933</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200933/tamagotchi-bathing-ape-bape-bandai-virtual-pets-streetwear"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T21:57:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Bathing Ape (BAPE) and Bandai’s classic Tamagotchi brand are teaming up for a fashion drop and co-branded virtual pets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Environmental Groups Need to Dig Deeper Into AI Energy Use, Researcher Says]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200932</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200932/ai-energy-use-environmental-concerns-crypto-mining"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T21:40:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Energy analyst Alex de Vries says limited data is one reason there was a slow response to the emerging threat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[As the Halving Approaches, Bitcoin Miner Hut 8 Is Selling Zero BTC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200922</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200922/as-the-halving-approaches-bitcoin-miner-hut-8-is-selling-zero-btc"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T21:13:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hut 8 says it is bullish on Bitcoin's long term price, and doesn't need to sell any to finance operations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Tezos (XTZ)?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=5705</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/tezos"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T21:08:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tezos is a crypto platform that supports smart contracts and Dapps. It also looks to evolve faster than other blockchains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Hussey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lightning Network Growth Is a ‘Shock‘, Says Bitcoin Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200923</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200923/shocking-growth-lightning-network-river-financial-analyst"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T21:05:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to a new report by River Financial, Bitcoin’s layer-2 solution has grown 1,212% over the past two years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Geopolitical Instability Makes Bitcoin a Good Bet, Says Paul Tudor Jones]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200848</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200848/geopolitical-instability-makes-bitcoin-a-good-bet-paul-tudor-jones"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T20:09:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The billionaire investor continues to praise Bitcoin as a safe haven asset during times of uncertainty.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['We Do Not Speak Your Language': Fashion Brands Signal Crypto Divide in Milan]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200896</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200896/we-do-not-speak-your-language-fashion-brands-signal-crypto-divide-milan"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T19:02:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Milan Fashion Week included prominent examples of fashion giants embracing emerging tech, but also hesitance from some brands.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leila Ismailova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Caroline Ellison: Sam Bankman-Fried Told Me to Take Billions From FTX Customers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200769</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200769/caroline-ellison-sam-bankman-fried-billions-ftx"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T17:28:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a brief hearing at Bankman-Fried's trial, Caroline Ellison told jurors that Bankman-Fried "directed her to commit crimes."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo,André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sony PlayStation 5 Slim Console Revealed—And It's More Expensive]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200863</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200863/new-playstation-5-console-announcement-size-price-sony"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T17:19:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The rumored slim Sony PlayStation 5 is coming in November with tweaks and upgrades, and a higher base price.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trader Joe’s Wants All Profits in Trademark Lawsuit Against Trader Joe DeFi Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200862</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200862/trader-joes-wants-all-profits-in-copyright-lawsuit-against-trader-joe-defi-platform"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T17:15:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grocery store chain Trader Joe's is once again attempting to shut down the similarly-named DeFi platform, after failing to last year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum DeFi Exchange AirSwap Rolls Out NFT Marketplace]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200764</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200764/ethereum-defi-exchange-airswap-rolls-out-nft-marketplace"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T17:01:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The DEX is marking its sixth anniversary with upgrades across its peer-to-peer crypto platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Look: Nintendo's Animal Crossing Gets the Lego Treatment]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200849</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200849/nintendo-animal-crossing-lego-sets-coming-march-2024"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T15:46:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Five Lego Animal Crossing sets are launching in 2024, starring some of the Nintendo game’s best-known characters.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Trial of Sam Bankman-Fried: Live Blog, Latest News and Insights]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199892</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199892/trial-sam-bankman-fried-live-blog-latest-news-insights"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T14:41:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried faces seven criminal charges related to the dramatic collapse of his crypto empire. Here's the latest on his trial.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried's Defense Seeks Details of Co-Founder's Alameda Loan Deals]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200839</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200839/sam-bankman-frieds-defense-seeks-details-co-founders-alameda-loan-deals"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T14:23:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bankman-Fried's legal team wants to know to what extent Wang's legal advice influenced his signing off on loans with Alameda Research.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Key Technologies Streamlining the Crypto User Experience]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200689</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200689/5-key-technologies-streamlining-the-crypto-user-experience"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T11:35:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These new technologies are helping to overcome blockchain’s early UX challenges and onboard new users to crypto, DeFi and Web3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Hussey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Israel Authorities Freeze Hamas-Linked Crypto Accounts on Binance]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200837</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200837/israel-authorities-freeze-hamas-linked-crypto-accounts-binance"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T10:28:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Israeli authorities, in coordination with the crypto exchange Binance, froze accounts suspected with suspected links to Hamas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tezos Jumps 7% on South Korean Volume Spike, Futures Liquidations]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200827</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200827/tezos-jumps-south-korean-volume-spike-futures-liquidations"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T10:05:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 24-hour trading volume for Tezos' native token XTZ jumped more than seven times its monthly average amid the latest rally.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Layer-2 Blockchains Host Most Ethereum Transactions: Messari]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200820</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200820/layer-2-majority-ethereum-transactions-messari"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T01:36:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The explosive launch of Base and the virality of friend.tech are behind the latest numbers, says analyst Kunal Goel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enlisting AI in Medicine and Longevity Research Will Be a ‘Net Positive’: Microsoft VP]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200814</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200814/ai-longevity-summit-medicine-healthcare-peter-lee"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T00:43:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Computer scientist Peter Lee said GPT-4 helped restore ‘family harmony’ in healthcare conversations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CrypToadz NFT Sells for $1.6 Million in Ethereum Linked to Tornado Cash]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200807</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200807/cryptoadz-nft-sale-1-6-million-ethereum-linked-tornado-cash"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T23:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A painful “fat finger” mistake—or obvious money laundering? This seven-figure CrypToadz NFT purchase has sparked fierce speculation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dating App Tool Upgraded with AI Is Poised to Power Catfishing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200787</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200787/lovegpt-ai-dating-apps-catfishing-hack-avast"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T22:03:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avast calls out an old tool that's learned new tricks, using AI to get even better at running romantic scams on dating apps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rage Quit? Unity CEO Departs After New Fees Pissed Off Game Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200797</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200797/rage-quit-unity-ceo-departs-after-new-fees-pissed-off-game-developers"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T21:54:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last month, Unity announced a "runtime fee" set to start in 2024, enraging developers. Now, longtime CEO John Riccitiello is leaving.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried Lawyers May Already Be Angling for an Appeal, Says Former Prosecutor]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200767</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200767/sam-bankman-fried-lawyers-may-already-be-angling-for-an-appeal-says-former-prosecutor"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T21:42:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Judge Kaplan called the defense’s repetitive cross-examination into question several times last week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Ukuhumusha’—A New Way to Hack OpenAI's ChatGPT]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200763</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200763/language-translation-chatgpt-hack"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T20:26:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers have discovered OpenAI's GPT-4’s security settings are ill-equipped to handle languages not commonly fed into its training data.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why NFL Alumni Are Turning to NFTs to Support Retired Football Players]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200684</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200684/why-nfl-alumni-turning-nfts-support-retired-football-players"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T19:46:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NFL Alumni Association is teaming with Aventus to help veteran players launch NFTs via Polkadot, with the aim of supporting former pros.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Cohen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Just One Game on Solana Is Doing More Daily Transactions Than All of Polygon]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200733</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200733/one-game-solana-doing-more-daily-transactions-than-polygon"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T19:34:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SAGE Labs, a web game from the team behind Star Atlas, made up 15% of all Solana activity on Sunday—and surpassed Polygon's network total.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Crypto Aid Israel' Launches to Raise Funds Amid Gaza Conflict]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200737</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200737/crypto-aiding-israel-gaza-war-intensifies"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T18:57:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The organization aims to raise funds for displaced Israelis since violence erupted in the region on Saturday. Gazans are also raising cryptocurrency.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Forks, Sui, Aptos and Apecoin Hit Hardest as Market Plunges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200685</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200685/bitcoin-forks-sui-aptos-and-apecoin-hit-hardest-as-market-plunges"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T18:33:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A number of altcoins—including two Bitcoin forks—have faltered as markets sank today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your Fantasy, On Demand: How AI Porn Is Reshaping a Taboo Industry]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200502</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200502/how-ai-porn-will-reshape-industry"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T18:08:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Generative AI makes it easier for adult content to be completely customized on demand. But is this the future we want?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Ethereum Foundation Just Sold $2.76 Million in ETH]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200680</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200680/the-ethereum-foundation-just-sold-2-76-million-in-eth"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T14:16:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s magnitudes smaller than previous transfers, but historically when the Ethereum Foundation moves ETH it’s been bearish.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Could Human Photosynthesis Be Possible?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200679</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/could-human-photosynthesis-be-possible"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T13:58:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Human photosynthesis, the belief that humans may someday be able to benefit from sunlight by turning it into energy in the same manner as plants, is broadly connected to a larger movement known as transhumanism.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Reiff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Shrapnel's Marketplace, New Map, and 'AI Director' Feature]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/F5RQCmvH/inside-shrapnels-marketplace-new-map-and-ai-director-feature</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/F5RQCmvH/inside-shrapnels-marketplace-new-map-and-ai-director-feature"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T16:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin chats with Shrapnel's Head of Studio Don Norbury to get the latest updates on how the NFT-powered first-person sci-fi extraction shooter's development is progressing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Art of the Times': Art Blocks Founder Erick Calderon on the State of Generative Art]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zSjfRrl5/art-of-the-times-art-blocks-founder-erick-calderon-on-the-state-of-generative-art</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zSjfRrl5/art-of-the-times-art-blocks-founder-erick-calderon-on-the-state-of-generative-art"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T18:10:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Art Blocks founder and CEO Erick Calderon sat down with Sander Lutz, lead culture reporter at Decrypt's SCENE, at Art Blocks Marfa Weekend 2023. They discuss the evolution of the company and the generative art world, along with what draws art enthusiasts to be an active part of the community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt Learn: Digital Ownership Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/6udZCotB/decrypt-learn-digital-ownership-explained</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/6udZCotB/decrypt-learn-digital-ownership-explained"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T10:57:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most powerful aspects of blockchain technology is its ability to provide us genuine ownership of our digital assets. This is called digital ownership. In this video, we’ll deep dive into digital ownership, why it matters, and how web3 makes owning digital assets like our social networks, music libraries, personal data, and beyond possible. Author: Clarissa Watson, Senior Writer at Consensys.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Martin Shkreli on E/ACC and SBF in Prison]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QONaWXKZ/martin-shkreli-on-e-acc-and-sbf-in-prison</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QONaWXKZ/martin-shkreli-on-e-acc-and-sbf-in-prison"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T22:03:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reza Jafery and Martin Shkreli sit down for a casual conversation about the growing movement that is E/ACC, what songs they could recite at gunpoint, and whether or not SBF will thrive or just survive during his time in prison.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Can AI Do in Gaming?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JKuqCMao/what-can-ai-do-in-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JKuqCMao/what-can-ai-do-in-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T17:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI Arena CEO Brandon Da Silva and COO Wei Xie discuss how artificial intelligence can shape the video game experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['There Are No Real Standards': Ready Player Me CEO Timmu Tõke on Building for an Open Gaming Ecosystem]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TH3KEAI0/there-are-no-real-standards-ready-player-me-ceo-timmu-tke-on-building-for-an-open-gaming-ecosystem</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TH3KEAI0/there-are-no-real-standards-ready-player-me-ceo-timmu-tke-on-building-for-an-open-gaming-ecosystem"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T17:29:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Timmu Tõke, co-founder and CEO of Ready Player Me, joins Decrypt contributor Ryan Gladwin to discuss the startup's approach to powering avatars that are interoperable across games and metaverse platforms—and what's needed to convince the industry to adopt standards and open up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain Is 'Only Way' Forward for Gaming, Says Shrapnel Studio Head]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/fhoy7Z8f/blockchain-is-only-way-forward-for-gaming-says-shrapnel-studio-head</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/fhoy7Z8f/blockchain-is-only-way-forward-for-gaming-says-shrapnel-studio-head"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T21:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shrapnel Studio Head Don Norbury tells Kate Irwin the reasons why the upcoming first-person shooter game will offer a wide range of NFTs. He also reveals team-based gameplay plans and shares how game maps have already changed this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Social Media Sentiment Is Key to Crypto Price Discovery]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/981TBppa/social-media-sentiment-is-key-to-crypto-price-discovery</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/981TBppa/social-media-sentiment-is-key-to-crypto-price-discovery"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T23:47:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sacha Ghebali, Director of Strategy and Business Development at The TIE, says social media sentiment remains a key factor in price movements for major cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin and Ethereum. However, he notes that sentiment has turned more negative lately amid regulatory uncertainty. Ghebali believes events like the Ripple lawsuit ruling significantly impacted sentiment and prices. André Beganski interviewed him at Messari Mainnet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[500Altcoins discusses DeFi Summer and the Dubai Crypto Scene - This Time Will Be Different - Episode 2]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cI7p8AK3/500altcoins-discusses-defi-summer-and-the-dubai-crypto-scene-this-time-will-be-different-episode-2</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cI7p8AK3/500altcoins-discusses-defi-summer-and-the-dubai-crypto-scene-this-time-will-be-different-episode-2"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our host Reza Jafery is joined by Gareth Fenney aka 500Altcoins. They discuss the glory days of DeFi Summer and whether or not its a smart move for builders in the crypto space to relocate to Dubai.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralize Derivatives Trading with Custom Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/lfmwAjB9/decentralize-derivatives-trading-with-custom-blockchain</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/lfmwAjB9/decentralize-derivatives-trading-with-custom-blockchain"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T10:37:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Gogel of dYdX discusses how the decentralized exchange is building a custom blockchain to fully decentralize derivatives trading. He explained how the new dYdX chain will allow validators to run order books in memory, enabling decentralized order matching at scale. This shift aims to increase security and transparency for traders while maintaining the performance of centralized exchanges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Most Crypto Users Don't Trust Themselves to Keep Their Seed Phrase Safe: Ledger CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/0kYf2Qed/most-crypto-users-dont-trust-themselves-to-keep-their-seed-phrase-safe-ledger-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/0kYf2Qed/most-crypto-users-dont-trust-themselves-to-keep-their-seed-phrase-safe-ledger-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Stacy Elliott sat down with Ledger CEO Pascal Gauthier to discuss crypto custody post-FTX, and the hardware wallet manufacturer's controversial Ledger Recover service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Accounting Challenges and Opportunities]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/0Sezz6pZ/crypto-accounting-challenges-and-opportunities</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/0Sezz6pZ/crypto-accounting-challenges-and-opportunities"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As crypto matures, accounting and tax regulations are evolving. Amy Kalnoki of Bitwave explains how her company helps crypto companies properly account for digital assets. She notes the importance of flexibility as new crypto assets emerge and regulations change. Stacy Elliott interviewed her at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[India's 1% Crypto Tax Has Been a Nightmare for High-Frequency Traders, Says Shardeum CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/fxygwLvH/indias-1-crypto-tax-has-been-a-nightmare-for-high-frequency-traders-says-shardeum-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/fxygwLvH/indias-1-crypto-tax-has-been-a-nightmare-for-high-frequency-traders-says-shardeum-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As India figures out its regulatory approach to the crypto industry, one thing is clear to Shardeum co-founder Nischal Shetty: “If you're a high-frequency trader, you can't afford to lose a percentage every time you sell,” he told Decrypt's Andre Beganski at Messari Mainnet in New York. “That's something that's caused a lot of issues.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Newly Partnered with Visa, Solana Focuses on Reliability]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/MZoxvulr/newly-partnered-with-visa-solana-focuses-on-reliability</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/MZoxvulr/newly-partnered-with-visa-solana-focuses-on-reliability"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana has improved network reliability through upgrades like Quick and local fee markets. It recently partnered with Visa to allow settling transactions in USDC on Solana. This could enable merchants to receive instant payments and save on credit card processing fees. Stacy Elliott spoke with Austin Federa, Head of Strategy for the Solana Foundation, at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Need to Start Thinking About How we Make Crypto Easy to Use: Robinhood Crypto General Manager]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PLZ0FpdC/we-need-to-start-thinking-about-how-we-make-crypto-easy-to-use-robinhood-crypto-general-manager</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PLZ0FpdC/we-need-to-start-thinking-about-how-we-make-crypto-easy-to-use-robinhood-crypto-general-manager"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Stacy Elliott sat down with Robinhood Crypto general manager Johann Kerbrat at Messari Mainnet 2023, to talk about the trading platform's crypto wallet, onboarding new users through simplicity, and keeping platform fees sustainable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin's Narrative Is Shifting Towards Layer-2 Solutions]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/axArPRp3/bitcoins-narrative-is-shifting-towards-layer-2-solutions</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/axArPRp3/bitcoins-narrative-is-shifting-towards-layer-2-solutions"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rich Rines, original Core DAO contributor and former Coinbase engineer, discusses how the narrative around Bitcoin is shifting in 2023. While Bitcoin remains digital gold, new layer 2 solutions are emerging to unlock more utility and value from the huge amounts of capital stored in Bitcoin. He says these innovations can benefit Bitcoin holders while keeping Bitcoin maximalists happy by building outside the base layer. André Beganski interviewed him at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Regulation Threatens U.S. Dominance of Financial Markets, Says CoinRoutes CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/CrpvzFjL/regulation-threatens-us-dominance-of-financial-markets-says-coinroutes-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/CrpvzFjL/regulation-threatens-us-dominance-of-financial-markets-says-coinroutes-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dave Weisberger, Co-Founder and CEO of CoinRoutes, argued that excessive regulation in the U.S. threatens to undermine the country's long-standing dominance in global financial markets. He warned that other countries are embracing blockchain and crypto to build more efficient digital markets, which could cause the US to lose its competitive edge and trillions in GDP. Weisberger said CoinRoutes is now focusing more on expanding internationally due to restrictive policies in the U.S. He was interviewed by André Beganski of Decrypt at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Explosive Growth Ahead for Enterprise Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/xXOrNbX9/explosive-growth-ahead-for-enterprise-blockchain</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/xXOrNbX9/explosive-growth-ahead-for-enterprise-blockchain"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paul Brody drives Ernst & Young (EY) initiatives and investments in blockchain technology across consulting, audit, and tax business lines. He says enterprise blockchain adoption is nearing an inflection point. Brody believes blockchains will one day handle 40 billion transactions daily across industries like automotive and pharma. Stacy Elliott interviewed him at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Developer-Friendly zkRollup to Scale Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/OvAFgxTd/building-a-developer-friendly-zkrollup-to-scale-ethereum</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/OvAFgxTd/building-a-developer-friendly-zkrollup-to-scale-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daniel Helm, head of Developer Relations at Scroll, discussess how they are building a zkRollup to scale Ethereum transactions and lower fees. He explained their focus on creating a seamless developer experience by maintaining Ethereum's ethos and tooling. Scroll aims to launch their mainnet soon, providing more scalable blockspace for Ethereum developers. Stacy Elliott of Decrypt interviewed him at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Base as a 'Bridge, Not an Island']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/oZPr7bzY/base-as-a-bridge-not-an-island</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/oZPr7bzY/base-as-a-bridge-not-an-island"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase's Jesse Pollak, creator of layer-2 blockchain Base, says the launch of the network has exceeded expectations, even if plans changed along the way. He believes Arbitrum One will help bring billions onto blockchain by enabling seamless user experiences. Stacy Elliott interviewed him at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>