<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-04-26T18:19:10.303Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-04-26T18:19:10.303Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 10 Tips for Every Bitcoin Multisig Beginner]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7436225ebb</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/guides/top-10-tips-for-every-bitcoin-multisig-beginner"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T18:14:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Originally published on Unchained.com.
Unchained is the official US Collaborative Custody partner of Bitcoin Magazine and an integral sponsor of related content published through Bitcoin Magazine. For more information on services offered, custody products, and the relationship between Unchained and Bitcoin Magazine, please visit our website. 

As technical director on the Concierge team at Unchained, I’ve fielded countless client questions about bitcoin multisig. If you’re just beginning to understand the benefits of multisig and how it works in a collaborative custody context, I hope these ten tips will address some of your questions.
Bitcoin doesn’t live on your device
The phrase hardware wallet might make it seem like your bitcoin live inside the wallet itself, but that’s not the case—b…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Unchained</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin halving won’t be enough to sustain a bull run: Kaiko Research]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19439887/Bitcoin-halving-wont-be-enough-to-sustain-a-bull-run-Kaiko-Research</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19439887/Bitcoin-halving-wont-be-enough-to-sustain-a-bull-run-Kaiko-Research"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T18:14:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin's latest halving event is unlikely to trigger a sustained bull run over the next 12 to 18 months, according to the report "Bitcoins Fourth Halving: This Time is Different?" by analysis firm Kaiko.Despite historical periods of substantial returns post-halving, the current climate is...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin Defies Regulatory Challenges: Seeks Partnership with OpenAI]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e743622aa0b</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/worldcoin-defies-regulatory-challenges-seeks-partnership-with-openai/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T18:13:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin is eying a potential partnership with  
artificial intelligence research firm OpenAI, according to a report by  
Bloomberg. This latest development arrives despite the regulatory hurdles  
facing the digital identity platform over privacy concerns. Through its parent company, Tools for Humanity, the cryptocurrency project plans to expand its services.
Navigating Regulatory Challenges  

Most recently, Spain and Portugal recently raised concerns over  
the inclusion of children in the project's iris scanning initiative, prompting  
regulatory action. Previously, the project collaborated with  
cybersecurity firm Okta Inc. to offer an authentication service. The company's  
identity systems offer solutions for validating individuals in an increasingly  
digital world dominated by AI. 
With the rise of artificial intelligence, the need to  
distinguish between humans and bots is important. Sam Altman, the Co-Founder of  
Worldcoin, is renowned for his involvement with OpenAI. Currently, he serves as  
the CEO of the company. Amidst regulatory challenges, Tools for Humanity is  
enhancing its product. The firm is planning to launch a layer-2 blockchain  
called World Chain and improve the orb device.
However, despite a successful fundraising round last  
year, Tools for Humanity is reportedly facing uncertainty in tapping into the  
crypto market for additional funding. Market volatility and pricing  
fluctuations have prompted a reevaluation of planned token sales.
Expect ongoing updates as this story evolves. 
 
  
 
  
This article was written by Jared Kirui at www.financemagnates.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong’s crypto ETFs off-limits for mainland China investors]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19439888/Hong-Kongs-crypto-ETFs-off-limits-for-mainland-China-investors</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19439888/Hong-Kongs-crypto-ETFs-off-limits-for-mainland-China-investors"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T18:12:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong is all set to roll out its first spot Bitcoin and Ethereum ETFs, but here’s the thing. If you’re investing from mainland ChiChina and Russia almost completely rid of US dollar in mutual tradena, you’re out of luck. Despite the close financial ties between Hong Kong and the mainland,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BitMEX Founder Arthur Hayes Says One Catalyst Could Lead to a Re-Acceleration of the Crypto Market]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19439873/BitMEX-Founder-Arthur-Hayes-Says-One-Catalyst-Could-Lead-to-a-Re-Acceleration-of-the-Crypto-Market</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19439873/BitMEX-Founder-Arthur-Hayes-Says-One-Catalyst-Could-Lead-to-a-Re-Acceleration-of-the-Crypto-Market"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T18:05:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BitMEX co-founder Arthur Hayes believes one catalyst could re-ignite bullish momentum for the cryptocurrency market. Hayes tells his 502,700 followers on the social media platform X that more liquidity could soon flood the markets, boosting risk-on assets like crypto. He is referring to the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Whales Inject Coinbase With 457M DOGE: Dump Coming?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19439871/Dogecoin-Whales-Inject-Coinbase-With-457M-DOGE-Dump-Coming</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19439871/Dogecoin-Whales-Inject-Coinbase-With-457M-DOGE-Dump-Coming"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T18:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin gets caught up in a massive digital asset offloading chronicle, putting investors on edge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China Dumps $74,000,000,000 in US Treasuries in One Year As Two BRICS Nations Say They’ve Abandoned Dollar in Mutual Trade]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19439872/China-Dumps-74000000000-in-US-Treasuries-in-One-Year-As-Two-BRICS-Nations-Say-Theyve-Abandoned-Dollar-in-Mutual-Trade</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19439872/China-Dumps-74000000000-in-US-Treasuries-in-One-Year-As-Two-BRICS-Nations-Say-Theyve-Abandoned-Dollar-in-Mutual-Trade"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T18:04:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[China has sold more than $74 billion in US Treasuries in the last year, according to new numbers from the Treasury Department. China has decreased its Treasuries holdings from $849 billion to $775 billion between the beginning of Q2 2023 and Q2 2024, reaching its lowest holdings since 2009....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trouble for Pendle?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19439869/Trouble-for-Pendle</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19439869/Trouble-for-Pendle"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T18:03:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Has PENDLE's epic run finally topped out?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jack Mallers: $250k Bitcoin this Cycle | EP 978]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19439298/Jack-Mallers-250k-Bitcoin-this-Cycle-EP-978</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19439298/Jack-Mallers-250k-Bitcoin-this-Cycle-EP-978"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T18:03:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jack Mallers expects the equivalent of at least 2-3x more money printing than COVID to bail the US out of the next financial disaster - Bitcoin Therapist ╔═╦╗╔╦╗╔═╦═╦╦╦╦╗╔═╗║╚╣║║║╚╣╚╣╔╣╔╣║╚╣═╣ ╠╗║╚╝║║╠╗║╚╣║║║║║═╣╚═╩══╩═╩═╩═╩╝╚╩═╩═╝✓ SUBSCRIBE TO SIMPLY BITCOIN - https://bit.ly/3QbgqTQ✓ LEAVE A...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pantera Capital Makes Major Solana Acquisition In 2,000 SOL Auction From FTX]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e743623f358</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/pantera-capital-makes-major-solana-acquisition/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T18:03:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Asset management firm Pantera Capital has emerged as one of the successful bidders in an auction of discounted Solana (SOL) tokens conducted by the liquidators overseeing the bankruptcy of the former FTX cryptocurrency exchange.
 
The sale, which included approximately 2,000 SOL tokens, signifies Pantera Capital’s continued interest in expanding its Solana portfolio.
 
FTX Sells Additional Locked Solana Tokens In Private Auction
 
The auction, whose details have not been publicly disclosed, was confirmed to Bloomberg by a source familiar with the matter who requested anonymity. Neither Pantera Capital nor representatives of the FTX estate provided have commented on the recent sale. 
 
 
This recent acquisition follows a deal earlier this month in which the FTX estate sold a substantial por…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pantera Capital Makes Major Solana Acquisition In 2,000 SOL Auction From FTX]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19439864/Pantera-Capital-Makes-Major-Solana-Acquisition-In-2000-SOL-Auction-From-FTX</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19439864/Pantera-Capital-Makes-Major-Solana-Acquisition-In-2000-SOL-Auction-From-FTX"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T18:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Asset management firm Pantera Capital has emerged as one of the successful bidders in an auction of discounted Solana (SOL) tokens conducted by the liquidators overseeing the bankruptcy of the former FTX cryptocurrency exchange. The sale, which included approximately 2,000 SOL tokens, signifies...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin crypto eyes partnership with ChatGPT’s OpenAI and PayPal]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19439849/Worldcoin-crypto-eyes-partnership-with-ChatGPTs-OpenAI-and-PayPal</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19439849/Worldcoin-crypto-eyes-partnership-with-ChatGPTs-OpenAI-and-PayPal"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T17:56:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Worldcoin (WLD) team announced a potential partnership with OpenAI and ongoing conversations with PayPal (NYSE: PYPL). Sam Altman is … Continue reading]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Climbs to $64,226 Amidst Positive Market Trends – Time to Buy]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19439866/Bitcoin-Price-Prediction-as-BTC-Climbs-to-64226-Amidst-Positive-Market-Trends-Time-to-Buy</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19439866/Bitcoin-Price-Prediction-as-BTC-Climbs-to-64226-Amidst-Positive-Market-Trends-Time-to-Buy"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T17:56:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amid rising market optimism, Bitcoin's resilience shines with a $1.25 trillion market cap, despite a minor pullback to $64,226—Is it time to buy]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram's Chosen Chain]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19439843/Telegrams-Chosen-Chain</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19439843/Telegrams-Chosen-Chain"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T17:55:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TON recently entered the top ten tokens by market cap, what's going on?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Is The Bitcoin Price Not Soaring? What’s Needed for a Rise? Analyst Says What to Watch]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19439844/Why-Is-The-Bitcoin-Price-Not-Soaring-Whats-Needed-for-a-Rise-Analyst-Says-What-to-Watch</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19439844/Why-Is-The-Bitcoin-Price-Not-Soaring-Whats-Needed-for-a-Rise-Analyst-Says-What-to-Watch"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T17:53:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why isn't the Bitcoin price rebounding to a new all-time high? Here is the analyst's theory. Continue Reading: Why Is The Bitcoin Price Not Soaring? What’s Needed for a Rise? Analyst Says What to Watch]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin weathers turbulent April, down 11% amid tax sell-offs, gold surge, and geopolitical tensions]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19439842/Bitcoin-weathers-turbulent-April-down-11-amid-tax-sell-offs-gold-surge-and-geopolitical-tensions</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19439842/Bitcoin-weathers-turbulent-April-down-11-amid-tax-sell-offs-gold-surge-and-geopolitical-tensions"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T17:52:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quick Take April has been a turbulent month for Bitcoin, with its price trading around $70,000 at the start of the month before encountering a series of challenges that brought it to local lows just below the $60,000 mark. Despite nearly four days remaining in the month, Bitcoin is currently...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Game On: The Hottest Upcoming Gaming Token Airdrops]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211029</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211029/game-on-hottest-upcoming-gaming-token-airdrops"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T17:45:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATED: Here's what you need to know about gaming airdrops and rewards around Notcoin, Immutable zkEVM, Saga, Illuvium, Apeiron, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$78 Million Worth of Bitcoin Deposited to Kraken by Major Whale as BTC Plunges]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19439852/78-Million-Worth-of-Bitcoin-Deposited-to-Kraken-by-Major-Whale-as-BTC-Plunges</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19439852/78-Million-Worth-of-Bitcoin-Deposited-to-Kraken-by-Major-Whale-as-BTC-Plunges"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T17:45:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are major whales taking profits?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cboe reorganization will merge or eliminate digital arm’s activities]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19439828/Cboe-reorganization-will-merge-or-eliminate-digital-arms-activities</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19439828/Cboe-reorganization-will-merge-or-eliminate-digital-arms-activities"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T17:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The exchange is optimizing operations after acquiring ErisX on the eve of crypto winter and expects to save millions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Crypto Doomed in the EU? New MiCA Rules Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19439827/Is-Crypto-Doomed-in-the-EU-New-MiCA-Rules-Explained</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19439827/Is-Crypto-Doomed-in-the-EU-New-MiCA-Rules-Explained"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T17:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The European Parliament tightens regulations to combat money laundering in the cryptocurrency space with stricter KYC rules for CASPs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ezETH depeg puts ETH restaking volatility into the limelight]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19439816/ezETH-depeg-puts-ETH-restaking-volatility-into-the-limelight</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19439816/ezETH-depeg-puts-ETH-restaking-volatility-into-the-limelight"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T17:28:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Renzo's liquid restaking token (LRT) ezETH experienced a dramatic drop this week, losing over 7% of its peg with Ether (ETH) within hours, with some 50% depeg in some decentralized applications. This decline was further intensified by the liquidation of leveraged yield farmers utilizing ezETH as...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polkadot community backs SnowBridge for seamless Ethereum integration]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19439806/Polkadot-community-backs-SnowBridge-for-seamless-Ethereum-integration</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19439806/Polkadot-community-backs-SnowBridge-for-seamless-Ethereum-integration"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T17:26:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Polkadot’s governance is currently mulling over a proposal to activate SnowBridge, a cross-chain bridge designed to link the Polkadot blockchain with Ethereum. A cross-chain bridge essentially serves as a decentralized application (DApp), streamlining asset transfers between blockchains to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin entering most likely 2 weeks for new BTC price dip — Analysis]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19439813/Bitcoin-entering-most-likely-2-weeks-for-new-BTC-price-dip-Analysis</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19439813/Bitcoin-entering-most-likely-2-weeks-for-new-BTC-price-dip-Analysis"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T17:26:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin market inertia is dragging on, and a BTC price drop over the next fortnight would correspond to classic post-halving behavior.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong Approves First Wave of Spot Bitcoin and Ether ETFs for Trading]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19439809/Hong-Kong-Approves-First-Wave-of-Spot-Bitcoin-and-Ether-ETFs-for-Trading</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19439809/Hong-Kong-Approves-First-Wave-of-Spot-Bitcoin-and-Ether-ETFs-for-Trading"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T17:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong’s financial regulator, the Securities and Futures Commission (SFC), recently greenlit the debut of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETFs Bleed Badly as Skittish Investors Cash Out $218 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228300</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228300/bitcoin-etf-outflows-end-71-day-run"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T17:25:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nearly $218 million exited the formerly red-hot investment vehicles in the wake of a weak U.S. economic report.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Is Built To Last: How The Network Defends Against Attacks]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74362a00a5</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/sponsored/bitcoin-is-built-to-last-how-the-network-defends-against-attacks"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T17:23:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin is one of the most robust distributed systems in the history of mankind. For fifteen years it has ticked along block by block with only two disruptions in its first few years that were very quickly handled by responsive developers the minute they manifested themselves. Aside from that, it has ticked along producing a block roughly every ten minutes with no interruptions. 
This reliability has set a golden standard of expectations for Bitcoin users, encouraging them to view it as a completely unstoppable system. In many peoples’ minds, Bitcoin has already won, and the world is just catching up with that realization. “Bitcoin is inevitable” as many would say. 
This doesn’t mean that Bitcoin is literally unstoppable though, there are possible events that could cause massive damage or …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EU Parliament Adopts AML Laws Regulating Bitcoin Based On Questionable Assumptions]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74362a0098</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/legal/eu-parliament-adopts-aml-laws-regulating-bitcoin-based-on-questionable-assumptions"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T17:23:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The European Parliament adopted a new AML law package which increases the reporting requirements of crypto asset service providers (CASPs) when sending and receiving ‘anonymous’ payments between self-hosted wallets and custodial service providers, in addition to limits on cash transactions and the establishment of a ‘central watchdog’ agency, which will develop regulatory technical standards. 
Under the new laws, EU CASPs will need to perform customer due diligence on transactions originating from self-custodial wallets for transactions below 1000 EUR, and implement additional KYC measures for transactions above 1000 EUR. The laws further regulate the operation of no-KYC custodial software service providers and the use of privacy coins, effectively banning CASPs from offering privacy asset…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>L0la L33tz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlocking New Possibilities: Solama Teams up With BingX and AssetDash]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74362bfda1</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/unlocking-new-possibilities-solama-teams-up-with-bingx-and-assetdash/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T17:09:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. Solama, one of the most captivating Solana meme coin 2024 craze, is partnering up with two essential platforms for a crypto project, such as BingX and AssetDash, as BingX mentioned on their X (Twitter) account. As a result of this team-up, all $SOLAMA enthusiasts could benefit from extensive accessibility, catering to all investors […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase, Uniswap Execs Praise Ethereum Giant Consensys for Taking On SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228274</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228274/coinbase-uniswap-ethereum-consensys-sec"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T17:07:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The heads of crypto industry titans like Coinbase and Uniswap are rallying behind Consensys in its fight to get the SEC to concede Ethereum is not a security.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NEAR and SHIB Led CoinDesk 20 Gainers Last Week: CoinDesk Indices Market Update]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74361531b0</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/04/26/near-and-shib-led-coindesk-20-gainers-last-week-coindesk-indices-market-update/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T17:01:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The majority of the assets posted gains despite a choppy market, but there were notable decliners as well.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tracy Stephens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Custodia Bank Appeals Court Loss in Fed Membership Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e743616b7c6</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/04/26/custodia-bank-appeals-court-loss-in-fed-membership-lawsuit/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T16:52:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Custodia, a Wyoming-based aspiring crypto bank, filed a notice of appeal against a court ruling that affirmed the Federal Reserve's rejection of its bid for a master account and membership.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eminem Promotes Crypto.com’s Latest NBA Playoff Ad to His 22 Million Followers]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7436173454</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/eminem-promotes-crypto-coms-latest-nba-playoff-ad-to-his-22-million-followers/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T16:49:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Friday, the cryptocurrency trading platform crypto.com unveiled a new advertisement set to debut at the forthcoming Lakers NBA playoff game in Los Angeles. Additionally, the ad was highlighted on the social media site X by the hip-hop icon Marshall Mathers, also known as Eminem. Marshall Mathers Amplifies Crypto.com Ad Ahead of NBA Playoff Showcase […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Analyst Reveals Play-By-Play Profit-Taking Strategy For Shiba Inu]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e743611b17e</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/profit-taking-strategy-shiba-inu/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T16:34:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto analyst Crypto Noan has revealed a profit-taking strategy that crypto investors can adopt as they invest in Shiba Inu (SHIB), the second-largest meme coin by market cap. This strategy would be most beneficial to those who need guidance in securing profits as the meme coin continues to make significant price gains. 
 
Price Levels To Secure Profits From Shiba Inu
 
In a chart shared on his X (formerly Twitter) platform, Crypto Noan highlighted four price targets from which Shiba Inu investors should look to take profits. The first take profit zone he highlighted was at $0.000028181. The second take profit zone was at $0.000032816; this serves as a moderate target for those who may not be satisfied with the returns at the initial take profit target. 
 
Related Reading: Investment Gian…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Warren Flags Crypto Ties to Child Sexual Abuse in Letter to DOJ, Homeland Security]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74361c9b9d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/04/26/warren-flags-crypto-ties-to-child-sexual-abuse-in-letter-to-doj-homeland-security/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T16:16:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leading crypto critic U.S. Sen. Elizabeth Warren (D-Mass.) has asked U.S. Attorney General Merrick Garland what tools the federal government needs to crack down on the use of digital assets to perpetrate child sexual exploitation, according to a letter she sent to the top U.S. law-enforcement official.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miners’ Average Revenue Per Block Dips 25% in 3 Days, Falling to 3.83 BTC]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7436051ea2</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-miners-average-revenue-per-block-dips-25-in-3-days-falling-to-3-83-btc/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T15:29:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the last 24 hours, bitcoin miners have faced significantly reduced earnings, with the current hashprice lingering at a significant low. Just five days ago, miners were harvesting an average of 5.105 BTC per block, between a blend of new BTC and transaction fees, following a peak in the hashprice. However, the average yield per […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DePIN for the Win: Spreading the Benefits of the Gig Economy]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7436052ff6</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2024/04/26/depin-for-the-win-spreading-the-benefits-of-the-gig-economy/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T15:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Community protocol networks that coordinate hardware-based services with tokens promise an upgrade in efficiency and fairness, says Ivo Entchev, a partner at Youbi Capital.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ivo  Entchev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oldest US Bank Invests In 2 Bitcoin ETFs, SEC Filing Shows]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7436007d18</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/oldest-us-bank-invests-in-bitcoin-etfs/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T15:10:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bank of New York Mellon Corporation (BNY Mellon), the oldest and one of the largest banks in the United States, has disclosed its investments in Bitcoin Exchange Traded Funds (ETFs). According to its recent Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) filings, BNY Mellon has acquired stakes in spot BTC ETFs managed by BlackRock and Grayscale.
 
BNY Mellon Bought Bitcoin ETFs Worth $1.2 Million
 
Julian Fahrer, co-founder and CEO of Apollo, highlighted the significance of this move on the social media platform X, formerly known as Twitter: “JUST IN: $49T bank BNY Mellon reports exposure to multiple Bitcoin ETFs in SEC filings! BNY is America’s oldest US bank.”
 
 
JUST IN:  $49T bank BNY Mellon reports exposure to multiple #Bitcoin ETFs in SEC filings!
 
BNY is America’s oldest bank 
 
— Ju…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Heroes of Mavia' Delays Ethereum Token Unlocks as Price Falls 65% Since February]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228271</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228271/heroes-mavia-delays-ethereum-token-unlocks"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T14:14:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MAVIA surged in price soon after its February launch, but has plunged since. Now the Heroes of Mavia team is shaking up its plans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Vs. SEC Lawsuit: Court Gives Regulator Tight Deadline To Strike Back]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74360ad847</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ripple-vs-sec-lawsuit-deadline/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T14:08:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the latest updates on the court case between Ripple and the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), the Magistrate Judge Sarah Netburn, has ordered strict deadlines for the regulatory agency to respond to the crypto firm’s motion. 
 
Judge Issues New Scheduling Order
 
On Thursday, April 25, the magistrate Judge Netburn issued a new scheduling order regarding the years-long legal battle between Ripple and the US SEC. 
 
 
Former federal prosecutor and defense lawyer, James K. Filan shared details of the scheduling order in an X (formerly Twitter) post. The order states that the SEC has been granted a deadline of Monday, April 29, 2024, to file a rebuttal to Ripple’s Motion to Strike. Following this, Ripple is mandated to file a response within three business days. 
 
Thi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Non-Custodial Conflict: US Government Actions Stir Crypto Community Concerns]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7437f617f0</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/the-non-custodial-conflict-us-government-actions-stir-crypto-community-concerns/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T13:48:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past two days, there has been a notable uptick in concern within the crypto community regarding the U.S. government’s actions toward non-custodial wallets, which facilitate the sovereign storage of crypto assets. Recent events have fueled a widespread belief that a targeted campaign against non-custodial wallets is now underway. Debate Over Crypto Wallet Regulation […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Canada Bets Big On Crypto: 40% Of Institutions Now Invest]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7437f9bc37</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/canada-40-of-institutions-now-invest-in-crypto/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T12:36:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Institutional investors in Canada are showing a strong appetite for cryptocurrencies, with a new survey revealing a significant surge in adoption rates. The report, conducted by KPMG in Canada and the Canadian Association of Alternative Assets and Strategies (CAASA), paints a picture of a booming crypto market fueled by investor confidence and a supportive regulatory environment.
 
 
Crypto Goes Mainstream In Canada
 
In 2023, a staggering 39% of surveyed institutional investors reported exposure to crypto assets, a sharp increase from 31% just two years prior. This newfound interest translates into action, with a significant portion of these investors allocating a substantial share of their portfolios to crypto.
 
The survey found that one-third of participating institutions had placed at…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Mover Americas: Bitcoin Holds Stable as ETF Outflows Increase]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7437fa7967</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/04/26/first-mover-americas-bitcoin-holds-stable-as-etf-outflows-increase/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T12:32:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest price moves in bitcoin (BTC) and crypto markets in context for April 26, 2024. First Mover is CoinDesk’s daily newsletter that contextualizes the latest actions in the crypto markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lyllah Ledesma, Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Asia's MicroStrategy' Metaplanet Buys ¥1 Billion Worth Bitcoin as Pledged]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7437e439e7</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/asias-microstrategy-metaplanet-buys-1-billion-bitcoin-yen"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T12:21:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Metaplanet, a publicly-listed Japanese company providing hotel-related and other services, has announced the purchase of ¥1 billion (approximately $6.25 million) worth of Bitcoin. 

NEW: 🇯🇵 Japanese Public Company Metaplanet just bought $6.25 million worth of #Bitcoin
Game theory has started playing out 🚀 pic.twitter.com/EJ19mcO9QF
— Bitcoin Magazine (@BitcoinMagazine) April 26, 2024
 
 
 
The company, which is listed on the Tokyo Stock Exchange, declared its intention to adopt Bitcoin as a treasury reserve asset earlier this month on X. Metaplanet stated its plan to buy ¥1 billion in Bitcoin as an initial commitment.
The company's recent announcement on X revealed that they have fulfilled their commitment, purchasing ¥1 billion worth of Bitcoin. 
This move closely mimics the strategy employed by MicroStrategy, a U.S.-based company that has been accumulating Bitcoin since 2020. MicroStrategy's Bitcoin purchases have led to a dramatic increase in its share price.
Following the announcement earlier this month, Metaplanet's stock price also saw a significant increase, indicating investor confidence in the company's decision to invest in Bitcoin. 
Jason, from Sora Ventures, referred to Metaplanet as "Asia's first MicroStrategy," highlighting the potential impact of this move on the Asian market.
 
                         
                         
                        Click the image to learn more. 
                     
                    
Metaplanet's Bitcoin investment offers Japanese investors a unique opportunity to gain exposure to Bitcoin without incurring an unrealized gains tax, which can be as high as 55%. 
Additionally, anyone with an account on the Tokyo Stock Exchange can now indirectly invest in Bitcoin through Metaplanet without facing the regulatory risks associated with direct purchases.
This development is seen as a positive step for Bitcoin and its market in Asia, as it demonstrates growing acceptance and adoption by traditional financial institutions and publicly listed companies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vivek Sen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Week in Polkadot: Web3 Foundation Backs Decentralized Storage]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228242</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228242/the-week-in-polkadot-web3-foundation-backs-decentralized-storage"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T12:11:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Web3 Foundation backs decentralized storage project StorageHub, while Polkadot founder Gavin Wood launches a new podcast.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will McCurdy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin-Linked Stablecoin Firm OpenDelta Raises $2.5M]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7437e5ceec</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2024/04/26/bitcoin-linked-stablecoin-firm-opendelta-raises-25m/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T12:10:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The startup is one of the first to build tokenized tech for Bitcoin's Runes era.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More of FTX's Solana Has Gone to Pantera Capital in Auction: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228191</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228191/more-of-ftxs-solana-has-gone-to-pantera-capital-in-auction-report"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T11:45:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More of FTX's Solana tokens have gone to Pantera Capital, as the bankrupt exchange's estate liquidates its $2.6 billion SOL holdings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK Police, National Crime Agency Gain New Crypto Seizure Powers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228197</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228197/uk-police-national-crime-agency-gain-new-crypto-seizure-powers"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T11:12:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the new powers, the UK government singled out privacy coins as "not conducive to the public good."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana ‘Chapter 2’ Airdrops Could Cover the Price of the Phone]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228171</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228171/solana-chapter-2-phone-maneki-mew-airdrops"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T23:33:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Saga Chapter 2 pre-orders could have their price offset by new MEW and MANEKI airdrops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Game 'MetalCore' Adding MON Token Rewards From 'Pixelmon']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228168</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228168/ethereum-game-metalcore-mon-token-rewards-pixelmon"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T22:53:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Immutable zkEVM allies MetalCore and Pixelmon are teaming up, with the mech shooter set to add MON token rewards for completing quests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Payments Giant Stripe Reenters Crypto With USDC on Ethereum, Solana and Polygon]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228152</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228152/stripe-stablecoin-payments-usdc-ethereum-solana"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T22:16:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A decade after an early attempt to support Bitcoin payments, the company sees a stablecoin-powered future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Sasha Stiles’ Experiential, AI-Infused NFT Drop with Bang & Olufsen]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/6Vi2IgYj/inside-sasha-stiles-experiential-ai-infused-nft-drop-with-bang-olufsen</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/6Vi2IgYj/inside-sasha-stiles-experiential-ai-infused-nft-drop-with-bang-olufsen"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T22:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At a launch party for the collection in New York’s SoHo neighborhood, the artist broke down her latest art experiment, “Four Core Texts,” with Decrypt’s Sander Lutz.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Immutable zkEVM Offering Up to $50 Million in Token Rewards to Ethereum Gamers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228155</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228155/immutable-zkevm-50-million-token-rewards-ethereum-gamers"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T21:51:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum users can earn IMX rewards for playing games, using exchanges, trading NFTs, and more on Immutable zkEVM.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rabbit R1 Reviews Herald ‘Standout’ AI Assistant After Disastrous Humane Pin Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228146</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228146/rabbit-r1-ai-reviews-gadget-hardware"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T20:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Affordability, user-friendly design, and impressive capabilities help the latest AI gadget hop ahead of its scant competition.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Franklin Templeton Enables Peer-to-Peer Trades of Blockchain Fund]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228135</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228135/franklin-templeton-enables-peer-to-peer-trades-of-blockchain-fund"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T19:46:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Participants in the OnChain U.S. Government Money Fund can now swap shares directly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consensys Sues SEC Over Attempts to Regulate Ethereum as a Security]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228134</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228134/consensys-sues-sec-attempts-regulate-ethereum-security"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T19:25:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum giant Consensys filed a preemptive suit against the SEC, revealing that it received a Wells Notice over MetaMask.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ohio Mulls Law to Protect Bitcoin Rights, Scrap Capital Gains Taxes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228124</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228124/ohio-mulls-law-to-protect-bitcoin-rights-scrap-capital-gains-taxes"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T18:33:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bill would also require state pension funds to consider investing in Bitcoin spot ETFs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Dip as Inflation Figures Hamstring Rate Cut Hopes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228113</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228113/bitcoin-ethereum-gdp-fed-rate-cuts-inflation"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T18:17:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Fed’s preferred inflation gauge showed personal expenditures grew 3.7% in the first quarter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CyberKongz Reveal Bitcoin Runes Airdrop Details, 'Mad Rush' Behind Etching]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228112</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228112/cyberkongz-reveal-bitcoin-runes-airdrop-details"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T17:51:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The "DECENTRALIZED" airdrop of Bitcoin Runes tokens is nearing. The CyberKongz team shared exclusive details with Decrypt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erika Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meme Coins Are Causing 'Damage' to Crypto, Says Andreessen Horowitz Exec]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228099</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228099/meme-coins-causing-damage-crypto-andreessen-horowitz-exec"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T16:58:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CTO of VC firm Andreessen Horowitz, Eddy Lazzarin, argued that meme coins are "undermining the long-term vision of crypto."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin 'Epic Sat' From the Halving Sells for $2.1 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228084</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228084/bitcoin-epic-sat-halving-sells-over-2-1-million"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T16:13:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first satoshi mined on Bitcoin after the halving, one of just four "epic sats" to date, fetched 33.3 BTC at auction. Here's why.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CryptoPunk Sells for $12.4 Million in Ethereum—One of the Biggest NFT Sales Ever]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228076</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228076/cryptopunk-sells-12-4-million-ethereum-one-biggest-nft-sales"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T15:56:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CryptoPunks NFT was the third ultra-rare Alien Punk to sell for over $10 million worth of Ethereum in the last two months alone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Gaming Tokens Battered as Bitcoin Price Sinks to $63,000]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228073</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228073/ethereum-gaming-tokens-battered-bitcoin-price-sinks"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T15:34:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some of the biggest Ethereum tokens tied to gaming projects, such as Immutable and Parallel, have plunged over the past 24 hours.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kokodi’s New NFT Collection 'The Masks' Is Set for Mint on Xterio Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228057</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228057/kokodis-new-nft-collection-the-masks-is-set-for-mint-on-xterio-games"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T13:51:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kokodi Inc, a modern video game company, is the mastermind behind the Mask NFT Mint. It’s the project’s second collection for an upcoming extraction shooter game built by the developer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>gamingwire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Started With Bitcoin Runes: A Guide to Etching, Minting and Trading]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=227968</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/how-get-started-bitcoin-runes-guide-etching-minting-trading"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Runes tokens are taking over the network, but they can be tricky to handle. Here's a guide on how to get started with Runes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erika Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Buy Bitcoin’ Notepad Held Behind Janet Yellen Sells for $1M]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228037</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228037/buy-bitcoin-notepad-held-behind-janet-yellen-sells-for-1m"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T12:08:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The iconic sign was held before cameras during a televised House Financial Services Committee hearing in 2017.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Slips Below $64,000 as $209 Million in Crypto Longs Liquidated]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228029</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228029/bitcoin-price-slips-below-64000-as-209-million-in-crypto-longs-liquidated"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T11:17:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The market slump saw over $209 million in crypto long positions liquidated, with over $52 million in Bitcoin longs liquidated.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETFs See $120 Million Outflows, BlackRock's IBIT Ends 71-Day Inflow Streak]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228027</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228027/bitcoin-etfs-see-120-million-outflows-blackrocks-ibit-ends-71-day-inflow-streak"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T10:45:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock's iShares Bitcoin Trust saw zero inflows yesterday, after scraping into the top 10 ETFs with the longest daily inflow streaks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Runes Transactions Are Taking Over the Network—And Dominating BRC-20]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228012</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228012/bitcoin-runes-transactions-dominate-btc-network-brc-20-dog"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T23:30:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The popular DOG collection helped Runes claim 81% of all transactions on the Bitcoin network Tuesday, Dune reports.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Ultra Light AI Model Fits on Your Phone and Can Beat ChatGPT]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=227974</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/227974/microsoft-phi-3-mini-small-ai-language-model"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T22:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft's latest “small language model” is well-suited to specific needs, offering cost-effective performance in a compact package.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interview: Hot 'Notcoin' Will Evolve After the NOT Token Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PprnGP14/interview-hot-notcoin-will-evolve-after-the-not-token-launch</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PprnGP14/interview-hot-notcoin-will-evolve-after-the-not-token-launch"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Open Builders founder Sasha Plotvinov speaks with Decrypt's Sander Lutz at Token 2049 Dubai about how he envisions Notcoin's expansion and evolution after the token drop—into something akin to the "Netflix of social, viral games."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Magic Runes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IGWg0R64/magic-runes</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IGWg0R64/magic-runes"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T13:59:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC stables at $66k, liquidations in narrow range. BTC funding again turns negative in bullish sign. ETFs net inflow after Grayscale moves to lower fees. BTC demand 5x vs supply post-halving: Bitfinex. SOL congestion issue now largely solved. Two SEC lawyers resign after ‘gross abuse of power’. Ripple fights to lower $2bn SEC fine. SAFE trades at $2.8bn FDV after OKX lists. MANEKI hits $150m on first day, China memes pump. Memecoins are ‘black hole you can’t ignore’. DeGods up 20%, may switch back to SOL. Magic Eden launches Runes platform ahead of time.  Louis Vuitton gifts Pharrell jacket to NFT holders. Melania Trump launches necklace with SOL NFTs. Hoodie Punk trades for $620K.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Luxury Watches, Designer Shoes Will Soon Trade Like NFTs: Arianee CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/CSNQG2md/luxury-watches-designer-shoes-will-soon-trade-like-nfts-arianee-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/CSNQG2md/luxury-watches-designer-shoes-will-soon-trade-like-nfts-arianee-ceo"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arianee CEO Pierre-Nicolas Hurstel sat down with Rug Radio founder Farokh and Decrypt’s Sander Lutz at NFT Paris to discuss everything from the future of on-chain luxury to the secret hack to finding the best restaurants in France.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notcoin's Co-Creator Explains the Game's Token Delay—And When to Expect NOT Now]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/7Zx33xo5/notcoins-co-creator-explains-the-games-token-delayand-when-to-expect-not-now</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/7Zx33xo5/notcoins-co-creator-explains-the-games-token-delayand-when-to-expect-not-now"/>
        <updated>2024-04-22T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Notcoin co-creator Sasha Plotvinov spoke with Decrypt's Sander Lutz at Token 2049 Dubai to discuss why the NOT token launch was pushed back from the original 4/20 target, when to expect the listing, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TON’s Justin Hyun Breaks Down The Importance of USDT Coming to Telegram]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ODQI6ACA/tons-justin-hyun-breaks-down-the-importance-of-usdt-coming-to-telegram</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ODQI6ACA/tons-justin-hyun-breaks-down-the-importance-of-usdt-coming-to-telegram"/>
        <updated>2024-04-19T10:14:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Token 2049 in Dubai, The Open Network’s director of investments sat down with Decrypt’s Sander Lutz to discuss what he sees as the game-changing integration of USDT onto TON, and his plans for getting Telegram’s 900 million users to start using crypto in the immediate future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Influencer Ansem Explains His Meme Coin Thesis and Why He’s Bullish on Bitcoin Runes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/u9DHFoK0/crypto-influencer-ansem-explains-his-meme-coin-thesis-and-why-hes-bullish-on-bitcoin-runes</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/u9DHFoK0/crypto-influencer-ansem-explains-his-meme-coin-thesis-and-why-hes-bullish-on-bitcoin-runes"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T21:56:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ansem, the crypto trader who's amassed a sizable following on the back of meme coin Dogwifhat (WIF) and other calls, chats with Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz at Token 2049 Dubai about his meme coin thesis, why he's bullish on Bitcoin Runes, and what he sees ahead for the crypto markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Sander Lutz Braves the Dubai Floods for a Crypto Conference]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/mtjVHGa3/decrypts-sander-lutz-braves-the-dubai-floods-for-a-crypto-conference</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/mtjVHGa3/decrypts-sander-lutz-braves-the-dubai-floods-for-a-crypto-conference"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T21:33:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz reports from Dubai amid a historic storm that flooded the famed city, trudging through the streets to complete his essential task: Attending the Token 2049 crypto conference.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gold Beats Its All Time High]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/6ULgUKVk/gold-beats-its-all-time-high</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/6ULgUKVk/gold-beats-its-all-time-high"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T09:53:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) maintains its trend of reaching higher lows amidst choppy market conditions. Exchange-traded funds (ETFs) witness another influx of $125 million. There's anticipation of Hong Kong approving ETFs for both Bitcoin and Ethereum (ETH) come Monday. Notable institutional investor BlackRock shows interest in Bitcoin. Recent filings reveal increased Bitcoin purchases by banks. A Bitcoin-friendly political party secures victory in the South Korean election. Analyst Kang predicts Bitcoin could surge to $80-100k by May. Meanwhile, Ethereum sees accumulation by stablecoin whales on the rise. A new Ethereum Improvement Proposal (EIP) aims to streamline signing requests. Solana (SOL) experiences a resurgence in activity, reaching yearly highs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NASA’s Next Deep Space Mission Won’t Use Artificial Intelligence]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/0WGP33Rp/nasas-next-deep-space-mission-wont-use-artificial-intelligence</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/0WGP33Rp/nasas-next-deep-space-mission-wont-use-artificial-intelligence"/>
        <updated>2024-04-13T18:42:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Thursday, Decrypt Media visited NASA's Jet Propulsion Laboratory in Pasadena, CA to meet with the Engineering team behind the Europa Clipper before its launch to Jupiter's Europa moon in October.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Do A Little with Weesh]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LnaOT9bF/we-do-a-little-with-weesh</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LnaOT9bF/we-do-a-little-with-weesh"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T07:46:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week’s episode, we did a little something different. We took the man who is usually behind the camera and put him in front of it. We sat down with our producer Weesh to dive into how in fell in love with art and became a collector, how he met Andy and fun childhood memories together, his biggest wins in crypto, and so much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside VanEck’s Crypto Takeover of the New York Stock Exchange]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9YAY4wGD/inside-vanecks-crypto-takeover-of-the-new-york-stock-exchange</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9YAY4wGD/inside-vanecks-crypto-takeover-of-the-new-york-stock-exchange"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T14:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worlds collide as Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz heads to the floor of the NYSE to witness a special closing bell ceremony hosted by VanEck in honor of Web3. Featuring Choose Rich Nick, VanEck Head of Web3 Matt Bartlett, and more!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wormhole Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9SNiIVfU/wormhole-wednesday</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9SNiIVfU/wormhole-wednesday"/>
        <updated>2024-04-07T17:42:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC hits $64.5K then rebounds, SOL outperforms. Government sends $2B BTC to Coinbase to sell. Funding rates stay low after sweep lower. ETFs see small inflow, Ark outflow more than GBTC. Wormhole W launches at $15B FDV. BTC ‘inflection point’ if it follows rates or gold. Gold & BTC very correlated for the last year. Expect slower ETF volume this month: Bloomberg. BTC 2x and 3x levered ETFs launch yesterday. BTC ETFs now half the size of gold.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Dogs, Now Cats]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/2KrbCFNp/first-dogs-now-cats</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/2KrbCFNp/first-dogs-now-cats"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T14:06:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC falls another 6% amid $400m liquidations. ETF outflows and dollar strength blamed for move. Funding completely reset to lows in move. BTC lower high leaves market in ‘no trade zone’. This cycle acting ‘nothing like previous cycle’. ETH unlikely to be classed a security: Coinbase CFO. Crypto VC funding up 53% in MarchAnsem’s cat coin sees more volume than NFT market. Most memecoins down 10-20% given move in majors. MEW up 10% after HTX lists, airdrop to Saga phones. MEME to launch memecoin chain, NFTs rise. Pixelmon releases trailer for Anime series.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Do A Little With Spencer Gordon-Sand]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/jSsgl6SQ/we-do-a-little-with-spencer-gordon-sand</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/jSsgl6SQ/we-do-a-little-with-spencer-gordon-sand"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T17:11:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week’s episode, we sit down with Spencer Gordon Sand, the mastermind behind Spencer Ventures. Before launching Spencer Ventures, Spencer was a competitive fencer, Magic the gathering player, and startup enjoyooor. 

We dive into Spencer’s investment thesis behind NFTs and how his fund invests, finding and buying distressed assets in a bear market , point farming optimization, a peak behind the 3AC liquidation and dickbutt buys, and so much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Get Your Foot In Ihe Door And Building During Bear Markets]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/d8FYP5tO/how-to-get-your-foot-in-ihe-door-and-building-during-bear-markets</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/d8FYP5tO/how-to-get-your-foot-in-ihe-door-and-building-during-bear-markets"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T11:37:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week’s episode, we sit down with Intern and Tunez from the Monad team. Prior to Monad, Tunez was working with Delphi Digital and Intern was working at CMS Holdings. They’re two of my oldest friends from crypto twitter.

We get into why they joined the Monad team, alpha for finding jobs in the space, biggest lessons from previous cycles, and so much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SBF Sentencing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZmRslhIl/sbf-sentencing</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZmRslhIl/sbf-sentencing"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T11:29:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC: 70.7k (+1%), ETH: 3585 (0%), SOL: 186 (-1%). Top 100 gainers: DOGE, GT, BCH, RBN. Crypto mixed, BTC-beta & memes outperform. SEC case vs Coinbase set to go to trial. DeFi win as case dismissed vs Coinbase wallet. ETFs see $244m inflows led by Ark. BlackRock ETF fastest growing in history: Fink. ETH ETF possible even if its a security: Fink. ETH spot ETF by May chances only 20%: GSR. SBF sentencing today, faces 50 years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The $63 Million Exploit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/l2sy2ZQY/the-63-million-exploit</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/l2sy2ZQY/the-63-million-exploit"/>
        <updated>2024-03-28T16:42:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC consolidates around $70k, funding still low. ETFs see $418m inflow as GBTC outflow tiny. BTC set to have record 7th-straight green month. AI coins soar, FET hits ATH amid merger rumour. FET, OCEAN, AGIX token proposed at $7.5bn FDV. DoJ charges KuCoin over money laundering. KuCoin sees $800m outflows after charges. CFTC names ETH & LTC commodities in charges. HK set to allow ‘in-kind’ style ETFs. HSBC launches tokenised gold fund. Fidelity files S1 form for ETH ETF. Short sellers bet $11bn crypto rally won’t last. More customer USDC balances to be stored on Base.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BTC Is Back On Top]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/1t8j4uWb/btc-is-back-on-top</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/1t8j4uWb/btc-is-back-on-top"/>
        <updated>2024-03-28T16:16:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC breaks $70K as $175M of shorts liquidated. ETFs see net inflow despite high GBTC outflows. Gold miner set to buy $1.7B BTC. UK to list crypto ETNs in May. ETH ETF may still be approved: Grayscale. Grayscale ETH discount falls to 22%. ETH ETF has no positive signs: Bloomberg. Coinbase pumps 10%, Ark continue to sell shares. Coinbase Int. record trading volumes in March. FTX to sell majority of Anthropic stake for $884M. Trader makes $20m profit in MEW rally. Puppets hit ATH, lead move higher in Ordinals. Azuki flips MAYC market cap in bounce. Magic Eden makes $15m in 30d trading revenue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Base On Top]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OGLEeanX/base-on-top</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OGLEeanX/base-on-top"/>
        <updated>2024-03-28T15:05:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Majors continue to rally as ETF sentiment improves. Genesis have likely sold half their GBTC position. BlackRock could flip GBTC holdings in 3 weeks. BTC short squeeze would liquidate $6.6bn by $75k. Lack of on-chain activity indicates ‘limited selling’. BTC crucial to the financial system: BlackRock. Resurging interest in crypto assets: Goldman Sachs. Crypto summer has started: Raoul Pal. Base outpaces SOL & ETH for trading volumes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>