<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-04-29T23:14:55.768Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-04-29T23:14:55.768Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s Where The Shiba Inu Price Is Headed In May According To Historical Data]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74341898b9</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-price-in-may/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T23:09:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Shiba Inu price, along with the rest of the crypto market, has suffered uncertain headwinds as a result of massive sell-offs suppressing the price. However, with the month of April drawing to an end, crypto investors are expecting the price direction. One way of getting an idea of where the price might be headed next is using historical data, so here is how Shiba Inu has performed in May, historically.
 
How Shiba Inu Performs In May
 
Historical data shows that the month of May her not been particularly bullish for the Shiba Inu price. According to data from CryptoRank, the meme coin has seen more red months in May than green months, suggesting that the trend could continue.
 
 
The last time that the Shiba Inu price finished in the green in the month of May was back in 2021, which wa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CasinoBello.com – Revolutionizing Online Gaming With Crypto Innovations]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7434189a2c</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/casinobello-com-revolutionizing-online-gaming-with-crypto-innovations/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T23:09:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. Casinobello.com, a Curacao-licensed online casino, is thrilled to gain the biggest popularity in its history and become one of the leading destinations for crypto-savvy iGaming users. With a strong presence in Germany, Austria, Switzerland, Italy, New Zealand, Canada, and Australia, Casinobello is pioneering the integration of cryptocurrency into the online gaming world to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s Where The Shiba Inu Price Is Headed In May According To Historical Data]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19446059/Heres-Where-The-Shiba-Inu-Price-Is-Headed-In-May-According-To-Historical-Data</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19446059/Heres-Where-The-Shiba-Inu-Price-Is-Headed-In-May-According-To-Historical-Data"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T23:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Shiba Inu price, along with the rest of the crypto market, has suffered uncertain headwinds as a result of massive sell-offs suppressing the price. However, with the month of April drawing to an end, crypto investors are expecting the price direction. One way of getting an idea of where the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong Bitcoin, Ethereum ETFs expected to outperform US counterparts’ volume on day 1]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19446040/Hong-Kong-Bitcoin-Ethereum-ETFs-expected-to-outperform-US-counterparts-volume-on-day-1</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19446040/Hong-Kong-Bitcoin-Ethereum-ETFs-expected-to-outperform-US-counterparts-volume-on-day-1"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T22:52:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Hong Kong braces for the debut of its first spot Bitcoin and Ethereum ETFs, expectations are soaring that the initial trading volumes will eclipse those witnessed during similar launches in the US, local media reported on April 29. Huaxia Fund Management (Hong Kong), along with digital asset...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[El Salvador Adopts Bitcoin As Legal Tender | Bitcoin Halving Top 21 Moments]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19446022/El-Salvador-Adopts-Bitcoin-As-Legal-Tender-Bitcoin-Halving-Top-21-Moments</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19446022/El-Salvador-Adopts-Bitcoin-As-Legal-Tender-Bitcoin-Halving-Top-21-Moments"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T22:26:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the #1 moment of 21 moments, we unveil the most groundbreaking event of the third Bitcoin epoch: El Salvador's historic decision to embrace Bitcoin as legal tender.At the forefront of this monumental shift was Jack Mallers of Strike, whose announcement at the Bitcoin 2021 conference,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microstrategy Boosts Bitcoin Holdings to 214,400 BTC With Latest Purchase]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7434071c1d</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/microstrategy-boosts-bitcoin-holdings-to-214400-btc-with-latest-purchase/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T22:09:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microstrategy, the Nasdaq-listed software intelligence firm and “the world’s first bitcoin development company,” has disclosed that it now holds 214,400 bitcoins after the latest purchase. “We acquired 25,250 additional bitcoins since the end of the fourth quarter, our 14th consecutive quarter of adding more bitcoin to our balance sheet,” said the company’s chief financial officer. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Expert Flags Dangers Of Spot Bitcoin ETFs: Labels Them ‘Orange FOMO Poker Chips’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e743407452f</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/expert-flags-dangers-of-spot-bitcoin-etfs/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T22:08:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Market expert and researcher Jim Bianco recently voiced cautionary remarks regarding the alleged risks of spot Bitcoin ETFs. Bianco’s insights shed light on these ETFs’ implications for the market and address specific concerns related to investor behavior.
 
Minimal Involvement In New Bitcoin ETFs?
 
In a thought-provoking social media post on X (formerly Twitter), Bianco emphasized his increasing worries as more data becomes available. Notably, he expressed concerns about the potential risks that spot Bitcoin ETFs pose to the market. 
 
Bianco highlighted that investment advisors (IAs) hold a substantial portion, approximately 35%, of all ETFs. Surprisingly, their holdings account for less than 1% of spot BTC ETFs. For Bianco, this revelation challenges the popular belief that “boomers ar…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$435,000,000 Leaves Bitcoin and Ethereum ETPs As Institutions Eye Altcoins: CoinShares]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19445966/435000000-Leaves-Bitcoin-and-Ethereum-ETPs-As-Institutions-Eye-Altcoins-CoinShares</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19445966/435000000-Leaves-Bitcoin-and-Ethereum-ETPs-As-Institutions-Eye-Altcoins-CoinShares"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T22:01:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Digital assets manager CoinShares says institutional investments in crypto products suffered their third consecutive week of outflows last week. In its latest Digital Asset Fund Flows report, CoinShares says crypto investment products lost $435 million in outflows last week, the largest week of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BNB rises against Bitcoin: What does this mean for the crypto market?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19445962/BNB-rises-against-Bitcoin-What-does-this-mean-for-the-crypto-market</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19445962/BNB-rises-against-Bitcoin-What-does-this-mean-for-the-crypto-market"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T22:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BNB outperformed BTC in terms of price performance over the last month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Expert Flags Dangers Of Spot Bitcoin ETFs: Labels Them ‘Orange FOMO Poker Chips’]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19445963/Expert-Flags-Dangers-Of-Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-Labels-Them-Orange-FOMO-Poker-Chips</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19445963/Expert-Flags-Dangers-Of-Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-Labels-Them-Orange-FOMO-Poker-Chips"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T22:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Market expert and researcher Jim Bianco recently voiced cautionary remarks regarding the alleged risks of spot Bitcoin ETFs. Bianco’s insights shed light on these ETFs’ implications for the market and address specific concerns related to investor behavior. Minimal Involvement In New Bitcoin...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These 4 Cryptos Could Drop to New Lows in May]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19446038/These-4-Cryptos-Could-Drop-to-New-Lows-in-May</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19446038/These-4-Cryptos-Could-Drop-to-New-Lows-in-May"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following the mixed cues received from the market throughout March and April, some cryptos shot up while some came closer to making new bearish records. As we move into May, the market has not changed considerably, meaning some of these altcoins could see massive declines. Bitcoin SV Could Fall...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Wavers Around $63K, Awaiting Hong Kong Spot Crypto ETF Debut]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7434003e37</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/04/29/bitcoin-wavers-around-63k-awaiting-hong-kong-spot-crypto-etf-debut/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T21:59:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite muted anticipation for the new products, an executive of one of the issuers reportedly expects that the first-day issuance of the Hong Kong offerings will exceed the U.S. debut in January.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nintendo Switch 2 Preview: Everything You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197793</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197793/nintendo-switch-2-rumors-leaks-latest-news"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T21:55:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATED: Magnetically attached Joy-Con controllers? Backwards compatibility? A huge 1080p screen? Here's the latest on the Nintendo Switch 2.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche Hoops Game ‘Rumble Kong League’ Nets Gatorade Deal]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228663</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228663/avalanche-hoops-game-rumble-kong-league-gatorade-deal"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T21:46:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Upcoming mobile basketball game Rumble Kong League will feature Gatorade-branded items.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche Hoops Game ‘Rumble Kong League’ Nets Gatorade Deal]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19445942/Avalanche-Hoops-Game-Rumble-Kong-League-Nets-Gatorade-Deal</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19445942/Avalanche-Hoops-Game-Rumble-Kong-League-Nets-Gatorade-Deal"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T21:46:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Upcoming mobile basketball game Rumble Kong League will feature Gatorade-branded items.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana illustrates the dark side of monolithic blockchains]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19445913/Solana-illustrates-the-dark-side-of-monolithic-blockchains</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19445913/Solana-illustrates-the-dark-side-of-monolithic-blockchains"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T21:37:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modular blockchains might lead to a poor user experience, but — unlike Solana — they remain functional even during periods of high demand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform proposes $1M penalty for SEC case, no relief or disgorgement]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19445909/Terraform-proposes-1M-penalty-for-SEC-case-no-relief-or-disgorgement</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19445909/Terraform-proposes-1M-penalty-for-SEC-case-no-relief-or-disgorgement"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lawyers for Terraform claimed that seeking disgorgement from the platform would involve the Luna Foundation Guard, a “non-party” in the SEC’s civil case.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crow-themed meme coin soars almost 600% in one week]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19445895/Crow-themed-meme-coin-soars-almost-600-in-one-week</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19445895/Crow-themed-meme-coin-soars-almost-600-in-one-week"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T21:22:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The meme coin crow with knife (CAW) rose by almost 600% in the past seven days and is the crypto asset with the most significant growth in this period, according to data aggregator CoinGecko. The token is deployed on Cronos, the blockchain related to the crypto exchange Crypto.com. CAW was...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy Bought 122 Bitcoin In April, Now Holds 214,400 BTC]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74340d26db</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/markets/microstrategy-bought-122-bitcoin-in-april-now-holds-214400-btc"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T21:17:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy, a leading business intelligence and software company, has continued its steadfast commitment to Bitcoin by purchasing an additional 122 BTC in April at a total cost of $7.8 million, Founder & Chairman Michael Saylor announced today.

BREAKING: MicroStrategy bought 122 more #Bitcoin for $7.8 million. pic.twitter.com/IZWUNj0kHY
— Bitcoin Magazine (@BitcoinMagazine) April 29, 2024
 
 
 
“As the world’s first Bitcoin Development Company, MicroStrategy is committed to the continued development of the bitcoin network through our activities in the financial markets, advocacy and technology innovation,” said Phong Le, President and Chief Executive Officer at MicroStrategy. “It is through our unique bitcoin strategy and solid track record as an operating company that we now hold 214,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nik Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Network Now Cheapest In 6 Months: What It Means]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74340e862c</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-network-now-cheapest-6-months-what-means/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T21:05:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data shows the Ethereum transaction fees is now at its lowest since October 2023. Here’s what it could mean for the cryptocurrency.
 
Ethereum Transfer Fees Has Recently Plunged To A Low Of $1.12
 
According to data from the on-chain analytics firm Santiment, the average fee on the Ethereum network has dropped to low levels recently. The fee here naturally refers to the amount that every sender has to attach to their transactions as compensation for the blockchain to process their move.
 
What fee an investor may have to attach in order for the transfer to swiftly go through depends on the network conditions at the time. During times of high activity, there can be high competition to get transactions through fast, so users who are in a rush may have to pay fees high enough to beat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUI Fails To Recover 83% Loss Despite Surging Chain Activity]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19445878/SUI-Fails-To-Recover-83-Loss-Despite-Surging-Chain-Activity</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19445878/SUI-Fails-To-Recover-83-Loss-Despite-Surging-Chain-Activity"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T21:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The token's month-long underperformance has kicked off its week on a sour note.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Network Now Cheapest In 6 Months: What It Means]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19445877/Ethereum-Network-Now-Cheapest-In-6-Months-What-It-Means</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19445877/Ethereum-Network-Now-Cheapest-In-6-Months-What-It-Means"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T21:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data shows the Ethereum transaction fees is now at its lowest since October 2023. Here’s what it could mean for the cryptocurrency. Ethereum Transfer Fees Has Recently Plunged To A Low Of $1.12 According to data from the on-chain analytics firm Santiment, the average fee on the Ethereum...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another U.S Bank Collapses! #shorts]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19445883/Another-US-Bank-Collapses-shorts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19445883/Another-US-Bank-Collapses-shorts"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T21:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Another U.S Bank Collapses!Introducing the ALTCOINBUZZ ALPHA x DECUBATE Special Offer! Decubate Bronze+ Tier Members can now claim a full refund on your 1st month of Altcoin Buzz Alpha Membership!Eligibility✅ Submit your Bronze+ Member email ID to #Alpha channel in Discord...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$50 Trillion Is Coming To Bitcoin & Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19445884/50-Trillion-Is-Coming-To-Bitcoin-Crypto</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19445884/50-Trillion-Is-Coming-To-Bitcoin-Crypto"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T21:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bill Barhydt is the Co-Founder & CEO of Abra, a new type of digital cash payments app and network enabling the transfer of cash between any two smartphones. In this conversation, we talk about the brand new regulatory approval as a registered investment advisor, what that means for Abra, how...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cracking the Crypto Code: ETH/BTC Signals The Next Altcoin Explosion – Here’s How]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19445866/Cracking-the-Crypto-Code-ETHBTC-Signals-The-Next-Altcoin-Explosion-Heres-How</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19445866/Cracking-the-Crypto-Code-ETHBTC-Signals-The-Next-Altcoin-Explosion-Heres-How"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T21:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, a seasoned crypto investor, Daan Crypto Trades, offered a fresh perspective on evaluating altcoin market sentiment. Daan believes the ETH/BTC ratio is a superior indicator of altcoin market sentiment over the SOL/BTC ratio, showing data that suggests the potential for an upcoming...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Binance CEO CZ’s Sentence Will Be Announced Tomorrow: Here are Estimates on How Much He Will Receive]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19445860/Former-Binance-CEO-CZs-Sentence-Will-Be-Announced-Tomorrow-Here-are-Estimates-on-How-Much-He-Will-Receive</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19445860/Former-Binance-CEO-CZs-Sentence-Will-Be-Announced-Tomorrow-Here-are-Estimates-on-How-Much-He-Will-Receive"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T20:52:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The decision on how much punishment CZ, the founder of Binance, the world's largest cryptocurrency exchange, will receive will be announced tomorrow. Continue Reading: Former Binance CEO CZ’s Sentence Will Be Announced Tomorrow: Here are Estimates on How Much He Will Receive]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Whales Trigger Market Chaos with $140 Million in ETH Sell-Off]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19445862/Ethereum-Whales-Trigger-Market-Chaos-with-140-Million-in-ETH-Sell-Off</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19445862/Ethereum-Whales-Trigger-Market-Chaos-with-140-Million-in-ETH-Sell-Off"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T20:51:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a tumultuous turn of events within the cryptocurrency realm, Ether, the second-largest crypto asset, finds itself in the eye of a storm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy Q1 Operating Loss of $53.1M After Bitcoin Holdings Impairment Charge of $191.6M]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74340874d5</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2024/04/29/microstrategy-q1-operating-loss-of-531m-after-bitcoin-holdings-impairment-charge-of-1916m/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T20:50:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To this point, the company has not adopted fair value accounting for its bitcoin stack, resulting in the first quarter write-down despite a major rally in prices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen  Alpher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy Buys Even More Bitcoin, Pushing Stash to $13.5 Billion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228660</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228660/microstrategy-buys-even-more-bitcoin-13-5-billion"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T20:50:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Saylor’s software firm MicroStrategy bought the dip, expanding its enormous pile of Bitcoin with more than 1% of the total supply in hand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mixed EIGEN Feelings]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19445858/Mixed-EIGEN-Feelings</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19445858/Mixed-EIGEN-Feelings"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T20:49:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not everyone is happy with the new EIGEN token plans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Wavers Around $63K, Awaiting Hong Kong Spot Crypto ETF Debut]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19445861/Bitcoin-Wavers-Around-63K-Awaiting-Hong-Kong-Spot-Crypto-ETF-Debut</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19445861/Bitcoin-Wavers-Around-63K-Awaiting-Hong-Kong-Spot-Crypto-ETF-Debut"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T20:48:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite muted anticipation for the new products, an executive of one of the issuers reportedly expects that the first-day issuance of the Hong Kong offerings will exceed the U.S. debut in January.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Launched Formal Investigation Into Ethereum’s Security Status Over a Year Ago, New Court Filing Shows]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74340a44f8</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/sec-launched-formal-investigation-into-ethereums-security-status-over-a-year-ago-new-court-filing-shows/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T20:35:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new court filing claims that the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), led by Chair Gary Gensler, initiated a formal investigation into ethereum’s potential classification as a security more than a year ago. SEC Enforcement Division Director Gurbir Grewal approved a formal investigative order in March last year to scrutinize potential securities transactions involving […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New AI Model Reka Rises to Challenge ChatGPT, Claude and Llama-3—And It's Free]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228507</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228507/reka-ai-core-free-competition-chatgpt-claude-llama-3"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T20:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lesser-known startup has produced a top-performing AI model, Reka Core. We put it to the test against its high-powered competition.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Restaking Protocol EigenLayer Reveals Token and Airdrop Plans]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228642</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228642/eigen-token-airdrop-plan-ethereum-restaking-protocol-eigenlayer"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T20:16:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Eigen Foundation will begin distributing EIGEN tokens on May 10, but US and VPN users will be blocked.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samourai Wallet Co-Founder Keonne Rodriguez Pleads Not Guilty, Released on $1M Bond]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7435f4e8c4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/04/29/samourai-wallet-co-founder-keonne-rodriguez-pleads-not-guilty-released-on-1m-bond/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T20:13:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NEW YORK — Samourai Wallet co-founder Keonne Rodriguez pleaded not guilty to two criminal charges tied to creating and marketing the privacy-focused bitcoin wallet application and mixing service in a Manhattan courtroom on Monday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cheyenne Ligon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[As Wasabi Wallet and Phoenix Leave the U.S., What’s Next for Non-Custodial Crypto?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7435f5af2c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2024/04/29/as-wasabi-wallet-and-phoenix-leave-the-us-whats-next-for-non-custodial-crypto/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T20:07:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following DOJ action against Samourai Wallet and a possible Metamask investigation, Wasabi Wallet and Phoenix are closing their U.S. offerings. Is non-custodial crypto under threat?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Kuhn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why This Crypto Analyst Believes PEPE Could Flip Dogecoin And Shiba Inu]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7435f5d7d3</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/pepe-flip-dogecoin-shiba-inu/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T20:06:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pepe (PEPE) has been one of the best-performing crypto assets since the beginning of the year, with a year-to-date (YTD) gain of over 400%. This crypto analyst predicts that PEPE can continue this impressive run and become the largest meme coin by market cap, ahead of Dogecoin and Shiba Inu.
 
PEPE To Flip Dogecoin (DOGE) And Shiba Inu (SHIB)
 
Crypto analyst and trader Murad mentioned in an X (formerly Twitter) post that it is “possible that PEPE flips SHIB and possibly even DOGE.” PEPE flipping these two meme coins will make it the largest meme coin by market cap, as they occupy the second and first positions, respectively. 
 
 
Murad further explained why he holds this belief, noting that PEPE is a “cult community with 10,000,000+ unique memes that is [sic] perpetually relevant to moder…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solo Bitcoin Miner Hits the Jackpot with $218,000 Block Reward]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228584</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228584/solo-bitcoin-miner-wins-block-reward-218000"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T20:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One miner's perseverance in the face of the dominance of centralized mining firms and major mining pools has paid off.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Clash of Clans' Maker Supercell Invests in Crypto Gaming Startup]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228607</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228607/clash-of-clans-maker-supercell-invests-games-living"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T19:36:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain startup Games for a Living has raised $3.2 million, with mobile gaming giant Supercell in the mix.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Press Briefing With ChinaAMC Executive Ahead of Tuesday Launch of Hong Kong Spot Bitcoin and Ether ETFs]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7435fd8cd1</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/04/29/press-briefing-with-chinaamc-executive-ahead-of-tuesday-launch-of-hong-kong-spot-bitcoin-and-ether-etfs/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T19:06:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zhu Haokang is head of digital asset management and family wealth at one of the ETF providers, ChinaAMC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen  Alpher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korea's Lazarus Group Laundered $200M in Crypto, Says Blockchain Sleuth—Here's How]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228606</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228606/north-koreas-lazarus-group-laundered-200m-in-crypto-says-blockchain-sleuth-heres-how"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T18:58:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain analyst ZachXBT has broken down exactly how North Korea’s notorious hacking group Lazarus laundered over $200 million into fiat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Rollups Could Boost Transaction Speeds 10X, Devs Claim]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228630</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228630/bitcoin-rollups-bitcoinos-whitepaper-10x-transaction-speed"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T18:45:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new BitcoinOS whitepaper says its scaling system is resistant to government attackers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu’s Decentralized Exchange ShibaSwap Expands To Shibarium]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7435f9db48</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-shibaswap-expands-to-shibarium/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T18:34:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu has announced the expansion of its decentralized exchange (DEX), ShibaSwap, to include support for Shibarium, its related Ethereum Layer 2 (L2) blockchain. This development introduces multi-chain functionality to ShibaSwap, allowing it to operate across both the Ethereum and Shibarium platforms, a move set to significantly enhance its operational flexibility and efficiency.
 
Shiba Inu Team Introduces Of Multi-Chain Capabilities
 
Lucie, Shiba Inu’s marketing lead, made the expansion announcement on X (formerly Twitter), stating, “ShibaSwap is going multi-chain, operating on both #Shibarium and Ethereum. Who knows what the future holds? We’re expanding our horizons. Don’t forget, Bone is the Shibarium gas fee token. IYKYK.” This strategic move underscores ShibaSwap’s shift toward…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EigenLayer, After Touching Off Restaking Frenzy, Plans Own EIGEN token]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7435fa2f29</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2024/04/29/eigenlayer-after-touching-off-restaking-frenzy-plans-own-eigen-token/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T18:32:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some 45% of the EIGEN token supply will go towards the EigenLayer community, while investors will be allocated 29.5% of the token supply, and 25.5% will go towards early contributors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Margaux Nijkerk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 AI Chatbots Predict Bitcoin’s Price Post-Halving; See $80K-$100K by Year-End]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7435e4ad13</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/7-ai-chatbots-predict-bitcoins-price-post-halving-see-80k-100k-by-year-end/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T18:14:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On April 28, 2024, the price of bitcoin was coasting along at $62,900 per unit as of 7:28 p.m. Eastern Time (ET). Since then, the price fell below the $62K mark by Monday morning ET, only to climb back above $62,000 by mid-afternoon. It has been nine days since the last halving event and 109 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Funds Bleed Investor Cash for Third Straight Week]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228620</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228620/digital-asset-investment-funds-lose-cash-three-weeks"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T18:10:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Persistent outflows from Grayscale’s Bitcoin Trust overshadowed the modest gains of its peers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Starting a Brokerage With B2Trader: Diversification Strategies for Brokers]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7435ec0c69</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/starting-a-brokerage-with-b2trader-diversification-strategies-for-brokers/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T17:24:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[B2Broker is a global liquidity provider that combines numerous B2B services under its umbrella, including CRM systems, payment processing solutions, and advanced trading software solutions. Founded in 2014, B2Broker has constantly iterated on its strong foundation, adding new features and improvements to its liquidity and white-label offerings. B2Broker’s expansive ecosystem includes B2BinPay, B2Core, B2Prime, B2Copy, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paypal's Green Mining Initiative Makes Zero Sense]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7435ede920</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/technical/paypals-green-mining-initiative-makes-zero-sense"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T17:12:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week Paypal released a whitepaper in partnership with Energy Web and DMG Blockchain Solutions, describing a “Green Mining Initiative” intended to redirect fees from participating users specifically to certified miners powering their operations with renewable energy. I can’t say I’m surprised by this honestly, mining has at this point become very normalized in terms of its use to further renewable energy or climate goals. Mining is actually very suited to this task given its nature, miners are mercenaries looking for the cheapest energy possible to devote towards solving the next block. If you have stranded power, or excess power, they will take it. 
The overall architecture of this system though is beyond the territory of Rube Goldberg. I am kind of amazed that this is the level of te…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shinobi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETFs Expected to Launch on Australia's ASX Exchange in 2024: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228563</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228563/bitcoin-etfs-expected-launch-australia-asx-exchange-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T17:11:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Approval of spot Bitcoin ETFs on the ASX exchange, which accounts for the bulk of Australia's equity trading, is reportedly near.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin To $300,000? Crypto Pundit Reveals What Will Drive It]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7435ef30b6</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-to-300000-crypto-pundit/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T17:03:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A crypto analyst has suggested that Bitcoin’s price movements were indicative of a potential surge to $300,000. The analyst has revealed key technical indicators and patterns that could signal BTC’s drive to a new target all-time high. 
 
Bitcoin Poised For Aggressive Bull Cycle Phase
 
A crypto analyst identified as ‘TradingShot’ on TradingView, a financial market analysis platform, released a post, predicting Bitcoin’s rise to $300,000. In their analysis of Bitcoin’s historical price movements from 2012 to 2024, TradingShot revealed that BTC had successfully tested and maintained the Mayer Multiple (MM) Mean and is currently in a consolidating phase.
 
 
The Mayer Multiple (MM) Mean is a technical indicator which computes the ratio between the price and the 200-day moving average. It is …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Holograph Expands 'Omnichain' Gaming NFT Push With New Funding]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228602</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228602/holographomnichain-gaming-nfts-new-funding"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T17:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With $3 million in fresh funding led by Mechanism Capital and Selini Capital, Holograph is pushing deeper into gaming with tokens that can be used across Ethereum-compatible chains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GBTC Reserves Dip Below 300,000 BTC Amidst 3 Weeks of Crypto Fund Outflows]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7435e89d8b</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/gbtc-reserves-dip-below-300000-btc-amidst-3-weeks-of-crypto-fund-outflows/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T16:55:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale’s Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) has witnessed a significant reduction in assets under management, with the trust’s holdings now falling below the 300,000 BTC mark, a key milestone. Additionally, the latest report on digital asset fund flows from Coinshares shows that bitcoin and ether exchange-traded products (ETPs) have seen withdrawals for three consecutive weeks. Heavy Withdrawals […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Token Runecoin Hits All-Time High Price Ahead of OKX Listing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228573</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228573/bitcoin-token-runecoin-all-time-high-price-okx-listing"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T16:28:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Centralized exchange OKX is the latest to embrace Bitcoin Runes, running a Runecoin rewards drive ahead of the listing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More Than $3 Billion in Tokens Unlock in May—Here’s What to Watch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228564</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228564/3-billion-token-unlocks-may-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T15:26:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some of the biggest unlocks are coming from DeFi oracle provider Pyth and decentralized crypto derivatives platform Aevo.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Has Secretly Considered Ethereum a Security Since 2023, Says Consensys in Unredacted Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228504</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228504/sec-declared-ethereum-security-last-year-consensys-lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T14:20:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unredacted portions of a lawsuit filed by Consensys reveal that the agency classified ETH as a security last April.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Payments Giant Stripe Expands Crypto Return With Avalanche Integration]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228359</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228359/payments-giant-stripe-expands-crypto-return-with-avalanche-support"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T13:01:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stripe's new Avalanche integration means that users can buy AVAX directly through the mobile app—without having to go through an exchange.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Primitives Protocol’s Decentralized Social Graph Has Facebook In its Sights]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=227044</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/227044/primitives-protocols-decentralized-social-graph-has-facebook-in-its-sights"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T13:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Built with Solana’s State Compression Technology, Primitives Protocol’s "non-fungible graphs" enable friends to migrate between social networks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Apeiron' Open Beta: Should You Play This Clever Mashup of Strategy Genres?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228218</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228218/apeiron-open-beta-should-you-play-clever-strategy-mashup"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T12:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's more than just airdrop hype behind Ronin game Apeiron, which smartly blends genres for a satisfying strategy affair.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friend.tech V2 Goes Live as Hype Builds for 100% Airdrop of FRIEND Token]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228473</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228473/friend-tech-v2-goes-live-as-hype-builds-for-100-airdrop-of-friend-token"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T11:11:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Friend.tech launches its version 2, hype builds among the community for its new points system and FRIEND token airdrop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Priest Fired by Catholic Group After Pitching Gatorade Baptisms]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228360</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228360/ai-priest-catholic-answers-father-justin"/>
        <updated>2024-04-28T19:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Pope Francis prepares to address AI at the G7 summit, a virtual priest loses his collar.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It's an Incredible Time for RPGs—Don't Miss These 11 Recent Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228395</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228395/11-must-play-role-playing-games-rpgs"/>
        <updated>2024-04-28T17:56:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Love role-playing games? RPG fans have been spoiled over the last year with huge sequels and clever originals. Here are 11 must-play games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Frederiksen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Crypto Games: Notcoin Token Launch Nears, Immutable's $50 Million Giveaway]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228386</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228386/this-week-crypto-games-notcoin-token-launch-immutable-50-million-giveaway"/>
        <updated>2024-04-28T13:31:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Notcoin launch is only days away, while Immutable is giving out rewards and Charles Hoskinson's studio released a game—not on Cardano.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week on Crypto Twitter: Bitcoin Runes Mania and More Ethereum Legal Drama]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228373</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228373/crypto-twitter-bitcoin-runes-cryptopunk-bored-ape-consensys-ethereum-lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2024-04-28T10:01:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As new Runes tokens dominated crypto, a proactive suit from Consensys against the SEC fostered a wartime mood among industry leaders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Cold Wallet' Review: The First Real Crypto Film]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228289</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228289/cold-wallet-review-first-real-crypto-film"/>
        <updated>2024-04-27T12:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a crypto exchange collapses, a group of Redditors set out to recover their funds from the CEO—by whatever means necessary.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Bitcoin Stumbles but Meme Coins Come Out Winning—Again]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228355</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228355/this-week-in-coins-bitcoin-meme-coins-bonk-pepe-floki"/>
        <updated>2024-04-27T10:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bonk, Pepe, and Floki are among the biggest gainers of the past seven days.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Altman, Satya Nadella Join High-Powered AI Safety Board for Homeland Security]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228348</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228348/openai-sam-altman-microsoft-satya-nadella-homeland-security-ai-safety-board"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T21:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twenty leading AI developers—including OpenAI, Microsoft, NVIDIA, and Google—pledge to help the US Department of Homeland Security protect critical infrastructure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Notcoin’ Game Token Is Launching Soon—Here's How the Claim Works]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228345</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228345/notcoin-game-token-launch-how-to-claim"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T19:56:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NOT token is dropping in a matter of days, Notcoin’s co-creator told Decrypt’s GG. Here’s what to expect from the claim process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Releases 8 Small AI Language Models To Compete With Microsoft’s Phi-3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228325</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228325/apple-small-ai-models-openelm-microsoft-phi-mini"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T19:46:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Competition in the AI space has started to shift from building the largest models to the smallest, most capable tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yuga Labs ‘Lost Its Way’ Says CEO as Bored Ape NFT Maker Reveals Layoffs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228336</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228336/yuga-labs-lost-way-says-ceo-bored-ape-nft-layoffs"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T19:19:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bored Ape Yacht Club creator Yuga Labs is restructuring with an aim to get back to its smaller, scrappier early days.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Allies: Arbitrum Team Helps Optimism Avoid ‘High Risk’ Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228318</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228318/arbitrum-offchain-labs-optimism-vulnerability"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T18:54:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reaching out to combat potential fraud, from one layer-2 to another.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elizabeth Warren Claims Crypto Is the ‘Payment of Choice’ for Child Abuse Material]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228317</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228317/elizabeth-warren-claims-crypto-is-the-payment-of-choice-for-child-abuse-material"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T18:21:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The top senator wants to help the Justice Department and Homeland Security clamp down on the use of cryptocurrency in child exploitation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Game On: The Hottest Upcoming Gaming Token Airdrops]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211029</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211029/game-on-hottest-upcoming-gaming-token-airdrops"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T17:45:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATED: Here's what you need to know about gaming airdrops and rewards around Notcoin, Immutable zkEVM, Saga, Illuvium, Apeiron, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETFs Bleed Badly as Skittish Investors Cash Out $218 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228300</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228300/bitcoin-etf-outflows-end-71-day-run"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T17:25:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nearly $218 million exited the formerly red-hot investment vehicles in the wake of a weak U.S. economic report.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase, Uniswap Execs Praise Ethereum Giant Consensys for Taking On SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228274</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228274/coinbase-uniswap-ethereum-consensys-sec"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T17:07:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The heads of crypto industry titans like Coinbase and Uniswap are rallying behind Consensys in its fight to get the SEC to concede Ethereum is not a security.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Sasha Stiles’ Experiential, AI-Infused NFT Drop with Bang & Olufsen]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/6Vi2IgYj/inside-sasha-stiles-experiential-ai-infused-nft-drop-with-bang-olufsen</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/6Vi2IgYj/inside-sasha-stiles-experiential-ai-infused-nft-drop-with-bang-olufsen"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T22:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At a launch party for the collection in New York’s SoHo neighborhood, the artist broke down her latest art experiment, “Four Core Texts,” with Decrypt’s Sander Lutz.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interview: How 'Notcoin' Will Evolve After the NOT Token Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PprnGP14/interview-how-notcoin-will-evolve-after-the-not-token-launch</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PprnGP14/interview-how-notcoin-will-evolve-after-the-not-token-launch"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Open Builders founder Sasha Plotvinov speaks with Decrypt's Sander Lutz at Token 2049 Dubai about how he envisions Notcoin's expansion and evolution after the token drop—into something akin to the "Netflix of social, viral games."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Magic Runes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IGWg0R64/magic-runes</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IGWg0R64/magic-runes"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T13:59:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC stables at $66k, liquidations in narrow range. BTC funding again turns negative in bullish sign. ETFs net inflow after Grayscale moves to lower fees. BTC demand 5x vs supply post-halving: Bitfinex. SOL congestion issue now largely solved. Two SEC lawyers resign after ‘gross abuse of power’. Ripple fights to lower $2bn SEC fine. SAFE trades at $2.8bn FDV after OKX lists. MANEKI hits $150m on first day, China memes pump. Memecoins are ‘black hole you can’t ignore’. DeGods up 20%, may switch back to SOL. Magic Eden launches Runes platform ahead of time.  Louis Vuitton gifts Pharrell jacket to NFT holders. Melania Trump launches necklace with SOL NFTs. Hoodie Punk trades for $620K.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Luxury Watches, Designer Shoes Will Soon Trade Like NFTs: Arianee CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/CSNQG2md/luxury-watches-designer-shoes-will-soon-trade-like-nfts-arianee-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/CSNQG2md/luxury-watches-designer-shoes-will-soon-trade-like-nfts-arianee-ceo"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arianee CEO Pierre-Nicolas Hurstel sat down with Rug Radio founder Farokh and Decrypt’s Sander Lutz at NFT Paris to discuss everything from the future of on-chain luxury to the secret hack to finding the best restaurants in France.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notcoin's Co-Creator Explains the Game's Token Delay—And When to Expect NOT Now]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/7Zx33xo5/notcoins-co-creator-explains-the-games-token-delayand-when-to-expect-not-now</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/7Zx33xo5/notcoins-co-creator-explains-the-games-token-delayand-when-to-expect-not-now"/>
        <updated>2024-04-22T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Notcoin co-creator Sasha Plotvinov spoke with Decrypt's Sander Lutz at Token 2049 Dubai to discuss why the NOT token launch was pushed back from the original 4/20 target, when to expect the listing, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TON’s Justin Hyun Breaks Down The Importance of USDT Coming to Telegram]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ODQI6ACA/tons-justin-hyun-breaks-down-the-importance-of-usdt-coming-to-telegram</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ODQI6ACA/tons-justin-hyun-breaks-down-the-importance-of-usdt-coming-to-telegram"/>
        <updated>2024-04-19T10:14:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Token 2049 in Dubai, The Open Network’s director of investments sat down with Decrypt’s Sander Lutz to discuss what he sees as the game-changing integration of USDT onto TON, and his plans for getting Telegram’s 900 million users to start using crypto in the immediate future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Influencer Ansem Explains His Meme Coin Thesis and Why He’s Bullish on Bitcoin Runes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/u9DHFoK0/crypto-influencer-ansem-explains-his-meme-coin-thesis-and-why-hes-bullish-on-bitcoin-runes</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/u9DHFoK0/crypto-influencer-ansem-explains-his-meme-coin-thesis-and-why-hes-bullish-on-bitcoin-runes"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T21:56:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ansem, the crypto trader who's amassed a sizable following on the back of meme coin Dogwifhat (WIF) and other calls, chats with Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz at Token 2049 Dubai about his meme coin thesis, why he's bullish on Bitcoin Runes, and what he sees ahead for the crypto markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Sander Lutz Braves the Dubai Floods for a Crypto Conference]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/mtjVHGa3/decrypts-sander-lutz-braves-the-dubai-floods-for-a-crypto-conference</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/mtjVHGa3/decrypts-sander-lutz-braves-the-dubai-floods-for-a-crypto-conference"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T21:33:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz reports from Dubai amid a historic storm that flooded the famed city, trudging through the streets to complete his essential task: Attending the Token 2049 crypto conference.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gold Beats Its All Time High]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/6ULgUKVk/gold-beats-its-all-time-high</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/6ULgUKVk/gold-beats-its-all-time-high"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T09:53:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) maintains its trend of reaching higher lows amidst choppy market conditions. Exchange-traded funds (ETFs) witness another influx of $125 million. There's anticipation of Hong Kong approving ETFs for both Bitcoin and Ethereum (ETH) come Monday. Notable institutional investor BlackRock shows interest in Bitcoin. Recent filings reveal increased Bitcoin purchases by banks. A Bitcoin-friendly political party secures victory in the South Korean election. Analyst Kang predicts Bitcoin could surge to $80-100k by May. Meanwhile, Ethereum sees accumulation by stablecoin whales on the rise. A new Ethereum Improvement Proposal (EIP) aims to streamline signing requests. Solana (SOL) experiences a resurgence in activity, reaching yearly highs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NASA’s Next Deep Space Mission Won’t Use Artificial Intelligence]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/0WGP33Rp/nasas-next-deep-space-mission-wont-use-artificial-intelligence</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/0WGP33Rp/nasas-next-deep-space-mission-wont-use-artificial-intelligence"/>
        <updated>2024-04-13T18:42:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Thursday, Decrypt Media visited NASA's Jet Propulsion Laboratory in Pasadena, CA to meet with the Engineering team behind the Europa Clipper before its launch to Jupiter's Europa moon in October.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Do A Little with Weesh]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LnaOT9bF/we-do-a-little-with-weesh</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LnaOT9bF/we-do-a-little-with-weesh"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T07:46:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week’s episode, we did a little something different. We took the man who is usually behind the camera and put him in front of it. We sat down with our producer Weesh to dive into how in fell in love with art and became a collector, how he met Andy and fun childhood memories together, his biggest wins in crypto, and so much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside VanEck’s Crypto Takeover of the New York Stock Exchange]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9YAY4wGD/inside-vanecks-crypto-takeover-of-the-new-york-stock-exchange</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9YAY4wGD/inside-vanecks-crypto-takeover-of-the-new-york-stock-exchange"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T14:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worlds collide as Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz heads to the floor of the NYSE to witness a special closing bell ceremony hosted by VanEck in honor of Web3. Featuring Choose Rich Nick, VanEck Head of Web3 Matt Bartlett, and more!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wormhole Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9SNiIVfU/wormhole-wednesday</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9SNiIVfU/wormhole-wednesday"/>
        <updated>2024-04-07T17:42:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC hits $64.5K then rebounds, SOL outperforms. Government sends $2B BTC to Coinbase to sell. Funding rates stay low after sweep lower. ETFs see small inflow, Ark outflow more than GBTC. Wormhole W launches at $15B FDV. BTC ‘inflection point’ if it follows rates or gold. Gold & BTC very correlated for the last year. Expect slower ETF volume this month: Bloomberg. BTC 2x and 3x levered ETFs launch yesterday. BTC ETFs now half the size of gold.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Dogs, Now Cats]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/2KrbCFNp/first-dogs-now-cats</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/2KrbCFNp/first-dogs-now-cats"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T14:06:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC falls another 6% amid $400m liquidations. ETF outflows and dollar strength blamed for move. Funding completely reset to lows in move. BTC lower high leaves market in ‘no trade zone’. This cycle acting ‘nothing like previous cycle’. ETH unlikely to be classed a security: Coinbase CFO. Crypto VC funding up 53% in MarchAnsem’s cat coin sees more volume than NFT market. Most memecoins down 10-20% given move in majors. MEW up 10% after HTX lists, airdrop to Saga phones. MEME to launch memecoin chain, NFTs rise. Pixelmon releases trailer for Anime series.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>