<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-09-22T19:11:42.110Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-09-22T19:11:42.110Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance vs. SEC Update: Crypto Exchange And CEO Fight Back With New Filing]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7545d50ad0</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/binance-vs-sec-ceo/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T18:50:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto exchange Binance, its US arm Binance.US, and Binance CEO Changpeng “CZ” Zhao are fighting back against the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) with a new court filing.
 
Binance And Binance CEO File Joint Motion Against SEC
 
On Thursday, September 21, 2023, Binance and Binance CEO Changpeng CZ Zhao filed a joint motion to dismiss the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC)’s lawsuit against them, including Bam Management Holdings Inc.
 
 
The filing claims that the SEC had not plausibly alleged various securities-related violations and the regulator was seeking to surround digital assets under its authority.
 
In the 60-page petition, Binance and Changpeng claimed that the regulator had overstepped its authority in filing a lawsuit against them. The regulator leveled a …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This is the Silliest Speculation About SHIB, According to LUCIE]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18922614/This-is-the-Silliest-Speculation-About-SHIB-According-to-LUCIE</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18922614/This-is-the-Silliest-Speculation-About-SHIB-According-to-LUCIE"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T18:45:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["The Shiba Ecosystem is undeniably attractive, and even the naysayers click to read about it," LUCIE argued.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Critic Senator Menendez Charged With Corruption, Bribery]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=198398</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/198398/bitcoin-critic-senator-menendez-corruption-bribery"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T18:39:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Senator Menendez, a long-time critic of Bitcoin and other crypto for its alleged association with criminals, faces up to 20 years in prison if convicted.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinShares Dives into the US with Investment Opportunities]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18922592/CoinShares-Dives-into-the-US-with-Investment-Opportunities</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18922592/CoinShares-Dives-into-the-US-with-Investment-Opportunities"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T18:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Hedge Fund division will offer crypto assets to U.S. investors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Next Crypto Market Boom to Happen After Bitcoin Halving: Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18922594/Next-Crypto-Market-Boom-to-Happen-After-Bitcoin-Halving-Analyst</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18922594/Next-Crypto-Market-Boom-to-Happen-After-Bitcoin-Halving-Analyst"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T18:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The analyst said the crypto market will see lower lows before hitting a bull rally post-halving. A crypto analyst said the U.S. Fed’s recession predictions align with the next crypto bear market. He predicted 2027 as the next bear market, around the same time the U.S. Fed pointed to a recession....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinShares Launches Hedge Fund Division In The US, Targeting Institutional Investors]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18922610/CoinShares-Launches-Hedge-Fund-Division-In-The-US-Targeting-Institutional-Investors</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18922610/CoinShares-Launches-Hedge-Fund-Division-In-The-US-Targeting-Institutional-Investors"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T18:33:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto asset manager CoinShares announced on Friday its foray into the U.S. with the launch of CoinShares Hedge Fund Solutions. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Cloud adds 11 blockchains to data warehouse 'BigQuery']]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18922570/Google-Cloud-adds-11-blockchains-to-data-warehouse-BigQuery</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18922570/Google-Cloud-adds-11-blockchains-to-data-warehouse-BigQuery"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T18:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s BigQuery added 11 new public datasets for blockchain networks, allowing users to obtain a variety of data from these networks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Founder’s Father Accused of Salary Dispute and Misappropriation in Bankruptcy Case]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18922583/FTX-Founders-Father-Accused-of-Salary-Dispute-and-Misappropriation-in-Bankruptcy-Case</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18922583/FTX-Founders-Father-Accused-of-Salary-Dispute-and-Misappropriation-in-Bankruptcy-Case"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T18:28:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joseph Bankman, the father of former FTX CEO Sam “SBF” Bankman-Fried, found himself embroiled in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong Regulators Crack Down on Crypto Fraud After JPEX Scandal]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18922584/Hong-Kong-Regulators-Crack-Down-on-Crypto-Fraud-After-JPEX-Scandal</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18922584/Hong-Kong-Regulators-Crack-Down-on-Crypto-Fraud-After-JPEX-Scandal"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T18:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong regulators are intensifying their scrutiny of the cryptocurrency market following the arrest of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ImmutableX skyrockets 30% after major crypto exchange lists IMX]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18922569/ImmutableX-skyrockets-30-after-major-crypto-exchange-lists-IMX</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18922569/ImmutableX-skyrockets-30-after-major-crypto-exchange-lists-IMX"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T18:20:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ImmutableX (IMX) price rose more than 30% after a top exchange listed the altcoin. While IMX still tops other crypto gainers in top 50 this past week, it has retreated from near $0.78, to $0.65 amid profit taking. ImmutableX (IMX) was among the hottest coins this week, skyrocketing more than 34%...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase’s Bitcoin Reserve Wallet Discovered: Here is How Much BTC It Holds]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18922568/Coinbases-Bitcoin-Reserve-Wallet-Discovered-Here-is-How-Much-BTC-It-Holds</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18922568/Coinbases-Bitcoin-Reserve-Wallet-Discovered-Here-is-How-Much-BTC-It-Holds"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T18:19:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The wallets where cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase holds Bitcoins were discovered by onchain researchers. Continue Reading: Coinbase’s Bitcoin Reserve Wallet Discovered: Here is How Much BTC It Holds]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Warns of Potential Scam in Calcium Token Trading]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18922552/Shiba-Inu-Warns-of-Potential-Scam-in-Calcium-Token-Trading</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18922552/Shiba-Inu-Warns-of-Potential-Scam-in-Calcium-Token-Trading"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T18:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kaal Dhairya, a Shiba Inu developer, has warned members of the meme coin’s community against a potential scam. In a recent post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Dhairya advised SHIB users not to buy or trade the Calcium token. According to him, the digital token has no liquidity, and claims of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There’s a ‘Good Chance’ Altcoins Will Be Struggling Over Coming Months, According to Benjamin Cowen – Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18922549/Theres-a-Good-Chance-Altcoins-Will-Be-Struggling-Over-Coming-Months-According-to-Benjamin-Cowen-Heres-Why</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18922549/Theres-a-Good-Chance-Altcoins-Will-Be-Struggling-Over-Coming-Months-According-to-Benjamin-Cowen-Heres-Why"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T18:05:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto analyst Benjamin Cowen says that altcoins will likely perform poorly for the remainder of 2023 based on historical patterns. Cowen tells his 787,000 YouTube subscribers that altcoins will likely struggle to close out the year as they had in other pre-halving years. The next Bitcoin (BTC)...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Small-Scale Bitcoin Holdings at ATHs, Vying Whales for Dominance]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18922544/Small-Scale-Bitcoin-Holdings-at-ATHs-Vying-Whales-for-Dominance</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18922544/Small-Scale-Bitcoin-Holdings-at-ATHs-Vying-Whales-for-Dominance"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T18:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[16 Joules per Terahash: Bitmain Unveils High-Efficiency S21 Bitcoin Miners at Hong Kong Summit]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7545d29307</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/16-joules-per-terahash-bitmain-unveils-high-efficiency-s21-bitcoin-miners-at-hong-kong-summit/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T18:04:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitmain, a leading bitcoin mining rig manufacturer, has introduced the newest addition to its Antminer products: the S21 series. The newest models have an efficiency rating under 20 joules per terahash (J/T) and produce between 200 terahash per second (TH/s) and 335 TH/s.
 
Bitmain Launches 2 New Antminers; Invests $54M in Core Scientific
 
At the 2023 World Digital Mining Summit in Hong Kong, Bitmain showcased its latest rigs from the Antminer S21 series. One machine employs hydro mining, and the other is air-cooled.
 
The S21 Hyd achieves up to 335 TH/s with an efficiency rating of 16 J/T. In contrast, the air-cooled S21 miner delivers up to 200 TH/s and has an efficiency rating around 17.5 J/T.
 
 
The Bitmain announcement comes after Canaan introduced its new Avalon miners. However, only one of them, the liquid cooling machine, has a 19.5 J/T efficiency, while Canaan’s air-cooled miner reaches 21.5 J/T.
 

 
Additionally, competitor Microbt aims to launch a machine with an efficiency under 20 J/T. Bitmain’s newest hydro-cooled rig contends with Microbt’s hydro-cooled M53S++ in hashrate. Nevertheless, its efficiency rating of 16 J/T outperforms Microbt’s rig, which has 22 J/T.
 
 
Besides Bitmain’s new rigs, the company has invested $54 million in Core Scientific through a fresh supply contract. Bitmain will deliver 27,000 bitcoin miners to Core Scientific and has entered a hosting agreement with the company.
 
The common stock and cash transaction will provide Core Scientific with Bitmain’s S19J XP Antiminer, which produces 151 TH/s and 21.7 J/T. “We look forward to deepening our strategic relationship with Core Scientific, our long-standing U.S.-based partner,” Max Hua, Bitmain’s CEO remarked.
 
What do you think about Bitmain’s latest mining rigs and the efficiency ratings they provide? Share your thoughts and opinions about this subject in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried’s trial starts Oct. 3: What you need to know]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18922563/Sam-Bankman-Frieds-trial-starts-Oct-3-What-you-need-to-know</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18922563/Sam-Bankman-Frieds-trial-starts-Oct-3-What-you-need-to-know"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T18:01:42.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Privacy For All: Brave To Integrate Zcash Protocol On Native Crypto Wallet]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18922548/Privacy-For-All-Brave-To-Integrate-Zcash-Protocol-On-Native-Crypto-Wallet</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18922548/Privacy-For-All-Brave-To-Integrate-Zcash-Protocol-On-Native-Crypto-Wallet"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T18:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During the Messari Mainnet event, the company behind the internet browser Brave announced a partnership with the Electric Coin Co. (ECC) and the Filecoin Foundation. These entities are the leading developers of the Zcash (ZEC) protocol and Filecoin (FIL). Related Reading: Bitcoin And Crypto Face...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance vs. SEC Update: Crypto Exchange And CEO Fight Back With New Filing]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18922538/Binance-vs-SEC-Update-Crypto-Exchange-And-CEO-Fight-Back-With-New-Filing</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18922538/Binance-vs-SEC-Update-Crypto-Exchange-And-CEO-Fight-Back-With-New-Filing"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T18:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4,098 ETH Worth $6M Was Just Burned]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18922562/4098-ETH-Worth-6M-Was-Just-Burned</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18922562/4098-ETH-Worth-6M-Was-Just-Burned"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T18:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What happened: On Thursday a total of 4,098.33 Ether (CRYPTO: ETH) worth $6,509,827, based on the current value of Ethereum at time of publication ($1,588.41), was burned from Ethereum transactions. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Exchange Reveals $70 Million Hack Due to Compromised Keys]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18922526/Crypto-Exchange-Reveals-70-Million-Hack-Due-to-Compromised-Keys</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18922526/Crypto-Exchange-Reveals-70-Million-Hack-Due-to-Compromised-Keys"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong-based cryptocurrency exchange, CoinEx, recently disclosed that compromised private keys led to a significant...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Real estate or Bitcoin: Which is more reliable?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18922515/Real-estate-or-Bitcoin-Which-is-more-reliable</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18922515/Real-estate-or-Bitcoin-Which-is-more-reliable"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Cloud Adds Support for Polygon, Optimism, Polkadot, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18922512/Google-Cloud-Adds-Support-for-Polygon-Optimism-Polkadot-and-More</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18922512/Google-Cloud-Adds-Support-for-Polygon-Optimism-Polkadot-and-More"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T17:58:56.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Citadel Securities Slapped with $7M Fine for Coding Error, SEC Says]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7545d3c3bb</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/citadel-securities-slapped-with-7m-fine-for-coding-error-sec-says/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T17:55:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Securities and  
Exchange Commission (SEC) has announced that Citadel Securities has settled  
charges of violating Regulation SHO, a law aimed at controlling  
short-selling practices. This violation pertained to Citadel Securities'  
alleged failure to accurately mark sale orders as long, short, or short exempt.  

The SEC's investigation  
revealed a pattern of mismarked orders over five years, attributing  
these inaccuracies to a coding error within Citadel Securities' automated  
trading system. During this time, the  
firm mistakenly classified short sales as long sales and vice versa. Even more  
concerning to the SEC was that Citadel provided this erroneous data  
to regulatory authorities, including the SEC, without detection or correction.
Citadel Securities'  
Five-Yea…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tom Emmer's Anti-CBDC Bill Passes House Committee | EP 830]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18922155/Tom-Emmers-Anti-CBDC-Bill-Passes-House-Committee-EP-830</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18922155/Tom-Emmers-Anti-CBDC-Bill-Passes-House-Committee-EP-830"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T17:49:47.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Non-Whale Addresses Now Control 41.1% Of Supply, A New All-Time High]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7545dc85e9</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-non-whale-addresses-41-1-all-time-high/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T17:49:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data shows that Bitcoin addresses carrying less than 100 BTC now control 41.1% of the total supply, a new all-time high.
 
Bitcoin Non-Whale Addresses Have Increased Their Supply Recently
 
According to data from the on-chain analytics firm Santiment, a shift has occurred in the BTC market during the last few months. The indicator of interest here is the “Supply Distribution,” which tells us about the total percentage of the Bitcoin supply the different investor groups hold.
 
Addresses or holders are divided into these groups based on the total number of coins they currently carry in their wallets. For example, the 1 to 10 coins cohort includes all investors that own at least 1 and at most 10 BTC.
 
If the Supply Distribution were applied to this specific group, it would measure …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hououin Kyouma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gucci's Milan Fashion Week Show Debuts on Roblox and Zepeto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=198384</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/198384/guccis-milan-fashion-week-show-debuts-on-roblox-and-zepeto"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T17:46:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gucci creative director Sabato de Sarno's first runway show for the fashion giant is also now in the metaverse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephanie Hirschmiller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[French Restaurant Seeks to Drive Bitcoin Adoption, Accepting Only BTC for High End Menu Item]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7545de38d3</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/french-restaurant-seeks-to-drive-bitcoin-adoption-accepting-only-btc-for-high-end-menu-item"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T17:36:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Can Bitcoin possibly rhyme with tradition?
This new currency is so young and so different from the usual dollars and euros, that for most people it seems disconnected from the economic reality and even further - from their lives. Despite the fact that paying with Bitcoin is not much more complicated than paying with a credit card, it looks like for the majority it is still a quasi-esoteric experience. 
There is definitely a psychological barrier to Bitcoin adoption.
To lower this barrier, what can be better than associating Bitcoin with something that is widely acknowledged and cherished? Something with a reputation that speaks for itself, capable of pulling Bitcoin from its shadow of “internet speculation” and propelling it into the realm of legit alternative money?..
For the French peopl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marie Poteriaieva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ether Turns Inflationary as Network Revenue Plunges to 9-Month Low]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7545dee318</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/09/22/ether-turns-inflationary-as-network-revenue-plunges-to-9-month-low/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T17:30:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH has given up its deflationary status as network fees are falling, putting pressure on the price of the second largest cryptocurrency.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Cloud Pushes Deeper Into Blockchain Data, Adding 11 Networks Including Polygon]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7545d8de42</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/09/22/google-cloud-pushes-deeper-into-blockchain-data-adding-11-networks-including-polygon/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T17:15:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s cloud-computing business has stored historical data on Bitcoin since 2018, claiming the service provides faster access than can be obtained directly from the blockchain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bradley Keoun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$250,000 Klever Blockchain Hackathon Open for Applications]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7545d9e8f5</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/250000-klever-blockchain-hackathon-open-for-applications/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T17:07:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. Switzerland – Date: 22nd September 2023. 
 
Venue: Online at Klever Hackathon Portal
 
Event Overview:
 
Klever.org is taking the lead in the evolution of blockchain technology. Inviting developers globally, we’re hosting the Klever Hackathon 2023, an event poised to be a watershed in decentralized ecosystem innovation.
 
Event Details:
 
Phase One: Competition
 
Reward: $250,000 in KLV + KFI tokens
 
 
Problem Proposal: 01/10/2023 – Submit your groundbreaking project idea.
 
Product Launch: 01/12/2023 – Roll out a functional product across web platforms, Apple Store, or Google Play Store.
 
Winner Announcement: 30/12/2023 – Prizes will be distributed as per milestone achievements.
 
Key Performance Indicators: DAU, MAU, Total Transactions on Klever Blockchain.
 
 
Phase Two…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[India’s Hefty Crypto Tax Rules Will Last Two More Years, WaxirX Chief Says]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7545c4c1cd</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/indias-hefty-crypto-tax-rules-cant-last-more/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T16:48:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[India has continued in its hawkish stance on crypto, and while most people expect the government to introduce crypto-friendly rules, Nischal Shetty, CEO of India-based crypto exchange WazirX expects the opposite. According to him, the hefty tax regime will likely last longer.
 
India Records Significant Drop In Trading Volume
 
In February 2022, during the budget presentation, India announced a 30% tax on revenue from cryptocurrencies. Also, the government said investors will pay a levy of 1% on all assets sold as tax deducted at source.
 
 
Meanwhile, the high taxes increased transaction costs, causing market makers and large investors to pull back on their activities. As a result, there was a significant drop in trading volumes on crypto exchanges.
 
Furthermore, reports revealed that th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kent Glory</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Did the NSA Invent Bitcoin? A 1996 Research Paper Reignites the Debate]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7545c66411</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/did-the-nsa-invent-bitcoin-a-1996-research-paper-reignites-the-debate/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T16:36:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recent buzz within crypto circles revolves around a 1996 research paper from the U.S. National Security Agency (NSA). There’s burgeoning speculation: did the NSA lay the groundwork for Bitcoin? Indeed, there are striking similarities between the NSA document and the Bitcoin white paper. However, a detailed look suggests a tighter connection to centralized Chaumian models described years prior.
 
From NSA’s Vaults to Satoshi’s Vision: Tracing Bitcoin’s Alleged Origins
 
Bitcoin, whose existence is widely attributed to the elusive Satoshi Nakamoto, now has whispers suggesting its true origin might be the U.S. Department of Defense’s intelligence arm, the NSA. This isn’t a new narrative, but we’ll dive into its prior emergence shortly. For now, it’s worth noting this theory, along with the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Subtle Art of Orange Pilling]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7545c7de53</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/the-subtle-art-of-orange-pilling"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T16:26:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Throughout the years, I have presented the case for Bitcoin to a lot of people from a wide range of backgrounds. The list includes curious cab drivers, financial advisors, young software developers, skeptical policymakers, voiceless activists, and once even an IMF employee. 
Needless to say, most of these attempts ended up falling on deaf ears. So I started asking myself “why would this person in front of me care about Bitcoin?” and immediately realized that getting a response was particularly challenging because—even among Bitcoiners—there is no common understanding of what Bitcoin is in the first place. Is it “peer-to-peer electronic cash” as Satoshi originally defined it? Or should we consider it as “digital property” as Michael Saylor suggests? Or maybe listen to Gary Gensler and defin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Colzani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biggest Movers: XRP Rebounds on Friday, Following Recent Decline]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7545c1f7e0</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/biggest-movers-xrp-rebounds-on-friday-following-recent-decline/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T16:12:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After being the victim of a red wave on Thursday, XRP rebounded in today’s session, as crypto bulls remained resilient. The global market cap is up by 0.40% at the time of writing, following a 2% drop yesterday. Stellar was another strong mover on Friday, and is currently up 2.25% 
 
XRP
 
XRP was back in the green on Friday, after bulls abruptly ended a three-day win streak during yesterday’s session.
 
Following a low at $0.5025 on Thursday, XRP/USD moved to a peak at $0.5134 earlier in the day.
 
The surge saw XRP, formerly ripple, once again make strides towards a key resistance level at $0.5450.
 
 
From the chart, it appears that the rebound came as the relative strength index (RSI) climbed back above a ceiling at 47.00.
 
At present, price strength is now sitting at 48.72, with the next visible ceiling near the 54.00 region.
 
In the event this target is hit, there is a strong likelihood that XRP moves above $0.5400.
 
 
Stellar (XLM)
 
Stellar (XLM) was also in the green in today’s session, after two consecutive days of price declines.
 
XLM/USD peaked at $0.1154 earlier in the day, which comes less than 24 hours after falling to a low of $0.1122.
 
As a result of the decline, bulls continued to push the token away from a recent floor at $0.1100, and back on course toward resistance at $0.1320.
 
 
Today’s rebound was helped by the RSI reaching a floor of its own at 37.00, and it is now tracking at 39.87.
 
A ceiling at 44.00 now awaits bulls, and could be the main hurdle preventing further gains this weekend.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
Where will stellar end this weekend? Let us know your thoughts in the comments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[European Parliament Calls for Tighter Oversight of Global Cryptocurrency Market]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=198369</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/198369/european-parliament-calls-for-tighter-oversight-of-global-cryptocurrency-market"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T16:07:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A European regulatory framework targeting digital assets should be in greater accord with global efforts, argues new research.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX’s Sam Bankman-Fried Served Another Massive Blow Just Two Weeks To Trial]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7545cdeab8</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ftx-sam-bankman-fried-blow/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T15:46:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With just two weeks to his trial, FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF) appealed his bail revocation ruling, hoping he would attend his trial from home when it commences. However, that is unlikely following the Court of Appeals order on September 21.
 
Sam Bankman-Fried To Remain In Jail
 
A three-judge panel of Circuit Judges including John M. Walker, Jr., Denny Chin, and William J. Nardini ordered that SBF’s motion for release pending trial be denied. That means that Sam Bankman-Fried will remain in detention until his trial commences.
 
 
SBF and his lawyers had appealed Judge Lewis Kaplan’s (the Judge in charge of SBF’s case) ruling, where he revoked the FTX founder’s bail and ordered that he be detained at the Brooklyn Metropolitan Detention Center (MDC) until his trial begins on Octobe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinEx Makes a Comeback: Deposits and Withdrawals to Resume Following $70M Hack]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7545cfb28c</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/coinex-makes-a-comeback-deposits-and-withdrawals-to-resume-following-70m-hack/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T15:34:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cryptocurrency exchange CoinEx is making a  
comeback after a devastating $70 million hack. The exchange announced today (Friday) that it had taken measures to rebuild its wallet system and ensure the safety  
and security of its users' assets.
As a result, CoinEx is now gradually resuming deposit  
and withdrawal services for a substantial number of cryptocurrencies, totaling  
190. The platform has asked users to use new deposit addresses to  
prevent permanent loss of assets.
Navigating Challenges and Re-Building Trust
"The wallet system is operating safely and  
steadily at present. We will gradually resume deposit and withdrawal services  
for the remaining 500+ cryptos," the exchange said.  
"Since the resumption of operations will be processed frequently, there will be  
no furt…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Should Be Decentralized, But How?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7545c8213b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/09/22/ai-should-be-decentralized-but-how/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T15:31:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The case for greater transparency and verifiability in AI. But is decentralization the best way to achieve that and is feasible in practice? Jesus Rodriquez says the technical challenges are tremendous.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesus Rodriguez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Huddle01 CEO Ayush Ranjan on Why Decentralized Audio and Video Infrastructure is Needed]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/YOHhQtWS/huddle01-ceo-ayush-ranjan-on-why-decentralized-audio-and-video-infrastructure-is-needed</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/YOHhQtWS/huddle01-ceo-ayush-ranjan-on-why-decentralized-audio-and-video-infrastructure-is-needed"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T15:11:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Huddle01 co-founder and CEO Ayush Ranjan joined Decrypt reporter André Beganski at Messari Mainnet 2023 to discuss the "people-powered communications network," which provides audio and video capabilities via a decentralized network and can be integrated into social media platforms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 Adventure Game Big Time Poised to Kickoff Its ‘Player-Owned Economy’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7545b715ad</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/web3/2023/09/22/web3-adventure-game-big-time-poised-to-kickoff-its-player-owned-economy/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T14:45:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During the last year of beta testing, the crypto and NFT-focused game’s community has grown to over 350,000 people on Discord and over a quarter million on X (formerly Twitter).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum: Dencun Upgrade Likely Delayed To Early Next Year]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7545b74008</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-dencun-upgrade-delayed-early-next-year/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T14:45:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The anticipated Ethereum upgrade, dubbed Dencun, amalgamating the consensus layer (Deneb) and the execution layer (Cancun), is poised for a likely delay to early next year. The discussions during the Ethereum All Core Developers Consensus Call (ACDC) #118, chaired by Danny Ryan from the Ethereum Foundation, signposted this potential delay amid discussions surrounding the pivotal Ethereum Improvement Proposals (EIPs) such as EIP-4844. In a recent blog post, Galaxy Digital Vice President of Research, Christine Kim, highlighted the developments.
 
Delay Concerns And Strategic Discussions
 
Tim Beiko of the Ethereum Foundation, during the ACDC call, raised the prospect of Dencun not launching on the mainnet before the close of 2023, considering its absence on public testnets and the approachin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Soft Landing Is a Primary Objective’ — Federal Reserve Signals One More Rate Hike in 2023]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7545bc5f0e</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/soft-landing-is-a-primary-objective-federal-reserve-signals-one-more-rate-hike-in-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T14:10:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Based on the U.S. Federal Reserve’s forecasts, it appears that the central bank is poised to enact an additional hike to the federal funds rate by the end of 2023. The news comes in the wake of the Federal Reserve’s decision to leave the interest rate unchanged during its recent gathering of the Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC). Jerome Powell, the chairman of the Federal Reserve, emphasized this week that the central bank’s strategy entails supporting “the policy rate and await further data.” He underlined the importance of maintaining a “restrictive policy” to achieve the desired goal of curbing inflation.
 
Powell: A Soft Landing Is What ‘We’ve Been Trying to Achieve for All This Time’
 
During the recent FOMC gathering, the U.S. central bank opted to maintain the status quo on inter…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CFTC Denies Kalshi’s Plan to Let Users Bet on Control of U.S. Congress]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7545bdbacc</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/09/22/cftc-denies-kalshis-plan-to-let-users-bet-on-control-of-us-congress/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T14:01:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Regulators said the plans weren't in the public interest, after a court squabble involving rival service PredictIt]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack Schickler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Next Moonshot? Santiment’s Intriguing Insights For Crypto Enthusiasts]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7545b86201</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-next-moonshot-santiment-insights/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T13:44:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC), the flagship cryptocurrency, is currently drawing significant attention as it stands poised for a potential upward surge. Santiment, a leading blockchain analytics platform, has identified a pivotal factor that could pave the way for a substantial rally in Bitcoin’s price. 
 
This factor centers around the remarkable increase in short interest observed on two of the most prominent cryptocurrency exchanges in the world, igniting hopes of a short squeeze that could propel BTC’s value well beyond the $30,000 mark.
 
Santiment’s comprehensive analysis cited in a new report delves into the evolving landscape of Bitcoin trading, revealing a noteworthy development that has captured the imagination of crypto enthusiasts and market observers alike.
 
 
Bitcoin Short Interest Sparks O…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Claims Trading Near 35% of Debt Amount in Secondary Markets]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=198356</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/198356/ftx-claims-trading-near-35-of-debt-amount-in-secondary-markets"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T12:10:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Analysts found that investors are actively purchasing claims with an expectation of strong returns as the settlement progresses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Island Onboards Museums to On-Chain Art: ‘There is Something to Gain for Both Worlds’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=198332</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/198332/the-island-onboards-museums-to-on-chain-art-there-is-something-to-gain-for-both-worlds"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T11:14:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The platform aims to onboard traditional artists and institutions to the blockchain while bringing museum-quality standards to Web3 art.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Files $157 Million Lawsuit Against Ex-Employees of Hong Kong Affiliate]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=198353</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/198353/ftx-files-157-million-lawsuit-against-ex-employees-of-hong-kong-affiliate"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T11:07:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The lawsuit alleges that four ex-staffers used their connections to pull their money out first when FTX's stability was in question.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance and CEO Changpeng Zhao Seek Dismissal of SEC Lawsuit, Citing Regulatory Overreach]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=198337</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/198337/binance-and-ceo-changpeng-zhao-seek-dismissal-of-sec-lawsuit-citing-regulatory-overreach"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T10:28:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto exchange accuses the U.S. regulator of misinterpreting securities laws and retroactively imposing its authority.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nansen Users’ Blockchain Addresses Exposed in Security Breach]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=198329</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/198329/nansen-users-blockchain-addresses-exposed-in-security-breach"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T09:20:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto analytics firm reported that some password hashes and blockchain addresses were exposed, along with email addresses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Korean Mobile Developer NHN Is Building Crypto Games on Sui]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=198238</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/198238/south-korean-mobile-developer-nhn-building-crypto-games-sui"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T01:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Another notable South Korean publisher embraces blockchain gaming, this time on Sui in partnership with Mysten Labs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Elder Scrolls VI: Everything You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=198282</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/198282/elder-scrolls-vi-everything-you-need-know-leaks-rumors-news"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T23:05:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Skyrim can only hold a fantasy fan's attention for so long. Luckily, The Elder Scrolls VI is officially on the horizon. Here's the latest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nym CEO Harry Halpin on Why Regulators Push Back Against Privacy Tech]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/4njYsMbN/nym-ceo-harry-halpin-on-why-regulators-push-back-against-privacy-tech</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/4njYsMbN/nym-ceo-harry-halpin-on-why-regulators-push-back-against-privacy-tech"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T22:46:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nym CEO Harry Halpin sat down with Decrypt Markets Editor Stacy Elliott at Messari Mainnet 2023 to discuss Nym and how mixnets work, increasing regulatory pushback to privacy-protecting technologies, and why he remains optimistic in the face of such resistance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nirvana Bassist Says AI Could Help Complete Old Demo Songs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=198276</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/198276/nirvana-bassist-says-ai-could-help-complete-old-demo-songs"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T22:31:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Krist Novoselic says he's interested in using AI to finish new Nirvana songs from old scraps—after using the tech on concert recordings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ali Shutler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Insider Trading Ahead of Cisco’s $28 Billion Splunk Acquisition?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=198262</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/198262/insider-trading-ciscos-splunk"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T22:12:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One "lucky" trader appears to have turned $22,000 into $10 million betting on SPLK, a 46,000% return.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Not Only Me': Actor Anil Kapoor Wins AI Deepfake Court Case]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=198256</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/198256/not-only-me-actor-anil-kapoor-wins-ai-deepfake-court-case"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T22:06:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Every actor has the right to protect themselves and their rights," said Slumdog Millionaire star Anil Kapoor after the Indian court verdict.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Financial Regulator Issues 'Final Warning' to Non-Compliant UK Crypto Firms]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=198263</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/198263/financial-regulator-final-warning-crypto-firms-uk"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T21:29:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The FCA says the vast majority of crypto firms in the U.K. have yet to reply to the regulator's questions regarding new standards set to come into effect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[YouTube Adds AI Features to Enhance and Simplify Video Creation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=198226</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/198226/youtube-adds-ai-features-enhance-simplify-video-creation"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T20:46:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has unveiled new AI-powered features to bolster video creation on YouTube for both Shorts and long-form clips.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tim Draper Launches Crypto Accelerator Despite US Regulatory 'Shitshow,' Says Partner]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=198223</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/198223/tim-draper-launches-crypto-accelerator-despite-us-regulatory-shitshow-says-partner"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T19:53:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Billionaire investor Tim Draper's new Draper Goren Blockchain will have 10-year time horizons and aim to help build companies from scratch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Bottle Shock' Film Director Plots Animated Musical Remake—Funded by NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=198125</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/198125/bottle-shock-film-director-plots-animated-musical-remake-funded-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T18:15:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The "Bottle Shock" revival will reimagine the original live-action Alan Rickman wine film. Its creators say NFT holders will profit if the film sells to a distributor.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CBDC Anti-Surveillance Bill Passes House Committee Despite Push Back From Democrats]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=198216</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/198216/anti-cbdc-bill-passes-house-committee"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T17:52:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Majority Whip Tom Emmer’s (R-MN) CBDC Anti-Surveillance State Act is now headed for a vote before the House.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether Resumes USDT Loans, Insists It Maintains Excess Reserves]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=198188</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/198188/tether-resumes-usdt-loans-insists-it-maintains-excess-reserves"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T16:22:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoin issuer Tether has resumed lending USDT to clients, walking back a prior commitment to discontinue the practice.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Korea's Dreamus Debuts Avalanche NFT Tickets for Events, K-Pop Concerts]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=198091</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/198091/south-koreas-dreamus-puts-nft-tickets-avalanche-events-kpop-concerts"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T15:01:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SK Planet's loyalty app OK Cashbag is integrating Avalanche NFTs for live events like K-pop concerts, musicals, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Pirate Nation' Studio Raises $33 Million to Build Fully On-Chain Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=198093</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/198093/pirate-nation-studio-raises-33-million-build-fully-on-chain-games"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T15:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Proof of Play, founded by the co-creator of Zynga’s FarmVille, reveals seed funding and free-to-play plans for Pirate Nation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avantgarde Finance: DeFi Didn't Soar After FTX, But It Hasn't Declined Either]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/oSnhba7l/avantgarde-finance-defi-didnt-soar-after-ftx-but-it-hasnt-declined-either</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/oSnhba7l/avantgarde-finance-defi-didnt-soar-after-ftx-but-it-hasnt-declined-either"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T12:21:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avantgarde Finance CEO and founder Mona El Isa talks about how DeFi has changed (and hasn't) changed since the collapse of FTX and what it takes to get more passively managed products onchain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Pioneer Hal Finney Explains ZK Proofs in Rediscovered Footage]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=198150</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/198150/bitcoin-pioneer-hal-finney-explains-zk-proofs-in-rediscovered-footage"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T11:12:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A video has resurfaced showing the late software developer and Bitcoin pioneer Hal Finney explaining zero-knowledge protocols in the 1990s.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Base Ever Have a Token? 'Not Something We've Ruled Out Entirely,' Says Coinbase's Paul Grewal]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/oWMD6y1W/will-base-ever-have-a-token-not-something-weve-ruled-out-entirely-says-coinbases-paul-grewal</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/oWMD6y1W/will-base-ever-have-a-token-not-something-weve-ruled-out-entirely-says-coinbases-paul-grewal"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T11:01:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Chief Legal Officer talks to Decrypt's Andre Beganski about the recent Uniswap court ruling, tokenizing its Base L2, and the company's own battle for clearer regulations in the U.S..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ImmutableX Up 25% After South Korean Traders Drive IMX Price Surge]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=198152</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/198152/immutablex-up-25-after-south-korean-traders-drive-imx-price-surge"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T10:44:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A sudden surge in trading volumes on South Korean exchanges drove the price of IMX up by over 30% Thursday morning.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mt. Gox Trustee Extends Deadline for Creditor Repayments By a Year]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=198147</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/198147/mt-gox-trustee-extends-deadline-for-creditor-repayments-by-a-year"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T09:51:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mt. Gox creditors have another wait on their hands, with the repayment deadline pushed back to October 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paris Saint-Germain Is Giving Away Free AI-Generated NFT Posters]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=198075</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/198075/paris-saint-germain-giving-away-free-ai-generated-nft-posters"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T08:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[French soccer club Paris Saint-Germain has teamed with sponsor Crypto.com to give out official NFT posters created with AI assistance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Cohen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brain Implant Testing: Neuralink Begins Recruiting for Human Thought-Reading Trials]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=198110</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/198110/neuralink-brain-implant-chip-human-testing-fda"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T00:55:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neuralink is ready to take things to the inevitable next level, testing its brain-reading chip in humans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Developer Asked AI to Name and Launch a Memecoin—It Raked In $12 Million In One Day]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=198069</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/198069/astropepex-memecoin-token-ai-name-code"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T23:35:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The name of the first coin, AstroPepeX, was suggested by ChatGPT after it analyzed other successful token names.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Game of Thrones Creator George R.R. Martin Joins Lawsuit Against OpenAI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=198076</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/198076/game-of-thrones-george-rr-martin-ai-openai"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T22:45:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prominent authors are joining the Authors Guild in a lawsuit against OpenAI, alleging copyright infringement in training ChatGPT.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[After Failed Bid to Reclaim Namesake Company, Ben 'Bitboy' Armstrong Asks Fans for Cash]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=198021</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/198021/after-failed-bid-reclaim-namesake-company-ben-bitboy-armstrong-asks-fans-cash"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T21:42:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[YouTuber Ben "Bitboy" Armstrong has received about $60,000 so far after a judge denied his emergency injunction to regain control.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New DALL-E 3 Image Generator is a Big Upgrade—With Guardrails]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=198035</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/198035/new-dall-e-3-image-generator-is-a-big-upgrade-with-guardrails"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T21:41:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI’s new model stands up well against MidJourney and SDXL, and refuses to mimic living artists.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale Investments Applies to Offer Ethereum Futures ETF]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=198032</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/198032/grayscale-etf-ethereum-futures-sec-application"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T20:57:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fund, if approved by the Securities and Exchange Commission, would be separate from the firm’s proposed Bitcoin ETF.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Andreessen-Backed Fintech Eco App ‘Doubles Down’ On Non-Custodial Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=198037</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/198037/andreesen-horowitz-backed-fintech-eco-app-pivots-non-custodial-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T20:51:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company will slowly fade out its custodial features and focus on Beam, a recently launched non-custodial crypto wallet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shrapnel Studio Head Talks Unity Fees and Game Industry Challenges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/F09XirN4/shrapnel-studio-head-talks-unity-fees-and-game-industry-challenges</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/F09XirN4/shrapnel-studio-head-talks-unity-fees-and-game-industry-challenges"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T20:15:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shrapnel's Head of Studio Don Norbury shares his perspective on the "tumultuous" video games industry and the Unity fee news that's upset developers with Decrypt's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon to Tap Its Own AI Model to Upgrade Alexa for Smart Homes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=198029</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/198029/amazon-alexa-artificial-intelligence-ai-llm-smart-home"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T19:57:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon annnounced ambitious plans to integrate generative AI across its product ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PayPal Brings PYUSD Stablecoin to Venmo]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=198022</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/198022/paypal-brings-pyusd-stablecoin-to-venmo"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T19:49:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Select Venmo users can already buy the payment platform’s ERC-20 stablecoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Music Streaming Service Launching—Will People Pay?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197995</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197995/ai-music-streaming-service-launching-people-pay-musixy"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T18:59:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Musixy.ai also takes requests and sells the rights to unofficial takes on hit singles, but it's entering a divisive and legally thorny space.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ali Shutler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chilean Drug Trafficking Ring Was Also Mining Bitcoin: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=198009</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/198009/santiago-chile-bitcoin-mining-drug-bust-report"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T18:05:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Police raided a house in the capital city of Santiago and found marijuana, ketamine, and 19 Bitcoin mining machines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Toncoin Surges Into Top 10 Cryptocurrencies, Briefly Topping Dogecoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197987</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197987/toncoin-surges-top-10-cryptocurrencies-briefly-topping-dogecoin"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T17:53:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Toncoin (TON) is now the 10th-largest digital asset by market cap, following news of a Telegram crypto wallet launch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fortnite Players Can Claim Part of a $245 Million Settlement—Here's Who Is Eligible]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197988</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197988/how-to-get-a-refund-for-fortnite-from-epic-games"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T16:27:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Epic Games is paying out nearly a quarter of a billion dollars in refunds to Fortnite players. Here’s how to file a claim.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hashflow Turned DeFi Trading Into a Sci-Fi Game—With an AI Dictator]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197904</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197904/hashflow-turned-defi-trading-into-sci-fi-game-with-ai-dictator"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Hashverse offers a gamified take on crypto trading and DAO governance, encouraging players to gain XP and dominate the leaderboard.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Max Zim talks Memecoins and SocialFi - This Time Will Be Different]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/RnMigbJP/max-zim-talks-memecoins-and-socialfi-this-time-will-be-different</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/RnMigbJP/max-zim-talks-memecoins-and-socialfi-this-time-will-be-different"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T16:20:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Max and Reza dive into conversations about the current memecoin meta, the rising popularity of SocialFi and social tokens, and discuss lessons learned from big wins and big losses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here's How Much Bitcoin We Earned Playing Minecraft]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/z8rit7yN/heres-how-much-bitcoin-we-earned-playing-minecraft</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/z8rit7yN/heres-how-much-bitcoin-we-earned-playing-minecraft"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T16:49:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can now mine Bitcoin in Minecraft. Decrypt contributor Ryan S. Gladwin shows us how.

Satlantis website: https://satlantis.net/
Minecraft server address: play.satlantis.net]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gods Unchained's Daniel Paez on the Future of NFT Gaming Interoperability]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/obt7FGYr/gods-unchaineds-daniel-paez-on-the-future-of-nft-gaming-interoperability</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/obt7FGYr/gods-unchaineds-daniel-paez-on-the-future-of-nft-gaming-interoperability"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T20:27:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daniel Paez, executive producer on NFT card-battling game Gods Unchained, speaks with Decrypt Culture Editor Andrew Hayward about what the future of NFT game interoperability will really look like—and what it won't.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Mino Games is Using Artificial Intelligence]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/SrT1Afj7/how-mino-games-is-using-artificial-intelligence</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/SrT1Afj7/how-mino-games-is-using-artificial-intelligence"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T22:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mino Games CEO Sasha McKinnon tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about how the studio's upcoming game Dimensionals will use real-time AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INTERVIEW: How Will Aurory Use NFTs and Crypto?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qv3VwNmM/interview-how-will-aurory-use-nfts-and-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qv3VwNmM/interview-how-will-aurory-use-nfts-and-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T15:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Natoli, Aurory's Head of Marketing and Business Development, tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how the Aurory games will use NFTs and crypto and shares the studio's broader stance on the tech.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Cloud's James Tromans on the Intersection of AI and Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OeD4uoLj/google-clouds-james-tromans-on-the-intersection-of-ai-and-web3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OeD4uoLj/google-clouds-james-tromans-on-the-intersection-of-ai-and-web3"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google's Global Head of Google Cloud for Web3 James Tromans sat down with Decrypt's Jason Nelson to discuss how AI can help Web3 companies come to market faster and the real value of Web3 tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastering NFT Trading - Degen U]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/HQGt1Vrq/mastering-nft-trading-degen-u</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/HQGt1Vrq/mastering-nft-trading-degen-u"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T07:08:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Take Degen U's new course, Mastering NFT Trading, and earn an on-chain certificate. A top instructor will help you identify trends, seize the right moment to trade, weed out scams—and have fun while doing it!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Space Nation CEO on Working With 'Independence Day' Director Roland Emmerich]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LpznLhtx/space-nation-ceo-on-working-with-independence-day-director-roland-emmerich</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LpznLhtx/space-nation-ceo-on-working-with-independence-day-director-roland-emmerich"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T17:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jerome Wu, CEO of Space Nation, tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the upcoming Space Nation Online game in development and shares details on Space Nation Cofounder Roland Emmerich's role in the project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GAME REVIEW: Champions Arena from Gala Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qUE1RlDx/game-review-champions-arena-from-gala-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qUE1RlDx/game-review-champions-arena-from-gala-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Champions Arena is a turn-based fantasy RPG from Gala Games, where characters can become NFTs and crypto can be used to purchase gems, one of the game's synthetic currencies. Decrypt's Kate Irwin takes us inside the game for her thoughts on the fun, mobile-first title.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apex Legends Voice Actor Ben Prendergast on the Future of Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/X3RKdsaG/apex-legends-voice-actor-ben-prendergast-on-the-future-of-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/X3RKdsaG/apex-legends-voice-actor-ben-prendergast-on-the-future-of-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T18:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Voice actor Ben Prendergast, who's voiced characters in games like Apex Legends and God of War Ragnarok, shares his opinions on the tech space's history of "bubbles" and whether blockchain gaming has a future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>