<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-10-06T17:13:08.145Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-10-06T17:13:08.145Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Far From the SBF Trial, a Very Different Web3 Narrative Is Unfolding]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74bc909e21</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/10/06/far-from-the-sbf-trial-a-very-different-web3-narrative-is-unfolding/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T17:05:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The story of Sevi, a talented artist who happens to be a 10-year-old autistic boy living in Manila.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Tapscott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DailyCoin Bitcoin Regular: Are We Bracing for a Market Shake-Up or Stability?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18953011/DailyCoin-Bitcoin-Regular-Are-We-Bracing-for-a-Market-Shake-Up-or-Stability</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18953011/DailyCoin-Bitcoin-Regular-Are-We-Bracing-for-a-Market-Shake-Up-or-Stability"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T17:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore the latest developments and market insights in Bitcoin's journey as we analyze its resilience and community sentiments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Hashrate Hits Another ATH As Miners Continue To Back BTC]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18953005/Bitcoin-Hashrate-Hits-Another-ATH-As-Miners-Continue-To-Back-BTC</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18953005/Bitcoin-Hashrate-Hits-Another-ATH-As-Miners-Continue-To-Back-BTC"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T17:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data shows the Bitcoin mining hashrate has hit another all-time high as miners continue to believe in the cryptocurrency. Bitcoin 7-Day Hashrate Hits New ATH Despite Struggling Price The “mining hashrate” is an indicator that keeps track of the total amount of computing power that the miners...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Vs. SEC: Crypto CEO Predicts SEC Will Drop Charges Against Executives]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18952982/Ripple-Vs-SEC-Crypto-CEO-Predicts-SEC-Will-Drop-Charges-Against-Executives</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18952982/Ripple-Vs-SEC-Crypto-CEO-Predicts-SEC-Will-Drop-Charges-Against-Executives"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T17:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The civil trial of the US Securities and Exchange Commission’s (SEC) case against Ripple and its top executives, Brad Garlinghouse and Chris Larsen, is set to commence on April 23, 2024. However, the Founder of Dizer Capital, Yasin Mobarak, believes that the SEC will withdraw its charges against...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amidst Legal Battle, Binance to Exit Russia]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74bc9168d7</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/amidst-legal-battle-binance-to-exit-russia"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T17:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The below is a piece from a recent edition of Bitcoin Magazine Pro, Bitcoin Magazine's premium markets newsletter. To be among the first to receive these insights and other on-chain bitcoin market analysis straight to your inbox, subscribe now.
 
         
         
         
         
    
Binance, one of the world’s largest cryptocurrency exchanges, has seen several difficult months of various legal challenges, and recently sold all assets of their Russian branch to a company only founded days earlier.
The trouble began for this major exchange in June, when the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) sued Binance for alleged violation of securities law. Citing the “unregistered offers and sales of securities” and lying to potential investors “regarding surveillance and controls over man…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Landon Manning</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Won’t Fix The Federal Reserve]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74bc9168bd</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/markets/bitcoin-wont-fix-the-federal-reserve"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T17:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article is featured in Bitcoin Magazine’s “The Withdrawal Issue”. Click here to subscribe now.
A PDF pamphlet of this article is available for download. 
You’re reading a print Bitcoin Magazine so you probably already like Bitcoin, which means you probably don’t like the title or premise of what you’re about to read, and so, you already hate it.
Alas, it is written and published.
The money has been the way it is now for some time and to be sure people have been saying: "Well, hold on a minute …" for probably that whole time. I wouldn't really know, I wasn't there, but there are enough Austrian economists who have been proselytizing sound money principles since before the Great Depression to suggest that at least someone was saying it.
Without going too in depth about gold as a monetar…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Kaloudis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Where Ethereum Fails: DLCs, Atomic.Finance, and Bitcoin-Native Financial Services]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18952970/Where-Ethereum-Fails-DLCs-AtomicFinance-and-Bitcoin-Native-Financial-Services</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18952970/Where-Ethereum-Fails-DLCs-AtomicFinance-and-Bitcoin-Native-Financial-Services"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Magazine sits down with Atomic.Finance's CTO Matthew Black, exploring DLCs, Atomic.Finance's infrastructure, the downsides of Ethereum smart contracts and the far-reaching implications of Bitcoin-native financial services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Investors Panicked, Selling at a Loss in These Three Altcoins! What Does This Signal? Santiment Reviewed!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18952993/Investors-Panicked-Selling-at-a-Loss-in-These-Three-Altcoins-What-Does-This-Signal-Santiment-Reviewed</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18952993/Investors-Panicked-Selling-at-a-Loss-in-These-Three-Altcoins-What-Does-This-Signal-Santiment-Reviewed"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T16:57:06.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Sees Spot Market Share Fall To 34%, What’s Going On?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74bc9223d1</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/binance-spot-market-34/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T16:54:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance, the world’s leading cryptocurrency exchange’s spot market share has fallen for the seventh consecutive month and the crypto firm has reportedly lost more of its spot market share in the previous month.
 
Binance Sees Spot Market Share Decline
 
Reports have shown that the trading platform has experienced a decline in its spot market share for the seventh time in a row. The Binance exchange spot market share fell from 38.5% in August 2023, to 34.3% in September 2023 according to data from CCData.
 
CCData noted that the spot trading volume that the trading platform lost went to other cryptocurrency exchanges. These include HTX (formerly Huobi), OKX, Bybit, Bitget, and DigiFinex.
 
 
The trading platform’s trading volumes also experienced a 57% decline in its 7-day trading volume fo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Shrapnel's Marketplace, New Map, and 'AI Director' Feature]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/F5RQCmvH/inside-shrapnels-marketplace-new-map-and-ai-director-feature</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/F5RQCmvH/inside-shrapnels-marketplace-new-map-and-ai-director-feature"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T16:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin chats with Shrapnel's Head of Studio Don Norbury to get the latest updates on how the NFT-powered first-person sci-fi extraction shooter's development is progressing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Shrapnel's Marketplace, New Map, and 'AI Director' Feature]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18953010/Inside-Shrapnels-Marketplace-New-Map-and-AI-Director-Feature</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18953010/Inside-Shrapnels-Marketplace-New-Map-and-AI-Director-Feature"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T16:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin chats with Shrapnel's Head of Studio Don Norbury to get the latest updates on how the NFT-powered first-person sci-fi extraction shooter's development is progressing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 5 cryptocurrencies with the highest address activity]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18952981/Top-5-cryptocurrencies-with-the-highest-address-activity</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18952981/Top-5-cryptocurrencies-with-the-highest-address-activity"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T16:51:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrencies encompass more than just their current trading price, total market cap, and tokenomics. This groundbreaking technology, that’s behind shifting … Continued]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CFTC weighing charges against ex-Voyager Digital CEO Stephen Ehrlich]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18952966/CFTC-weighing-charges-against-ex-Voyager-Digital-CEO-Stephen-Ehrlich</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18952966/CFTC-weighing-charges-against-ex-Voyager-Digital-CEO-Stephen-Ehrlich"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T16:40:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) investigators have determined that Stephen Ehrlich, a co-founder of Voyager Digital, violated derivatives regulations before the company’s bankruptcy last year, Bloomberg reported on Oct. 6. According to the report, the enforcement division of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thorswap Halts Operations Amidst FTX Hacker’s Fund Movement; RUNE Drops 8.6%]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74bc9c43d6</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/thorswap-halts-operations-amidst-ftx-hackers-fund-movement-rune-drops-8-6/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T16:39:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The decentralized exchange (dex) Thorswap has paused operations after a series of funds stemming from the FTX hacker was sent to the dex protocol. Thorswap took to social media and said that the team “stands firmly against any and all criminal actions.”
 
Thorswap Pauses Amidst FTX Hack Fallout; RUNE Value Takes a Hit
 
After the FTX hacker moved thousands of ether (30,000 ETH) for the first time since the November 2022 breach, onchain observers noted that the funds were sent to Thorswap and the decentralized finance (defi) application Railgun. On October 6, 2023, Thorswap updated the community and said that the dex was down for maintenance. The dex team said:
 

Yesterday, following a careful evaluation of the situation and consultation with advisors, legal counsel, and law enforcement, the decision was made to temporarily transition the Thorswap interface into maintenance mode.
 
The dex will remain paused until “until a more permanent and robust solution” becomes available. Thorchain’s native crypto asset RUNE dropped 8.6% on the news. Thorswap said the developers are doing everything they can to get the application back up and running again.
 

 
“Swaps are paused. LP actions, Earn (savers), Borrow (lending), Staking actions are all fully operational,” Thorswap further detailed.
 
Consensys product manager Taylor Monahan insisted on the social media platform X (formerly Twitter) that over the past four months, “more than 50% of the ether to Thorswap router to bitcoin transactions have been stolen funds.”
 
What do you think about the Thorswap pause? Share your thoughts and opinions about this subject in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Crime Jumps to $7B as Cross-Chain Laundering Surges]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18952946/Crypto-Crime-Jumps-to-7B-as-Cross-Chain-Laundering-Surges</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18952946/Crypto-Crime-Jumps-to-7B-as-Cross-Chain-Laundering-Surges"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T16:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elliptic sounds the alarm on the rising rate of cross-chain crypto crime in 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Readers Responses To The Cult Of The Covenant]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74bc9dccbc</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/technical/readers-respond-to-the-cult-of-the-covenant"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T16:30:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shinobi’s Strawman is a weekly series where our Technical Editor Shinobi challenges the Bitcoin community, aiming to stir up conversation around heated technical debates.
_________________________________________________________________
Last week I published a short prompt looking to hear some readers thinking on different covenant proposals. The design space of covenants has rapidly evolved in the last two years or so, going from a mere two proposals (CTV and APO) to almost a dozen different proposals for very basic functionality that can offer large optimizations to existing use cases such as cold storage schemes or off-chain protocols like the Lightning network. It's quite a lot to reason through on the part of the communities in this space trying to assess what proposals they should or…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shinobi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kim Kardashian’s Secret Plan To Dominate Wall Street]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18952933/Kim-Kardashians-Secret-Plan-To-Dominate-Wall-Street</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18952933/Kim-Kardashians-Secret-Plan-To-Dominate-Wall-Street"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T16:30:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Emma Hinchliffe is a senior writer at Fortune, where she covers women in business. She also is the author of the 5-time a week newsletter called "Broadsheet." Emma recently wrote an article "Kim Kardashian turned Skims into a $4 billion company. She wants to build the next generation of unicorns...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amidst Legal Battle, Binance to Exit Russia]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18952910/Amidst-Legal-Battle-Binance-to-Exit-Russia</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18952910/Amidst-Legal-Battle-Binance-to-Exit-Russia"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 platform Galxe hit by DNS attack on front-end website]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18952917/Web3-platform-Galxe-hit-by-DNS-attack-on-front-end-website</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18952917/Web3-platform-Galxe-hit-by-DNS-attack-on-front-end-website"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T16:22:23.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Secures Major Victory, Bitcoin Soars to $28K: This Week’s Crypto Recap]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18952906/Ripple-Secures-Major-Victory-Bitcoin-Soars-to-28K-This-Weeks-Crypto-Recap</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18952906/Ripple-Secures-Major-Victory-Bitcoin-Soars-to-28K-This-Weeks-Crypto-Recap"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T16:13:38.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Lewis' SBF Biography Will Confuse People About Crypto]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74bc98d2d4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/10/06/michael-lewis-sbf-biography-will-confuse-people-about-crypto/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T16:10:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The author's sympathetic picture of the alleged fraudster as a weirdo whom nobody understood contrasts with his portrayal of crypto as a no-good industry ripe for adult supervision, says Amanda Cassatt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amanda Cassatt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Far From the SBF Trial, a Very Different Web3 Narrative Is Unfolding]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18952903/Far-From-the-SBF-Trial-a-Very-Different-Web3-Narrative-Is-Unfolding</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18952903/Far-From-the-SBF-Trial-a-Very-Different-Web3-Narrative-Is-Unfolding"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T16:08:28.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Canada Strengthens Crypto Regulation with New Guidelines]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18952875/Canada-Strengthens-Crypto-Regulation-with-New-Guidelines</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18952875/Canada-Strengthens-Crypto-Regulation-with-New-Guidelines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T16:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New regulations focus on increased transparency and investor protection in the Canadian crypto industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Sees Spot Market Share Fall To 34%, What’s Going On?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18952871/Binance-Sees-Spot-Market-Share-Fall-To-34-Whats-Going-On</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18952871/Binance-Sees-Spot-Market-Share-Fall-To-34-Whats-Going-On"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T16:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance, the world’s leading cryptocurrency exchange’s spot market share has fallen for the seventh consecutive month and the crypto firm has reportedly lost more of its spot market share in the previous month. Binance Sees Spot Market Share Decline Reports have shown that the trading platform...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biggest Movers: AVAX 7% Higher, TON Maintains Bullish Momentum on Friday]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74bc9a4d9a</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/biggest-movers-avax-7-higher-ton-maintains-bullish-momentum-on-friday/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T16:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche rose to a six-week high on Friday, after the token climbed above a key resistance level. The move saw price rise by as much as 7%, despite the global crypto market cap mostly in the red in today’s session. Toncoin remained higher, following recent gains. 
 
Avalanche (AVAX)
 
Avalanche (AVAX) was a big mover on Friday, as the cryptocurrency rose by as much as 7% during the day.
 
Following a low of $9.85 on Thursday, AVAX/USD rose to a peak of $10.80 earlier in today’s session.
 
The move pushed avalanche to its highest level since August 29, past a key price ceiling of $10.00 in the process.
 
 
Looking at the chart, the relative strength index (RSI) also escaped a resistance level of its own at 65.00.
 
At the time of writing, price strength now resides at 68.54, which is its highest point since mid-April this year.
 
The next target for current buyers will likely be $11.00, however with the price now overbought, a reversal could also be on the cards.
 
 
Toncoin (TON)
 
Toncoin (TON) was in the green for a second straight session, moving closer to a key resistance level in the process.
 
TON/USD jumped nearly 3% higher on Friday, peaking at the $2.15 level at the time of writing.
 
Overall, this is the strongest point TON has hit since the end of September, when price last collided with a ceiling of $2.25.
 
 
From the chart, it appears that this occurred as the RSI continued to close in on a ceiling at the 57.00 mark.
 
With price strength now at a reading of 54.22, the chances are high that a move to 57.00 will result in toncoin trading at $2.25.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
Do you expect toncoin bulls to push price above $2.25 this weekend? Let us know your thoughts in the comments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BEST way to stake and earn ETH on Lido]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18952902/BEST-way-to-stake-and-earn-ETH-on-Lido</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18952902/BEST-way-to-stake-and-earn-ETH-on-Lido"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T16:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gary Gensler: Bitcoin's Friend Turned Foe? | Backstage w/David Zell!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18951426/Gary-Gensler-Bitcoins-Friend-Turned-Foe-Backstage-wDavid-Zell</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18951426/Gary-Gensler-Bitcoins-Friend-Turned-Foe-Backstage-wDavid-Zell"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T16:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week we are mining deep on Gary Gensler's history and his current trajectory and what it means for Bitcoin. We go backstage with David Zell, Co-Founder at Bitcoin Policy Institute. Plus we cover the news of the week, including SBF's trial, a new interview with RFK Jr., US debt hitting a new...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Latest from Web3 gaming: Gaming Demo Day with Cointelegraph Accelerator, Animoca Brands, BGA, Metaera, Cipholio and Sandbox]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18952873/Latest-from-Web3-gaming-Gaming-Demo-Day-with-Cointelegraph-Accelerator-Animoca-Brands-BGA-Metaera-Cipholio-and-Sandbox</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18952873/Latest-from-Web3-gaming-Gaming-Demo-Day-with-Cointelegraph-Accelerator-Animoca-Brands-BGA-Metaera-Cipholio-and-Sandbox"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 8 DeFi Categories by TVL: Liquid Staking Takes the Lead]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18952858/Top-8-DeFi-Categories-by-TVL-Liquid-Staking-Takes-the-Lead</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18952858/Top-8-DeFi-Categories-by-TVL-Liquid-Staking-Takes-the-Lead"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T15:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s Next For Bitcoin Bull Robert Kiyosaki? Hint: It’s Not Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74bc9af4cb</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/whats-next-for-bitcoin-bull-robert-kiyosaki/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T15:56:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vocal Bitcoin bull Robert Kiyosaki has turned his attention to another asset with high-profit potential: Apple stocks. While Kiyosaki typically extols the virtues of Bitcoin, gold, and silver in his tweets, his recent tweet has Apple investors buzzing with curiosity.
 
Kiyosaki pointed out a significant development in the tech giant’s camp – Apple CEO Tim Cook’s decision to sell his own shares of Apple stock. This move coincided with a downgrade in the company’s rating by Keybank, raising eyebrows in the financial world. 
 
 
Although Kiyosaki doesn’t currently hold any Apple shares, he suggested that the recent drop in Apple’s stock price, which has dipped below the $150 mark, might be an opportune time to consider an investment. 
 
“I do not own any Apple,” he revealed on X. “Maybe it’s …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bored Ape Yacht Club NFT Creator Yuga Labs Confirms Layoffs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200455</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200455/bored-ape-yacht-club-nft-creator-yuga-labs-confirms-layoffs"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T15:53:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yuga Labs reveals a restructuring effort that has impacted U.S. employees as the $4 billion Bored Ape startup rethinks its priorities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried Ordered ‘Special Privileges’ for Alameda, FTX Co-Founder Gary Wang Testifies]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74bc9bf931</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/10/06/sam-bankman-fried-ordered-special-privileges-for-alameda-ftx-co-founder-gary-wang-testifies/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T15:49:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Sam told me to make sure Alameda’s accounts would never get liquidated on FTX,” Wang said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Nelson, Helene Braun, Elizabeth Napolitano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Komainu Enters UK Crypto Custody Space with FCA Registration]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74bc85d964</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/komainu-enters-uk-crypto-custody-space-with-fca-registration/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T15:37:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The UK Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) has granted Komainu  
the approval to operate as a custodian wallet provider, granting it access to  
the UK's crypto-custody market. This approval was obtained by the Nomura-backed crypto platform under the Money  
Laundering, Terrorist Financing, and Transfer of Funds Regulations 2017.
With the FCA's approval, Komainu can now provide  
crypto-custody services in the UK. This includes the provision of collateral  
management services through its Komainu Connect, a collateral management platform, for safe and  
compliant storage and handling of digital assets in the region, the company said.
Eying UK's Growing Crypto Market
Nicolas Bertrand, CEO of Komainu, stated: "This is a  
key regulatory milestone as the UK remains one of the most important hub…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does Bitcoin Adoption Hinge on its Price?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74bc8105b3</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/does-bitcoin-adoption-hinge-on-its-price/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T15:17:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, the  
world's first and most well-known cryptocurrency, has received a lot of  
attention due to its price volatility. While its price has fluctuated  
dramatically, many people worry whether Bitcoin's adoption and acceptance in  
mainstream banking and everyday transactions are purely dependent on its price  
performance. 
The Price  
Volatility of Bitcoin
Bitcoin's path  
has been characterized by dramatic price fluctuations. Bitcoin's price has been  
a rollercoaster ride since its birth in 2009, when it was almost worthless, to  
its all-time high of nearly $65,000 in April 2021. This instability has drawn  
both ardent supporters and harsh detractors.
The Price as  
an Attention Driver
Bitcoin price  
increases frequently attract the attention of the media, investors, and the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Ferreira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Trial of Sam Bankman-Fried: Live Blog, Latest News and Insights]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199892</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199892/trial-sam-bankman-fried-live-blog-latest-news-insights"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T15:03:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried faces seven criminal charges related to the dramatic collapse of his crypto empire. Here's the latest on his trial.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Halving: What The Past Reveals With Only 193 Days To Go]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74bc83ff91</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-halving-what-past-reveals-193-days-to-go/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T14:57:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In just 193 days, the world will witness the Bitcoin halving, an event that occurs roughly every four years (210,000 blocks) and halves the reward miners receive for new blocks. This inherent mechanism, which serves to regulate Bitcoin supply, has had a significant impact on the asset’s market price in the past, and historical patterns may indicate what happens next.
 
Unpacking The Bitcoin Halving Phases
 
Crypto analyst, Rekt Capital, provided a comprehensive breakdown today of the typical phases surrounding the Bitcoin halving events. Reflecting on historical patterns, he observed the pre-halving period as a time when Bitcoin might undergo a deeper retrace, suggesting this would likely occur over the next 140 days (highlighted in orange).
 
Drawing comparisons, he noted that “You can de…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[72% of CEOs Consider Generative AI a Top Investment Priority: KPMG]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200400</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200400/72-of-ceos-consider-generative-ai-a-top-investment-priority-kpmg"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T14:29:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A fresh report from KPMG shows that executives are more focused on buying new technology than upskilling their workers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Organya: The Next Evolution in Web3 Gaming Is Launching October 18th]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74bc884a62</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/organya-the-next-evolution-in-web3-gaming-is-launching-october-18th/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T14:27:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. RealFevr is thrilled to announce the imminent launch of “Organya: The Interplenetary Football Strategy Game ” on October 18th, 2023. Organya marks a monumental leap forward in web3 gaming, not only evolving from the beloved FEVR Battle Arena but also introducing an entirely new universe known as The Organya World.
 
In Organya, players will become the architects of their own football dream teams, featuring their favorite football legends, thanks to RealFevr’s exclusive intellectual property. These teams will engage in strategic battles where players take on the role of coaches, competing against one another to secure glory and substantial rewards.
 
This dynamic game will offer a thrilling array of modes, including Arenas for head-to-head showdowns, Survival with single-life…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OFAC’s Sanction Bucket Grows: BTC, TRX, and ETH Addresses Flagged Over Fentanyl Ties]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74bc8b3b03</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ofacs-sanction-bucket-grows-btc-trx-and-eth-addresses-flagged-over-fentanyl-ties/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T14:07:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Office of Foreign Asset Control (OFAC) under the Treasury has released an updated version of the specially designated nationals (SDN) list, featuring multiple alleged fentanyl traffickers from China along with their associated cryptocurrency addresses. These highlighted crypto addresses are connected to decentralized networks such as Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Tron.
 
OFAC Targets Chinese Fentanyl Traffickers; Sanctions 17 Crypto Addresses
 
Continually broadening its database of crypto addresses linked to potential wrongdoers, OFAC identified 17 new addresses on October 3, 2023. Associated with blockchains like Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Tron, as well as digital assets like tether (USDT), these addresses were linked to a network of fentanyl suppliers primarily located in China but also connec…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nexo Responds to FCA: Ending Crypto Card Transactions in the UK]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74bc8b8b92</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/nexo-responds-to-fca-ending-crypto-card-transactions-in-the-uk/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T14:04:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nexo is ending some of its crypto services for clients in the  
United Kingdom. This is in response to the upcoming regulatory changes imposed  
by the Financial Conduct Authority (FCA).
According to a report by Coindesk, the crypto platform will  
phase out cashback payouts for transactions on Nexo Exchange and Nexo Card and  
terminate their referral and affiliate programs, effective October 8. 
This move aligns with the FCA's stringent promotion rules  
for the cryptocurrency industry, requiring companies to be registered for  
self-approval of advertisements and to modify their systems to allow  
first-time buyers a minimum of 24 hours to reconsider their investment decisions.
Nexo Adapting to FCA Regulations
Nexo joins the ranks of companies adjusting their offerings  
to align with F…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Holding Vs. Trading: Analyst Reveals The Best Way To Make Money With XRP]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74bc7496a6</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/xrp-holding-vs-trading/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T13:58:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the years, there have been different methods when it comes to investing in cryptocurrencies such as XRP. As usual, investors have seen successes using these different methods but the argument remains about whether it is better to hold a coin or to continuously trade it. Along this line, a crypto analyst has come forward with their own research on which is the better of the two.
 
Better To Invest And Hold
 
In an X (formerly Twitter) post, an analyst outlined why it is better to buy and hold XRP rather than to try trade it for higher profits. He points out that buying and holding XRP over the last five years would yield better results than trying to use an indicator investors believe would bring more profits.
 
 
According to him, investing $100,000 back toward the end of the year 201…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tokenized U.S. Treasuries Arrive on Coinbase’s Base with Backed’s RWA Token Issuance]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74bc76af17</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/10/06/tokenized-us-treasuries-arrive-on-coinbases-base-with-backeds-rwa-token-issuance/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T13:43:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The market for tokenized U.S. Treasuries has grown sixfold this year to $666 million, according to a real-world asset data provider.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Backed Launches Tokenized Blackrock ETF on Base Network]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200389</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200389/backed-launches-tokenized-blackrock-etf-base-network"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T13:42:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tokenization protocol Backed Finance is rolling out its tokenized bond offering on the Coinbase-incubated layer-2 network Base.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Technical Analysis: ETH Ends 4-Day Losing Streak, BTC Briefly Above $28,000]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74bc77ad7c</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-ethereum-technical-analysis-eth-ends-4-day-losing-streak-btc-briefly-above-28000/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T13:36:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum snapped a four-day losing streak on Friday, as markets reacted to the latest nonfarm payrolls in the United States. Payrolls came in at 336,000, which is nearly double the 170,000 jobs many thought would be added in September. Bitcoin retreated from a brief stint above the $28,000 level.
 
Bitcoin
 
Bitcoin (BTC) had a brief stint above the $28,000 level late on Thursday, as market volatility increased ahead of today’s nonfarm payrolls report.
 
BTC/USD peaked at $28,091.86 towards the tail end of yesterday’s session, before slipping to a bottom of $27,375.60 earlier today.
 
Prices have since rebounded, with the world’s largest cryptocurrency now trading at $27,649.56 as of writing.
 
 
Bitcoin chart by TradingView
 

 
 

 
BTC retreated from yesterday’s high after the relative strength index (RSI) failed to sustain a surge above a key resistance level of 60.00.
 
The index is currently at a reading of 58.95, however there could be another attempt to move beyond 60.00 in the coming hours.
 
In the event that the next advance is successful, there is a strong possibility bitcoin will be back trading above $28,000.
 
 
Ethereum
 
Ethereum (ETH) returned to the green in today’s session, following a spell of four consecutive days trading lower.
 
After hitting a one-week low of $1,608 on Thursday, ETH/USD rose to a peak of $1,649.13 earlier in the day.
 
This came as bulls opted to reenter the market following a breakout below a support point at the $1,620 level.
 
 
Ethereum chart by TradingView
 

 
 
Earlier gains have somewhat faded, as ETH approached a ceiling near the 50.00 level on the RSI indicator.
 
Currently, price strength is tracking at 48.93, with ethereum trading at $1,634, and bulls maintaining a target of $1,700 in the short-term.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
Will ethereum move beyond $1,700 over the weekend? Leave your thoughts in the comments below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Added 336K Jobs in September, Nearly Doubling Expectations; Bitcoin Slips 1%]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74bc706d8e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/10/06/us-added-336k-jobs-in-september-nearly-doubling-expectations-bitcoin-slips-1/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T13:31:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The unemployment rate TKTK]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen  Alpher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RUNE Plummets 9% as Thorswap Freezes Operations Amid 'Potential Illicit Activity']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200388</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200388/rune-plummets-thorswap-freezes-operations-amid-potential-illicit-activity"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T10:56:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thorswap has halted activity after it was revealed that illicit funds may have been funneled through the decentralized exchange.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Adopting 'International-First Mentality', Says Policy Lead]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200378</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200378/coinbase-adopting-international-first-mentality-says-policy-lead"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T10:39:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase is looking to extend its reach beyond its home market in the U.S. amid the current regulatory climate in the country.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Toncoin Jumps After '8-Figure' Investment by MEXC Ventures]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200376</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200376/toncoin-jumps-after-8-figure-investment-mexc-ventures"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T09:31:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TON blockchain’s token continued its bullish run from last quarter after a partnership announcement with messaging giant Telegram.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feds Flag More Bitcoin, Ethereum Addresses Tied to Chinese Fentanyl Trade]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200366</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200366/feds-flag-more-bitcoin-ethereum-addresses-tied-chinese-fentanyl-trade"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T22:27:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The list of 17 addresses associated with the fentanyl trade also includes the first set of sanctioned wallets connected to Tron.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['We're Creating Our Own Thing': Art Blocks Founder Erick Calderon on the State of Generative Art]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200327</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200327/video-interview-art-blocks-founder-erick-calderon-state-generative-art"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T22:13:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Erick Calderon sits down for a video interview to discuss his company's string of recent successes at Art Blocks' annual Marfa Weekend event.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Even the Worst Version of Claude AI Is Better Than GPT 3.5, Researchers Say]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200345</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200345/even-the-worst-version-of-claude-ai-is-better-than-gpt-3-5-researchers-say"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T21:36:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic’s models are available for free—and every single one beats OpenAI’s free model according to a new global ranking.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Insider Gary Wang: Sam Bankman-Fried Allowed Alameda to Withdraw Unlimited Funds]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200344</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200344/ftx-insider-gary-wang-sam-bankman-fried-allowed-alameda-to-withdraw-unlimited-funds"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T21:19:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FTX co-founder Gary Wang testified on Thursday, saying that company insiders committed fraud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott,André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Cyberpunk 2077' Goes Hollywood as Game Sells 25 Million Copies]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200338</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200338/cyberpunk-2077-goes-hollywood-game-sells-25-million-copies"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T20:57:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hollywood production company Anonymous Content plans to craft a live-action story set in the world of Cyberpunk 2077. Here's what we know so far.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bored Ape Creator Yuga Labs Invests in Spatial Computing Startup to Power 'Otherside']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200313</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200313/bored-ape-maker-invests-spatial-computing-startup-power-otherside"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T20:01:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hadean will establish a U.S. team to help Yuga Labs build out tech for the Bored Ape Yacht Club-themed Otherside metaverse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried Trial: All the Names You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=198989</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/198989/sam-bankman-fried-trial-all-the-names-you-need-to-know"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T19:43:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These are the big players you should know before tuning into Sam Bankman-Fried's trial next week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deadmau5-Backed Nitro Nation NFT Racing Game Hits iOS and Android]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200314</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200314/deadmau5-backed-nitro-nation-nft-racing-game-ios-android"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T19:03:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mythical Games, the maker of NFL Rivals, has released a mobile racing game called Nitro Nation World Tour with optional NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are Developers Leaving Crypto? Here’s What’s Going On]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200328</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200328/are-developers-leaving-crypto-heres-whats-going-on"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T18:40:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you look at open source crypto projects, active developers are at a 3-year low. But that's not necessarily bad, says a16z.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Sluggish After Sunday Surge—But Toncoin, Aave and Maker Make Gains]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200319</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200319/bitcoin-sluggish-toncoin-aave-and-maker-make-gains"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T18:20:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin's price hasn't moved much, but a number of DeFi tokens are on the up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Art of the Times': Art Blocks Founder Erick Calderon on the State of Generative Art]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zSjfRrl5/art-of-the-times-art-blocks-founder-erick-calderon-on-the-state-of-generative-art</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zSjfRrl5/art-of-the-times-art-blocks-founder-erick-calderon-on-the-state-of-generative-art"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T18:10:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Art Blocks founder and CEO Erick Calderon sat down with Sander Lutz, lead culture reporter at Decrypt's SCENE, at Art Blocks Marfa Weekend 2023. They discuss the evolution of the company and the generative art world, along with what draws art enthusiasts to be an active part of the community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK Won’t Be ‘Copying’ MiCA: Crypto Parliamentary Group Chair]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200289</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200289/uk-wont-be-copying-mica-crypto-parliamentary-group-chair"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T15:20:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Speaking at CCDAS 2023, Dr. Lisa Cameron MP said that the UK is exploring a “bespoke approach” to crypto regulation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOJ Lays Claim to 2 Luxury Jets Allegedly Owned by Sam Bankman-Fried]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200296</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200296/doj-lays-claim-2-luxury-jets-allegedly-owned-sam-bankman-fried"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T14:28:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Island Air Capital has disputed the DOJ's move to forfeit the two jets totaling $28 million, claiming the aircrafts belonged to it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sui Foundation Announces Ecosystem Fund Worth Over $50M]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200295</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200295/sui-foundation-announces-ecosystem-fund-worth-over-50m"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T13:12:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The foundation will reclaim 117 million SUI tokens worth $51.3 million from market makers to strengthen its DeFi ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong Police, SFC Launch Task Force to Monitor Crypto Exchanges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200269</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200269/hong-kong-police-sfc-launch-task-force-monitor-exchanges"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T11:07:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong's police force and leading securities regulator are integrating their efforts to monitor illegal exchange activities after the JPEX incident.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt Learn: Digital Ownership Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/6udZCotB/decrypt-learn-digital-ownership-explained</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/6udZCotB/decrypt-learn-digital-ownership-explained"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T10:57:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most powerful aspects of blockchain technology is its ability to provide us genuine ownership of our digital assets. This is called digital ownership. In this video, we’ll deep dive into digital ownership, why it matters, and how web3 makes owning digital assets like our social networks, music libraries, personal data, and beyond possible. Author: Clarissa Watson, Senior Writer at Consensys.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friend.tech Users Robbed of $385,000 in Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200274</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200274/friend-tech-users-robbed-385000-ethereum-yesterday"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T10:32:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto sleuth ZachXBT identified yet another swatch of SIM Swap attacks on four different Friend.tech users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Just 2% of Firms Cashing In on AI Hype Will Survive, Says Bitpanda CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200268</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200268/just-2-of-firms-cashing-in-on-ai-hype-will-survive-says-bitpanda-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T10:09:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“The crypto bros are now the AI bros” Bitpanda’s CEO Eric Demuth said, comparing the latest investment wave to previous booms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alys Key</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ZK-Proofs ‘Particularly Relevant in Financial Services’: Google Cloud Web3 Lead]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200136</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200136/zk-proofs-particularly-relevant-in-financial-services-google-cloud-web3-lead"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T09:19:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Cloud’s Web3 engineering lead highlighted use cases for on-chain privacy preserving technologies like ZK-proofs at CCDAS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Canva Bolsters AI Toolkit with Video Generation by Runway]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200251</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200251/canva-ai-magic-generative-tool-runway"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T01:43:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To fight deepfakes, Canva’s new platform restricts its AI from generating images of celebrities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Warner Music’s Head of NFTs and AI Departs: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200244</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200244/warner-musics-head-of-nfts-and-ai-departs-report"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T00:27:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oana Ruxandra, Warner’s chief digital officer, is officially departing the label after spearheading its aggressive push to embrace emerging technologies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Social Protocol Stars Arena Takes on Friend.Tech While Boosting AVAX]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200242</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200242/stars-arena-social-token-friend-tech-avax"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T00:14:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Stars Arena thrives, the AVAX token rides the wave, while some users remain skeptical.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried Trial Invoked Dogecoin and Solana on Day One—But Not FTT]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200236</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200236/sam-bankman-fried-trial-ftt-bitcoin-ethereum-dogecoin-solana"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T23:57:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was the shocking slide in the value of FTX's token that marked the final days of the doomed exchange.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Pours AI Powers Into Its New Pixel Phone and Home Assistant]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200223</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200223/google-ai-assistant-bard-pixel-phone-photo-editing"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T23:17:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just announced, an AI-powered multimodal super assistant, AI-powered photo editors, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Polygon in Trouble? Another Executive Departs Amid Crypto Market Downturn]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200194</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200194/polygon-in-trouble-executive-departures"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T22:47:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The co-founder's exit extends a long list of similar departures from prominent crypto projects in 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Latin American Crypto Scene Shows No Signs of Stopping: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200221</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200221/latin-american-crypto-scene-shows-no-signs-of-stopping-report"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T22:24:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As investor motivations shift over time, regulation continues to be the region's number one hurdle.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nintendo 3DS and Wii U Going Offline in 2024—Here's Why]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200206</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200206/nintendo-3ds-wii-u-going-offline-2024-heres-why"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T22:06:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nintendo is sunsetting online services for its Nintendo 3DS and Wii U consoles, with a few exceptions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Ubisoft Execs Arrested in France Amid Sexual Harassment Investigation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200177</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200177/former-ubisoft-execs-arrested-in-france-amid-sexual-harassment-investigation"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T21:34:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two ex-Ubisoft executives accused of enabling or committing sexual harassment and assault are among those detained by French police this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China May Be Reversing Its Anti-Crypto Stance: Chainalysis]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200213</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200213/hong-kong-crypto-mainland-china-chainalysis"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T21:29:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong has seen a surge in cryptocurrency activity that rivals mainland China.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Craig Wright Is Not Satoshi Nakamoto': Drama Inspires Bitcoin Banger]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200193</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200193/craig-wright-not-satoshi-nakamoto-drama-inspires-bitcoin-banger"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T20:42:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Musician Jonathan Mann has crafted a catchy tune about the latest twists around Craig Wright, who claims to have invented Bitcoin]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chain Letters: MoMA Launches 'Postcard' NFT Art Project]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200146</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200146/chain-letters-moma-launches-postcard-nft-art-project"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T20:23:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The MoMA Postcard program is designed to onboard the museum’s community to the potential of art created on the blockchain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Martin Shkreli on E/ACC and SBF in Prison]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QONaWXKZ/martin-shkreli-on-e-acc-and-sbf-in-prison</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QONaWXKZ/martin-shkreli-on-e-acc-and-sbf-in-prison"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T22:03:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reza Jafery and Martin Shkreli sit down for a casual conversation about the growing movement that is E/ACC, what songs they could recite at gunpoint, and whether or not SBF will thrive or just survive during his time in prison.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Can AI Do in Gaming?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JKuqCMao/what-can-ai-do-in-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JKuqCMao/what-can-ai-do-in-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T17:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI Arena CEO Brandon Da Silva and COO Wei Xie discuss how artificial intelligence can shape the video game experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['There Are No Real Standards': Ready Player Me CEO Timmu Tõke on Building for an Open Gaming Ecosystem]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TH3KEAI0/there-are-no-real-standards-ready-player-me-ceo-timmu-tke-on-building-for-an-open-gaming-ecosystem</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TH3KEAI0/there-are-no-real-standards-ready-player-me-ceo-timmu-tke-on-building-for-an-open-gaming-ecosystem"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T17:29:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Timmu Tõke, co-founder and CEO of Ready Player Me, joins Decrypt contributor Ryan Gladwin to discuss the startup's approach to powering avatars that are interoperable across games and metaverse platforms—and what's needed to convince the industry to adopt standards and open up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain Is 'Only Way' Forward for Gaming, Says Shrapnel Studio Head]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/fhoy7Z8f/blockchain-is-only-way-forward-for-gaming-says-shrapnel-studio-head</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/fhoy7Z8f/blockchain-is-only-way-forward-for-gaming-says-shrapnel-studio-head"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T21:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shrapnel Studio Head Don Norbury tells Kate Irwin the reasons why the upcoming first-person shooter game will offer a wide range of NFTs. He also reveals team-based gameplay plans and shares how game maps have already changed this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Social Media Sentiment Is Key to Crypto Price Discovery]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/981TBppa/social-media-sentiment-is-key-to-crypto-price-discovery</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/981TBppa/social-media-sentiment-is-key-to-crypto-price-discovery"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T23:47:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sacha Ghebali, Director of Strategy and Business Development at The TIE, says social media sentiment remains a key factor in price movements for major cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin and Ethereum. However, he notes that sentiment has turned more negative lately amid regulatory uncertainty. Ghebali believes events like the Ripple lawsuit ruling significantly impacted sentiment and prices. André Beganski interviewed him at Messari Mainnet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[500Altcoins discusses DeFi Summer and the Dubai Crypto Scene - This Time Will Be Different - Episode 2]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cI7p8AK3/500altcoins-discusses-defi-summer-and-the-dubai-crypto-scene-this-time-will-be-different-episode-2</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cI7p8AK3/500altcoins-discusses-defi-summer-and-the-dubai-crypto-scene-this-time-will-be-different-episode-2"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our host Reza Jafery is joined by Gareth Fenney aka 500Altcoins. They discuss the glory days of DeFi Summer and whether or not its a smart move for builders in the crypto space to relocate to Dubai.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralize Derivatives Trading with Custom Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/lfmwAjB9/decentralize-derivatives-trading-with-custom-blockchain</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/lfmwAjB9/decentralize-derivatives-trading-with-custom-blockchain"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T10:37:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Gogel of dYdX discusses how the decentralized exchange is building a custom blockchain to fully decentralize derivatives trading. He explained how the new dYdX chain will allow validators to run order books in memory, enabling decentralized order matching at scale. This shift aims to increase security and transparency for traders while maintaining the performance of centralized exchanges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Accounting Challenges and Opportunities]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/0Sezz6pZ/crypto-accounting-challenges-and-opportunities</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/0Sezz6pZ/crypto-accounting-challenges-and-opportunities"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As crypto matures, accounting and tax regulations are evolving. Amy Kalnoki of Bitwave explains how her company helps crypto companies properly account for digital assets. She notes the importance of flexibility as new crypto assets emerge and regulations change. Stacy Elliott interviewed her at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Most Crypto Users Don't Trust Themselves to Keep Their Seed Phrase Safe: Ledger CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/0kYf2Qed/most-crypto-users-dont-trust-themselves-to-keep-their-seed-phrase-safe-ledger-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/0kYf2Qed/most-crypto-users-dont-trust-themselves-to-keep-their-seed-phrase-safe-ledger-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Stacy Elliott sat down with Ledger CEO Pascal Gauthier to discuss crypto custody post-FTX, and the hardware wallet manufacturer's controversial Ledger Recover service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[India's 1% Crypto Tax Has Been a Nightmare for High-Frequency Traders, Says Shardeum CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/fxygwLvH/indias-1-crypto-tax-has-been-a-nightmare-for-high-frequency-traders-says-shardeum-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/fxygwLvH/indias-1-crypto-tax-has-been-a-nightmare-for-high-frequency-traders-says-shardeum-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As India figures out its regulatory approach to the crypto industry, one thing is clear to Shardeum co-founder Nischal Shetty: “If you're a high-frequency trader, you can't afford to lose a percentage every time you sell,” he told Decrypt's Andre Beganski at Messari Mainnet in New York. “That's something that's caused a lot of issues.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Newly Partnered with Visa, Solana Focuses on Reliability]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/MZoxvulr/newly-partnered-with-visa-solana-focuses-on-reliability</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/MZoxvulr/newly-partnered-with-visa-solana-focuses-on-reliability"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana has improved network reliability through upgrades like Quick and local fee markets. It recently partnered with Visa to allow settling transactions in USDC on Solana. This could enable merchants to receive instant payments and save on credit card processing fees. Stacy Elliott spoke with Austin Federa, Head of Strategy for the Solana Foundation, at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Need to Start Thinking About How we Make Crypto Easy to Use: Robinhood Crypto General Manager]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PLZ0FpdC/we-need-to-start-thinking-about-how-we-make-crypto-easy-to-use-robinhood-crypto-general-manager</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PLZ0FpdC/we-need-to-start-thinking-about-how-we-make-crypto-easy-to-use-robinhood-crypto-general-manager"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Stacy Elliott sat down with Robinhood Crypto general manager Johann Kerbrat at Messari Mainnet 2023, to talk about the trading platform's crypto wallet, onboarding new users through simplicity, and keeping platform fees sustainable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Regulation Threatens U.S. Dominance of Financial Markets, Says CoinRoutes CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/CrpvzFjL/regulation-threatens-us-dominance-of-financial-markets-says-coinroutes-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/CrpvzFjL/regulation-threatens-us-dominance-of-financial-markets-says-coinroutes-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dave Weisberger, Co-Founder and CEO of CoinRoutes, argued that excessive regulation in the U.S. threatens to undermine the country's long-standing dominance in global financial markets. He warned that other countries are embracing blockchain and crypto to build more efficient digital markets, which could cause the US to lose its competitive edge and trillions in GDP. Weisberger said CoinRoutes is now focusing more on expanding internationally due to restrictive policies in the U.S. He was interviewed by André Beganski of Decrypt at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin's Narrative Is Shifting Towards Layer-2 Solutions]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/axArPRp3/bitcoins-narrative-is-shifting-towards-layer-2-solutions</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/axArPRp3/bitcoins-narrative-is-shifting-towards-layer-2-solutions"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rich Rines, original Core DAO contributor and former Coinbase engineer, discusses how the narrative around Bitcoin is shifting in 2023. While Bitcoin remains digital gold, new layer 2 solutions are emerging to unlock more utility and value from the huge amounts of capital stored in Bitcoin. He says these innovations can benefit Bitcoin holders while keeping Bitcoin maximalists happy by building outside the base layer. André Beganski interviewed him at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Explosive Growth Ahead for Enterprise Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/xXOrNbX9/explosive-growth-ahead-for-enterprise-blockchain</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/xXOrNbX9/explosive-growth-ahead-for-enterprise-blockchain"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paul Brody drives Ernst & Young (EY) initiatives and investments in blockchain technology across consulting, audit, and tax business lines. He says enterprise blockchain adoption is nearing an inflection point. Brody believes blockchains will one day handle 40 billion transactions daily across industries like automotive and pharma. Stacy Elliott interviewed him at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Developer-Friendly zkRollup to Scale Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/OvAFgxTd/building-a-developer-friendly-zkrollup-to-scale-ethereum</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/OvAFgxTd/building-a-developer-friendly-zkrollup-to-scale-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daniel Helm, head of Developer Relations at Scroll, discussess how they are building a zkRollup to scale Ethereum transactions and lower fees. He explained their focus on creating a seamless developer experience by maintaining Ethereum's ethos and tooling. Scroll aims to launch their mainnet soon, providing more scalable blockspace for Ethereum developers. Stacy Elliott of Decrypt interviewed him at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Base as a 'Bridge, Not an Island']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/oZPr7bzY/base-as-a-bridge-not-an-island</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/oZPr7bzY/base-as-a-bridge-not-an-island"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase's Jesse Pollak, creator of layer-2 blockchain Base, says the launch of the network has exceeded expectations, even if plans changed along the way. He believes Arbitrum One will help bring billions onto blockchain by enabling seamless user experiences. Stacy Elliott interviewed him at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>