<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-12-19T01:07:04.631Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-12-19T01:07:04.631Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analyst Predicts Rallies for Avalanche (AVAX) and Fetch.ai (FET), Outlines Area of Interest for Gaming Altcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118220/Analyst-Predicts-Rallies-for-Avalanche-AVAX-and-Fetchai-FET-Outlines-Area-of-Interest-for-Gaming-Altcoin</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118220/Analyst-Predicts-Rallies-for-Avalanche-AVAX-and-Fetchai-FET-Outlines-Area-of-Interest-for-Gaming-Altcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T01:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A widely followed crypto trader is predicting more rallies for smart contract protocol Avalanche (AVAX) and artificial intelligence (AI)-focused altcoin Fetch.ai (FET). Pseudonymous analyst Altcoin Sherpa tells his 201,600 followers on the social media platform X that Avalanche is likely not yet...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Small ESG-Focused Crypto Asset Manager Is Another Late Entrant to Bitcoin ETF Race]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748d210596</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/12/19/small-esg-focused-crypto-asset-manager-is-another-late-entrant-to-bitcoin-etf-race/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T00:41:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A small ESG-focused crypto asset manager, 7RCC, is the latest applicant to join the race for a spot-bitcoin exchange traded fund (ETF), a filing with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) shows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Inscriptions cross $1 mln: Will SOL reap the benefits?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118200/Solana-Inscriptions-cross-1-mln-Will-SOL-reap-the-benefits</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118200/Solana-Inscriptions-cross-1-mln-Will-SOL-reap-the-benefits"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T00:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More inscriptions were created on Solana in the last three days than all of the ones created prior to that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Spot Bitcoin ETF Effect: Analysts Predict ‘Bloodbath’ Impact On Crypto Trading Platforms]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748d221804</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/spot-bitcoin-etf-effect-analysts-predict-bloodbath/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T00:30:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Industry analysts Nate Geraci, President of The ETF Store, and Eric Balchunas, a prominent Bloomberg Exchange Traded Fund (ETF) analyst, have recently spotlighted a potential game-changer in the crypto world: introducing a spot Bitcoin ETF in the United States.
 
According to their analysis, this development could bring benefits and notable challenges, particularly for established crypto exchanges such as Coinbase.
 
The duo’s insights, shared on X, paint a picture of a changing market dynamics. Geraci’s post highlighted the potential impact of a spot Bitcoin ETF, which he describes as a “bloodbath” for crypto exchanges.
 
 
Their argument hinges on transaction fees – a critical revenue stream for platforms like Coinbase.
 
 
Gonna be a bloodbath for crypto exchanges…
 
— Nate Geraci (@Nat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Spot Bitcoin ETF Effect: Analysts Predict ‘Bloodbath’ Impact On Crypto Trading Platforms]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118201/The-Spot-Bitcoin-ETF-Effect-Analysts-Predict-Bloodbath-Impact-On-Crypto-Trading-Platforms</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118201/The-Spot-Bitcoin-ETF-Effect-Analysts-Predict-Bloodbath-Impact-On-Crypto-Trading-Platforms"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T00:30:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Industry analysts Nate Geraci, President of The ETF Store, and Eric Balchunas, a prominent Bloomberg Exchange Traded Fund (ETF) analyst, have recently spotlighted a potential game-changer in the crypto world: introducing a spot Bitcoin ETF in the United States. According to their analysis, this...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Tax Planning: Merging Tax-Loss Harvesting With Charitable Giving]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748d22f43b</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/crypto-tax-planning-merging-tax-loss-harvesting-with-charitable-giving/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T00:21:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the year winds down, cryptocurrency investors can combine tax-loss harvesting with cryptocurrency donations to charities, a move that optimizes tax benefits while supporting worthy causes.
 
Embrace Year-End Tax Strategy With Charitable Giving Twist
 
As the end of the year rapidly approaches, crypto investors are not only focusing on tax-loss harvesting but also exploring the benefits of charitable contributions in cryptocurrency. This strategic approach allows investors to potentially reduce their tax liabilities while supporting charitable causes.
 
The concept of tax-loss harvesting in the crypto realm involves selling digital assets at a loss to offset capital gains taxes. This method can be particularly advantageous given the volatility and potential for significant price fluctuat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Sencil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Small ESG-Focused Crypto Asset Manager Is Another Late Entrant to Bitcoin ETF Race]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118181/Small-ESG-Focused-Crypto-Asset-Manager-Is-Another-Late-Entrant-to-Bitcoin-ETF-Race</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118181/Small-ESG-Focused-Crypto-Asset-Manager-Is-Another-Late-Entrant-to-Bitcoin-ETF-Race"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T00:15:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A small ESG-focused crypto asset manager, 7RCC, is the latest applicant to join the race for a spot-bitcoin exchange traded fund (ETF), a filing with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) shows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitter Faces EU Inquiry Over Failing to Moderate Illegal Content and Disinformation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210217</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210217/twitter-faces-eu-inquiry-over-failing-to-moderate-illegal-content-and-disinformation"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T00:07:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first-of-its-kind investigation will review whether Twitter did what it said it would do about Israel-Palestine content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gianluigi Buffon Invests in OQtima, Signaling a Shift in Sports-Finance Collaborations]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748d2cda63</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/gianluigi-buffon-invests-in-oqtima-signaling-a-shift-in-sports-finance-collaborations/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T00:02:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. Renowned Italian football goalkeeper Gianluigi Buffon has recently confirmed his strategic investment in OQtima, an innovative online trading company, marking a significant departure from traditional sponsorship deals.
 
Buffon’s active involvement in OQtima signifies a profound collaboration between the realms of professional sports and financial trading platforms. This move establishes a new era where sports legends become not only brand ambassadors but key stakeholders and strategic partners in the financial sector, thereby revolutionizing the landscape of partnerships.
 
A New Age For Partnerships
 
In a groundbreaking development at the crossroads of finance and sports, partnerships between online trading platforms, cryptocurrency exchanges, and sports icons are undergo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Court Greenlights Landmark Settlement Against Binance and Changpeng ‘CZ’ Zhao]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118167/US-Court-Greenlights-Landmark-Settlement-Against-Binance-and-Changpeng-CZ-Zhao</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118167/US-Court-Greenlights-Landmark-Settlement-Against-Binance-and-Changpeng-CZ-Zhao"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T23:45:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) has secured a significant legal victory as the U.S. District Court approves the settlement against Binance and its CEO. The court officially entered a consent order. This imposed a series of penalties and injunctions against the crypto exchange and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ubisoft's 'Champions Tactics' Ethereum NFTs Generate Millions After Free Mint]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210213</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210213/ubisoft-champions-tactics-ethereum-nfts-generate-millions-after-free-mint"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T23:42:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following a drop that minted out in under 20 minutes, Ubisoft’s Warlords NFTs for Champions Tactics are reselling for $600 or more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ubisoft's 'Champions Tactics' Ethereum NFTs Generate Millions After Free Mint]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118141/Ubisofts-Champions-Tactics-Ethereum-NFTs-Generate-Millions-After-Free-Mint</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118141/Ubisofts-Champions-Tactics-Ethereum-NFTs-Generate-Millions-After-Free-Mint"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T23:42:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following a drop that minted out in under 20 minutes, Ubisoft’s Warlords NFTs for Champions Tactics are reselling for $600 or more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock Goes Cash]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118135/BlackRock-Goes-Cash</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118135/BlackRock-Goes-Cash"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T23:39:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock has amended the bitcoin spot ETF to state creation and redemption will be in cash, with in-kind to follow subject to approval.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rule changes at Helium Mobile address suspicious token farming activities]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118122/Rule-changes-at-Helium-Mobile-address-suspicious-token-farming-activities</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118122/Rule-changes-at-Helium-Mobile-address-suspicious-token-farming-activities"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T23:25:04.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Revolut Scales Back Crypto Services Amid Regulatory Changes: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118168/Revolut-Scales-Back-Crypto-Services-Amid-Regulatory-Changes-Report</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118168/Revolut-Scales-Back-Crypto-Services-Amid-Regulatory-Changes-Report"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T23:18:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Revolut is reportedly set to temporarily suspend some of its cryptocurrency services for business customers in the UK. This decision comes in response to the Financial Conduct Authority’s (FCA) announcement of new rules for crypto assets, slated for implementation in the new year. Revolut Halts...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock’s proposed spot bitcoin ETF gets a ticker in latest filing with SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118112/BlackRocks-proposed-spot-bitcoin-ETF-gets-a-ticker-in-latest-filing-with-SEC</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118112/BlackRocks-proposed-spot-bitcoin-ETF-gets-a-ticker-in-latest-filing-with-SEC"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T23:16:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The updated filing from BlackRock about its proposed spot bitcoin ETF includes new language about the fund's creation and redemption model.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin to restart operations in Kenya by early 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118109/Worldcoin-to-restart-operations-in-Kenya-by-early-2024</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118109/Worldcoin-to-restart-operations-in-Kenya-by-early-2024"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T23:12:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin, the cryptocurrency project known for using iris biometric technology, is reportedly on the verge of resuming its operations in Kenya. This development follows a period of regulatory scrutiny that led to suspending its activities in the country. According to recent reports, Worldcoin...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Lead Dev Reflects On New Partnership To Drive Global Adoption]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748d2ae642</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-dev-global-adoption/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T23:02:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Shiba Inu team seems to be hard at work over the last few months and the latest development has been a special announcement teased by lead developer Shytoshi Kusama. Kusama first mentioned the announcement last week where he said that it would be ‘game-changing’ and Shiba Inu marketing lead Lucie said it would break the internet. As the community tentatively anticipates this announcement, Kusama has shared more insight into the partnership and why they’re doing it.
 
Promoting The Worldwide Adoption Of Shiba Inu
 
In a December 16 thread post on X (formerly Twitter), developer Kusama said that he was looking forward to the announcement which is supposed to happen this week. However, the post didn’t only focus on the announcement as Kusama also alluded to the SHIB burns that the team is…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Best Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Federal judge approves settlement between CFTC and Binance]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118103/Federal-judge-approves-settlement-between-CFTC-and-Binance</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118103/Federal-judge-approves-settlement-between-CFTC-and-Binance"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T23:02:13.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Under-the-Radar Altcoin Surges 60% in 24 Hours Amid Network Expansion and Explosive Demand for Solana Smartphone]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118102/Under-the-Radar-Altcoin-Surges-60-in-24-Hours-Amid-Network-Expansion-and-Explosive-Demand-for-Solana-Smartphone</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118102/Under-the-Radar-Altcoin-Surges-60-in-24-Hours-Amid-Network-Expansion-and-Explosive-Demand-for-Solana-Smartphone"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T23:01:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A decentralized wireless network altcoin on the Solana (SOL) blockchain is soaring amid two big consumer-driven events. The decentralized finance (DeFi) telecommunications project Helium Mobile (MOBILE) is up 60% in the past 24 hours, going from Sunday’s low of $0.0042 to $0.0067 at time of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Machine Learning Algorithm Predicts When Cardano Price Will Hit New $6.5 ATH]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118094/Machine-Learning-Algorithm-Predicts-When-Cardano-Price-Will-Hit-New-65-ATH</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118094/Machine-Learning-Algorithm-Predicts-When-Cardano-Price-Will-Hit-New-65-ATH"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T23:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mysterious 2015 Whale Transfers 2,101 BTC, Stirring $88M in Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748d2b1ed7</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/mysterious-2015-whale-transfers-2101-btc-stirring-88m-in-bitcoin/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T23:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Dec. 18, 2023, a colossal cache of dormant bitcoins stirred after remaining inactive for eight years and ten months. The whale transferred 2,101 bitcoins, originating from 2015, now valued at $88.55 million, utilizing the prevailing BTC exchange rates.
 
$88M Worth of Bitcoin Moved by Long-Dormant Whale
 
On Feb. 17, 2015, a substantial accumulation of dormant bitcoins was first recorded. This stash came to life after eight years and ten months on a Monday, with the whale from past years moving 2,101 BTC valued at $88.55 million at block height 821,802. The transfer originated from the BTC address “1DJs7,” a movement that was detected by btcparser.com.
 
Back in 2015, when 1DJs7 initially received the 2,101 BTC from “1CJee,” the total value stood at $510,543, with each bitcoin priced at…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK Builds Digital Securities Sandbox to Test New Technolgies]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210202</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210202/uk-builds-digital-securities-sandbox-to-test-new-technolgies"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T22:46:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The setup aims to house controlled testing of blockchain and other emerging infrastructure technologies before wider deployment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ARK Amends the Bitcoin Spot ETF]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118058/ARK-Amends-the-Bitcoin-Spot-ETF</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118058/ARK-Amends-the-Bitcoin-Spot-ETF"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T22:39:26.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Ethereum developer claims 70% of ETH was pre-mined]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118052/Ex-Ethereum-developer-claims-70-of-ETH-was-pre-mined</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118052/Ex-Ethereum-developer-claims-70-of-ETH-was-pre-mined"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T22:37:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lane Rettig, a former core developer for Ethereum, has recently raised serious allegations about the distribution of Ethereum’s native cryptocurrency, ETH. In a statement that garnered significant attention from the crypto community, Rettig claimed that approximately 70% of all ETH was...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will AVAX Gains Close Above 100%? Weekly Burned Tokens At Highest, New Partnerships On Record]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118083/Will-AVAX-Gains-Close-Above-100-Weekly-Burned-Tokens-At-Highest-New-Partnerships-On-Record</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118083/Will-AVAX-Gains-Close-Above-100-Weekly-Burned-Tokens-At-Highest-New-Partnerships-On-Record"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T22:35:39.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Ethereum’s prediction holds as price drops]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118046/What-Ethereums-prediction-holds-as-price-drops</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118046/What-Ethereums-prediction-holds-as-price-drops"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T22:30:58.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Game 'Aurory' Suffers $830K Exploit, Disables Arbitrum Bridge]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210153</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210153/solana-game-aurory-suffers-830k-exploit-disables-arbitrum-bridge"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T22:30:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An exploit on Aurory's marketplace led to one user siphoning about 600,000 AURY tokens. The game's bridge is down while devs work on a fix.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Game 'Aurory' Suffers $830K Exploit, Disables Arbitrum Bridge]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118050/Solana-Game-Aurory-Suffers-830K-Exploit-Disables-Arbitrum-Bridge</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118050/Solana-Game-Aurory-Suffers-830K-Exploit-Disables-Arbitrum-Bridge"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T22:30:56.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[With all eyes on bitcoin ETF decision, SEC kicks ether can down the road]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118026/With-all-eyes-on-bitcoin-ETF-decision-SEC-kicks-ether-can-down-the-road</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19118026/With-all-eyes-on-bitcoin-ETF-decision-SEC-kicks-ether-can-down-the-road"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T22:24:09.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Failure To Launch Worries Investors, But Analyst Says It Could Change Soon]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748d108cdd</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-failure-to-launch/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T22:09:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite being the most popular meme coin in the crypto market right now, the price of Dogecoin has not performed as well as investors expected. Instead of following the overall trend of all coins in the space to new yearly highs, the price continued to stall. So far, Dogecoin has proved to be undergoing a failure to launch, but this could be changing soon.
 
Dogecoin Price Still Stalling
 
So far in 2023, the price of cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum have rallied to new yearly highs, but Dogecoin has struggled to perform to the same extent. Even though the price has risen nicely from its 2023 lows of $0.058, it has continued to see only small gains when other assets have been seeing double-digit gains.
 
 
At the beginning of December, multiple developments also contributed to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cipher Mining Enhances Bitcoin ASIC Fleet With 7.1 EH/s Bitmain Deal]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748d10951a</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/cipher-mining-enhances-bitcoin-asic-fleet-with-7-1-eh-s-bitmain-deal/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T22:09:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Monday, Cipher Mining revealed its acquisition of 7.1 exahash per second (EH/s) in new mining equipment from Bitmain. The company invested in Bitmain’s T21 series miners, totaling a purchase price of $99.5 million.
 
Cipher Mining’s Strategic $99.5 Million Investment in Next-Gen Bitmain Miners
 
In recent months, following the introduction of several advanced bitcoin mining units, mining operations have been actively acquiring state-of-the-art mining rigs. On Dec. 18, the bitcoin mining company Cipher Mining (Nasdaq: CIFR) announced its purchase of 7.1 EH/s in next-generation mining machinery from Bitmain.
 
Cipher Mining spent $14 per terahash, amounting to a total investment of $99.5 million in the latest hardware. The Bitmain Antminer T21, an air-cooled device, offers 190 terahash pe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitwise Is First to Bitcoin ETF Ad Race With ‘Most Interesting Man in the World’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210186</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210186/bitwise-firstbitcoin-etf-ad-with-most-interesting-man-in-the-world"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T22:05:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The message: "Bitwise Is Interesting.” It stars Jonathan Goldsmith, well-known for portraying “The Most Interesting Man in the World” in beer ads.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Fees Continue to Surge Thanks to Ordinal Mania]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210168</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210168/bitcoin-fees-continue-to-surge-thanks-to-ordinal-mania"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T22:01:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s again very expensive to make a transaction on Bitcoin’s blockchain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Helium Mobile Cracks Down on MOBILE Token Farmers]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748d18e85d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/12/18/helium-mobile-cracks-down-on-mobile-token-farmers/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T20:53:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New users are pouring into Helium's low-cost phone plan. Some are more interested in the MOBILE token rewards than the cell service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale Clarifies Investor Tax Implications of a Cash-Created Spot Bitcoin ETF]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748d1aa0bb</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/grayscale-clarifies-investor-tax-implications-of-a-cash-created-spot-bitcoin-etf/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T20:38:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale, one of the biggest cryptocurrency asset management firms, has addressed the issue of taxation regarding the adoption of a cash creation model in an upcoming spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF). The firm clarified that “no spot Bitcoin ETF that qualifies as a grantor trust would be at a disadvantage in relation to any other spot Bitcoin ETF” regarding cash redemptions. 
Grayscale Clarifies Cash-Created Spot Bitcoin ETF Tax Controversies
Grayscale, one of the world’s largest cryptocurrency asset management firms, clarified the potential tax implications of applying a cash redemption model for an upcoming spot bitcoin ETF product.
In a recent article, the firm explained how the cash redemption process would work in a spot bitcoin ETF, with only qualified investors operating to …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pro-XRP Lawyer Sounds Alarm As Warren’s Crypto Bill Gains 20% Senate Support]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748d1aa7d6</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/pro-xrp-alarm-warrens-crypto-bill-20-senate-support/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T20:38:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a move that has ignited strong reactions within the crypto community, Senator Elizabeth Warren recently introduced the Digital Asset Anti-Money Laundering Act. This bill aims to impose stricter regulations on the crypto industry, triggering concerns about the potential consequences for innovation and individual freedoms. 
 
Notably, the bill has steadily gained support in the Senate since its inception and subsequent reintroduction in July 2023.
 
Far-Reaching Consequences For Crypto
 
According to pro-XRP lawyer John Deaton, the bill has garnered increased backing in the Senate, with 20% of senators already expressing their support for what he calls Warren’s “de facto ban” on cryptocurrencies, including Bitcoin (BTC), in the United States. 
 
Deaton further asserts that Warren is lever…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Next BONK? Solana Meme Coin Dogwifhat Pumps 2,000X in a Month]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210151</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210151/next-bonk-solana-meme-coin-dogwifhat-pumps-2000x-month"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T20:04:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s a dog. With a hat. And the Solana token based on the dogwifhat meme is the latest to surge in value after BONK's boom.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF On The Verge Of Approval? Bitwise’s Latest Ad Suggests Impending Deadline Success]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748d006c03</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitwises-ad-indicates-potential-for-bitcoin-etf/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T19:48:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In mounting anticipation surrounding the long-awaited approval of spot Bitcoin ETF applications by the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), Bitwise Invest has boldly released a commercial starring Jonathan Goldsmith.
 
 Bitwise Invest’s Bitcoin ETF Ad
 
Bitwise Invest, one of several asset management firms awaiting SEC approval, seeks to capitalize on the growing interest in cryptocurrencies by launching a spot Bitcoin ETF. 
 
The commercial, featuring Goldsmith, aims to capture attention and intrigue, highlighting the actor’s famous catchphrase: “You know what is interesting these days? Bitcoin.”
 
While the commercial highlights the imminent launch of a spot BTC ETF, it also emphasizes Bitwise Invest’s position in the crypto ETF space. Unlike larger asset management players, Bitw…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zcash Developer Electric Coin CEO Zooko Wilcox Steps Down, Swihart Named to Role]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748d00e2d1</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/12/18/zcash-developer-electric-coin-ceo-zooko-wilcox-steps-downs-swihart-named-to-role/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T19:44:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The overseeing board of Zcash, known for its privacy-oriented "shielded" addresses or "z-addresses," credited Wilcox with delivery of "the first real-world application of zero-knowledge proofs."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bradley Keoun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A New Kind of Insider Trading? Hegic's DeFi Bets Might Attract SEC's Attention, Experts Say]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748d02f12e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/12/18/a-new-kind-of-insider-trading-hegics-defi-bets-might-attract-secs-attention-experts-say/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T19:27:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hegic recently scored a windfall buy buying WHITE tokens ahead of big news. The trade might cross the line, according to experts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Funds See 'Profit-Taking' Dip, But Investors Still Like Solana]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210155</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210155/bitcoin-funds-see-profit-taking-dip-but-investors-still-like-solana"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T19:16:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana and other altcoin funds saw $21 million deposited last week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano Founder Gives Reasons Why ADA Can Never Work With XRP]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748d0d53ba</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/cardano-founder-ada-xrp/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T19:08:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano founder, Charles Hoskinson, has once again reasserted his opinion on a potential partnership between XRP and Cardano’s ADA. His recent comment after a member of the XRP community dug up past remarks that the Cardano founder had made on this same subject.  
 
Why ADA Will Not Work With XRP
 
In a post on his X (formerly Twitter) platform, Hoskinson explained that the reason ADA will not partner with XRP is because of the “two years of daily harassment” by the XRP community. He also highlighted the “lack of technical overlap” between both tokens and the “different product market fit” as other reasons why a partnership is unlikely. 
 
 
The Cardano founder mentioned that Ripple (possibly alluding to XRP) was “built for a different purpose.” This is unlike Cardano, Tezoz, Ethereum, Pol…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Revolut Halts Crypto Purchases for UK Business Customers: Report]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748d0fe24d</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/revolut-halts-crypto-purchases-for-uk-business-customers-report/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T18:48:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Revolut will temporarily halt certain cryptocurrency  
services for its business customers in the UK in response to upcoming regulatory  
changes by the Financial Conduct Authority (FCA). 
According to a report by City A.M., the fintech firm disclosed its decision to suspend the ability to purchase cryptocurrencies via  
Revolut Business starting January 3, 2024, aligning with the FCA's new  
guidelines on crypto assets.
Navigating Regulatory Changes
Recently, the FCAsignaled imminent guidelines, compelling Revolut to pause the purchasing option  
for cryptocurrencies through Revolut Business from January 3, 2024. While this  
pause affects buying, business customers retain the ability to hold and sell  
crypto, with no impact on Revolut's Retail customers.
The FCA's impending regulations …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale CEO Foresees Spot Bitcoin ETFs Unlocking '$30 Trillion Worth of Advised Wealth']]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748d08515a</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/markets/grayscale-ceo-foresees-spot-bitcoin-etfs-unlocking-30-trillion-worth-of-advised-wealth"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T18:44:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an appearance on CNBC today, the CEO of Grayscale Investments, Michael Sonnenshein, shared insights regarding the potential impact of a spot Bitcoin Exchange-Traded Fund (ETF) on the cryptocurrency market. Sonnenshein highlighted that a spot Bitcoin ETF could "unlock" around "$30 trillion worth of advised wealth."



Sonnenshein discussed the significance of introducing a spot Bitcoin ETF in the United States, emphasizing the vast pool of wealth held within advised assets and the substantial opportunity a regulated Bitcoin ETF could present to tap into these resources.
"When we look ahead to the hopeful approval for spot Bitcoin ETFs, it really is going to unlock the opportunity to a part of the investment community that for better or worse has been locked out for the opportunity to participate in having Bitcoin exposure in their portfolio," Sonnenshein said. "We're really taking about the advised market here in the US. Which is today, about $30 trillion worth of advised wealth that we hope the approval of spot Bitcoin ETFs, the up-listing of GBTC, will allow for that opportunity and for those investors to partake in it as well."
According to Sonnenshein, the introduction of a spot Bitcoin ETF would open the doors for financial advisors and institutional investors to participate in the Bitcoin market more seamlessly. This influx of institutional capital into the market could be substantial, representing a significant step towards mainstream institutional adoption and recognition of Bitcoin as a legitimate asset class.
As discussions around approving a spot Bitcoin ETF persist within regulatory circles, Sonnenshein's comments add weight to the potential impact such an ETF could have on the broader financial landscape. The unlocking of vast advised wealth, as envisioned by Sonnenshein, might significantly alter the dynamics of Bitcoin's market participation and pave the way for increased institutional involvement in the space.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nik Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adam Back States ‘You Can’t Stop JPEGs on Bitcoin,’ Proposes Block Size Increase to Host Inscriptions]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748d091dfd</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/adam-back-states-you-cant-stop-jpegs-on-bitcoin-proposes-block-size-increase-to-host-inscriptions/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T18:38:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adam Back, CEO of Blockstream and legendary cryptographer, has acknowledged that inscriptions, media embedded directly on top of Bitcoin, cannot be stopped, stating that any action focused on this will only prompt users to do it in “worse ways.” Instead, Back proposed adding a new blob of data to Bitcoin blocks dedicated to inscription purposes.
Adam Back Proposes Block Size Increase to Support Inscriptions
Blockstream CEO Adam Back recognized that fighting Ordinal inscriptions, media embedded directly on the Bitcoin blockchain, is useless. In recent statements posted in X, Back stated that JPEGs (images) on Bitcoin were unstoppable and that any actions directed to stop them would only worsen the situation.
Back declared:
Complaining will only make them do it more. trying to stop them and …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK Publishes Regulations for a Digital Securities Sandbox]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748d0be4f3</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/12/18/uk-publishes-regulations-for-a-digital-securities-sandbox/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T18:17:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The sandbox will let regulators and companies test solutions, including distributed ledger technology, to tokenize securities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camomile Shumba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin.com’s VERSE Token Now Live on Polygon Network: A Leap Forward for Economic Freedom]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748ef50cde</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-coms-verse-token-now-live-on-polygon-network-a-leap-forward-for-economic-freedom/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T18:08:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin.com, a pioneering force in making cryptocurrency more accessible, is excited to announce the successful deployment of its ecosystem token VERSE on the Polygon Network. Leveraging Polygon’s low-fee, high-performance architecture, this strategic move broadens access to empowering financial technologies for Bitcoin.com’s millions of users worldwide.
 
“Deploying VERSE on Polygon is a pivotal step in our mission to create economic freedom,” said Bitcoin.com CEO, Dennis Jarvis. “This integration is about empowering our users globally with more accessible and advanced economic tools. Critically, it paves the way for the introduction of micro-rewards for Bitcoin.com ecosystem users, which will significantly enhance engagement and growth.”
 
Innovative Features and Integration
 
With Bitco…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Helium Tokens Surge Amid Network Expansion, Solana Saga BONK Mania]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210147</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210147/helium-tokens-surge-amid-network-expansion-solana-saga-bonk-mania"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T14:04:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following Helium's nationwide U.S. rollout, the Solana-based tokens powering the decentralized 5G network have surged.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Slips Below $41,000 as Crypto Price Rally Cools]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210131</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210131/bitcoin-slips-below-41000-as-crypto-price-rally-cools"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T10:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price slump comes as Bitcoin's average transaction fee has surged to a yearly high, driven by the growing popularity of Ordinals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week on Crypto Twitter: BONK Simply Won’t Quit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210073</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210073/this-week-on-crypto-twitter-bonk-simply-wont-quit"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T10:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ever-ascendant Solana meme coin dominated Twitter discourse for yet another week, as inscriptions hobbled traffic on multiple layer 2 networks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Biggest Games Coming Out in 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210052</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210052/biggest-games-coming-out-nintendo-playstation-xbox-pc"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From Final Fantasy VII Rebirth to Star Wars Outlaws and plenty in between, these are our most anticipated games of 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Bonk Continues Surge With Solana Hype, Bitcoin Dips]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210009</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210009/this-week-in-coins-bonk-continues-surge-with-solana-hype-bitcoin-dips"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T10:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin and other major coins and tokens are down. But new meme coin BONK is still rallying.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Voice Generating Startup Resemble AI Promises to Restore Old Audio]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210063</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210063/resemble-ai-voice-enhance-recordings"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T01:34:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An AI startup has built a tool that it says can make low-fidelity speech recordings sound like new.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not That Grok: Musician Grimes and OpenAI Launch Plush Toy with AI Inside]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210024</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210024/grok-ai-twitter-toy-elon-musk-grimes-trademark"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T22:36:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk’s ex partners with Curio to launch a line of AI-powered toys designed to cut back on screen time and enhance interaction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jupiter Airdrop Set for January With a Billion JUP for Solana DeFi Users]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210017</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210017/jupiter-airdrop-set-january-billion-jup-solana-defi-users"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T22:10:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Half of the 10 billion JUP supply will ultimately go to the Jupiter community, with 10% landing in Solana wallets during the first airdrop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Weighs Demand for Saga Phones After Sellout Amid BONK Boom]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210036</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210036/solana-weighs-demand-saga-phones-after-sellout-amid-bonk-boom"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T21:51:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Saga is sold out in the U.S. and EU supplies are nearly tapped out. Solana Labs told Decrypt how it’s assessing next moves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Tech Giant Alibaba Unveils New AI Video Tool]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210018</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210018/alibaba-ai-text-to-video-generative-cloud"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T21:07:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alibaba says its I2VGen-XL model can handle “visualization, sampling, training, inference, join training using images and videos, acceleration, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitch Walks Back Changes After Surge in Nudity: 'We Went Too Far']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209998</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209998/twitch-walks-back-changes-after-surge-nudity-went-too-far"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T19:37:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, Twitch announced it would allow artistic nudity. Now, it’s blocked again, in part because of concerns around AI realism.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Plans to Challenge SEC Denial of Crypto Rulemaking Petition]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209997</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209997/coinbase-plans-challenge-sec-denial-crypto-rulemaking"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T18:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC today denied crypto exchange Coinbase's petition to clarify new crypto rules for the digital assets industry. Coinbase isn't taking "no" for an answer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Scaler Arbitrum Suffers Outage—And Inscriptions Are to Blame]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209996</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209996/ethereum-scaler-arbitrum-suffers-outage-inscriptions-blame"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T18:12:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arbitrum and other chains have recently been bombarded by users making "inscriptions" as on Bitcoin, even though such networks support NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gary Gensler: SEC 'Taking a New Look' at Bitcoin ETF Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209964</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209964/gary-gensler-sec-taking-new-look-bitcoin-etf-applications"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T16:06:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC chair stated that the regulator is reviewing spot Bitcoin ETF applications in light of a recent court ruling.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BONK Spikes 101% Amid Solana Saga Sales Frenzy to Claim Airdrop]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209966</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209966/bonk-spikes-101-amid-solana-saga-sales-frenzy-to-claim-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T15:40:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana-based meme coin BONK has continued to soar in value and hit new all-time highs—and the Saga smartphone is an unexpected beneficiary.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SocialFi Startup Reach Aims to Improve Crypto Twitter With Anti-Bot Protocol]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209903</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209903/socialfi-reach-crypto-twitter-anti-bot-protocol-token"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T15:01:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest addition to the "point" meta seeks to address the challenges of Crypto Twitter with the support of Seedphrase, Pranksy, Gmoney, and Zeneca.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SafeMoon Files for Bankruptcy, SFM Token Crashes 50% to All-Time Low]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209951</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209951/safemoon-files-for-bankruptcy-sfm-token-crashes-50-to-all-time-low"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T10:08:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Chapter 7 bankruptcy filing comes after SafeMoon's founders were indicted by the DOJ for a "multi-million dollar international fraud scheme."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Casio Drops Virtual G-Shock Watches as Ethereum NFTs—With Exclusive Perks]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209939</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209939/casio-drops-virtual-g-shock-watches-ethereum-nfts-exclusive-perks"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T03:02:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The G-Shock watch brand debuts a pair of fantastical digital designs on Ethereum, with a variety of special benefits for holders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vatican Says AI Is the ‘Highest-Stakes Gamble of Our Future’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209925</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209925/pope-declares-ai-the-highest-stakes-gamble-of-our-future"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T00:46:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pope Francis urged global leaders to work together to adopt a binding international treaty that regulates AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grindr Dating App Adds an AI ‘Wingman’ to Help Users Find Love]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209919</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209919/grindr-dating-app-adds-an-ai-wingman-to-help-users-find-love"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T00:18:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“If you’re not first to market with something in AI, you’re going to miss out," says Grindr CEO George Arison.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Devs Got a BONK Airdrop Worth $300 Last Christmas—It's Now Worth $500,000]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209906</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209906/solana-devs-bonk-airdrop-worth-300-last-christmas-now-worth-500000"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T23:01:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers in LamportDAO received a gift of billions of BONK last year. It helped some pay rent—and others get crypto-rich (maybe).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Instagram Adds Generative AI That Swaps Image Backgrounds]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209868</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209868/instagram-adds-generative-ai-that-swaps-image-backgrounds"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T21:59:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The green screen-like Backdrop feature lets users replace their messy kitchens with lush tropical forests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Native Bitcoin Staking on Ethereum and Solana Could Soon Be a Reality]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209867</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209867/native-bitcoin-staking-ethereum-solana-soon-reality-babylon"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T21:24:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto startup Babylon says it's developed a way to stake Bitcoin on any proof-of-stake blockchain. Here's how it works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana DeFi Hacker Pleads Guilty in First-Ever Smart Contract Fraud Conviction]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209859</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209859/solana-defi-hacker-pleads-guilty-smart-contract-fraud-conviction"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T21:01:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's the "first ever conviction for such a hack,” according to the DOJ. The hacker will be sentenced in March.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Did Michael Cohen Let AI Write His Legal Briefs?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209869</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209869/did-michael-cohen-let-ai-write-his-legal-briefs"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T20:53:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cohen's attorneys must prove the existence of cases they cited as speculation swirls around potential AI-generated content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emerge 2023 Project of the Year: OpenAI ChatGPT 3.5]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209784</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209784/emerge-2023-project-of-the-year-openai-chatgpt"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T19:37:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In barely over a year, ChatGPT rocketed from obscure, largely academic roots to the embodiment of a global revolution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Kawailani Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana's BONK Becomes 69th Largest Coin as Market Cap Tops $1 Billion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209850</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209850/solanas-bonk-69th-largest-coin-market-cap-tops-1-billion"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T18:55:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BONK continues its recent boom with a 64% surge on the day, landing in the meme-friendly #69 spot on CoinGecko’s market ranking.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Farcana Raises $10 Million for NFT Esports Shooter That Pays Out Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209817</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209817/farcana-raiases-10-million-nft-esports-shooter-pays-out-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T18:36:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Exclusive: The sci-fi, team-based hero shooter Farcana is still in early development. Now, it has a fresh round of capital to tap into.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a Single Phishing Link Unleashed Chaos on Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209838</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209838/single-phishing-link-unleashed-chaos-on-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T18:14:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ledger has confirmed the attack began because “a former Ledger employee fell victim to a phishing attack.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating peaceful money & taking over your local government w/ Joseph Schiarizzi]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zb0VG27G/creating-peaceful-money-taking-over-your-local-government-w-joseph-schiarizzi</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zb0VG27G/creating-peaceful-money-taking-over-your-local-government-w-joseph-schiarizzi"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T23:23:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week our host Reza Jafery is joined by Joseph Schiarizzi, founder of OpenDollar and prolific solidity developer. 


We discuss: 
- Onchain beer
- Taking over your local government
- His Emmy and 3 patents?!?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INTERVIEW: Ember Sword CEO Says NFT Games Are More 'Transparent']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/M9OHCVpA/interview-ember-sword-ceo-says-nft-games-are-more-transparent</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/M9OHCVpA/interview-ember-sword-ceo-says-nft-games-are-more-transparent"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T21:58:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ember Sword CEO Mark Laursen shares why some big game studios "irk" him—and why he got into game development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Director Jordan Bayne on the State of Film3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZLoEDkL9/director-jordan-bayne-on-the-state-of-film3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZLoEDkL9/director-jordan-bayne-on-the-state-of-film3"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T00:11:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the 2023 Film3 Summit, Jordan Bayne—director and founder of The Squad—spoke with Decrypt's Sander Lutz about how the Film3 world has progressed over the last year and what decentralized technologies can offer to creators that want to buck the Hollywood system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Questions With SCENE: Phil Mohun]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TwOjXfOR/5-questions-with-scene-phil-mohun</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TwOjXfOR/5-questions-with-scene-phil-mohun"/>
        <updated>2023-12-01T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bright Moments co-founder Phil Mohun joins 5 Questions With SCENE to recount some favorite moments from the road, including negotiating with Patagonian gauchos, falling in love with Tokyo, and gaining a newfound appreciation for shrooms chocolate bars.

Shot and edited by Vincent Roazzi Jr.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are NFTs Ever Coming Back?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qLmFpNKE/are-nfts-ever-coming-back</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qLmFpNKE/are-nfts-ever-coming-back"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T18:38:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this weeks episode we sit down with Cashtro from Arcade.xyz to discuss NFTs, shitcoins, what collections have held onto their floor prices, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Summit: Will Web3 Gaming Ever be Mainstream?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OvVWhGbW/web-summit-will-web3-gaming-ever-be-mainstream</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OvVWhGbW/web-summit-will-web3-gaming-ever-be-mainstream"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T19:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animoca Brands CEO Robby Yung, EndeavorXR CEO Amy Peck and Gamee co-founder CEO Bozena Rezab joined Decrypt's Stephen Graves on stage at Web Summit to talk about the future of Web3 gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Allie Eve Knox on Spankchain and the life of a Crypto Financial Dominatrix]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/16rVeg6o/allie-eve-knox-on-spankchain-and-the-life-of-a-crypto-financial-dominatrix</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/16rVeg6o/allie-eve-knox-on-spankchain-and-the-life-of-a-crypto-financial-dominatrix"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T21:20:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the first IRL episode of This Time Will Be Different!

In this week's episode, our host, Reza Jafery, is joined by Allie Eve Knox, the Spankchain Chief of Staff and FinDomme. 

They discuss
- How to sell feet pics
- If crypto is really as permissionless as it seems
- the intersections between crypto and sex work]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>