<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-01-21T16:18:37.935Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-01-21T16:18:37.935Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the Coinbase vs SEC Showdown Could Alter "Securities”]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19191965/How-the-Coinbase-vs-SEC-Showdown-Could-Alter-Securities</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19191965/How-the-Coinbase-vs-SEC-Showdown-Could-Alter-Securities"/>
        <updated>2024-01-21T16:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a court battle with far-reaching implications, crypto giant Coinbase clashes with the SEC over the definition of a "security"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[9 Freshly Launched Spot Bitcoin ETFs Gather Over 81,000 BTC, Valued at $3.39 Billion]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f104ffc2</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/9-freshly-launched-spot-bitcoin-etfs-gather-over-81000-btc-valued-at-3-39-billion/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-21T16:01:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since Jan. 12, 2024, Grayscale’s newly transitioned spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF), GBTC, experienced a withdrawal of 50,106.59 bitcoin. Meanwhile, the nine newly launched spot bitcoin ETFs have collectively accumulated 81,366 bitcoin, valued at approximately $3.39 billion.
 
Grayscale, Blackrock, and Fidelity Dominate ETF Holdings— More Than 95% Is Stored on Coinbase
 
Recent data reveals that the nine spot bitcoin ETFs launched recently have amassed a substantial quantity of bitcoin since their market debut. GBTC remains the top bitcoin custodian with 566,973.40 BTC, valued at an estimated $23.5 billion. This figure comes after a withdrawal of 50,106.59 BTC from GBTC’s holdings since Jan. 12. The second-highest bitcoin balance in a U.S.-based spot bitcoin ETF belongs to Blackroc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Artfi Fundamental Analysis: Revolutionizing the Multi-Trillion Dollar Art Investment Sector with Blockchain and AI]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19191952/Artfi-Fundamental-Analysis-Revolutionizing-the-Multi-Trillion-Dollar-Art-Investment-Sector-with-Blockchain-and-AI</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19191952/Artfi-Fundamental-Analysis-Revolutionizing-the-Multi-Trillion-Dollar-Art-Investment-Sector-with-Blockchain-and-AI"/>
        <updated>2024-01-21T15:47:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artfi fundamental analysis will help you learn about the significance of Artfi as a company for democratizing investment in high-value artwork. Democratization of art investment is a unique proposition by Artfi that aims to foster widespread participation in the largely elusive high-end art...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Could Be In For A 70% Plunge, Says Fund Manager, After Apex Crypto Fails To Take Off On Spot ETF Launch: 'We Have Seen This Move Before']]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19191963/Bitcoin-Could-Be-In-For-A-70-Plunge-Says-Fund-Manager-After-Apex-Crypto-Fails-To-Take-Off-On-Spot-ETF-Launch-We-Have-Seen-This-Move-Before</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19191963/Bitcoin-Could-Be-In-For-A-70-Plunge-Says-Fund-Manager-After-Apex-Crypto-Fails-To-Take-Off-On-Spot-ETF-Launch-We-Have-Seen-This-Move-Before"/>
        <updated>2024-01-21T15:46:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (CRYPTO: BTC) flattered only to deceive. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cold Wallet Manufacturer Trezor Announces That It Has Detected A Vulnerability In Its System: Who is Affected?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19191941/Cold-Wallet-Manufacturer-Trezor-Announces-That-It-Has-Detected-A-Vulnerability-In-Its-System-Who-is-Affected</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19191941/Cold-Wallet-Manufacturer-Trezor-Announces-That-It-Has-Detected-A-Vulnerability-In-Its-System-Who-is-Affected"/>
        <updated>2024-01-21T15:37:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trezor, which produces hardware wallets, confirmed that it detected a security vulnerability in its systems in its latest research. Continue Reading: Cold Wallet Manufacturer Trezor Announces That It Has Detected A Vulnerability In Its System: Who is Affected?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Whales Taking Advantage of Bitcoin, Ethereum and Chainlink Dips, According to Lookonchain]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19191937/Crypto-Whales-Taking-Advantage-of-Bitcoin-Ethereum-and-Chainlink-Dips-According-to-Lookonchain</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19191937/Crypto-Whales-Taking-Advantage-of-Bitcoin-Ethereum-and-Chainlink-Dips-According-to-Lookonchain"/>
        <updated>2024-01-21T15:30:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto whales are buying up the correction in digital assets markets, according to blockchain tracking firm Lookonchain. Lookonchain says that as Ethereum dipped in price, a “smart whale” with a solid track record of profitable trades bought up the dip with over 3,600 ETH. “After the price of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BTC price recovers from $40.3K lows with Bitcoin volumes &#039;decimated&#039;]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19191931/BTC-price-recovers-from-403K-lows-with-Bitcoin-volumes-039decimated039</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19191931/BTC-price-recovers-from-403K-lows-with-Bitcoin-volumes-039decimated039"/>
        <updated>2024-01-21T15:26:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin is still taking stock of the ETF launch, analysts conclude, with BTC price lacking a convincing trend.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Tokens Vs. Ripple Shares: CTO David Schwartz Reveals His Choice]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f1028e4d</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/xrp-tokens-vs-ripple-shares-cto-david-schwartz-reveals-his-choice/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-21T15:11:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple CTO David Schwartz disclosed he went for Ripple shares instead of XRP tokens in a recent social media post. The CTO of the payments technology company made this known in a discussion regarding Ripple’s XRP holdings on social media platform X. However, according to him, he is yet to determine if he made the right choice at the time. 
 
Ripple’s CTO Preference For Ripple Shares
 
 
 
 
Although his exact holdings weren’t disclosed, Ripple CTO David Schwartz mentioned that he did go for Ripple’s shares as against XRP when was given the choice. However, Schwartz noted that the XRP choice would certainly be more liquid right now, insinuating a better chance of taking profit on XRP tokens than Ripple shares. 
 
 
Yes. The jury is still out on whether that was a good decision. The XRP cert…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Tokens Vs. Ripple Shares: CTO David Schwartz Reveals His Choice]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19191886/XRP-Tokens-Vs-Ripple-Shares-CTO-David-Schwartz-Reveals-His-Choice</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19191886/XRP-Tokens-Vs-Ripple-Shares-CTO-David-Schwartz-Reveals-His-Choice"/>
        <updated>2024-01-21T15:10:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple CTO David Schwartz disclosed he went for Ripple shares instead of XRP tokens in a recent social media post. The CTO of the payments technology company made this known in a discussion regarding Ripple’s XRP holdings on social media platform X. However, according to him, he is yet to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Corrupt Are The "Elites"?! #bitcoin #crypto #shorts]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19191901/How-Corrupt-Are-The-Elites-bitcoin-crypto-shorts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19191901/How-Corrupt-Are-The-Elites-bitcoin-crypto-shorts"/>
        <updated>2024-01-21T15:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michelle Weekley explains how corrupt the elites actually are ....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto vs. stock traders  #shorts]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19191885/Crypto-vs-stock-traders-shorts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19191885/Crypto-vs-stock-traders-shorts"/>
        <updated>2024-01-21T15:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto vs. stock tradersIntroducing the ALTCOINBUZZ ALPHA x DECUBATE Special Offer! Decubate Bronze+ Tier Members can now claim a full refund on your 1st month of Altcoin Buzz Alpha Membership!Eligibility✅ Submit your Bronze+ Member email ID to #Alpha channel in Discord...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Hiring: Crypto Council for Innovation adds Circle and Solana, stocks up on policy hires]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19191911/Crypto-Hiring-Crypto-Council-for-Innovation-adds-Circle-and-Solana-stocks-up-on-policy-hires</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19191911/Crypto-Hiring-Crypto-Council-for-Innovation-adds-Circle-and-Solana-stocks-up-on-policy-hires"/>
        <updated>2024-01-21T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elsewhere, Axie Infinity’s developer gets its first CEO and 1inch DAO lawyers up]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10,000 Bitcoin Sold In A Single Day]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19191884/10000-Bitcoin-Sold-In-A-Single-Day</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19191884/10000-Bitcoin-Sold-In-A-Single-Day"/>
        <updated>2024-01-21T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto markets’ growth in 2023 -The numbers as per CoinGecko]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19191863/Crypto-markets-growth-in-2023-The-numbers-as-per-CoinGecko</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19191863/Crypto-markets-growth-in-2023-The-numbers-as-per-CoinGecko"/>
        <updated>2024-01-21T14:58:48.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SHIB Burn Rate Turns Positive as Bulls Prepare for Shiba Inu Price Rally]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19191868/SHIB-Burn-Rate-Turns-Positive-as-Bulls-Prepare-for-Shiba-Inu-Price-Rally</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19191868/SHIB-Burn-Rate-Turns-Positive-as-Bulls-Prepare-for-Shiba-Inu-Price-Rally"/>
        <updated>2024-01-21T14:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spot Bitcoin ETFs See Robust Growth with 10,667 BTC Accumulated in 5 Days]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19191857/Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-See-Robust-Growth-with-10667-BTC-Accumulated-in-5-Days</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19191857/Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-See-Robust-Growth-with-10667-BTC-Accumulated-in-5-Days"/>
        <updated>2024-01-21T14:38:33.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin 250% Volume Spike Excites DOGE Bulls, Levels to Watch]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19191856/Dogecoin-250-Volume-Spike-Excites-DOGE-Bulls-Levels-to-Watch</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19191856/Dogecoin-250-Volume-Spike-Excites-DOGE-Bulls-Levels-to-Watch"/>
        <updated>2024-01-21T14:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin (DOGE) triggers 250% volume spike as bulls get in action for price]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Crypto Weekend – What’s happening as BTC falls under $42K]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19191854/The-Crypto-Weekend-Whats-happening-as-BTC-falls-under-42K</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19191854/The-Crypto-Weekend-Whats-happening-as-BTC-falls-under-42K"/>
        <updated>2024-01-21T14:30:51.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Justin Sun Relocks 656.4 Billion Shiba Inu in Private Wallet]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19191835/Justin-Sun-Relocks-6564-Billion-Shiba-Inu-in-Private-Wallet</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19191835/Justin-Sun-Relocks-6564-Billion-Shiba-Inu-in-Private-Wallet"/>
        <updated>2024-01-21T14:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain resource Lookonchain has called attention to the transaction activities of the renowned founder of the Tron (TRX) blockchain, Justin Sun. Per the disclosure, Justin Sun has withdrawn an estimated $60 million in multiple crypto assets from Binance over the past 30 days. Among the most...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin price prediction post-ETF hype; What’s next for BTC]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19191833/Bitcoin-price-prediction-post-ETF-hype-Whats-next-for-BTC</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19191833/Bitcoin-price-prediction-post-ETF-hype-Whats-next-for-BTC"/>
        <updated>2024-01-21T14:15:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following the launch of the spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF), the value of the maiden cryptocurrency has experienced a decline … Continue reading]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price Eyes $38,000 as Top Analyst Warns Investors Ahead of Halving]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19191834/Bitcoin-BTC-Price-Eyes-38000-as-Top-Analyst-Warns-Investors-Ahead-of-Halving</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19191834/Bitcoin-BTC-Price-Eyes-38000-as-Top-Analyst-Warns-Investors-Ahead-of-Halving"/>
        <updated>2024-01-21T14:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are cryptocurrency hedge funds, and how do they work?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19191817/What-are-cryptocurrency-hedge-funds-and-how-do-they-work</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19191817/What-are-cryptocurrency-hedge-funds-and-how-do-they-work"/>
        <updated>2024-01-21T14:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano Founder Fires Back At Crypto Report Asking Investors To Dump ADA]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f2f697b7</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/cardano-founder-fires-back-at-crypto-report-asking-investors-to-dump-ada/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-21T13:12:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano founder Charles Hoskinson recently dismissed a report tarnishing the image of the crypto’s blockchain ecosystem. According to the report, the network currently has almost no real-world utility compared to other major cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin and Ethereum. The report also noted that despite its huge daily transaction count, Cardano’s native token, ADA has mostly been speculative.
 
Hoskison Dismisses Damning Report On Cardano
 
Cardano has grown to become one of the biggest cryptocurrencies in terms of market cap. Despite this, a detailed examination from K33 Research earlier in the week hinted that its network activity has been nothing but fabrications. The report, titled “Why you should sell all your ADA (Cardano),” compared activity on the Cardano network to other altcoins l…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale’s 4K Bitcoin Transfer, Blackrock CEO Favorable on Bitcoin, Ripple’s XRP Ousted, and More — Week in Review]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f2f7028f</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/grayscales-4k-bitcoin-transfer-blackrock-ceo-favorable-on-bitcoin-ripples-xrp-ousted-and-more-week-in-review/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-21T13:08:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale stirred speculation by transferring 4,000 bitcoins, while Blackrock CEO Larry Fink endorsed bitcoin as “digital gold,” surpassing government influence. In regulatory news, Ripple’s XRP was removed from Hong Kong Virtual Asset Consortium’s top crypto index. Meanwhile, Elon Musk reaffirmed his commitment to Dogecoin, along with revealing that his company Spacex holds a substantial amount of bitcoin.
 
Grayscale’s 4,000 Bitcoin Transfer Worth $175M Stirs Speculation
 

 
Recent blockchain analytics reveal that 4,000 bitcoins, valued at approximately $175 million, have been transferred from addresses believed to be controlled by Grayscale’s Bitcoin Trust, commonly referred to as GBTC.
 
Read More
 
 
Blackrock CEO Larry Fink on Bitcoin: I’m a Big Believer
 

 
Larry Fink, the CEO of Blackrock, the world’s largest asset manager, says he has become “a big believer” in bitcoin, emphasizing that it is “bigger than any government.” Calling the cryptocurrency “digital gold,” the executive stressed: “Unlike gold, where we manufacture new gold, we’re almost at the ceiling of the most of the amount of bitcoin that could be created.”
 
Read More
 
Ripple’s XRP Ousted From Hong Kong Top Crypto Index
 

 
As Hong Kong strengthens its crypto regulatory framework and embraces ETFs, the Hong Kong Virtual Asset Consortium (HKVAC) has updated its top crypto indexes, showing a preference for tokens with market performance and growing industry partnerships.
 
Read More
 
Elon Musk Still Owns Dogecoin — Spacex Owns Bitcoin
 

 
Tesla CEO and Spacex chief Elon Musk has revealed that he still owns “a bunch of dogecoin,” affirming his commitment to keep buying and supporting the meme cryptocurrency. Musk additionally revealed that his company Spacex still owns “a bunch of bitcoin.”
 
Read More
 
Do you think the bulk of GBTC bitcoin reallocation is done, or is there more selling into other spot bitcoin ETFs to come? Share your thoughts and opinions about this subject in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Sencil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LBank Labs Announces Incubation Fund Investment in AMBBi]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f2fd1b36</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/lbank-labs-announces-incubation-fund-investment-in-ambbi/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-21T12:07:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. LBank Labs has established a dedicated Incubation Fund for Inscription Projects, and AMBBi, an innovative dual-asset project on the Bitcoin blockchain, is the first to be inducted into this groundbreaking initiative. This investment not only highlights LBank Labs’ vision but also marks a new chapter in the evolution of the Bitcoin ecosystem.
 
AMBBi: A Trailblazer in the Bitcoin Ecosystem
 
AMBBi, standing for “Art Meets Blockchain & Beyond innovation,” is a first-of-its-kind project in the Bitcoin ecosystem, featuring the BRC20 inscriptions AMB and BRC69 trendy play NFT AMBBi. With an active community of over 3600 address holders, AMBBi is a testament to the growing interest and belief in the potential of Bitcoin-based assets.
 
Technological Innovation and Cultural Integra…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trezor Alerts 66,000 Users To Risk Of Phishing Attack]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f2fa0393</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/trezor-alerts-66000-users-to-risk-of-phishing/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-21T11:18:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prominent hardware wallet company Trezor has revealed a security breach involving unauthorized access to the platform of one of its third-party service providers. Trezor states that there was no loss of funds. However, the security incident has now exposed 66,000 of its customers to the risks of a phishing attack. 
 
 
Trezor Raises Alarm Following Security Incident 
 
According to Trezor’s statement, they identified an unauthorized access to its third-party support ticketing portal on January 17, 2024, at exactly 20:24 CET. The hardware wallet company states the breach was only at the level of the third service provider, and they were able to effectively revoke the stranger’s access in no time.
 
Upon the commencement of an internal audit, they discovered there is a potential that the bad…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Semilore Faleti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South African Fintech Startup Ukheshe Acquires 100% Stake in EFT Corporation]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f2fb2c8c</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/south-african-fintech-startup-ukheshe-acquires-100-stake-in-eft-corporation/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-21T11:07:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[South African fintech startup Ukheshe recently announced that it has acquired a 100% stake in EFT Corporation, an Africa-focused payment services provider. According to the startup, the acquisition takes Ukheshe closer to its stated goal of attaining a larger footprint in Africa and beyond. 
 
Access to New Technologies and Markets
 
The South African fintech startup, Ukheshe, recently disclosed that it had acquired a 100% stake in EFT Corporation, an Africa-focused payment services provider. The acquisition provides the combined entity with access to new technologies and opportunities and enhances Ukheshe’s exposure to different markets, customers, and business opportunities.
 
According to a statement from Ukheshe, the acquisition of EFT Corporation from its parent firm Loita Transaction…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week on Crypto Twitter: Wall Street, Republican Candidates Embrace Crypto Ethos]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213609</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213609/this-week-on-crypto-twitter-wall-street-republican-candidates-embrace-crypto-ethos"/>
        <updated>2024-01-21T11:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recent moves appear to have cemented Trump’s status as the most attractive presidential candidate for crypto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Proponent Sees ‘Centralized Garbage’ XRP Crashing To $0.01 – Will It?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f2ed0dd0</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-proponent-sees-xrp-crashing-to-0-01/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-21T09:26:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Max Keiser, the flamboyant advocate for Bitcoin, has once again taken center stage, directing his critique at Ripple’s XRP in a recent Twitter rant. Labeling XRP as “centralized garbage,” Keiser boldly predicted a plunge in its price to a mere one cent.
 
Unsurprisingly, Keiser’s followers, accustomed to his unwavering support for Bitcoin and skepticism towards alternative coins, nodded in agreement. Keiser perceives XRP’s centralized structure as a fundamental flaw, drawing sharp contrasts with the decentralized architecture of Bitcoin. He even went as far as insinuating ulterior motives, hinting that the creators of XRP might be involved in questionable activities.
 
 
Is Keiser Right About His Prediction?
 
However, is Keiser’s crystal ball truly clear? XRP did experience a recent dip, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CFTC Files Civil Enforcement Action Against Bogus Crypto Exchange Debiex]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f2eef32a</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/cftc-files-civil-enforcement-action-against-bogus-crypto-exchange-debiex/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-21T09:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. commodities regulator revealed on Jan. 19 that it had filed a civil enforcement action against a bogus digital asset exchange platform. According to the Commission, Debiex customers were not aware that the entire set-up was a clever scam designed to dupe prospective investors.
 
Romance Scam Tactics
 
The Commodities Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) announced on Jan. 19 that it had filed a civil suit against Debiex, a bogus crypto exchange platform it accuses of fraudulently misappropriating $2.3 million in customer funds. The CFTC alleges that the exchange’s representatives used romance scam tactics to fleece millions from the five unnamed prospective investors.
 
The Commission also identified Zhāng Chéng Yáng as a relief defendant because he is suspected of enabling Debiex’s f…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Booms: Hash Rate Records Shattered, Bullish Signal Unleashed]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f2d6d511</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-booms-hash-rate-records-shattered/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-21T07:35:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an impressive display of computational might, the Bitcoin network has shattered its all-time high hash rate, surpassing a staggering 500 exahashes per second. This unprecedented surge signals a robust increase in the raw processing power securing the king of cryptocurrencies, sending ripples of excitement and cautious optimism through the industry.
 
For the uninitiated, hash rate essentially measures the muscle behind Bitcoin’s digital fortress. It reflects the number of complex calculations the network can perform every second, acting as a formidable barrier against potential attackers. This recent leap signifies a dramatic beefing up of security, making it exponentially harder for anyone to tamper with the blockchain.
 
 

 
Thriving Ecosystem: Bitcoin Hash Rate Soars 
 
But the impl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[L2 Protocol Manta Network Suffers DDoS Attack, Project Leaders Face Money Laundering Allegations]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f2d1427f</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/l2-protocol-manta-network-suffers-ddos-attack-project-leaders-face-money-laundering-allegations/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-21T07:06:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manta Network, a modular layer two (L2) protocol, said a distributed denial-of-service attack on Jan. 18 resulted in the network accumulating a large queue of recent transactions. The attack, which occurred during a token-issuing event, is believed to have severely limited communication between the protocol and Manta Network apps. 
 
An Aggressive and Timed Attack
 
On Jan. 18, the Manta Network, a modular layer two (L2) protocol, announced that it was a victim of a distributed denial-of-service (DDoS) attack. The attack resulted in a sharp increase in the number of pending transactions. According to Kenny Li, who shared the DDoS attack alert via X (formerly), the attack initially saw 135 million requests hitting remote procedure call (RPC) nodes, proving that “a very aggressive and timed …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former SEC Official: Crypto Holds the Key to 2024 US Presidential Election]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f2da8871</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/former-sec-official-crypto-holds-the-key-to-2024-us-presidential-election/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-21T05:07:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission’s former head of internet enforcement has explained that crypto holds the key to the 2024 U.S. presidential election. He stressed that every U.S. presidential candidate should immediately appoint an internal Crypto Czar. “The stark reality is that above all else, people have always voted with their wallets,” he emphasized.
 
Former SEC Official on Crypto and Presidential Election
 
Former U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) official John Reed Stark has shared his view on crypto and how it could influence the outcome of the 2024 U.S. presidential election. Stark is currently president of cybersecurity firm John Reed Stark Consulting. He founded and served as chief of the SEC Office of Internet Enforcement for 11 years. He was also an SEC…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blackrock Seeks SEC Approval to Offer Options on Spot Bitcoin ETF — Ishares Bitcoin Trust Now Holds 28,622 BTC]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f2c2e2dc</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/blackrock-seeks-sec-approval-to-offer-options-on-spot-bitcoin-etf-ishares-bitcoin-trust-now-holds-28622-btc/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-21T03:07:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blackrock, the world’s largest asset manager, is seeking approval from the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to offer options on its spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF). The SEC has opened a comment period for a proposed rule change, filed by Nasdaq, to list and trade options on Blackrock’s spot bitcoin ETF. Since launch, Blackrock’s Ishares Bitcoin Trust has amassed 28,622 bitcoins. 
 
SEC Opens Comment Period for Options Trading on Ishares Bitcoin Trust
 
Blackrock, the world’s largest asset manager, is seeking to offer options on its spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF), the Ishares Bitcoin Trust (IBIT).
 
Nasdaq, which lists and trades IBIT, filed a proposed rule change (Form 19b-4) with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) on Friday to list and trade op…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mad Money Host Jim Cramer Sees ‘Nasty Beginning to Bitcoin Selloff’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f2cb47a4</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/mad-money-host-jim-cramer-sees-nasty-beginning-to-bitcoin-selloff/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-21T01:06:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jim Cramer, the host of CNBC’s Mad Money show, has warned of a bitcoin selloff. While cautioning investors about investing in bitcoin and the newly launched spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs), he said: “I’m not as stridently against these new investment vehicles as Gary Gensler is … At this point, Bitcoin’s been around for 15 years, it’s fairly well-established, and I don’t want to try to stop anyone from speculating in this stuff, as long as they do their research.”
 
Jim Cramer’s Bitcoin Prediction
 
Mad Money host Jim Cramer weighed in on the bitcoin price outlook several times this week, particularly focusing on how the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission’s approval of spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) could affect its trajectory. Cramer is a former hedge fund manage…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Under New Scrutiny: Appellate Court Orders Independent Investigation]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f2b3c588</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ftx-under-new-scrutiny-appellate-court-orders-independent-investigation/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-20T23:12:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An independent examiner was initially barred from delving into the FTX bankruptcy case. However, the Third Circuit Court of Appeals in Philadelphia has recently overturned this decision, mandating that the defunct crypto exchange undergo an investigation by an external party. This ruling points out that such an inquiry may intensify oversight and inform prospective investors about the inner workings of these types of operations.
 
Court Mandates External Probe into FTX, Highlighting Potential Crypto Market Risks
 
The U.S. government has expressed a strong desire for an independent examination of the FTX debacle. When U.S. trustee Andrew Vara, overseeing the case, requested a third-party investigation, Judge John Dorsey rejected the plea. Consequently, the government escalated the matter t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Network’s Mining Difficulty Drops 3.9% to 70.34 Trillion, Easing Miner Workload Amid Texas Cold Snap]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f2a545c7</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-networks-mining-difficulty-drops-3-9-to-70-34-trillion-easing-miner-workload-amid-texas-cold-snap/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-20T21:10:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Saturday, the Bitcoin network experienced its first difficulty reduction of the year, witnessing a 3.9% decrease at block height 826,560. As a result, the network’s mining difficulty now stands at 70.34 trillion, with the next adjustment anticipated on Feb. 4, 2024.
 
Bitcoin Difficulty Slips to 70.34 Trillion, Lightening Load for Miners
 
Mining bitcoin (BTC), the leading crypto asset in terms of market capitalization, has become slightly more feasible for miners following this recent difficulty modification. This change took place on Jan. 20, 2024, at block height 826,560, rendering the process of discovering a block reward 3.9% less challenging than during the preceding two weeks. Previously, the difficulty level was pegged at 73.19 trillion, but it has now declined to the present fi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is BlackRock Looking To File For An XRP ETF? Insider Has Answers]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f2a23e6c</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/blackrock-file-for-an-xrp-etf/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-20T20:10:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since the approval of Spot Bitcoin ETFs, speculations about the potential for an XRP Spot ETF continue to grow in the crypto community. However, recent reports have suggested a lack of clear prospects for an XRP ETF in the future. 
 
Notably, Charles Gasparino, an American journalist and senior correspondent at Fox Business has revealed that BlackRock has dismissed any possibility of filing for an XRP ETF. 
 
No Prospects For An XRP ETF
 
In a recent X (formerly Twitter) post, Gasparino disclosed that BlackRock, one of the world’s leading investment companies, has allegedly declared having “no plans” for an XRP ETF. The shocking news shared on Thursday, January 18, had a swift but unfavorable response from the XRP community. Interestingly, this disclosure also follows BlackRock’s Chief Exe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Oasys? The Gaming Blockchain With Ubisoft and Sega Onboard]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213499</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-oasys-gaming-blockchain-ubisoft-sega-onboard"/>
        <updated>2024-01-20T19:49:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oasys wants to be a crypto gaming destination for the biggest developers. Here’s how it works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weekly NFT Sales Dip — Ethereum Outshines Bitcoin, Solana and Avalanche Record Gains]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f2af713a</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/weekly-nft-sales-dip-ethereum-outshines-bitcoin-solana-and-avalanche-record-gains/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-20T19:10:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest statistics indicate a further decline in non-fungible token (NFT) sales this week, showing a 5.05% decrease compared to the previous week. Sales of NFTs reached $297 million, with Ethereum leading the way this week. Ethereum’s sales amounted to $106 million, overtaking Bitcoin’s $70 million in sales over the same seven-day period.
 
 
Ethereum Leads in Weekly NFT Sales, Outperforming Bitcoin as Digital Collectibles Market Experiences Overall Decline
 
Sales of non-fungible tokens (NFTs) have seen a 5.05% decrease from the previous week, yet there’s been an 82.40% rise in buyers and a 77.46% increase in sellers. Recently, Bitcoin had been leading in sales, but Ethereum has now captured the leading position with $106 million in NFT sales, marking a 28.15% increase from last week. …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GBTC’s Mixed Fortune: 54% Market Share in ETF Trade Volume Accompanied by $2 Billion BTC Exodus]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f292a90a</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/gbtcs-mixed-fortune-54-market-share-in-etf-trade-volume-accompanied-by-2-billion-btc-exodus/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-20T17:11:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over a span of six days in the U.S. market, nine newly launched spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs), along with the recently revamped GBTC, collectively saw a trading volume of $16.53 billion. GBTC, commanding the majority of this trade volume, experienced a substantial reduction in its bitcoin holdings. In just the past 24 hours, the trust shed over 14,300 bitcoin, decreasing its total holdings to 566,973 bitcoin. 
 
$2 Billion in Bitcoin Depart Grayscale’s GBTC Since Jan. 12
 
GBTC, now recognized as a spot bitcoin ETF, maintains a considerable reserve of bitcoin (BTC). Since transitioning into a publicly traded ETF, the trust has experienced notable outflows. On Thursday, GBTC’s holdings decreased by 10,823.86 BTC, and following the trading sessions on Friday, the fund saw a furth…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Analyst Predicts 1,300% Move To $7 For Cardano – Here’s The Trigger]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f292fdae</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-analyst-predicts-1300-for-cardano/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-20T17:07:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto analyst Ali Martinez has provided a bullish narrative for Cardano (ADA) based on a historical pattern. According to him, the crypto token could hit a new all-time high if this pattern were to continue.
 
Cardano Could Rise To As High As $7
 
In a post on his X (formerly Twitter) platform, Martinez shared an analysis of how ADA could run to $7. The analyst highlighted the fact that ADA’s current consolidation phase was mirroring its “late 2020 behavior.” and that the crypto token could hit that price level if history repeats itself. He elaborated on how ADA’s price movement could turn out on its way to $7. 
 
 
 
#Cardano‘s current consolidation phase mirrors its late 2020 behavior. If history repeats itself, we might see $ADA resuming its upward trend around April. This pattern cont…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk’s xAI Raises $500 Million: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213614</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213614/elon-musks-xai-raises-500-million-report"/>
        <updated>2024-01-20T16:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AI start-up is eyeing an up to $20 billion valuation, according to Bloomberg.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Despite ETF Hype, Bitcoin and Ethereum Plunge Hard]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213494</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213494/this-week-in-coins-despite-etf-hype-bitcoin-and-ethereum-plunge-hard"/>
        <updated>2024-01-20T11:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin has taken a big hit over the past seven days following the launch of long-awaited spot Bitcoin ETFs on Wall Street.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Church Allegedly Issued Crypto Token Backed by Nothing But God's Word]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213592</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213592/church-allegedly-issued-crypto-token-backed-nothing-but-gods-word"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T23:21:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Colorado couple had their assets frozen by a state judge after making millions on a cryptocurrency they say they created at God’s command.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale Is Sending Bitcoin to Coinbase in $500 Million Clips—Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213564</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213564/grayscale-sending-bitcoin-coinbase-500-million-why"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T21:57:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cash continues to flow out from Grayscale's Bitcoin ETF, while other funds see gains. Here's what's going on.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Ubisoft, Xbox, and Blizzard Are Using AI to Make Next-Generation Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147436</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147436/ai-game-development-ubisoft-roblox-blizzard"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T21:53:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATED: Final Fantasy maker Square Enix says it used AI tools for its big new game, plus Ubisoft is tapping Nvidia's gaming tech for NPCs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Coinbase Win Dismissal of SEC Lawsuit? Legal Experts Weigh In]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213566</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213566/will-coinbase-win-dismissal-sec-lawsuit-legal-experts-weigh-in"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T21:27:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lawyers were impressed by Coinbase's oral arguments, and say full dismissal of the SEC's suit is a realistic possibility.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brazil Stock Exchange to Open After Hours Trading, Give Bitcoin a Boost]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213568</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213568/brazil-stock-exchange-to-open-after-hours-trading-give-bitcoin-a-boost"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T21:10:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin was the only asset besides the country’s own Ibovespa index approved for late night trading sessions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Game On: The Hottest Upcoming Gaming Token Airdrops]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211029</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211029/game-on-hottest-upcoming-gaming-token-airdrops"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T20:26:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATED: Gaming airdrops are heating up, with Nifty Island, Nyan Heroes, and Apeiron revealing plans after the buzzy XAI token launch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘You Can See the Demand Out There for Bitcoin’: Franklin Templeton CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213537</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213537/you-can-see-the-demand-out-there-for-bitcoin-franklin-templeton-ceo"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T19:21:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The global asset manager’s Bitcoin ETF is the latest in blockchain-related investment opportunities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ronin Gaming Wallet Now Supports Ethereum, Polygon, and BNB Chain]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213540</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213540/ronin-gaming-wallet-now-supports-ethereum-polygon-bnb-chain"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T19:06:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ronin’s mobile wallet for iOS and Android will see a new security feature as well as a refreshed design that lets users view more data about their crypto and NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nintendo Switch 2 Preview: Everything You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197793</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197793/nintendo-switch-2-rumors-leaks-latest-news"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T18:13:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATED: Hundreds of developers admit in a major industry survey that they're working on Nintendo Switch 2 games. Here's everything we know so far.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saga Expands Airdrop Rewards to Solana, Polygon, and Avalanche Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213528</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213528/saga-expands-airdrop-rewards-solana-polygon-avalanche-games"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T18:08:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Upcoming gaming network Saga is bringing its play-to-airdrop push to games like Parallel, Shrapnel, and Gas Hero on other chains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana, Avalanche Tumble as Bitcoin Slides Towards $40,000]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213511</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213511/solana-avalanche-tumble-bitcoin-slides-towards-40000"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T17:34:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin is down bad—but major altcoins like Solana, Avalanche, and Cardano are also experiencing a brutal selloff.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Dips Into Bitcoin Ordinals as His NFT Ambitions Fizzle]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213478</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213478/trump-is-doing-bitcoin-ordinals-as-he-tries-to-revive-flailing-nft-drop"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T12:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 presidential hopeful’s latest project involves 200 NFTs inscribed on the Bitcoin blockchain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Punts Fidelty Spot Ethereum ETF Decision to March]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213480</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213480/sec-punts-fidelty-spot-ethereum-etf-decision-to-march"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T11:04:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC has stated it needs "sufficient time to consider the proposed rule change and the issues raised therein."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Crime Down 29% in 2023: Chainalysis Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213470</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213470/crypto-crime-down-29-percent-in-2023-chainalysis-report"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T01:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FTX tipped the scales in the amount of illicit cryptocurrency reported after the conviction of Sam Bankman-Fried.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Nifty Island' Is Already Better Than Most NFT Sandbox Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213423</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213423/nifty-island-already-better-most-nft-sandbox-games"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T23:24:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PREVIEW: Our first hands-on playtest of Nifty Island’s public beta was surprisingly addicting, allowing tons of room for imagination.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Someone Microwaved a Solana Saga Phone—Now Degens Are Buying Meme NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213457</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213457/someone-microwaved-solana-saga-phone-now-degens-buying-meme-nfts"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T23:06:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s one less Solana Saga in the world after a viral experiment... but 3,333 more NFTs commemorating it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Is Coming for Gold's Global Market, Says Cathie Wood]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213442</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213442/bitcoin-is-coming-for-golds-global-market-says-cathie-wood"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T22:45:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ARK Invest CEO says financial investors should go with crypto over the precious metal, and tech investors should stick with software.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former OpenSea Exec Argues NFT Insider Trading Conviction Violated Law]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213440</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213440/former-opensea-exec-argues-nft-insider-trading-conviction-violated-law"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T22:21:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nathaniel Chastain was convicted last year for profiting off of information he was privy to as an executive at NFT marketplace OpenSea.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Plunges 12% in 7 Days as BlackRock Collects $1.1 Billion From ETF]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213422</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213422/bitcoin-price-down-blackrock-1-billion-etf"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T21:02:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock's Bitcoin ETF has broken records—but BTC's price is down bad since the historic launch of the long-awaited investment vehicles.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Crypto Unicorns’ Game Ditching Polygon for Arbitrum’s Xai Network]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213416</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213416/crypto-unicorns-game-ditching-polygon-arbitrum-xai-network"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T21:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following last week’s XAI token airdrop, Arbitrum gaming network Xai will add Crypto Unicorns and related NFT games from Polygon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Half of Game Devs Use AI, But Creatives Are Wary: Survey]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213411</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213411/half-game-developers-use-ai-designers-worried-jobs"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T20:51:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[84% of developers raise ethical concerns, with AAA studios more likely to have AI policies, according to Game Developer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Vision Pro Preorders Begin Friday—What You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213404</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213404/apple-vision-pro-preorders-begin-friday-what-need-know"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T19:27:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Got $3,499 burning a hole in your pocket? The Apple Vision Pro is nearly here, and the first wave of orders are set to begin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether Snaps Up More Bitcoin, Brings Holdings to $2.8 Billion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213393</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213393/tether-buys-more-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T18:02:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The stablecoin issuer continues to load up on Bitcoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi Exchange dYdX Dethrones Ethereum's Uniswap as Token Outpaces the Market]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213380</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213380/defi-exchange-dydx-dethrones-ethereums-uniswap-as-token-outpaces-the-market"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T18:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized cryptocurrency exchange dYdX is hotter than ever, beating Uniswap v3 Ethereum in volume—and the charts back the hype.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PIXEL Token Launch 'Very Close' as Pixels Game Sets Play-to-Airdrop End]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213348</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213348/pixel-token-launch-very-close-pixels-game-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T16:41:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Popular Ronin farming and social game Pixels is nearing its token launch as the current airdrop campaign winds down.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EU Provisionally Agrees Tougher AML Rules for Crypto Firms]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213327</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213327/eu-provisionally-agrees-tougher-aml-rules-for-crypto-firms"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T13:03:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Under the new rules, crypto firms in the European Union would need to conduct due diligence checks on transactions over €1,000.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Celestia (TIA)? The Coin Created by a CIA Hacker Spikes 800%]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213312</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213312/what-is-celestia-tia-the-coin-created-by-a-cia-hacker-spiked-800-in-3-months"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T12:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A modular blockchain with a notorious founder is the new obsession among crypto enthusiasts, its token value up 40% since December 18.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Vows to 'Never Allow' U.S. CBDC if Reelected]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213324</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213324/trump-vows-to-never-allow-u-s-cbdc-if-reelected"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T10:54:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a campaign speech in New Hampshire, the former U.S. President called central bank digital currencies "government tyranny."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Laser-Eyed Franklin Templeton Sets Sights on Ethereum, Solana After Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213281</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213281/franklin-templeton-layer-one-ethereum-solana-after-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T03:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The investment giant highlighted Solana's vision and Ethereum's ecosystem in its bullish Twitter thread.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Apeiron’ God Game Begins Airdrop Rewards on Ethereum Scaler Ronin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213295</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213295/apeiron-god-game-begins-airdrop-rewards-ethereum-scaler-ronin"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T00:34:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ronin’s latest big game has launched a play-to-airdrop campaign, letting users earn while playing and engaging online.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Nifty Island' NFT Game Launches Open Beta With Airdrop Rewards]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213275</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213275/nifty-island-nft-game-launches-open-beta-airdrop-rewards"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T00:05:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nifty Island, the create-an-island game with NFTs, is offering future token perks to active players who mint NFTs and create experiences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Case Judge Asks If SEC Is ‘Sweeping Too Broadly’ as She Weighs Dismissal]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213288</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213288/coinbase-case-judge-asks-if-sec-is-sweeping-too-broadly-as-she-weighs-dismissal"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T23:52:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. District Judge Katherine Polk Failla will decide whether to dismiss the SEC’s lawsuit against the crypto exchange for alleged securities violations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are you the one being farmed? w/ Frisson]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/i3sesrao/are-you-the-one-being-farmed-w-frisson</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/i3sesrao/are-you-the-one-being-farmed-w-frisson"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T18:38:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reza is joined by Frisson from Tallyx.xyz

They reflect on:
- building in the bear market
- the points system meta
- will zoomers care about decentralization]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Look Touch Own': OONA Discusses Her Performance Art Exhibition]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/79jpGlCe/look-touch-own-oona-discusses-her-performance-art-exhibition</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/79jpGlCe/look-touch-own-oona-discusses-her-performance-art-exhibition"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T16:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Conceptual artist OONA joins moderator Raina Marie to discuss "Look Touch Own," her performance art exhibition featuring her own former breast implants, which have been tokenized. This conversation was recorded at Rug Radio's R Haus event at Art Basel Miami in December 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Genius Marketing by Genius Marketers: How Crypto Builders Can Reach the Masses]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/YiQgzWJW/genius-marketing-by-genius-marketers-how-crypto-builders-can-reach-the-masses</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/YiQgzWJW/genius-marketing-by-genius-marketers-how-crypto-builders-can-reach-the-masses"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rug Radio founder Farokh Sarmad moderates a conversation between 9dcc founder and CEO Gmoney and Serotonin founder and CEO Amanda Cassatt about the challenges and opportunities in Web3 marketing and how they're navigating the ever-evolving space. Recorded at Rug Radio's R Haus event at Art Basel Miami in December 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generative Art Across Mediums: Artists Discuss the Evolving Space]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/GK3aN0zo/generative-art-across-mediums-artists-discuss-the-evolving-space</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/GK3aN0zo/generative-art-across-mediums-artists-discuss-the-evolving-space"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T02:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this panel discussion from Rug Radio's R Haus at Art Basel Miami 2023, Sofia Garcia, Ismail Tazi, Emily Edelman, and Aleksandra Art discuss the expanding generative art space—and why "generative" doesn't necessarily have to mean digital.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The AI Coin to Rule Them All with Mike Grantis]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rkYpU8TJ/the-ai-coin-to-rule-them-all-with-mike-grantis</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rkYpU8TJ/the-ai-coin-to-rule-them-all-with-mike-grantis"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T18:46:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reza is joined by Mike Grantis from Contango Digital to discuss
- The AI coin to rule them all
- The Solana Ecosystem 
- What's next for Solana airdrops]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conversation With Snowfro: Bringing 'Chromie Squiggle' #8107 to the Physical Space]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/DcrU04gG/conversation-with-snowfro-bringing-chromie-squiggle-8107-to-the-physical-space</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/DcrU04gG/conversation-with-snowfro-bringing-chromie-squiggle-8107-to-the-physical-space"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Art Blocks founder and CEO and "Chromie Squiggle" project creator Erick "snowfro" Calderon spoke with Benny Redbeard Gross at Rug Radio's R Haus event at Art Basel 2023, to discuss how and why "Chromie Squiggle" NFT #8107 was given a special edition print run in collaboration with Avant Arte.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don't Underestimate Mobile Gaming: Qualcomm's Matthew Grossman]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/34Oil4Qu/dont-underestimate-mobile-gaming-qualcomms-matthew-grossman</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/34Oil4Qu/dont-underestimate-mobile-gaming-qualcomms-matthew-grossman"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Qualcomm product marketing manager Matthew Grossman tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin why mobile esports is exploding in popularity around the world—and dispels some of the misconceptions around mobile gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF: This Is the 'Calm Before the Storm', Says ETF Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/VOX04ytt/bitcoin-etf-this-is-the-calm-before-the-storm-says-etf-analyst</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/VOX04ytt/bitcoin-etf-this-is-the-calm-before-the-storm-says-etf-analyst"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T20:20:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bloomberg Senior ETF Analyst Eric Balchunas joins Farokh Sarmad, Michael Anderson, and Ovie Faruq on the FOMO Hour to share the latest intel on the looming approval for a spot Bitcoin ETF, what might happen when the very different worlds of TradFi and crypto collide, and his insights on “Genslish,” the unique and strategic language of SEC chair Gary Gensler.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Losing 1500 BTC on Mt Gox and the Problem with Women in Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/EfNuNu8a/losing-1500-btc-on-mt-gox-and-the-problem-with-women-in-web3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/EfNuNu8a/losing-1500-btc-on-mt-gox-and-the-problem-with-women-in-web3"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T19:02:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week our host is joined by Brooke Lacey! 

They discuss:  
- Making and losing generational wealth
- Trauma Bond
- Women in Web3
- The Problem with WAGMI]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ESL Faceit Group Exploring Blockchain 'Opportunistically,' Says Exec]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/yvrs4lBx/esl-faceit-group-exploring-blockchain-opportunistically-says-exec</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/yvrs4lBx/esl-faceit-group-exploring-blockchain-opportunistically-says-exec"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T02:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Braithwaite—ESL Faceit Group's VP of Game Ecosystems, Mobile, and Snapdragon Pro Series—shares the esports firm's approach to blockchain technology with GG's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bryan Johnson Explains His Quest for Immortality and Why He Started with the Penis]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tAwP55g9/bryan-johnson-explains-his-quest-for-immortality-and-why-he-started-with-the-penis</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tAwP55g9/bryan-johnson-explains-his-quest-for-immortality-and-why-he-started-with-the-penis"/>
        <updated>2023-12-24T19:38:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Billionaire biohacker Bryan Johnson shared with Decrypt's Jason Nelson why he began his longevity quest and how technology has shaped the endeavor. Johnson also discusses some of his controversial experiments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>