<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-11-09T20:15:51.199Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-11-09T20:15:51.199Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Price Pullback: Crypto Analyst Highlights Levels To Watch]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a675d3b0</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-analyst-predicts-pullback-for-xrp-price/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T20:09:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Popular cryptocurrency analyst Cryptonary has recently shed light on his predictions concerning the XRP price and has revealed there might be a pullback for the cryptocurrency’s price.
 
Crypto Analyst’s Prediction For XRP
 
Cryptoary took to his official X (formerly Twitter) handle to share his recent prediction on the price movement of XRP. The X post was accompanied by a short video clip to further elaborate on his prospects.
 
The crypto analyst’s prediction was fueled by the recent price decline of XRP from its highest point of $0.73 this week and believes that the token price fell due to the rejection at the $0.70 key resistance.
 
 
“For XRP, we’d be very cautious here. Price has moved into a major resistance at $0.70 and has initially been rejected from this level. Alongside this, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Godspower Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former head of compliance at OneCoin pleads guilty; Crypto Queen remains at large]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19028098/Former-head-of-compliance-at-OneCoin-pleads-guilty-Crypto-Queen-remains-at-large</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19028098/Former-head-of-compliance-at-OneCoin-pleads-guilty-Crypto-Queen-remains-at-large"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T20:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Irina Dilkinska, who reportedly served as “Head of Legal and Compliance” for the supposed crypto project, pleaded guilty to charges of wire fraud and money laundering on Nov. 9 in a Manhattan federal court. The announcement was made by U.S. Attorney for the Southern District of New York Damian...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Price Pullback: Crypto Analyst Highlights Levels To Watch]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19028122/XRP-Price-Pullback-Crypto-Analyst-Highlights-Levels-To-Watch</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19028122/XRP-Price-Pullback-Crypto-Analyst-Highlights-Levels-To-Watch"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T20:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Popular cryptocurrency analyst Cryptonary has recently shed light on his predictions concerning the XRP price and has revealed there might be a pullback for the cryptocurrency’s price. Crypto Analyst’s Prediction For XRP Cryptoary took to his official X (formerly Twitter) handle to share his...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two Giant Companies Announced They Will Partnership for Bitcoin and Ethereum ETF!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19028109/Two-Giant-Companies-Announced-They-Will-Partnership-for-Bitcoin-and-Ethereum-ETF</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19028109/Two-Giant-Companies-Announced-They-Will-Partnership-for-Bitcoin-and-Ethereum-ETF"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T19:57:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ark Invest and 21Shares are launching a suite of ETFs that will give investors solid options for including digital assets in their portfolios. Continue Reading: Two Giant Companies Announced They Will Partnership for Bitcoin and Ethereum ETF!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MELB: The Community-Powered Gem of Minelab’s AI-Driven Cryptocurrency Mining]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19028108/MELB-The-Community-Powered-Gem-of-Minelabs-AI-Driven-Cryptocurrency-Mining</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19028108/MELB-The-Community-Powered-Gem-of-Minelabs-AI-Driven-Cryptocurrency-Mining"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T19:51:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the cryptocurrency world where innovation and community engagement are key, MELB emerges as a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bitcoin Dev’s Bot Bucked BRC-20s—Now He Might Share ‘The Sophon’ With the World]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=205377</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/205377/a-bitcoin-devs-bot-bucked-brc-20s-now-he-might-share-the-sophon-with-the-world"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T19:49:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Text-based inscriptions associated with BRC-20s plummeted 72% after the code was unleashed. There's signs someone is running a copy of it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bitcoin Dev’s Bot Bucked BRC-20s—Now He Might Share ‘The Sophon’ With the World]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19028099/A-Bitcoin-Devs-Bot-Bucked-BRC-20sNow-He-Might-Share-The-Sophon-With-the-World</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19028099/A-Bitcoin-Devs-Bot-Bucked-BRC-20sNow-He-Might-Share-The-Sophon-With-the-World"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T19:49:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Text-based inscriptions associated with BRC-20s plummeted 72% after the code was unleashed. There's signs someone is running a copy of it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Athena Bitcoin to Boost Crypto ATM Efficiency with Lightning Network Integration]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19028090/Athena-Bitcoin-to-Boost-Crypto-ATM-Efficiency-with-Lightning-Network-Integration</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19028090/Athena-Bitcoin-to-Boost-Crypto-ATM-Efficiency-with-Lightning-Network-Integration"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T19:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Athena Bitcoin, the company overseeing a network of crypto ATMs in El Salvador, has unveiled...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 social media to disrupt a $100B market: Pop Social joins Cointelegraph Accelerator]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19028082/Web3-social-media-to-disrupt-a-100B-market-Pop-Social-joins-Cointelegraph-Accelerator</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19028082/Web3-social-media-to-disrupt-a-100B-market-Pop-Social-joins-Cointelegraph-Accelerator"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T19:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 social media dApp Pop Social becomes the newest member of the Cointelegraph Accelerator program.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Over $249,000,000 in Bitcoin, Ethereum and Solana Shorts Liquidated in Hours As BTC Blows Past $37,000]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19028088/Over-249000000-in-Bitcoin-Ethereum-and-Solana-Shorts-Liquidated-in-Hours-As-BTC-Blows-Past-37000</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19028088/Over-249000000-in-Bitcoin-Ethereum-and-Solana-Shorts-Liquidated-in-Hours-As-BTC-Blows-Past-37000"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T19:41:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hundreds of millions of dollars worth of Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH), and Solana (SOL) shorts have been liquidated as the king crypto shoots past $37,000. According to new data from blockchain tracking platform Coinglass, during the last 24 hours, the top crypto asset by market cap has seen...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Shiba Inu (SHIB) Is Moving]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19028094/Why-Shiba-Inu-SHIB-Is-Moving</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19028094/Why-Shiba-Inu-SHIB-Is-Moving"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T19:38:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (CRYPTO: SHIB) is trading lower by 2.7% to the $0.000008-level Thursday afternoon, pulling back following recent strength. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Accuses Bitwise's Ex-CEOs of Alleged $70 Million Deception Scheme]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a671e034</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/sec-accuses-bitwises-ex-ceos-of-alleged-70-million-deception-scheme/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T19:37:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The former co-CEOs of Bitwise Industries Inc., a  
private technology services startup based in Fresno, California, have been  
charged by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) for falsifying  
financial documents while raising approximately $70 million from investors in  
2022. 
The allegations against Jake Soberal and Irma  
Olguin, Jr. expose a scheme of deception that ultimately led to the downfall of  
the company. The former co-CEOs are accused of making material  
misrepresentations and fabricating financial documents to mislead investors  
regarding Bitwise's financial health. 
The documents included falsified bank records and a  
counterfeit audit report, both of which allegedly portrayed Bitwise as a  
thriving business with healthy financial performance. In reality, Bitwise was  
grappling with chronic cash shortages and struggling to sustain its operations.
According to the SEC, the scheme's consequences became  
evident in May 2023 when Bitwise was unable to meet its payroll obligations and  
was forced to terminate its entire workforce. 
 
  
 
  
This article was written by Jared Kirui at www.financemagnates.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Fees Climb 150% in 3 Days as Block Space Grows More Expensive]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a672b797</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-fees-climb-150-in-3-days-as-block-space-grows-more-expensive/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T19:30:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Transaction fees within the Bitcoin network have surged considerably, eclipsing the figures recorded merely three days prior. A transfer deemed high-priority, which formerly cost an average of $3.38, now demands a fee of $8.46. This significant increase was recorded on Thursday, November 9, 2023, at precisely 9:52 a.m. Eastern Time. This upsurge coincides with a backlog exceeding 200,000 pending transactions in Bitcoin’s mempool, a situation attributed to both the escalated fees and a recent spike in Ordinal inscriptions.
 
Bitcoin Fees Skyrocket in 72 Hours as Users Scramble for Tightening Block Space
 
The demand for space in Bitcoin’s ledger has witnessed a sharp rise, compelling miners to face a daunting 429 megabytes of data backlog, equivalent to approximately 229 blocks. At block he…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft enters $100M partnership with Canadian firm after quantum breakthrough]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19028034/Microsoft-enters-100M-partnership-with-Canadian-firm-after-quantum-breakthrough</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19028034/Microsoft-enters-100M-partnership-with-Canadian-firm-after-quantum-breakthrough"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T19:28:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photonic’s founder and Chief Quantum Officer says the company can bring a quantum computer to market within the next five years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BREAKING: FED Chairman Jerome Powell is Speaking – Making Some Hawkish Remarks]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19028031/BREAKING-FED-Chairman-Jerome-Powell-is-Speaking-Making-Some-Hawkish-Remarks</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19028031/BREAKING-FED-Chairman-Jerome-Powell-is-Speaking-Making-Some-Hawkish-Remarks"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T19:19:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell participated in a panel on monetary policy challenges in the global economy at the International Monetary Fund's annual research conference. The panel was expected to have a moderated Q&A. Powell announced that the FED will begin its next framework review...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Surges as Investor Confidence Grows Amid Economic Uncertainty]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19028030/Bitcoin-Surges-as-Investor-Confidence-Grows-Amid-Economic-Uncertainty</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19028030/Bitcoin-Surges-as-Investor-Confidence-Grows-Amid-Economic-Uncertainty"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T19:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past two weeks, Bitcoin has maintained a relatively tight trading range, fluctuating within...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2 Years Ago, Bitcoin Hit an All-Time High. Is Another Rally on the Way?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a67c94fb</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/11/09/2-years-ago-bitcoin-hit-an-all-time-high-is-another-rally-on-the-way/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T19:15:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We were full of “irrational exuberance” in November 2021.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Kuhn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining Potential Highlighted In Top Science Journal]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a67d5aa1</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-mining-potential-top-science-journal/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T19:10:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new peer-reviewed research paper has emerged, shedding light on the potential symbiosis between Bitcoin mining and renewable energy initiatives. Dennis Porter, CEO and co-founder of Satoshi Act Fund, a non-profit educational organization dedicated to informing policymakers and regulators about Bitcoin mining’s benefits, and president of Satoshi Educate, shared his insights via X, underscoring the importance of the study. He remarked, “JUST IN: New peer-reviewed research states that Bitcoin mining ‘could serve as a bridge to foster investments in renewable energy.’”
 
Top Science Journal Praise Bitcoin Mining’s Potential
 
Murray Rudd, Science Advisor for Satoshi Educate, provided a comprehensive overview of the paper, titled “From mining to mitigation: how Bitcoin can support renewable e…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trader Says Ethereum Altcoin That’s Up 130% in Three Weeks ‘Looks Pretty Strong,’ Names Targets for Chainlink]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19028002/Trader-Says-Ethereum-Altcoin-Thats-Up-130-in-Three-Weeks-Looks-Pretty-Strong-Names-Targets-for-Chainlink</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19028002/Trader-Says-Ethereum-Altcoin-Thats-Up-130-in-Three-Weeks-Looks-Pretty-Strong-Names-Targets-for-Chainlink"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T19:05:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A popular crypto analyst is remaining bullish on one red-hot altcoin that more than doubled in value within a few weeks. Pseudonymous trader Altcoin Sherpa tells his 197,900 followers on the social media platform X that the gaming studio and NFT (non-fungible token) marketplace platform Vulcan...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining Potential Highlighted In Top Science Journal]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19027998/Bitcoin-Mining-Potential-Highlighted-In-Top-Science-Journal</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19027998/Bitcoin-Mining-Potential-Highlighted-In-Top-Science-Journal"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T19:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new peer-reviewed research paper has emerged, shedding light on the potential symbiosis between Bitcoin mining and renewable energy initiatives. Dennis Porter, CEO and co-founder of Satoshi Act Fund, a non-profit educational organization dedicated to informing policymakers and regulators about...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analyst Predicts Bitcoin And Crypto Market Crash Of Epic Proportions, Here’s When]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19027980/Analyst-Predicts-Bitcoin-And-Crypto-Market-Crash-Of-Epic-Proportions-Heres-When</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19027980/Analyst-Predicts-Bitcoin-And-Crypto-Market-Crash-Of-Epic-Proportions-Heres-When"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T19:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin and the entire crypto market are currently in an uptrend which has been a cause for celebration for investors all across the space. However, not everyone expects this uptrend to continue. One crypto analyst has made a case for why Bitcoin and the crypto market at large could be headed...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polkadot Decreases More Than 3% Within 24 hours]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19028023/Polkadot-Decreases-More-Than-3-Within-24-hours</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19028023/Polkadot-Decreases-More-Than-3-Within-24-hours"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T19:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Polkadot's (CRYPTO: DOT) price has decreased 3.19% over the past 24 hours to $4.87. This is contrary to the coins performance over the past week where it has experienced an up-trend of 5.0%, moving from $4.66 to its current price. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Litecoin Down More Than 3% Within 24 hours]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19028024/Litecoin-Down-More-Than-3-Within-24-hours</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19028024/Litecoin-Down-More-Than-3-Within-24-hours"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T19:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Litecoin's (CRYPTO: LTC) price has decreased 3.65% over the past 24 hours to $71.21. This is contrary to the coins performance over the past week where it has experienced an up-trend of 3.0%, moving from $69.21 to its current price. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Falls More Than 6% In 24 hours]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19028025/Dogecoin-Falls-More-Than-6-In-24-hours</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19028025/Dogecoin-Falls-More-Than-6-In-24-hours"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T19:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past 24 hours, Dogecoin's (CRYPTO: DOGE) price has fallen 6.16% to $0.07. This is opposite to its positive trend over the past week where it has experienced a 5.0% gain, moving from $0.07 to its current price. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Wallstreet Journal FALSELY claims crypto funded terrorism #bitcoin #crypto #shorts]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19027985/The-Wallstreet-Journal-FALSELY-claims-crypto-funded-terrorism-bitcoin-crypto-shorts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19027985/The-Wallstreet-Journal-FALSELY-claims-crypto-funded-terrorism-bitcoin-crypto-shorts"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T19:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WSJ has woken up the hornets nest. Don't believe the false narrative created to make you hate Bitcoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Want Free Rare Pokémon Cards? Courtyard Is Giving Them Away via NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=205346</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/205346/want-free-rare-pokemon-cards-courtyard-giving-away-via-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T19:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto collectibles startup Courtyard is giving away hundreds of branded mystery packs containing graded and tokenized Pokémon cards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Want Free Rare Pokémon Cards? Courtyard Is Giving Them Away via NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19028001/Want-Free-Rare-Pokemon-Cards-Courtyard-Is-Giving-Them-Away-via-NFTs</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19028001/Want-Free-Rare-Pokemon-Cards-Courtyard-Is-Giving-Them-Away-via-NFTs"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T19:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto collectibles startup Courtyard is giving away hundreds of branded mystery packs containing graded and tokenized Pokémon cards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wild Bitcoin, Ether Price Swings Spur $400M of Crypto Liquidations, the Most Since August]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a67fe7f5</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/11/09/wild-bitcoin-ether-price-swings-spur-400m-of-crypto-liquidations-the-most-since-august/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T18:50:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[tktk]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celsius to Emerge from Bankruptcy With Repayment Plan Approved]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=205367</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/205367/celsius-to-emerge-from-bankruptcy-with-repayment-plan-approved"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T18:42:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Backed by a new entity with $450 million in seed funding, the failed crypto lender may come back to life.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enhanced Steam Deck OLED Handheld Gaming PC Coming Next Week]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=205358</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/205358/enhanced-steam-deck-oled-handheld-gaming-pc-coming-next-week"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T18:34:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Valve's enhanced Steam Deck OLED upgrades the handheld gaming PC with a better screen, longer battery life, and other tweaks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt AI, Edited by Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Filecoin Executive Exposes The Internet’s Secret Perils: Key Insights Unveiled]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a6658ec2</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/filecoin-exec-exposes-dangers-on-the-net/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T18:10:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Filecoin, a prominent name in the world of blockchain technology and decentralized storage, is making waves with its emphasis on data ownership. The recent panel discussion at Benzinga’s Future of Digital Assets highlighted the growing awareness of the importance of data ownership in the crypto space. 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
Rachel Green Horn, the head of Marketing and Communications at Filecoin Foundation, highlighted the internet’s vulnerability during the discussion. Following a revealing survey conducted last summer, Horn noted that only 25% of respondents acknowledged the internet’s fragility.
 
She was surprised by the stark contrast between the low acknowledgment of the internet’s fragility (25%) and the high number of people (70%) who had faced difficulties accessing their data.
 
 
The…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto for Advisors: Innovating Legacy Programs with Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a6607570</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/web3/2023/11/09/crypto-for-advisors-innovating-legacy-programs-with-blockchain/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T17:50:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week's issue of Crypto for Advisors, learn how brands are leveraging blockchain to innovate loyalty programs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Morton, Sam Ewen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase, Ether Liquid Staking Tokens Lido, RocketPool Surge on BlackRock ETH ETF News]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a6607565</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/11/09/coinbase-ether-liquid-staking-tokens-lido-rocketpool-surge-on-blackrock-eth-etf-news/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T17:50:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Asset management giant BlackRock registered a Delaware company for a spot ether trust, fueling speculations about a potential ETF filing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OneCoin Legal Chief Pleads Guilty to Role in Cryptoqueen's $4 Billion Fraud]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=205356</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/205356/onecoin-legal-chief-pleads-guilty-to-role-in-cryptoqueens-4-billion-fraud"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T17:47:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Irina Dilkinska admitted in Manhattan federal court to helping launder $110 million in illicit profits generated through OneCoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt AI, Edited by Stacy Elliot</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blackrock Registers Ishares Ethereum Trust With Delaware’s Division of Corporations]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a6624b68</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/blackrock-registers-ishares-ethereum-trust-with-delawares-division-of-corporations/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T17:38:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blackrock may be taking steps toward obtaining approval from the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) for a spot ethereum exchange-traded fund (ETF) in the near future. This comes on the heels of the company’s application for an Ishares Ethereum Trust with the Delaware Division of Corporations on Thursday.
 
Speculation Rises on Blackrock’s Preparations for Spot Ether ETF Launch
 
As the world’s largest asset manager by assets under management, Blackrock has formally recorded its Ishares Ethereum Trust with Delaware’s Division of Corporations. The document, dated November 9, 2023, identifies the trust as statutory and acknowledges Blackrock Advisors as the filing party.
 
James Seyffart, a Bloomberg ETF analyst, called attention to the filing on the social platform X, verifying its authenticity. “Multiple people asking ‘is this real’ — yes it’s real,” Seyffart confirmed. “An entity with this name was indeed registered in Delaware. That’s all we can really confirm at this time. Those images are real and from the State of Delaware website.”
 
 
Market watchers speculate that Blackrock is positioning itself to introduce a spot ether ETF, subsequent to regulatory consent for its spot bitcoin ETF initiative. Blackrock’s submission for a spot bitcoin ETF was made on June 15, 2023, and the firm is currently awaiting the SEC’s decision.
 
In the meantime, ethereum’s (ETH) value has seen an uptick of over 5% in the last 24 hours, temporarily crossing the $2,000 mark per unit. The surge was a lot more pronounced following the circulation of the Blackrock story across social media networks. However, only time will reveal Blackrock’s next move with the Ishares ETH trust.
 
What do you think about Blackrock’s registration in Delaware? Share your thoughts and opinions about this subject in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Now Lend Your NFTs to Gamers and Earn Passive Income]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=205003</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/205003/you-can-now-lend-your-nfts-gamers-earn-passive-income"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T17:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LootRush will let gamers list their NFTs for rent on its marketplace, allowing them to earn passive income for game items like cards and land.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BREAKING: Shiba Inu Marketing Lead Calls On Robinhood To List BONE]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a66ff11d</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-robinhood-bone/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T17:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since its launch in 2021, the BONE token has enjoyed a lot of support from the core Shiba Inu community. The token, which was initially released as the native token for the ShibaSwap decentralized exchange), has since expanded its use case as the native utility token for the SHIB Layer 2 blockchain Shibarium. Following the success of the coin so far, SHIB’s marketing lead, Lucie, has taken to X (formerly Twitter) to propose a potential new listing.
 
Getting Robinhood To List BONE
 
Shiba Inu marketing team lead Lucie has suggested that crypto and stock trading platform Robinhood list the BONE token. Tagging the official Robinhood X (formerly Twitter) account in the post, Lucie pitched the token, telling the trading platform that it is the token that powers Shibarium, an Ethereum Layer 2 b…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can Stablecoins Get Past Their Instability?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a66aab07</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/11/09/can-stablecoins-get-past-their-instability/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T16:43:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Moody's Head of DeFi Rajeev Bamra considers the role stablecoins play cryptocurrency markets, and the risks posed by "depegging" events.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajeev Bamra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTT Skyrockets Amid FTX Acquisition Rumors Tied to NYSE’s Ex-President]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a66ba0ab</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ftt-skyrockets-amid-ftx-acquisition-rumors-tied-to-nyses-ex-president/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T16:37:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FTX’s proprietary token, FTT, has witnessed an impressive surge of over 80% following reports that say Tom Farley, the former president of the New York Stock Exchange (NYSE), is potentially interested in acquiring and rebooting the collapsed exchange.
 
FTT Price Jumps More Than 80% Over FTX 2.0 Speculation
 
On Thursday, FTT’s value soared, escalating from an early-day trough of $1.22 to a zenith of $2.38. Sparking this ascent were disclosures hinting at Tom Farley, who steered the NYSE Group from 2014 to 2018, as a contender in the pool of prospective buyers for FTX.
 
These speculations were fueled by a Wall Street Journal article quoting sources “familiar with the matter.” Since the announcement, FTT has notched an 82% gain against the dollar, and its 30-day trajectory shows a 111.8% u…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Union Of Bitcoin And The Climate Change Agenda]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a66bcfe5</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/the-union-of-bitcoin-and-the-climate-change-agenda"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T16:35:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t worry, this isn’t an article to either espouse or attack the current global climate change agenda. Debating whether the earth will perish in a few years or not isn’t my plan. While not only being a believer and investor in the Bitcoin echo-system, I am also an avid supporter of start-ups and innovators supporting green technologies to provide for a more energy efficient future. Here I simply want to discuss how Bitcoiners should adopt the concepts quite effectively applied by the global climate change movement under their green investment proposals to also promote expanded Bitcoin adoption. These are techniques that I have seen implemented first-hand among the climate change posse. 
While there are certainly natural reasons to adopt Bitcoin, especially considering the world’s current…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enza Coin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Gains BlackRock’s Support: Asset Manager Registers Trust As ETH Tops $2,000]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a6568daa</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-blackrock-registers-trust-as-eth-tops-2000/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T16:19:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH), the second-largest cryptocurrency by market capitalization, has witnessed a remarkable surge of 7.4% in the past 24 hours, reaching $2,023 since April 2023. 
 
This surge in Ethereum’s value closely mirrors the recent upward movement of Bitcoin (BTC). It coincides with reports indicating that BlackRock, a renowned asset manager overseeing $9 trillion in assets, has registered an Ethereum Trust in Delaware.
 
Blackrock Ethereum ETF On The Horizon?
 
BlackRock made significant waves earlier this year when it submitted a filing for a spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) with the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). 
 
Subsequently, BlackRock’s iShares Bitcoin Trust successfully obtained registration, solidifying the firm’s presence in the emerging cryptocurrency ind…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Tops $2,000 for First Time Since July]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=205331</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/205331/ethereum-soars-past-2000"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T16:18:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum has followed Bitcoin's rally today, rallying past the $2,000 mark.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Surge To $37,000 Flushes $157 Million In Crypto Shorts]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a6505d84</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-37000-flushes-134-million-crypto-shorts/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T16:09:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data shows a huge amount of liquidations have occurred on the crypto futures market today following Bitcoin’s sharp surge toward $37,000.
 
Crypto Futures Market Has Registered Mass Liquidations During Past Day
 
A futures contract is said to be “liquidated” when the derivative exchange with which it’s open forcefully closes it up due to the position amassing losses of a specific degree (the exact percentage could differ from platform to platform).
 
There are two factors that can significantly raise the risk of a contract undergoing liquidation. First and the most obvious one is the volatility of the asset with which the contract is open. A high amount of price fluctuations naturally means that it’s harder to bet in any specific direction.
 
 
The other factor is the leverage that the use…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Venture Capital Lightspeed Faction Starts $285M Fund for Blockchain Startups]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a650677e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/11/09/venture-capital-lightspeed-faction-starts-285m-fund-for-blockchain-startups/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T16:08:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new fund will focus mainly on early-stage crypto projects, participating in seed-stage and Series A funding rounds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aoyon Ashraf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EU Parliament Approves Data Act With Smart-Contract Kill Switch Provision]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a65197e7</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/11/09/eu-parliament-approves-data-act-with-smart-contract-kill-switch-provision/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T16:01:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The final version of the bill's text, reviewed by CoinDesk in July, revealed that it contained a smart-contract kill switch clause.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camomile Shumba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ether Soars Above $2K as BlackRock iShares Ethereum Trust Registered As Corporate Entity In Delaware]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a65197c4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/11/09/ether-soars-above-2k-as-blackrock-ishares-ethereum-trust-registered-as-corporate-entity-in-delaware/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T16:01:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock declined to comment on the filing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock Registers Ethereum Trust in Delaware—ETH ETF Next?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=205332</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/205332/blackrock-rethereum-trust-delaware-eth-etf"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T15:54:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Analysts say the registration could be a precursor for an ETF filing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Supply Chain Disruption: A Tokenized Approach]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a652f780</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/supply-chain-disruption-a-tokenized-approach/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T15:53:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an era of relentless global  
disruptions, the call for resilient supply chains echoes louder than ever. This  
exploration delves into the transformative potential of blockchain on the  
supply chain network. We navigate  
the landscape of disruptions and propose nuanced tokenization strategies,  
fostering a holistic approach to optimizing and navigating complex supply chain  
operations.
Understanding the  
Disruption Landscape
Over the past decade,  
economic and geopolitical events have rippled through the global economy,  
disrupting supply chains on an unprecedented scale. As such, the need for resilient supply chains is undeniable. In  
response, a strategic shift is required in order to attain a bird's eye view of the entire supply chain network.
4 Steps Towards Improving Suppl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Ferreira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why OTK Is Making Video Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/1NCV4Fk0/why-otk-is-making-video-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/1NCV4Fk0/why-otk-is-making-video-games"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One True King (OTK) Chief Strategy Officer Zachary Diaz tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about OTK's long-term strategy and vision to become a content creator-powered media and video games company.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Soars Past $37,000, Touching 18-Month High on ETF Optimism]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=205317</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/205317/bitcoin-blows-past-37000-touching-18-month-high-on-etf-optimism"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T14:45:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin is rallying on optimism surrounding the approval of a spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Business Sim Game Legacy Launches With Competitive Events on Gala Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204010</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204010/business-sim-game-legacy-launches-with-competitive-events-on-gala-games"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T13:51:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Players can take part in events including design and sales competitions to win in-game Gems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yuga Labs Says 'UV-A Emitting Lights' to Blame for ApeFest Attendees' Eye Pain]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=205298</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/205298/yuga-labs-says-uv-emitting-lights-blame-burned-apefest-attendees"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T11:10:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Owners of the Bored Ape Yacht Club NFT collection complained of eye pain following the three-day ApeFest event in Hong Kong.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTT Token Jumps 84% Following Gensler's FTX Revival Comments]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=205306</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/205306/ftt-token-jumps-following-genslers-ftx-revival-comments"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T10:55:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FTX's token surged following reports that the exchange could be revived—though there's no indication the token would be part of that revival.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SAG-AFTRA Ends Strike After Deal to Protect Actors From 'Threat of AI']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=205299</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/205299/sag-aftra-ends-strike-after-deal-protect-actors-threat-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T09:33:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The "tentative agreement" between the actors' union and the AMPTP reportedly hinged on clauses regarding the use of AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Assassin's Creed Maker Ubisoft Is Building a Crypto 'Gaming Experience' With Immutable]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204992</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204992/assassins-creed-maker-ubisoft-building-crypto-gaming-experience-immutable"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T06:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ubisoft and Immutable are developing a new blockchain gaming project that plans to offer "digital ownership." Here's what we know so far.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Congress Moves to Clip the SEC's Wings as Gensler Signals Openness to a Revived FTX]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=205293</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/205293/gary-gensler-ineffective-incompetent-revived-ftx"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T03:59:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hitting out at the SEC Chair, Representative Tom Emmer called Gary Gensler “ineffective” and “incompetent.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Arrives on YouTube With Comment Summaries and Video Suggestions]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=205285</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/205285/google-ai-youtube-comment-section-subscriber-chatbot"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T01:29:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[YouTube’s AI tool aims to turn comment chaos into organized insights.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Illuvium Ethereum Token Surges After Epic Games Store Listing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=205271</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/205271/illuvium-ethereum-token-surges-after-epic-games-store-listing"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T00:20:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lavish Immutable X game Illuvium is coming to the Epic Games Store, and the news fueled a spike in the ILV token price.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Shameless’: CZ Slams Bitcoin Hater Nouriel Roubini's New Token]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=205158</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/205158/cz-calls-nouriel-roubini-shameless-atlas-capital-token"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T23:58:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Dr. Doom” used Binance’s brand recognition to promote his new blockchain venture, just months after calling CZ a "ticking time bomb."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Killer Combo: ChatGPT Merged With Dall-E, Vision, Web Browsing and Code Interpreter]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204934</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204934/what-can-you-do-with-chatgpt-gpt4-turbo-multimodal-features"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T23:14:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here's what you can do now with multimodal capabilities, where it's not just about what you say, but what you show.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bored Ape NFT Holder Threatens Legal Action Over ApeFest Eye Injuries]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204996</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204996/bored-ape-nft-holder-threatens-legal-action-over-apefest-eye-injuries"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T23:10:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CEO of Artfi, Asif Kamal, is one of several ApeFest attendees who experienced eye pain after the festival.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Questions With SCENE: LoVid]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=205009</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/205009/5-questions-with-scene-lovid"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T22:58:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome the latest guests in the "5 Questions" hot seat: tech innovators, artistic duo, and married couple LoVid.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mozilla Enlists Fakespot for AI Chatbot to Safeguard Online Shopping]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=205012</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/205012/mozilla-enlists-fakespot-for-ai-chatbot-to-safeguard-online-shopping"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T22:25:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is AI the solution to fake, AI-generated product reviews?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best AI Tools for Teachers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204998</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204998/how-to-ai-best-ai-tools-for-teachers"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T22:20:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence is reshaping education and finding its way into the classroom, for better or worse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[12 Bitcoin ETFs Have 'Brief Window' for SEC Approval Starting Tomorrow]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=205004</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/205004/sec-approval-of-bitcoin-spot-etf-could-come-tomorrow"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T22:14:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Analysts theorize that the regulatory agency could authorize spot trading between Nov. 8 and Nov. 17.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Questions With SCENE: LoVid]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/E8BZZBWX/5-questions-with-scene-lovid</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/E8BZZBWX/5-questions-with-scene-lovid"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T21:47:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artistic duo LoVid, aka Tali Hinkis and Kyle Lapidus, joins 5 Questions with SCENE to answer burning questions about art, lettuce, and the hellscape (in someone’s opinion) that is Miami.

Video shot and edited by Vincent Roazzi Jr.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft, Meta Lay Down AI Rules to Safeguard Elections]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204987</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204987/microsoft-facebook-meta-election-politics-ai-deepfakes"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T21:16:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Focusing on authenticity and transparency ahead of 2024, two tech titans outline measures to combat AI-powered political disinformation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Gaming Sidechain Ronin Is On Fire—Here's Why]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204979</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204979/ethereum-gaming-sidechain-ronin-on-fire-heres-why"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T20:52:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Axie Infinity’s Ronin network is growing as more games launch, tripling active users and pumping the price of RON.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two Republicans Want to Protect Your Ability to Self-Custody Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204968</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204968/two-republicans-want-to-protect-your-ability-to-self-custody-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T20:21:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sen. Ted Budd said his bill is meant to ensure Americans can "maintain control over their own digital assets."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt AI, Edited by Stacy Elliot</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ATMs in El Salvador are Getting a Lightning Network Upgrade]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204933</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204933/lightning-network-hits-bitcoin-atms-in-el-salvador"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T19:44:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The switch will "enable smaller and potentially more frequent transactions," according to Genesis Coin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Barney on DeFi, Privacy, and Vega]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/hgDzjboU/barney-on-defi-privacy-and-vega</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/hgDzjboU/barney-on-defi-privacy-and-vega"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T18:27:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week our host is joined by Barney the founder of Vega Protocol. 

They discuss the current state of DeFi, what's wrong with the apps being built today, whether or not privacy matters when its only applied to an L2, and most importantly-- which form of sales tax is the sexiest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Disrespectful and Dangerous': Video Game Writers, Actors Blast Microsoft for Xbox AI Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204923</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204923/disrespectful-dangerous-video-game-writers-actors-blast-microsoft-xbox-ai-tools"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T16:39:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft is making more AI tools, but game industry talent are very concerned that the Xbox AI push will lead to more job losses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gucci Cosmos Land Opens in The Sandbox Metaverse Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204761</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204761/gucci-cosmos-land-opens-sandbox-metaverse-game"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T16:01:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Luxury house Gucci brings its London historical exhibit into the metaverse with Gucci Cosmos Land in The Sandbox.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt AI, Edited by Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HSBC, Ripple-Backed Metaco to Launch Tokenized Custody Service Next Year]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204911</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204911/hsbc-ripple-backed-metaco-launch-tokenized-custody-service-next-year"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T15:56:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HSBC continues to plow ahead with tokenization, this time partnering with Metaco for a new institutional custody service slated for 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Investors Bet $5.5 Million on Stackr to Onboard JavaScript Devs to Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204912</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204912/investors-bet-5-5-million-stackr-onboard-javascript-devs-to-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T15:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With an aim to onboard more developers to crypto, Stackr has landed fresh funding to make that transition even easier.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUI Gains 12% While Chainlink and Polygon Keep Alt Rally Rolling]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204888</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204888/sui-gains-12-chainlink-and-polygon-rallying"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T15:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin is up 1.3% today, but alts like MATIC, LINK, and SUI are taking the lead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Grand Theft Auto 6 Trailer Coming in December, Rockstar Confirms]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204907</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204907/first-grand-theft-auto-6-trailer-coming-december-rockstar-confirms"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T14:39:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over a decade after the last game launched, Rockstar Games will finally take the wraps off of Grand Theft Auto 6.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Are Ordinals? A Beginner's Guide to Bitcoin NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=121590</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-are-ordinals-a-beginners-guide-to-bitcoin-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T13:06:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bitcoin community has gone wild over Ordinal Inscriptions, but what is the new thing taking over Crypto Twitter?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoin Behemoth Circle Mulls 2024 IPO: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204784</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204784/stablecoin-behemoth-circle-mulls-2024-ipo-report"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T11:54:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Circle is reportedly eyeing another attempt at going public in 2024 after its SPAC plans were called off in 2022.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt AI, Edited by Liam Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Toncoin Briefly Overtakes Dogecoin Amid 8% Rally]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204785</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204785/toncoin-briefly-overtakes-dogecoin-rally"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T11:28:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram-associated cryptocurrency Toncoin (TON) is leading the market's gains among the top 100 digital assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Launches Self-Custody Crypto Wallet With Exclusive 'Airdrop Zone' for Users]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204776</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204776/binance-launches-self-custody-crypto-wallet-boasting-exclusive-airdrops-for-users"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T10:01:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The newly launched Binance Web3 Wallet uses multi-party computation to abstract away the need for a seed phrase.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Is Phantom Galaxies Releasing Two Versions of Its Game?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QtnWGSSJ/why-is-phantom-galaxies-releasing-two-versions-of-its-game</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QtnWGSSJ/why-is-phantom-galaxies-releasing-two-versions-of-its-game"/>
        <updated>2023-11-06T17:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animoca Brands-owned Blowfish Studios is building a space mech pilot game called Phantom Galaxies. Blowfish Cofounder Ben Lee tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about his plans for the game's release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sophie Maxx on NFTs, Augmented Reality, and Fashion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/VByufHjn/sophie-maxx-on-nfts-augmented-reality-and-fashion</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/VByufHjn/sophie-maxx-on-nfts-augmented-reality-and-fashion"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T23:37:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week our host is joined by Sophie Maxx (Web3Maxx) to discuss NFTs, augmented reality, the metaverse, how blockchain is sneaking into the fashion world, and more!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Questions With SCENE: Kevin Rose]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/u9LDX8Vr/5-questions-with-scene-kevin-rose</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/u9LDX8Vr/5-questions-with-scene-kevin-rose"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kevin Rose, co-founder and CEO of PROOF and co-creator of the hit Moonbirds NFT collection, joins 5 Questions with SCENE to answer some hard-hitting questions about his childhood dreams, his wife’s candy preferences, and his undying love of rap music.

Video shot and edited by Vincent Roazzi Jr.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Happened to Atari's Token? Inside Atari's Blockchain Plans]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/7OtQIdqa/what-happened-to-ataris-token-inside-ataris-blockchain-plans</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/7OtQIdqa/what-happened-to-ataris-token-inside-ataris-blockchain-plans"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T18:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin chats with Atari X director Tyler Drewitz about what happened with Atari's token plans, whether a token is coming, and what Atari games might be getting the blockchain treatment. Oh, and there's lots of Easter eggs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitch CEO Dan Clancy Is a 'Wild Card,' Says Marketing Director]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/qCOCtPKe/twitch-ceo-dan-clancy-is-a-wild-card-says-marketing-director</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/qCOCtPKe/twitch-ceo-dan-clancy-is-a-wild-card-says-marketing-director"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T20:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twitch Senior Director of Community Marketing Mary Kish speaks with Decrypt's Kate Irwin about Twitch CEO Dan Clancy, Ninja, Twitch's new simulcasting rules, the biggest differences between Twitch and rival platform Kick, and the role of esports on the streaming platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why NFT Paris has Launched a Loyalty Token]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/91tPVJff/why-nft-paris-has-launched-a-loyalty-token</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/91tPVJff/why-nft-paris-has-launched-a-loyalty-token"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T13:26:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NFT Paris founder Alexandre Tsydenkov told Decrypt what to expect from the upcoming 2024 edition of the conference, the launch of its loyalty token and its plans to create a Web3 loyalty program that rewards the most engaged members of the community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Game Review—Formula E: High Voltage Is a Fun Play-to-Earn Racer That Lacks Direction]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/hzkx0TDg/game-reviewformula-e-high-voltage-is-a-fun-play-to-earn-racer-that-lacks-direction</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/hzkx0TDg/game-reviewformula-e-high-voltage-is-a-fun-play-to-earn-racer-that-lacks-direction"/>
        <updated>2023-10-29T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Formula E: High Voltage is a play-to-earn racing game with a distinctive strategic approach. Decrypt contributor Ryan Gladwin put Animoca's web-based game through its paces in this review, highlighting the unique gameplay design, the role of NFTs and crypto, and where the game currently comes up short.

Follow Decrypt's GG on Twitter: https://twitter.com/ggdecrypt 

Check out GG for daily gaming news: https://decrypt.co/gg 

Subscribe to our GG newsletter with over 50,000 subscribers: https://decrypt.co/newsletters/gg 

Join our official Discord: https://discord.com/invite/3bc4QpA57C]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amanda Cassatt on Web3 Marketing and the early days of Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5Cm0ENyc/amanda-cassatt-on-web3-marketing-and-the-early-days-of-ethereum</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5Cm0ENyc/amanda-cassatt-on-web3-marketing-and-the-early-days-of-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T16:40:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week's episode, our host is joined by Amanda Cassatt! 

Amanda is the founder of Serotonin, a web3 marketing agency, the author of the first book ever published on web3 marketing, and led the marketing team that helped bring Ethereum to market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Midnight Society's Rob Bowling on Deadrop's New Cars and User-Generated Modes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/A0auyZzn/midnight-societys-rob-bowling-on-deadrops-new-cars-and-user-generated-modes</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/A0auyZzn/midnight-societys-rob-bowling-on-deadrops-new-cars-and-user-generated-modes"/>
        <updated>2023-10-22T01:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt reporter and GG producer Kate Irwin interviews Midnight Society Studio Head Rob Bowling about Deadrop's development and Snapshot VII.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Game Review: 'Raini: The Lords of Light' Brands Itself With Memes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/32YyJHCJ/game-review-raini-the-lords-of-light-brands-itself-with-memes</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/32YyJHCJ/game-review-raini-the-lords-of-light-brands-itself-with-memes"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T19:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Raini: Lords of Light is an NFT-optional card game bursting with crypto memes. From SBF to CZ and Elon, this free-to-play game has some truly wild animations. Decrypt contributor Ryan S. Gladwin shares his honest thoughts on the game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Art Blocks Marfa Weekend Recap]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/QaTBP6eO/art-blocks-marfa-weekend-recap</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/QaTBP6eO/art-blocks-marfa-weekend-recap"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T19:19:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Relive the Art Blocks Marfa Weekend 2023 event with this highlights video, produced by Vincent Roazzi Jr. for Decrypt Studios in partnership with Art Blocks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Phantom Galaxies: A Look Inside the Mech Shooter NFT Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QI1uDwQv/phantom-galaxies-a-look-inside-the-mech-shooter-nft-game</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QI1uDwQv/phantom-galaxies-a-look-inside-the-mech-shooter-nft-game"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T21:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animoca Brands and game studio Blowfish are developing Phantom Galaxies, an upcoming sci-fi mech shooter game inspired by mech battlers like Transformers. Decrypt's Kate Irwin asks Blowfish Studios Cofounder and Managing Director Ben Lee about what it's like to play the game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Clip: DeepMedia's DeepID Deepfake Detection Tool at Work]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/m4Vy4vhC/clip-deepmedias-deepid-deepfake-detection-tool-at-work</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/m4Vy4vhC/clip-deepmedias-deepid-deepfake-detection-tool-at-work"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T16:48:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A clip showcasing how DeepMedia's DeepID deepfake detection tool works. Courtesy: DeepMedia]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentraland AI World Fair Trailer]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/3tUb56Fv/decentraland-ai-world-fair-trailer</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/3tUb56Fv/decentraland-ai-world-fair-trailer"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A trailer for the AI World Fair event in metaverse game Decentraland, taking place from October 25-27. Courtesy: Decentraland.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BackTheBunny - Money, Conspiracy, Milady]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BRoKZzer/backthebunny-money-conspiracy-milady</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BRoKZzer/backthebunny-money-conspiracy-milady"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T19:48:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our host Reza Jafery sits down with BackTheBunny to dive deep into money, the fight against crypto that we're witnessing in real-time, and milady culture. 

Our Host: https://twitter.com/rezajafery
Our Guest: https://twitter.com/BackTheBunny

Our Sponsors
https://decrypt.co/1000x]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['A Grand Experiment': Shrapnel Studio Head Don Norbury Talks Game Economics]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Z2OMMsC5/a-grand-experiment-shrapnel-studio-head-don-norbury-talks-game-economics</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Z2OMMsC5/a-grand-experiment-shrapnel-studio-head-don-norbury-talks-game-economics"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T17:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How much of Shrapnel's in-game items are tradeable NFTs? Don Norbury, Studio Head at Shrapnel and CTO at game studio NEON, tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about Shrapnel's approach to game economics, including different game pricing models and how NFT game economies create different challenges for developers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trezor Safe 3 and Trezor Keep Metal Unboxing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/IjqnO9pR/trezor-safe-3-and-trezor-keep-metal-unboxing</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/IjqnO9pR/trezor-safe-3-and-trezor-keep-metal-unboxing"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T14:45:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trezor has launched the Safe 3, a hardware wallet aimed at "new entrants to crypto," alongside the new Keep Metal recovery seed storage device. We take a first look at what comes in the box.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>