<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-05-21T15:13:28.051Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-05-21T15:13:28.051Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Should Corporations Add Bitcoin to Their Holdings?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18395364/Should-Corporations-Add-Bitcoin-to-Their-Holdings</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18395364/Should-Corporations-Add-Bitcoin-to-Their-Holdings"/>
        <updated>2023-05-21T14:55:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tether recently announced plans to allocate up to 15% of their profits to bitcoin]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden opposes debt deal friendly to “crypto traders” amid threat of U.S. default]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18395353/Biden-opposes-debt-deal-friendly-to-crypto-traders-amid-threat-of-US-default</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18395353/Biden-opposes-debt-deal-friendly-to-crypto-traders-amid-threat-of-US-default"/>
        <updated>2023-05-21T14:42:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. President Joe Biden keen to strike a debt deal but not one that is friendly to "crypto traders."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Analyst Unveils Massive Downside Target for Bitcoin (BTC) – Here’s His Outlook]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18395341/Crypto-Analyst-Unveils-Massive-Downside-Target-for-Bitcoin-BTC-Heres-His-Outlook</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18395341/Crypto-Analyst-Unveils-Massive-Downside-Target-for-Bitcoin-BTC-Heres-His-Outlook"/>
        <updated>2023-05-21T14:30:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An analyst closely followed in the crypto space is targeting much lower prices for Bitcoin (BTC) despite the crypto king being well off its lows for the year. In a new strategy session, Nicholas Merten tells his 511,000 DataDash subscribers that Bitcoin appears poised for a sustained downtrend...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decoding Bitcoin’s Transaction Surge: The Emergence Of History’s Greatest Accounting Innovation]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750ee448bd</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/accounting-for-bitcoin-transaction-spike"/>
        <updated>2023-05-21T14:30:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is an opinion editorial by Darin Feinstein, the co-founder and co-chairman of Bitcoin mining firm Core Scientific.
The recent surge in transaction volume on the Bitcoin network has sparked conversation and debate about heightened transaction fees and Bitcoin's overall goals and purpose. This has resulted in questions regarding the network's future and its ability to handle the increasing demand. 
In response to those questions, it can be helpful to consider the intricacies of Bitcoin’s transaction volume through an accounting lens, as the Bitcoin network, at its foundation, is an accounting ledger with its data written to a public chain and recorded forever. Through this lens, we’ll delve into why Bitcoin’s transaction volume matters, how often such surges will occur and whether or no…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darin Feinstein</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PSYOP Faces Lawsuit and Fraud Allegations Amid Investor Losses]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18395354/PSYOP-Faces-Lawsuit-and-Fraud-Allegations-Amid-Investor-Losses</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18395354/PSYOP-Faces-Lawsuit-and-Fraud-Allegations-Amid-Investor-Losses"/>
        <updated>2023-05-21T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin vs The IMF - Bitcoin 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18395340/Bitcoin-vs-The-IMF-Bitcoin-2023</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18395340/Bitcoin-vs-The-IMF-Bitcoin-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-05-21T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['SEC Can Still Win': Ex-Ripple Exec on Latest XRP News]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18395328/SEC-Can-Still-Win-Ex-Ripple-Exec-on-Latest-XRP-News</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18395328/SEC-Can-Still-Win-Ex-Ripple-Exec-on-Latest-XRP-News"/>
        <updated>2023-05-21T14:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matt Hamilton highlights concerns as internal SEC emails cast doubt on case against Ripple]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Paxful Founder: Ethereum Is A Drain And Drag On Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750ee7386f</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/former-paxful-founder-ethereum-is-a-drain-and-drag-on-bitcoin/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-21T14:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ray Youssef, the former founder of Paxful, thinks Ethereum, the world’s largest smart contracting platform, is a “drain and drag” on Bitcoin.
 
Ethereum Slowing Down Bitcoin?
 
In his post on May 21, it is evident that the former CEO is critical of Ethereum and thinks it is a hindrance and obstacle to Bitcoin’s progress.
 
Breaking down his view, Youssef appears to suggest that Ethereum’s impact has been largely negative, delaying advancements in crypto.
 
 
Ethereum is simply a drain and drag on #bitcoin We should be grateful that it slowed things down as we needed time to figure things out and get the pieces in play. We have been steady now it is time to blaze. #civkit will be what Eth should have been and I am Vitalik on roids. pic.twitter.com/CdbfB0UpaP
 
— Ray Youssef (@raycivkit) May…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dalmas Ngetich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Paxful Founder: Ethereum Is A Drain And Drag On Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18395299/Former-Paxful-Founder-Ethereum-Is-A-Drain-And-Drag-On-Bitcoin</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18395299/Former-Paxful-Founder-Ethereum-Is-A-Drain-And-Drag-On-Bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-05-21T13:58:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ray Youssef, the former founder of Paxful, thinks Ethereum, the world’s largest smart contracting platform, is a “drain and drag” on Bitcoin. Ethereum Slowing Down Bitcoin? In his post on May 21, it is evident that the former CEO is critical of Ethereum and thinks it is a hindrance and obstacle...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Presidential Candidate Embraces Bitcoin For Campaign Funding]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750ee12a2d</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/vivek-ramaswamy-embraces-bitcoin-campaign-funding/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-21T13:40:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vivek Ramaswamy, a Republican presidential candidate, is revolutionizing his campaign strategy by embracing Bitcoin, a digital currency, as a crucial tool for accepting campaign donations. Furthermore, he plans to introduce an innovative proposal that aims to relax tax regulations on Bitcoin mining operations in the United States.
 
Vivek Ramaswamy joins the ranks of presidential candidates who embrace digital currencies for campaign donations, following in the footsteps of Senator Rand Paul. Notably, Paul set the precedent during his 2016 White House campaign by accepting Bitcoin contributions.
 
 
Ramaswamy’s decision demonstrates the continued recognition among political contenders of the importance and potential of digital currencies in the realm of campaign financing. This move highli…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>anushsamal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rand Plunges After US Weapons Accusations Against South Africa, Schiff Criticizes Misleading Inflation Numbers, and More — Bitcoin.com News Week in Review]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750ee1c699</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/rand-plunges-after-us-weapons-accusations-against-south-africa-schiff-criticizes-misleading-inflation-numbers-and-more-bitcoin-com-news-week-in-review/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-21T13:34:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Another exciting week in crypto and finance has come and gone, with news of U.S. government accusations against South Africa, regarding the alleged supply of the Russian state with ammunition. In other news, ten Southeast Asian nations are challenging U.S. dollar dominance, having agreed to “encourage the use of local currencies for economic and financial transactions.” In the world of crypto, Monday’s Bitcoin Cash network upgrade now sees the protocol with thousands of tokens being created via the Cashtokens functionality. This and much more, just below.
 

 
South African Currency Plunges to New Low Versus the Dollar a Day After the US Accused Country of Secretly Supplying Ammunition to Russia
 
The South African currency’s exchange rate versus the U.S. dollar plunged to a new all-time l…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu’s Shibarium Hits 10M Transaction Volume Milestone]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18395293/Shiba-Inus-Shibarium-Hits-10M-Transaction-Volume-Milestone</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18395293/Shiba-Inus-Shibarium-Hits-10M-Transaction-Volume-Milestone"/>
        <updated>2023-05-21T13:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu's Shibarium has averaged more than 300,000 daily transactions since May 12, according to Puppyscan data.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a VTuber, and how do you become one?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18395248/What-is-a-VTuber-and-how-do-you-become-one</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18395248/What-is-a-VTuber-and-how-do-you-become-one"/>
        <updated>2023-05-21T13:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A VTuber is a virtual content creator who uses an animated avatar. To become one, create an avatar, use motion capture technology, and produce content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monero Community Expresses Privacy Concerns And Criticizes ‘Mordinals’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750eed43e2</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/monero-privacy-concerns-and-criticizes-mordinals/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-21T12:59:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mordinals, also known as Monero Ordinals, serve as a means to inscribe data alongside transactions stored on the Monero blockchain. This unique feature allows users to include additional information within the Monero network, enhancing its capabilities beyond simple transactional data storage.
 
The concept of Ordinals was introduced to simplify the issuance of tokens and NFTs on the Bitcoin network. Over the past 30 days, Bitcoin ordinals have gained significant popularity within the crypto sector.
 
 
However, this newfound popularity has had a negative consequence, as it has resulted in a noticeable increase in the average transaction fees on the Bitcoin network. The introduction of the Ordinals concept on the Monero blockchain network received mixed reactions.
 
While a few individuals…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>anushsamal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Exploit Sanctioned Crypto Mixer Tornado Cash, Unleashing Chaos]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750eed43db</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/hackers-exploit-sanctioned-mixer-tornado-cash/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-21T12:59:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an unexpected turn of events, Tornado Cash, a prominent service enabling users to obfuscate cryptocurrency transactions, has fallen victim to a hostile takeover by hackers through a malicious governance proposal. 
 
Following the attack, Binance temporarily suspended the deposits of the protocol’s governance token, TORN. The attack, which allowed the hackers to gain full control over the protocol, has raised concerns about the security and integrity of decentralized systems.
 
Governance Takeover Unleashes Chaos
 
Security researcher Samczsun from Paradigm, a renowned crypto investment firm, revealed on Twitter that the attacker manipulated the governance mechanism, granting themselves a staggering 1.2 million fraudulent votes. 
 
Surpassing the 700,000 legitimate votes, this exploit ha…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monero Community Expresses Privacy Concerns And Criticizes ‘Mordinals’]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18395222/Monero-Community-Expresses-Privacy-Concerns-And-Criticizes-Mordinals</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18395222/Monero-Community-Expresses-Privacy-Concerns-And-Criticizes-Mordinals"/>
        <updated>2023-05-21T12:58:15.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Exploit Sanctioned Crypto Mixer Tornado Cash, Unleashing Chaos]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18395223/Hackers-Exploit-Sanctioned-Crypto-Mixer-Tornado-Cash-Unleashing-Chaos</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18395223/Hackers-Exploit-Sanctioned-Crypto-Mixer-Tornado-Cash-Unleashing-Chaos"/>
        <updated>2023-05-21T12:53:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an unexpected turn of events, Tornado Cash, a prominent service enabling users to obfuscate cryptocurrency transactions, has fallen victim to a hostile takeover by hackers through a malicious governance proposal. Following the attack, Binance temporarily suspended the deposits of the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hidden crypto holdings turn divorce battles into high-stakes cases, attorneys warn]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18395211/Hidden-crypto-holdings-turn-divorce-battles-into-high-stakes-cases-attorneys-warn</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18395211/Hidden-crypto-holdings-turn-divorce-battles-into-high-stakes-cases-attorneys-warn"/>
        <updated>2023-05-21T12:38:35.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Inferno Drainer’ Scam Sees Nearly $6 Million In Crypto Stolen]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750ee82bc0</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/inferno-drainer-scam-sees-nearly-6-million-in-crypto-stolen/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-21T12:28:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new scam dubbed the “Inferno Drainer,” has successfully siphoned off approximately $6 million from unsuspecting cryptocurrency users.
 
Scam Sniffer, a reputable company that monitors web-based fraudulent activities, uncovered this alarming trend, shedding light on the evolving landscape of scams targeting the crypto community.
 
Details Of The Scam
 
The Inferno Drainer offers fraudsters readily available code that enables them to steal cryptocurrencies, in exchange for a significant share, typically around 20%, of the ill-gotten gains.
 
 
Scammers, targeting unsuspecting crypto holders, employ this scam-as-a-service model, resulting in substantial losses for victims who fall prey to their deceptive tactics.
 
 
1/ Inferno Drainer, a scam vendor specializing in multi-chain scams, has s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dalmas Ngetich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Inferno Drainer’ Scam Sees Nearly $6 Million In Crypto Stolen]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18395125/Inferno-Drainer-Scam-Sees-Nearly-6-Million-In-Crypto-Stolen</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18395125/Inferno-Drainer-Scam-Sees-Nearly-6-Million-In-Crypto-Stolen"/>
        <updated>2023-05-21T12:28:03.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple vs. SEC: Here’s why it could be “game over” for SEC in XRP case]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18395126/Ripple-vs-SEC-Heres-why-it-could-be-game-over-for-SEC-in-XRP-case</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18395126/Ripple-vs-SEC-Heres-why-it-could-be-game-over-for-SEC-in-XRP-case"/>
        <updated>2023-05-21T12:20:49.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Legal Battle Brews: EOS Network vs. Block.one Over $1B Investment Commitment]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18395217/Legal-Battle-Brews-EOS-Network-vs-Blockone-Over-1B-Investment-Commitment</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18395217/Legal-Battle-Brews-EOS-Network-vs-Blockone-Over-1B-Investment-Commitment"/>
        <updated>2023-05-21T12:18:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The EOS Network Foundation has called out Block.one for not living up to a 2018 promise to invest a billion dollars in the EOS ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Ordinals and BRC20 Tokens are Driving Bitcoin Layer 2 Development]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18395116/Why-Ordinals-and-BRC20-Tokens-are-Driving-Bitcoin-Layer-2-Development</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18395116/Why-Ordinals-and-BRC20-Tokens-are-Driving-Bitcoin-Layer-2-Development"/>
        <updated>2023-05-21T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano Creator Charles Hoskinson Comments on Ledger Wallet Controversy, Says Social Contracts Shouldn’t Be Broken]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18395093/Cardano-Creator-Charles-Hoskinson-Comments-on-Ledger-Wallet-Controversy-Says-Social-Contracts-Shouldnt-Be-Broken</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18395093/Cardano-Creator-Charles-Hoskinson-Comments-on-Ledger-Wallet-Controversy-Says-Social-Contracts-Shouldnt-Be-Broken"/>
        <updated>2023-05-21T11:45:14.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Africa and Asia-Focused Fintech Jia Raises $4.3 Million in Seed Funding Round]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750ed4834e</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/africa-and-asia-focused-fintech-jia-raises-4-3-million-in-seed-funding-round/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-21T11:42:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jia, a blockchain fintech startup, recently revealed it has raised $4.3 million in a seed funding round which was led by the early-stage consumer crypto fund TCG Crypto. Jia has said it will use the funds raised to bolster its Kenyan and Philippines operations. Later, Jia will also use the capital raised to fund the exploration of new markets. 
 
Affordable Financing for Small Businesses
 
Jia, an Africa and Asia-focused blockchain fintech, recently raised $4.3 million in seed funding plus an additional $1 million for onchain liquidity. According to a Techcrunch report, TCG Crypto, an early-stage consumer crypto fund, led the round.
 
Also participating in the round were Blocktower, Hashed Emergent, Saison Capital and Global Coin Research. Angel investors that participated in the round inc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Gold Still The Best Insurance Against Corruption and Incompetence, Says Kiyosaki]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18395072/Bitcoin-Gold-Still-The-Best-Insurance-Against-Corruption-and-Incompetence-Says-Kiyosaki</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18395072/Bitcoin-Gold-Still-The-Best-Insurance-Against-Corruption-and-Incompetence-Says-Kiyosaki"/>
        <updated>2023-05-21T11:15:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The author of Rich Dad, Poor Dad had some harsh words against US President Joe Biden.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano-Based DEX Performs Swaps In Minutes Now]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18395064/Cardano-Based-DEX-Performs-Swaps-In-Minutes-Now</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18395064/Cardano-Based-DEX-Performs-Swaps-In-Minutes-Now"/>
        <updated>2023-05-21T11:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These US Presidential Candidates Are Accepting Bitcoin (BTC) Donations]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18395069/These-US-Presidential-Candidates-Are-Accepting-Bitcoin-BTC-Donations</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18395069/These-US-Presidential-Candidates-Are-Accepting-Bitcoin-BTC-Donations"/>
        <updated>2023-05-21T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Partner In Brazil Granted Payment Institution License]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750ed27bf8</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/binance-partner-in-brazil-obtains-payment-license/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-21T10:38:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Latam Gateway, Binance’s payment provider in Brazil, has earned a license from the Central Bank of Brazil to serve as a payment institution and electronic money issuer in the country. With Brazil as one of Binance’s biggest markets, this approval represents a move in the right direction for one of crypto’s major players.
 
 
Latam Gateway Gains Central Bank Approval In Brazil 
 
On Friday, May 19, a wave of positivity rippled through the Brazilian financial industry as Latam Gateway was granted a license to operate as a payment institution and electronic currency issuer. This was also considered good news for the cryptocurrency sector, considering the relationship between Latam Gateway and the world’s largest crypto exchange, Binance.
 
Binance Exchange and Latam Gateway first became partn…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Opeyemi Sule</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OKX Maintains Support Of Bitcoin Ordinals, Lists Major BRC-20 Token]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750ede8cc5</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/okx-support-bitcoin-ordinals-lists-major-brc-20/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-21T09:55:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prominent cryptocurrency exchange OKX is gaining attention for its commitment to Bitcoin Ordinals and BRC-20 tokens in recent times. In its latest show of support, the Seychelles-based company and world’s second-largest crypto exchange by trading volume just announced the listing of a major BRC-20 token driving much excitement across the entire Bitcoin community.
 
 
OKX Lists Premier BRC-20 Token ORDI
 
Through a press release on Friday, May 20, OKX announced its platform is one of the first exchanges to list the premier and biggest BRC-20 token, ORDI. 
 
Originally launched as a meme coin in March, ORDI has maintained its position as the most successful BRC-20 project with an impressive market cap of over $272 million, according to data by CoinMarketCap. 
 
According to its press stateme…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Semilore Faleti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russia Involved in De-Dollarization Talks With the Islamic World to Create Independent Financial System]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750edfaaaf</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/russia-involved-in-de-dollarization-talks-with-the-islamic-world-to-create-independent-financial-system/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-21T09:43:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Russia and the Islamic world are currently discussing how to deepen the de-dollarization agenda to create a new financial system. According to statements from Russian Deputy Prime Minister Alexey Overchuk, these topics are inscribed in broader deglobalization talks, and the Russian government is invested in developing these issues with Islamic countries.
Russia Talks De-Dollarization With Islamic Nations
Russia is veering to the east in order to build a less polarized world and is currently involved in talks about de-dollarization and the construction of a new financial system away from the dominance of the traditional hegemonies. According to Russian Deputy Prime Minister Alexey Overchuk, the Russian Federation is currently in broad talks with the Islamic world that include these subjects…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Attacker Takes Over Tornado Cash DAO With Vote Fraud, Token Slumps 40%]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750ec5012d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/05/21/attacker-takes-over-tornado-cash-dao-with-vote-fraud-token-slumps-40/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-21T08:45:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A malicious proposal allowed an unidentified attacker to take over Tornado Cash, opening up the floodgates to a potential treasury drain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Luxury Auction House Sotheby’s Sells Portion of 3AC’s NFT Collection for $2.5 Million]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750ec2b1dd</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/luxury-auction-house-sothebys-sells-portion-of-3acs-nft-collection-for-2-5-million/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-21T07:40:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sotheby’s, the luxury auction house, successfully generated $2.5 million through the sale of non-fungible tokens (NFTs) from the now-defunct crypto hedge fund Three Arrows Capital (3AC). Among the sold pieces was Fidenza #725, a digital collectible crafted by the artist Tyler Hobbs. This Fidenza #725 NFT commanded an auction price of over $1 million during Sotheby’s Contemporary Day Sale.
 
Sotheby’s Brings in $2.5 Million From 3AC’s NFT Collection
 
On May 19, 2023, Sotheby’s auction unveiled the sales figures for the NFT collection of Three Arrows Capital (3AC), a now-bankrupt Singaporean crypto hedge fund, with a total of $2.5 million. Sotheby’s took to Twitter on Friday afternoon to announce that Tyler Hobbs’ Fidenza #725 NFT fetched $1,016,000, nearly five times the high estimate. The…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Apple and Google Are Systemic Risks to Crypto,’ Says Ex-Coinbase CTO]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750eb4b97f</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/apple-and-google-are-systemic-risks-to-crypto-says-ex-coinbase-cto/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-21T05:38:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authorities in the U.S. and elsewhere may try to compel tech firms like Apple and Google to exfiltrate private keys from devices and apps under their control, crypto entrepreneur Balaji Srinivasan warned on social media. The former executive of Coinbase believes this would be done to remit funds to cash-hungry governments.
 
Tech Giants Apple, Google Could Extract Private Keys From iPhone and Android Devices, Srinivasan Fears
 
If having sufficient bitcoin becomes the most important political issue in the coming years, bankrupt governments may attempt to get hold of some of people’s crypto, according to Balaji Srinivasan, former chief technology officer (CTO) at crypto exchange Coinbase.
 
While a conventional 51% attack through mining isn’t something the U.S. could easily pull off now, it…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lubomir Tassev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK Lawmakers Call for Crypto Trading to Be Regulated as Gambling]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750ebd352d</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/uk-lawmakers-call-for-crypto-trading-to-be-regulated-as-gambling/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-21T03:39:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A committee of British lawmakers has recommended regulating crypto trading as gambling. Viewing retail trading of cryptocurrencies as more akin to gambling rather than a financial service, the U.K. Treasury Committee stated that “Cryptocurrencies such as bitcoin have no intrinsic value and serve no useful social purpose, while consuming large amounts of energy and being used by criminals in scams, fraud, and money laundering.”
 
UK Lawmakers Propose Regulating Crypto Like Gambling
 
The U.K. Parliament announced Wednesday that the Treasury Committee has called for “consumer trading in unbacked crypto to be regulated as gambling.” The Treasury Committee is appointed by the House of Commons to examine the expenditure, administration, and policy of HM Treasury, HM Revenue and Customs, and ass…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Renowned Investor Jim Rogers Warns US Dollar’s Time ‘Coming to an End’ as Countries Seek Alternatives]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750ea5028a</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/renowned-investor-jim-rogers-warns-us-dollars-time-coming-to-an-end-as-countries-seek-alternatives/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-21T01:36:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Veteran investor Jim Rogers, who co-founded the Quantum Fund with billionaire investor George Soros, says the U.S. dollar’s time is coming to an end as more countries are seeking alternatives to the USD. “Many friends of America are moving, trying to find something to compete with and ultimately replace the U.S. dollar. It will happen. It has always happened,” he warned.
 
‘American Dollar’s Time Is Coming to an End,’ Says Rogers
 
Famed investor Jim Rogers shared why he expects the U.S. dollar to lose its status as the world’s reserve currency in an interview with Sputnik, published Wednesday. Rogers is George Soros’ former business partner who co-founded the Quantum Fund and Soros Fund Management.
 
“Many friends of America are moving, trying to find something to compete with and ultimat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zoltan Pozsar, Who Just Left Credit Suisse, Addresses Issues Facing The Federal Reserve And The Dollar At Bitcoin 2023]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750ea51c7c</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/markets/zoltan-pozsar-on-bitcoin-financial-system"/>
        <updated>2023-05-21T01:34:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zoltan Pozsar, who until recently worked as the managing director of investment bank Credit Suisse, offered his insight into financial markets and the issues that are weakening the dollar’s dominance around the world.
In his role at Credit Suisse, Pozsar’s insight into the ins and outs of the legacy financial system and market dynamics was highly sought after. His recent departure from the bank came shortly after it was purchased by UBS in March as an attempt to keep it from collapsing amid existential turmoil for banks around the world. On stage at Bitcoin 2023, Pozsar addressed how U.S. banks have been impacted.
"This is basically an episode where the large banks are largely insulated from the problems," Pozsar said. "It's basically lessons in not being able to run interest rate risk, no…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Chawaga</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robert Kiyosaki: US Economy Headed for Crash Landing, Financial Pandemic Started, Corruption High]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750eac12c4</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/robert-kiyosaki-us-economy-headed-for-crash-landing-financial-pandemic-started-corruption-high/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-20T23:44:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rich Dad Poor Dad author Robert Kiyosaki believes that the U.S. economy is headed for a crash landing. “I hope I am wrong yet that is what I believe,” he opined. The famous author also said a financial pandemic has started and corruption is high, reiterating his recommendation to buy gold, silver, and bitcoin. 
 
Robert Kiyosaki Believes a Crash Landing Is Coming
 

 
The author of Rich Dad Poor Dad, Robert Kiyosaki, is back with more warnings about the U.S. economy. Rich Dad Poor Dad is a 1997 book co-authored by Kiyosaki and Sharon Lechter. It has been on the New York Times Best Seller List for over six years. More than 32 million copies of the book have been sold in over 51 languages across more than 109 countries. Kiyosaki tweeted Thursday:
 

Soft landing? Hard landing? Or Crash landi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The World’s Largest Bitcoin Conference Will Take Place In Nashville For 2024]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750ea8a8c1</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/industry-events/worlds-largest-bitcoin-conference-will-take-place-in-nashville-for-2024"/>
        <updated>2023-05-20T22:35:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Disclaimer: The Bitcoin Conference and Bitcoin Magazine are both operated by BTC Inc.
The Bitcoin Conference, the world's largest and most prestigious gathering of the Bitcoin industry, is set to take place in Nashville, Tennessee, from July 25-27, 2024. The decision to move the conference to Nashville underscores the organizers' efforts to promote Bitcoin adoption beyond traditional financial centers. With a focus on fostering local adoption, the conference aims to unite thought leaders, industry experts and businesses in exploring the limitless possibilities presented by Bitcoin.
David Bailey, CEO of Bitcoin Magazine, expressed his optimism about Nashville's potential for Bitcoin growth, stating, "We believe that Nashville possesses the ideal blend of freedom-loving mindset and entrepren…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BtcCasey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BRICS, Eurasian Economic Union, SCO Members Plan to Discuss Forming an Extensive Alliance]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750e94d5a9</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/brics-eurasian-union-sco-members-discuss-forming-extensive-alliance/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-20T21:35:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In four days, representatives from the BRICS nations and the Eurasian Economic Union free trade group are set to convene to explore the possibility of integration with the Shanghai Cooperation Organization (SCO), as revealed by a recent russia-briefing.com report. The report emphasizes the formation of a vast Eurasian regional alliance that excludes Western involvement, with the aim of fostering greater collaboration and “reformatting the global economic architecture.”
 
BRICS, EAEU, SCO to Discuss Moving Beyond Western Boundaries
 
Russia Briefing, in its May 17, 2023 publication, unveiled an interesting development involving the convergence of several prominent nations. The leaders of the BRICS nations — Brazil, Russia, India, China, and South Africa — are scheduled to convene with polic…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pudgy Penguins Smash Amazon Debut, Sells Over 20,000 Toys]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140825</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140825/pudgy-penguins-phygital-toys-amazon-sales"/>
        <updated>2023-05-20T21:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The “Phygital” toy collection brings in half a million dollars in sales in two days.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: SEC and CBDC News Drives XRP Rally During Slow Week]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140820</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140820/bitcoin-ethereum-xrp-sec-cbdc-update"/>
        <updated>2023-05-20T18:41:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the third week running, the prices of most leading cryptocurrencies didn’t move much.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gary Vee Is Hyped About AI—And Expands VeeCon Beyond NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140781</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140781/gary-vee-veecon-ai-nft-web3-business-conference"/>
        <updated>2023-05-20T18:14:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With VeeCon 2023 underway, Gary Vaynerchuk joins Decrypt to discuss the rise of AI and his take on the volatile NFT market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gary Vee Discusses the Rise and Impact of AI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/E2erJr3t/gary-vee-discusses-the-rise-and-impact-of-ai</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/E2erJr3t/gary-vee-discusses-the-rise-and-impact-of-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-05-20T16:46:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During VeeCon 2023, entrepreneur spoke with Decrypt's Andrew Hayward about the rise of AI tools, what excites him about the technology, and what kind of impact he thinks it will have on creators and business.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meme Tokens and NFTs Took Over Bitcoin—Now It's Happening on Dogecoin and Litecoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140683</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140683/meme-tokens-nfts-took-over-bitcoin-now-happening-dogecoin-litecoin"/>
        <updated>2023-05-20T13:27:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ordinals hype has spread from Bitcoin to both Dogecoin and Litecoin, driving network activity on all three chains to recent all-time peaks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi Heavyweight Lido Finance Mulls LDO Staking, Token Buyback]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140716</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140716/defi-heavyweight-lido-finance-mulls-ldo-staking-token-buyback"/>
        <updated>2023-05-20T10:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Liquid staking protocol Lido Finance is looking to add a bit more utility to what is just a simple voting token. Here's how LDO could change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Bans Employees From Using ChatGPT Over AI Privacy Fears: WSJ]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140750</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140750/apple-bans-employees-using-chatgpt-over-ai-privacy-fears-wsj"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T22:22:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tech giant Apple reportedly restricted internal use of the AI chatbot over data leak concerns, joining Samsung and other corporate giants.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robert F. Kennedy Jr. Says COVID Protests Led Him to Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140788</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140788/robert-f-kennedy-jr-rfk-covid-protests-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T22:01:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RFK Jr. is deep down the Bitcoin rabbit hole—and it was the vaccine-mandate protests in Canada that got him started down the path.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet the Dudes Using AI Chatbots to Get Real Dates]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140648</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140648/meet-dudes-ai-chatbots-chatgpt-dates"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T21:09:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Can ChatGPT help you find your significant other? Some guys are definitely scoring.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gary Vee Discusses VeeCon 2023's Broader Shift Beyond Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/FqIm7PfV/gary-vee-discusses-veecon-2023s-broader-shift-beyond-web3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/FqIm7PfV/gary-vee-discusses-veecon-2023s-broader-shift-beyond-web3"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T20:25:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VeeCon is back in 2023, moving from Minneapolis to Indianapolis, and creator and entrepreneur Gary Vaynerchuk joined Decrypt's Andrew Hayward to discuss his aim to make it the "coolest business conference in the world." And that means expanding the focus beyond NFTs and Web3 to include AI and other tech innovations, along with broader business and pop culture content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gary Vee on the NFT Market and Why 'NFTs Are Stuffed Animals']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Sij5GHus/gary-vee-on-the-nft-market-and-why-nfts-are-stuffed-animals</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Sij5GHus/gary-vee-on-the-nft-market-and-why-nfts-are-stuffed-animals"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T20:25:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gary Vaynerchuk called the NFT market decline back in 2021, but the owner of CryptoPunks and other valuable tokenized assets still believes that a sustainable market will eventually form. He joins Decrypt's Andrew Hayward amid VeeCon 2023 to discuss why he thinks the NFT space will be comparable to collectible sports cards, art, and even stuffed animals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Immutable's Chris Clay Learned in 23 Years of Game Development]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/lpOWjBfU/what-immutables-chris-clay-learned-in-23-years-of-game-development</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/lpOWjBfU/what-immutables-chris-clay-learned-in-23-years-of-game-development"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T20:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Immutable VP & Gods Unchained Game Director Chris Clay tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about what it's like to work in the game industry for decades and why he's not giving up on NFT games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Las Vegas Man Charged in CoinDeal $45M Crypto Fraud Case]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140749</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140749/las-vegas-man-charged-in-coindeal-45m-crypto-fraud-case"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T20:05:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Las Vegas man has been hit with new charges as part of the CoinDeal crypto and metaverse alleged scam—and could face up to 100 years behind bars.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden's 30% Tax on Bitcoin Miners 'Isn't Going to Happen,' Says Cynthia Lummis]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140751</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140751/bitcoin-miner-30-excise-tax-isnt-going-to-happen-says-cynthia-lummis"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T19:11:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto legislation has been hard to work on due to "fear that Bitcoin and cryptocurrencies are being used for criminal activities,” Lummis said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another CertiK Audited Project Rugs as $3M Disappears From Arbitrum DeFi Exchange]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140744</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140744/certik-taking-heat-as-another-project-it-audited-swaprum-gets-rugged"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T18:34:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The team behind Swaprum appears to have disappeared with $3 million in customer funds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your Old Game Boy Can Now Be Turned Into a Bitcoin and Ethereum Hardware Wallet]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140730</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140730/old-game-boy-could-next-bitcoin-ethereum-wallet"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T17:46:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto startup Keyp is creating an offline crypto storage solution with a Game Boy cartridge that gamifies the seed phrase process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deadfellaz NFT Owners Can Now Use Their Avatars in Twitch Streams]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140684</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140684/now-deadfellaz-owners-can-appear-as-their-nft-avatar-in-livestreams-video-calls"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T16:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ethereum project just launched Streamingfellaz, letting NFT holders appear as their zombified avatars on streams and video calls.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi Projects Built on Ethereum Scaling Solution Starknet Hit $10M]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140703</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140703/defi-projects-built-ethereum-scaling-solution-starknet-hit-10m"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T13:13:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The total value locked in smart contracts using the Ethereum Layer-2 scaling solution has just hit an all-time high of over $10 million.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoin Issuers Pour Money Into DC as Crypto Legislation Hits Agendas]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140698</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140698/stablecoin-issuers-pour-money-dc-crypto-legislation-hits-agendas"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T11:36:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoin issuers Tether and Circle have been regularly paying lobbyists to stay on top of possible regulations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alys Key</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['So Much Anger, So Much Hate', Says Ledger Co-Founder Amid Botched Recover Service Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140692</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140692/so-much-anger-so-much-hate-says-ledger-co-founder-amid-botched-recover-service-launch"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T11:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After Crypto Twitter took Ledger to the chopping block over its Recover service, the firm’s co-founder took to Reddit to explain his views]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Australia’s Stock Exchange ASX Axes Blockchain Initiative—for Good]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140689</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140689/australias-stock-exchange-asx-axes-blockchain-initiative-good"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T10:16:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The leading stock exchange Downunder no longer considers blockchain among possible technologies for its trading software upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Finally Launches Subscription Service Overseas, Focuses on Staking]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140661</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140661/coinbase-finally-launches-subscription-service-focuses-on-staking"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T01:01:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The exchange has launched Coinbase One—and is accelerating its push overseas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy Looking at Bitcoin Ordinals for App Development, Says Michael Saylor]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140670</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140670/microstrategy-looking-at-bitcoin-ordinals-for-app-development-says-michael-saylor"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T00:57:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Right now, enterprises have weak security compared to Bitcoin,” Saylor told Decrypt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beeple, Bitboy, and a 'Dumping' Bored Ape: How It All Hit the Fan]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140664</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140664/beeple-bitboy-dumping-bored-ape-how-all-hit-fan"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T00:38:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Famed digital artist Beeple waded into a Crypto Twitter mess centered on influencer Bitboy’s relationship to a controversial meme token.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jack Dorsey Leads $6 Million Raise for Bitcoin Payments Company Azteco]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140657</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140657/jack-dorsey-leads-6-million-raise-bitcoin-payments-company-azteco"/>
        <updated>2023-05-18T21:29:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Block CEO and former Twitter CEO Jack Dorsey, a noted Bitcoin aficionado, led the round for a startup focused on redeemable Bitcoin vouchers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alyssa Hertig</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Companies Must Provide 'Proof of Reserves' in Texas]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140647</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140647/texas-proof-of-reserves-for-crypto-exchanges"/>
        <updated>2023-05-18T20:26:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto exchanges with Texas customers have to provide "proof of reserves" and make sure customers funds can always be "fully withdrawn."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin 2023 Attendees in Miami Blame Bear Market Vibes for Lower Attendance]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140595</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140595/bitcoin-2023-in-miami-bear-market-lower-attendance"/>
        <updated>2023-05-18T19:45:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day one attendees said they expect crowds to look less sparse tomorrow, when general admission pass holders show up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Litecoin Activity Hits All-Time High Thanks to Ordinals Mania]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140608</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140608/litecoin-experiences-highest-blockchain-activity-thanks-to-ordinals"/>
        <updated>2023-05-18T18:55:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The blockchain is being used to mint Ordinals following Bitcoin congestion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI Debuts ChatGPT App for Apple iPhone, Says Android Coming Soon]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140609</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140609/openai-launches-chatgpt-app-for-apple-iphone"/>
        <updated>2023-05-18T18:12:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI launches free iOS ChatGPT app, enabling history sync and GPT-4 access for Plus subscribers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Custody Services Are Coming to Custodia Bank, Says CEO Caitlin Long]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140603</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140603/bitcoin-custody-services-are-coming-to-custodia-bank-says-ceo-caitlin-long"/>
        <updated>2023-05-18T17:25:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Custodia Bank CEO said she, a hardcore Bitcoiner, started a bank because the world isn't ready for "hyperbitcoinization” yet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Azra Games CEO Mark Otero is Not a Fan of "Play-to-Earn" Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/F08xddFc/why-azra-games-ceo-mark-otero-is-not-a-fan-of-play-to-earn-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/F08xddFc/why-azra-games-ceo-mark-otero-is-not-a-fan-of-play-to-earn-games"/>
        <updated>2023-05-18T16:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Each game is a miracle," says Azra Games CEO Mark Otero. In this clip, he shares his thoughts on "play-to-earn" games and gamer motivation with Decrypt's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFT Lending Platform Blend Surges Past 100,000 Ethereum in Total Volume]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140599</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140599/nft-lending-platform-blend-surges-past-100000-ethereum-total-volume"/>
        <updated>2023-05-18T15:23:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After adding two blue-chip NFT collections, Blend strengthened its market-leading position, just weeks after its launch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Europe a 'Significant Beneficiary' of US Crypto Regulatory Confusion: Ripple CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140587</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140587/europe-significant-beneficiary-us-crypto-regulatory-confusion-ripple-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-05-18T14:42:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With regulators stateside still scrambling to rein in the industry, rule makers in Europe, notably in France, are extending invitations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFT Artist and Collector OSF: 'NFTs Are Just a Medium']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140569</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140569/nft-artist-and-collector-osf-nfts-are-just-a-medium"/>
        <updated>2023-05-18T14:08:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The House of Fine Art gallery is playing host to an exhibition of pioneering NFT artists—but the word “NFT” is nowhere to be seen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Rolls Out CBDC Platform for Governments, Financial Institutions]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140584</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140584/ripple-cbdc-launching-platform-governments-financial-institutions"/>
        <updated>2023-05-18T13:28:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto firm Ripple is pushing further into the CBDC game, unveiling a new platform for creating blockchain-based digital currencies]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Australia Loses Crypto Ramp PayID ‘With Immediate Effect’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140559</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140559/binance-australia-loses-crypto-ramp-payid-immediate-effect"/>
        <updated>2023-05-18T11:18:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Australia has had to suspend PayID AUD deposits due to a decision by a third-party service provider.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi Token Synthetix Soars 10% as Community Mulls PEPE Market Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140551</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140551/defi-token-synthetix-soars-community-mulls-pepe-market-launch"/>
        <updated>2023-05-18T10:03:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SNX surged overnight as the Synthetix community weighs integrating the popular meme cryptocurrency PEPE into its DeFi offering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bankrupt Crypto Broker Voyager Cleared to Repay $1.3B to Creditors]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140547</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140547/bankrupt-crypto-broker-voyager-cleared-repay-creditors"/>
        <updated>2023-05-18T09:45:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Voyager said the initial payments will be made either in crypto through the Voyager app or in cash after a waiting period of 30 days.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gala Games Burns Over $600 Million Worth of GALA Tokens]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140539</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140539/gala-games-burns-over-600-million-worth-gala-tokens"/>
        <updated>2023-05-18T01:56:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 startup Gala Games said that it has virtually depleted its own treasury to alleviate concerns of a future token selloff.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adidas Web3 Lead Thought She ‘Could Get Fired’ for Signing Bored Ape Deal]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140527</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140527/adidas-web3-lead-thought-could-fired-signing-bored-ape-deal"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T23:13:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Erika Wykes-Sneyd joins Decrypt’s gm podcast to discuss how apparel giant Adidas approaches NFTs and emerging culture alike.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seizing Upon Ledger Stumble, Hardware Wallet Competitors Offer Discounts]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140520</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140520/ledger-recover-competitors-trezor-cold-card-blockstream-jade"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T21:57:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BitBox, Cold Card, Trezor and Blockstream all announced sale prices on their cold storage devices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Most Americans Consider AI a Threat to Humanity, New Poll Finds]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140515</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140515/most-americans-see-artificial-intelligence-as-a-threat-new-poll-finds"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T21:43:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Reuters/Ipsos poll shows that 61% of Americans believe AI to be a threat to humanity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Many Games Are Building On Solana? The Answer Might Surprise You]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/WV6HegEv/how-many-games-are-building-on-solana-the-answer-might-surprise-you</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/WV6HegEv/how-many-games-are-building-on-solana-the-answer-might-surprise-you"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T16:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Games General Manager Johnny Lee tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the current state of Solana's Web3 gaming ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Problems With Being an 'On-Chain Purist'  in Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/uOwArY6a/problems-with-being-an-on-chain-purist-in-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/uOwArY6a/problems-with-being-an-on-chain-purist-in-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T15:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[InfiniGods Cofounders Owen O'Donoghue and Damon Gura keep it real with Decrypt's Kate Irwin, sharing thoughts on game balancing and what to do when in-game assets become NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Solana Won't Become A Web3 Game Publisher]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/RgSzjeSw/why-solana-wont-become-a-web3-game-publisher</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/RgSzjeSw/why-solana-wont-become-a-web3-game-publisher"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T16:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Foundation's Games General Manager Johnny Lee tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about Solana's "build together" approach as well as his thoughts on crypto firms becoming game publishers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The State Of Web3 Gaming On Hedera]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/7TTEckkZ/the-state-of-web3-gaming-on-hedera</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/7TTEckkZ/the-state-of-web3-gaming-on-hedera"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T14:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hedera VP Alex Russman tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about Hedera's Web3 gaming ecosystem and shares a game he's particularly excited about.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Mirandus is Innovating Video Game Audio]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kLHZIUsl/how-mirandus-is-innovating-video-game-audio</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kLHZIUsl/how-mirandus-is-innovating-video-game-audio"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T20:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mirandus' Lead Developer and Gala Games Cofounder Michael McCarthy tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the game's thoughtful approach to audio design and the technologies being built to support the MMORPG's immersive world.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do Gamers Hate NFTs?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/X0FtIw0j/do-gamers-hate-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/X0FtIw0j/do-gamers-hate-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin asks the InfiniGods developers Damon Gura and Owen O’Donoghue about gamers and NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: Avenged Sevenfold's M. Shadows on Deathbats, Fandom, and AI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JEgr9COw/gm-avenged-sevenfolds-m-shadows-on-deathbats-fandom-and-ai</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JEgr9COw/gm-avenged-sevenfolds-m-shadows-on-deathbats-fandom-and-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T20:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avenged Sevenfold lead singer Matt Sanders, aka M. Shadows, is rehearsing for the band's upcoming tour. He's also figuring out how to upend what it means to be a music fan. The band launched a Deathbats Club NFT collection in 2021. That is to say: They were early. The lead singer said it was timed to give fans a chance to get comfortable with Web3 technology ahead of the group's 2023 tour, when the NFT holders can use their Deathbats for early access to tickets. M. Shadows also talked to hosts Andrew Hayward and Stephen Graves about AI and bringing Web3 into gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Mojo Melee's Lore with Creator Mike Levine and Art Director Eric Campanella]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BfIB2H5e/inside-mojo-melees-lore-with-creator-mike-levine-and-art-director-eric-campanella</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BfIB2H5e/inside-mojo-melees-lore-with-creator-mike-levine-and-art-director-eric-campanella"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T22:29:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the Game Developers' Conference, Mojo Melee Creator Mike Levine and Art Director Eric Campanella tell Decrypt's Kate Irwin about their autobattler game and its unique characters, which are also NFTs on Polygon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why 'Blair Witch' Exec Producer Kevin Foxe Is '1,000% In' on Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZXj16C8r/why-blair-witch-exec-producer-kevin-foxe-is-1-000-in-on-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZXj16C8r/why-blair-witch-exec-producer-kevin-foxe-is-1-000-in-on-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T23:02:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["The Blair Witch Project" Executive Producer Kevin Foxe wants to avoid corporate overlords and enlighten fans of the dark "Mandala" graphic novel with a video game adaptation and NFTs across multiple blockchains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gala Games Co-Founder on the Aesthetic of Mirandus]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/1bQV1R6l/gala-games-co-founder-on-the-aesthetic-of-mirandus</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/1bQV1R6l/gala-games-co-founder-on-the-aesthetic-of-mirandus"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T14:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["When assets are overdone, they just feel a little dirty. It's not pretty to look at," shared Mirandus' Lead Developer and Gala Games co-founder Michael McCarthy in an interview with Decrypt's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Games GM: Play-to-Earn Games Are DeFi Products, Not Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yp7btQtl/solana-games-gm-play-to-earn-games-are-defi-products-not-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yp7btQtl/solana-games-gm-play-to-earn-games-are-defi-products-not-games"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T16:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Games' General Manager Johnny Lee offers a hot take on the first generation of Web3 gaming with Decrypt's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brycent's Advice For Gaming Content Creators]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/o19nZCeN/brycents-advice-for-gaming-content-creators</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/o19nZCeN/brycents-advice-for-gaming-content-creators"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T20:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XSET's Brycent shares his advice for Web3 content creators with Decrypt's Kate Irwin, including which social media platform is best for posting content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Behind the Scenes of Jeremy Cowart's 'Auras' NFT Event]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/C0ZeidQg/behind-the-scenes-of-jeremy-cowarts-auras-nft-event</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/C0ZeidQg/behind-the-scenes-of-jeremy-cowarts-auras-nft-event"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T22:54:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A look at the preparation behind "Auras," an event in which photographer Jeremy Cowart produced and starred in 10,000 photo-based NFTs, captured in less than 30 minutes before a live audience. Credit: Brett Carlsen for Decrypt]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jeremy Cowart Discusses 'Auras' Event, Live-Shooting 10,000 Photo NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/E3ViHsPd/jeremy-cowart-discusses-auras-event-live-shooting-10-000-photo-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/E3ViHsPd/jeremy-cowart-discusses-auras-event-live-shooting-10-000-photo-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T18:32:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jeremy Cowart speaks with Decrypt's Sander Lutz in Nashville ahead of the "Auras" event, in which the noted photographer live-shot 10,000 unique photo-based NFTs in less than 30 minutes. The NFTs will be released through OpenSea on May 9. Video credit: Brett Carlsen for Decrypt]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azra Games CEO on Putting Fun Before Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/03W3KZjM/azra-games-ceo-on-putting-fun-before-web3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/03W3KZjM/azra-games-ceo-on-putting-fun-before-web3"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T14:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["The Web3 interfaces cannot be on the foreground of the player's initial experience," says Azra Games CEO Mark Otero.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>