<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-01-16T16:20:17.679Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-01-16T16:20:17.679Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Exchange Outflows & Inflows Hit Historical Highs, Volatility Soon?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fdd1cec2</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-exchange-outflows-inflows-highs-volatility/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T16:02:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data shows the combined Bitcoin exchange inflow and outflow volume has hit historically significant values, a sign that speculators are active.
 
Bitcoin Exchange Flow Volume Has Spiked To $4.07 Billion
 
According to data from the on-chain analytics firm Glassnode, exchange deposits and withdrawals on the Bitcoin blockchain have recently continued to increase.
 
The relevant indicator here is the “Exchange Flow Volume,” which keeps track of the combined amount of volume flowing into the wallets of all centralized exchanges (that is, the inflows) and that moving out of these platforms (the outflows).
 
 
When the value of this metric rises, it means that the investors are moving large amounts of the cryptocurrency in and out of the exchanges currently. Since holders use these platforms for…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Analyst Implores Users to Dump their ADA Tokens: Here is Why]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19179774/Crypto-Analyst-Implores-Users-to-Dump-their-ADA-Tokens-Here-is-Why</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19179774/Crypto-Analyst-Implores-Users-to-Dump-their-ADA-Tokens-Here-is-Why"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T16:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent post, Anders Helseth, head of research at K33 Research, asked cryptocurrency community members to stay clear of layer-1 blockchain Cardano (ADA). According to Helseth, “the Cardano network’s complete lack of meaningful activity will make the ADA token worthless over time. Helseth...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Institutional Inflows Into XRP Surges 244% Amid ETF Speculation]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19179730/Institutional-Inflows-Into-XRP-Surges-244-Amid-ETF-Speculation</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19179730/Institutional-Inflows-Into-XRP-Surges-244-Amid-ETF-Speculation"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T16:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XRP has reacted positively since the launch of spot Bitcoin ETFs in the US, both in its price and general market sentiment. At the same time, recent data from CoinShares on the weekly inflow into digital asset funds reveal that the positive sentiment flowed into XRP-based investment products,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How ETFs affected BTC futures trading in the U.S.]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19179768/How-ETFs-affected-BTC-futures-trading-in-the-US</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19179768/How-ETFs-affected-BTC-futures-trading-in-the-US"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T16:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The launch of the spot Bitcoin ETFs in the U.S. marked a watershed moment in the crypto industry. While the impact it could have on the global Bitcoin market, like legitimizing it as an asset class or creating more demand, has been analyzed at length, few have focused on its effects on other...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s Ordinal Inscriptions Soar Beyond 55 Million, Achieving Third Highest Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fdd22fa1</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoins-ordinal-inscriptions-soar-beyond-55-million-achieving-third-highest-daily-record/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T16:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following the weekend, the tally of Ordinal inscriptions on the Bitcoin blockchain surpassed 55 million. Notably, on Jan. 13, 2024, the blockchain witnessed its third-highest day of inscriptions, settling an impressive 477,751 inscription-based transactions on Saturday. Additionally, from the inception of the first inscription in December 2022, bitcoin miners have amassed $246 million worth of bitcoin, capitalizing on this growing trend.
 
Miners Net $246 Million From 55 Million Inscriptions
 
From Dec. 28, 2023, to Jan. 12, 2024, the pace of daily Ordinal inscriptions on the Bitcoin blockchain moderately decelerated. However, a surge occurred on Saturday, Jan. 13, marking a record-breaking number of daily inscriptions. This date became the third-largest in terms of inscriptions, with an i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Exchange Outflows & Inflows Hit Historical Highs, Volatility Soon?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19179759/Bitcoin-Exchange-Outflows-Inflows-Hit-Historical-Highs-Volatility-Soon</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19179759/Bitcoin-Exchange-Outflows-Inflows-Hit-Historical-Highs-Volatility-Soon"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T16:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data shows the combined Bitcoin exchange inflow and outflow volume has hit historically significant values, a sign that speculators are active. Bitcoin Exchange Flow Volume Has Spiked To $4.07 Billion According to data from the on-chain analytics firm Glassnode, exchange deposits and withdrawals...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Bitcoin Halving: Why This Time Could Be Different]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19179710/The-Bitcoin-Halving-Why-This-Time-Could-Be-Different</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19179710/The-Bitcoin-Halving-Why-This-Time-Could-Be-Different"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fourth Bitcoin halving is approaching, and this one has the potential to be a very different experience from prior halvings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale Moves 10,000 Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19179739/Grayscale-Moves-10000-Bitcoin</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19179739/Grayscale-Moves-10000-Bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T15:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) has moved around 10,000 bitcoin today, worth $430 million at the current price.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chainlink and Circle join forces for seamless cross-chain USDC transactions]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19179698/Chainlink-and-Circle-join-forces-for-seamless-cross-chain-USDC-transactions</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19179698/Chainlink-and-Circle-join-forces-for-seamless-cross-chain-USDC-transactions"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T15:47:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chainlink integrates Circle’s CCTP into CCIP, enhancing USDC for cross-chain DeFi transactions. Developers gain tools for secure USDC transfers with CCTP’s permissionless on-chain utility. CCIP’s advanced risk management features bolster security in decentralized applications. In a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hedera Network Enhances Accessibility with MetaMask Integration through Hedera Wallet Snap]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19179700/Hedera-Network-Enhances-Accessibility-with-MetaMask-Integration-through-Hedera-Wallet-Snap</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19179700/Hedera-Network-Enhances-Accessibility-with-MetaMask-Integration-through-Hedera-Wallet-Snap"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T15:43:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Hedera network has announced the launch of the Hedera Wallet Snap. The innovative integration connects Hedera, an open-source, leaderless proof-of-stake network, with MetaMask, a leading cryptocurrency wallet boasting 30 million monthly active users. Developed by Tuum Technologies, a pioneer...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EBA Takes On Crypto Risks: Extends Money Laundering Guidelines to CASPs]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fddee425</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/eba-takes-on-crypto-risks-extends-money-laundering-guidelines-to-casps/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T15:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The European Banking Authority (EBA) has extended its  
guidelines on money laundering (ML) and terrorist financing (TF) risk factors  
to crypto-asset service providers (CASPs). This initiative is significant in the EU's ongoing battle against illicit financial  
activities. As crypto-assets become increasingly susceptible to misuse for  
criminal purposes, the EBA's guidelines aim to equip CASPs with the knowledge  
and tools to identify and effectively mitigate these risks.
The EBA's guidelines shed light on the risks CASPs face, emphasizing factors such as the rapid crypto-asset transfers  
and features that conceal user identities. These risks necessitate a  
comprehensive understanding, prompting the EBA to provide a list  
of factors indicating exposure levels to ML and TF risks. 
C…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Benjamin Cowen Updates Bitcoin Price Forecast, Says Fed Rate Cuts Not As Bullish as Market Expects]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19179648/Benjamin-Cowen-Updates-Bitcoin-Price-Forecast-Says-Fed-Rate-Cuts-Not-As-Bullish-as-Market-Expects</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19179648/Benjamin-Cowen-Updates-Bitcoin-Price-Forecast-Says-Fed-Rate-Cuts-Not-As-Bullish-as-Market-Expects"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T15:30:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto analyst Benjamin Cowen is updating his outlook on Bitcoin (BTC) as investors begin to anticipate the possibility that the Federal Reserve will reverse its tight monetary policies in the coming months. In a new strategy session, Cowen tells his 789,000 YouTube subscribers that when the Fed...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Miner Extractable Value (MEV) and Programmable Money: The Good, The Bad, and The Ugly]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fddf154c</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/technical/miner-extractable-value-mev-and-programmable-money-the-good-the-bad-and-the-ugly"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The core of Bitcoin’s security model relies on this basic game theory—miners, armed with their digital pickaxes, are in a relentless chase for profit. And it’s this pursuit that keeps the network secure. Basic vanilla mining involves producing blocks to earn the block rewards and transaction fees, but have you ever considered that miners might have other ways to extract value from the blockchain beyond this standard mining process? Are there other avenues for profit on the blockchain where miners can leverage their unique position as validators?
What is MEV?
In proof-of-work systems, “Miner Extractable Value” (MEV) is a term that describes the profits miners can earn by manipulating how transactions are prioritized, excluded, rearranged, or altered in the blocks they mine. However, since E…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kiara Bickers</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gold Slides on Uncertain Monetary Policy Path But Downside Remains Limited]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19179667/Gold-Slides-on-Uncertain-Monetary-Policy-Path-But-Downside-Remains-Limited</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19179667/Gold-Slides-on-Uncertain-Monetary-Policy-Path-But-Downside-Remains-Limited"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T15:23:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gold fell over 0.7% on Tuesday amid strengthening dollar and rising yields, as well as uncertain Fed path.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BitMEX moon mission to end with bitcoin burning up on re-entry]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19179645/BitMEX-moon-mission-to-end-with-bitcoin-burning-up-on-re-entry</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19179645/BitMEX-moon-mission-to-end-with-bitcoin-burning-up-on-re-entry"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T15:22:18.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chainlink partners with Circle to enable cross-chain USDC transactions via CCIP]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19179612/Chainlink-partners-with-Circle-to-enable-cross-chain-USDC-transactions-via-CCIP</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19179612/Chainlink-partners-with-Circle-to-enable-cross-chain-USDC-transactions-via-CCIP"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T15:19:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized oracle network Chainlink announced today the integration of Circles Cross-Chain Transfer Protocol (CCTP) with its Chainlink Cross-Chain Interoperability Protocol (CCIP), enabling developers to build secure applications that facilitate the transfer of USDC across multiple blockchain...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[dForce Launches Innovative Grants Program to Propel DeFi Ecosystem Forward]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19179614/dForce-Launches-Innovative-Grants-Program-to-Propel-DeFi-Ecosystem-Forward</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19179614/dForce-Launches-Innovative-Grants-Program-to-Propel-DeFi-Ecosystem-Forward"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T15:17:59.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Founder Supports Elon Musk's Recent Meme Post]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19179620/Dogecoin-Founder-Supports-Elon-Musks-Recent-Meme-Post</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19179620/Dogecoin-Founder-Supports-Elon-Musks-Recent-Meme-Post"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T15:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk’s recent meme tweet has prompted response from one of two Dogecoin founders]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chainlink Teams Up With Circle to Allow Cross-Chain Stablecoin Transfers]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fdd9c4e2</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2024/01/16/chainlink-teams-up-with-circle-to-allow-cross-chain-stablecoin-transfers/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T15:13:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The integration allows developers to build cross-chain use cases via Chainlink's CCIP that involve multichain transfers of Circle's USDC stablecoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lyllah Ledesma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celestia's TIA Token Sets Stage For Potential Gold Rush, Says Crypto Expert]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19179632/Celestias-TIA-Token-Sets-Stage-For-Potential-Gold-Rush-Says-Crypto-Expert</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19179632/Celestias-TIA-Token-Sets-Stage-For-Potential-Gold-Rush-Says-Crypto-Expert"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T15:12:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celestia (CRYPTO: TIA) could go parabolic by the end of this cycle, according to Taiki Maeda, founder and CEO of HFA Re read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anti-Defamation League (ADL) report unmasks how cryptocurrencies are secretly funding hate groups]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19179571/Anti-Defamation-League-ADL-report-unmasks-how-cryptocurrencies-are-secretly-funding-hate-groups</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19179571/Anti-Defamation-League-ADL-report-unmasks-how-cryptocurrencies-are-secretly-funding-hate-groups"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T15:09:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent report by the Anti-Defamation League (ADL), a concerning trend has emerged within the realms of cryptocurrency and extremist funding. The ADL, a renowned New York-based organization dedicated to combating antisemitism and extremism, has highlighted how certain white supremacist...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chainlink integrates with Circle’s CCTP protocol for cross-chain USDC transfers]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19179575/Chainlink-integrates-with-Circles-CCTP-protocol-for-cross-chain-USDC-transfers</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19179575/Chainlink-integrates-with-Circles-CCTP-protocol-for-cross-chain-USDC-transfers"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T15:05:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chainlink has integrated Circle’s cross-chain transfer protocol with its CCIP system — aiming to securely move USDC across networks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon’s MATIC Token Controversy: What’s Behind the Suspicious Flows?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19179581/Polygons-MATIC-Token-Controversy-Whats-Behind-the-Suspicious-Flows</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19179581/Polygons-MATIC-Token-Controversy-Whats-Behind-the-Suspicious-Flows"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T15:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SHIB, BONE Prices Strive for Rebound Amid New Shibarium Integration]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19179570/SHIB-BONE-Prices-Strive-for-Rebound-Amid-New-Shibarium-Integration</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19179570/SHIB-BONE-Prices-Strive-for-Rebound-Amid-New-Shibarium-Integration"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T15:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Aptos Falls More Than 5% In 24 hours]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19179606/Cryptocurrency-Aptos-Falls-More-Than-5-In-24-hours</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19179606/Cryptocurrency-Aptos-Falls-More-Than-5-In-24-hours"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T15:03:49.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Team Discloses Project’s True Strength, Here’s What It Is]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fddb9569</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-team-discloses-projects-true-strength/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T15:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an exciting turn of events, the team behind the Ethereum-based meme coin Shiba Inu, also known as “Dogecoin Killer”, has revealed the major driving force behind the project’s consistency and success over time. 
 
True Strength Of Shiba Inu Is Not What You Think
 
The Shiba Inu team unveiled the altcoin’s true strength on the social media platform X (formerly Twitter) on Monday. According to the team, the major strength behind the project’s success and consistency lies in the support of its community, commonly referred to as ShibArmy.
 
 
The post simply highlights how important, active, and dedicated the SHIB community has been since the project was launched in 2020. Consequently, the Shiba Inu team has acknowledged this effort and has constantly praised the members of the community.
 
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Godspower Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Attempted Bitfinex Exploit for $15 Billion XRP Fails]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fdc73786</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/attempted-bitfinex-exploit-for-15-billion-xrp-fails/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T14:37:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitfinex’s security protocols came into the spotlight when a seemingly massive XRP transfer, initially causing alarm among crypto watchers, turned out to be a foiled exploit attempt.
 
$15 Billion of XRP Transfer Attempt Fizzles Out
 
A failed exploit attempt on cryptocurrency exchange Bitfinex was brought to light, involving nearly $15 billion worth of XRP tokens, a sum that represents almost half of XRP’s $31 billion market capitalization. This incident, initially flagged by the blockchain tracking account Whale Alert, caused a stir among market watchers and crypto enthusiasts due to its magnitude.
 
The attempt, which occurred early Monday, was reported as a massive transaction of 25.6 billion XRP to Bitfinex. However, this turned out to be a deceptive maneuver as the actual transfer wa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Sencil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EU Banking Watchdog Extends Anti-Money Laundering Measures to Cover Crypto Firms]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fdc0ac09</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2024/01/16/eu-banking-watchdog-extends-anti-money-laundering-measures-to-cover-crypto-firms/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T14:28:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The European Banking Authority's new guidance for crypto firms will take effect on Dec. 30.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandali Handagama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EU Banking Watchdog Extends Anti-Money Laundering Measures to Cover Crypto Firms]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fdc0abef</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/01/16/eu-banking-watchdog-extends-anti-money-laundering-measures-to-cover-crypto-firms/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T14:28:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The European Banking Authority issued new guidance for crypto firms that will come into effect on Dec. 30, 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandali Handagama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Anichess' NFT Game Launches With Backing From World Chess Champ Magnus Carlsen]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212959</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212959/anichess-nft-game-launches-backing-chess-champ-magnus-carlsen"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After raising $1.5 million last year, Anichess is now playable with support from Chess.com and vaunted chess grandmaster Magnus Carlsen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Analyst Gives Timeline For Parabolic Breakout For XRP Price, Here’s When]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fdcfee39</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/parabolic-breakout-xrp-price/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T13:39:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There could be a significant surge in the XRP price soon enough based on this crypto analyst’s prediction. Such a development will no doubt be exciting for the XRP community, which has had to endure the crypto token’s tepid movement for a while now. 
 
“Massive Breakout” On The Horizon For XRP Price
 
In a post on his X (formerly Twitter) platform, Crypto Rover shared a weekly XRP price chart and remarked that XRP was going to experience a massive breakout. As part of his prediction, he said that this parabolic move from XRP will happen in the “upcoming 8 weeks.” Going by this, XRP’s price could potentially rise sometime in March.
 
 
Crypto Rover didn’t mention what price level XRP could hit when this impending breakout happens. However, from the chart that he shared, there is the possibi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Mover Americas: Binance Traders Led “Sell-The-Fact” Pullback in Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fdc90f26</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/01/16/first-mover-americas-binance-traders-led-sell-the-fact-pullback-in-bitcoin/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T13:32:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest price moves in bitcoin [BTC] and crypto markets in context for Jan. 16, 2024. First Mover is CoinDesk’s daily newsletter that contextualizes the latest actions in the crypto markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lyllah Ledesma, Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Study: Venture Capital Investments in Top Ten Web3 Projects Were 70% Lower in 2023]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fdb53da0</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/study-venture-capital-investments-in-top-ten-web3-projects-were-70-lower-in-2023/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T13:04:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2023, the top ten Web3 projects collectively raised $1.78 billion in funding, a figure which is 70% lower than the $5.87 billion raised in the previous year, the findings of a new study have shown. The findings also show that Web3 projects were able to attract $9 billion in capital with infrastructure projects accounting for 36.5% of the total. 
 
Most Capital Raised in the Latter Half of 2023
 
According to a study conducted by the crypto exchange Binance, venture capital investments in the top ten Web3 projects saw a significant downturn in 2023, with only $1.78 billion raised. This total is 70% lower than the $5.87 billion raised in 2022.
 

 
As explained in the study report, the fundraising fortunes of the top ten projects are a reflection of the bearish market conditions that prev…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Mobile Plans 'Cheaper' Follow-Up to Saga Smartphone: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212981</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212981/solana-mobile-plans-cheaper-follow-up-to-saga-smartphone-report"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T12:28:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A cheaper successor to the Solana Saga is reportedly planned, after the original phone sold out as buyers harvested bundled tokens and airdrops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BREAKING – Bitcoin Proponent Vivek Ramaswamy Withdraws From Presidential Race, Endorses Trump]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fdb3c681</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-proponent-withdraws-from-presidential-race/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T12:20:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an unexpected turn of events, entrepreneur and Bitcoin proponent Republican presidential candidate Vivek Ramaswamy has officially withdrawn from the 2024 presidential race after a lackluster performance in the Iowa caucuses.
 
Despite an initial surge that propelled him to third place in national polls over the summer, the 38-year-old failed to gain sufficient support in Iowa, securing only 7.7% of the vote and a meager three delegates.
 
 
Ramaswamy, relatively unknown before entering the political arena, invested significant time and resources in Iowa, hoping to solidify his standing.
 
Bitcoin Advocate Vivek Ramaswamy Backs Out
 
However, his efforts fell short, prompting the entrepreneur to announce his withdrawal from the race. Addressing his supporters in Des Moines, he stated:
 
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Game-Changing Subscription Model for Marketing Services Unveiled by Ninjapromo.io]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fdbe3b1c</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/game-changing-subscription-model-for-marketing-services-unveiled-by-ninjapromo-io/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T12:03:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. Ninjapromo.io, a pioneering force in the web3 marketing landscape, announces the launch of a subscription-based model that is set to redefine the dynamics of client-agency collaborations. This innovative approach empowers clients to subscribe for a specified number of hours per month, gaining access to a full-suite marketing department that covers services ranging from PR and digital marketing to SMM, community management, and design.
 
After executing marketing campaigns for over 200 clients and helping raise over $2bn for some of the industry’s leaders, including HTX (formerly Huobi) and Damex.io, Ninjapromo experts learned all the ins and outs of the dynamic web3 landscape, which resulted in the creation of this unique offer for their existing and future clients. It allow…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether Hits Back at UN Report Alleging Role of USDT in Illicit Activity in East Asia]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fdba2b1e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/01/16/tether-hits-back-at-un-report-alleging-role-of-usdt-in-illicit-activity-in-east-asia/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T11:36:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tether, the issuer of the largest stablecoin by market cap, has challenged the United Nations (UN) for its report on underground banking and money laundering infrastructure in East and Southeast Asia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amitoj Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI and Blockchain Convergence to Reshape Crypto and Web3 in 2024]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fdba301b</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/ai-and-blockchain-convergence-to-reshape-crypto-and-web3-in-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T11:36:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The year 2023 has been a remarkable one for the crypto and  
Web3 space, with many innovations, challenges, and opportunities emerging. The  
adoption of decentralized technologies has grown exponentially, reaching new  
heights of user engagement, value creation, and social impact. 
As we enter  
2024, what are some of the trends that will shape the future of crypto and  
Web3? Here are some of my predictions and thoughts as we delve into the first part of our crypto and Web 3 predictions for 2024. It is based on the current state  
of the industry, the latest developments, and the potential scenarios.
New UX User Experience
One of the main barriers to mass adoption of crypto and Web3  
is the user experience (UX), which is often complex, confusing, and  
intimidating for newcomers. Users…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anndy Lian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USDT at the Heart of Pig Butchering Scams Says the UN]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fdbae69d</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/usdt-at-the-heart-of-pig-butchering-scams-says-the-un/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T11:31:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The stablecoin tether has emerged as one of the preferred payment methods for money launderers and fraudsters operating out of Southeast Asia, the findings of a new United Nations study have shown. According to Jeremy Douglas, criminals are choosing to use tether because they know that “cryptocurrency regulations are way behind [the illicit activity].”
 
Underground Tether Money Laundering Teams
 
According to a study conducted by the United Nations Office on Drugs and Crime (UNDOC), the stablecoin tether or USDT has emerged as one of the payment methods often chosen by money launderers and fraudsters operating in Southeast Asia. In addition, the stablecoin was found to be at the heart of the so-called pig butchering scams.
 
Online gambling platforms, many of which are unregulated, have t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk’s Grok Declares Dogecoin As The Best Crypto For X]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fda6387b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/elon-musk-grok-dogecoin-best-crypto-x/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T11:09:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk’s Grok, an Artificial Intelligence (AI) chatbot developed by xAI, has declared Dogecoin as the best cryptocurrency for X (formerly known as Twitter). This statement came in response to a query from CryptoQuant CEO Ki Young Ju, who asked Grok, “What is the best cryptocurrency for Twitter?”
 
Grok’s response was clear and unequivocal: “The best cryptocurrency for Twitter would be Dogecoin. Elon Musk, the owner of Twitter, has been a vocal supporter of Dogecoin and has even mentioned it in several of his tweets. This has led to a surge in its popularity and adoption. Additionally, the Dogecoin community is very active on Twitter, making it a great choice for those looking to engage with fellow crypto enthusiasts.”
 
In a further exploration of the relationship between Elon Musk, DOG…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashKey Group Hits 'Unicorn' Status With $100 Million Raise, $1.2 Billion Valuation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212978</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212978/hashkey-group-hits-unicorn-status-with-100-million-raise-1-2-billion-valuation"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T10:39:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OKX Ventures was reportedly among the lead investors in the Series A round, which carried HashKey Group over the $1 billion "unicorn" threshold.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manta Pacific Replaces Base as Fourth Largest Scaling Solution: L2Beat]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fda333d8</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2024/01/16/manta-pacific-replaces-base-as-fourth-largest-scaling-solution-l2beat/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T10:34:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manta Pacific is the native layer 2 of the Manta Network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hedera Council Boosts Blockchain Innovation With Billions in HBAR]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fdafe190</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/hedera-council-boosts-blockchain-innovation-with-billions-in-hbar/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T10:01:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Hedera Council announces an allocation of 4.86 billion HBARs, primarily focused on bolstering initiatives like the HBAR Foundation, Hashgraph Association, and DLT Science Foundation.
 
Hedera Council Commits 4.86 Billion HBARs
 
In a move towards enhancing its network and decentralized governance, the Hedera Council has approved an allocation of funds amounting to 4.86 billion HBARs, Hedera’s native cryptocurrency. This decision, aimed at bolstering ecosystem development, comes as part of the council’s strategy to fortify its base.
 
The bulk of this allocation, totaling 4.248 billion HBARs, is earmarked for existing initiatives. These include the HBAR Foundation, the Hashgraph Association, and the DLT Science Foundation. The grants for the HBAR Foundation and Hashgraph Association are…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Sencil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Misinformation Could Rock the 2024 Elections—Here's How OpenAI Plans to Fight It]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212946</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212946/ai-misinformation-could-rock-2024-elections-how-openai-plans-fight"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T01:31:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI has intensified its efforts to prevent AI misuse, including deepfakes, to protect democratic processes amid the upcoming elections.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Rise and Fall of GameStop's NFT Marketplace]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212944</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212944/rise-fall-gamestop-nft-marketplace"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T00:12:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What happened to GameStop’s blockchain plans? Here’s a look back into how the gaming retailer got into NFTs—and then bailed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Assassin's Creed Maker Ubisoft Backs Yet Another Crypto Gaming Network]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212928</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212928/assassins-creed-maker-ubisoft-backs-yet-another-crypto-gaming-network"/>
        <updated>2024-01-15T22:15:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Major video game publisher Ubisoft is among Wemix's 40 "node council partners" that will validate its blockchain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mysterious Ordinals Inscription Teases 'Cursed' Bitcoin Art Project]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212908</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212908/mysterious-ordinals-inscription-teases-cursed-bitcoin-art-project"/>
        <updated>2024-01-15T21:47:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptic '10,000 sats' message on Ordinal 55,365,041 baffles Ordinals experts, igniting speculation in the Bitcoin community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Saylor Sounds Alarm on Deepfake Bitcoin Scams]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212892</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212892/microstrategy-michael-saylor-deepfake-bitcoin-scams"/>
        <updated>2024-01-15T20:09:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No, Michael Saylor won’t be sending you some Bitcoin, despite what you think he might have said on YouTube.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jupiter Finally Sets a Date for JUP Airdrop, Teases Meme Coin Drop on Solana]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212884</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212884/jupiter-finally-sets-date-jup-airdrop-teases-meme-coin-drop-solana"/>
        <updated>2024-01-15T19:51:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nearly a million Solana DeFi users will be able to claim JUP later this month in the airdrop, with Jupiter teasing a meme coin launch too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GTA 6 Preview: Everything You Need to Know About the New Grand Theft Auto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154049</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154049/grand-theft-auto-6-release-date-rumors-leaks-news"/>
        <updated>2024-01-15T19:15:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATE: T-Pain says he's working on GTA 6—and that Rockstar asked him to stay away from a particular game server in the meantime.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Steal Over $4 Million in Fake Airdrops and Other Scams on Solana]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212875</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212875/hackers-steal-over-4-million-fake-airdrops-other-scams-solana"/>
        <updated>2024-01-15T18:12:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The attacks have duped thousands of Solana users by employing a variety of tactics, swiping millions of dollars worth of tokens like BONK.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Biggest Games Coming Out in 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210052</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210052/biggest-games-coming-out-nintendo-playstation-xbox-pc"/>
        <updated>2024-01-15T17:14:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATED: From Final Fantasy VII Rebirth to Star Wars Outlaws and plenty in between, these are our most anticipated games of 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xai Gaming Token Surges 35% as Airdrop Value Hits $140 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212866</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212866/xai-gaming-token-surges-35-as-airdrop-value-hits-140-million"/>
        <updated>2024-01-15T16:53:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arbitrum’s XAI token tied to a layer-3 gaming network spiked to a new all-time high price Monday, less than a week after its airdrop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CES 2024: Mercedes-Benz Previews In-Car NFT Gallery, 'Emotional' AI Assistant]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212831</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212831/ces-2024-mercedes-benz-previews-in-car-nft-gallery-emotional-ai-assistant"/>
        <updated>2024-01-15T13:54:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The German automaker's updated MBUX Virtual Assistant will leverage an LLM to interact with drivers using one of four "emotional profiles."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Dips Under $42,000 as Market Sentiment Turns Neutral Post-ETF]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212828</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212828/bitcoin-dips-under-42000-as-market-sentiment-turns-neutral-post-etf"/>
        <updated>2024-01-15T11:21:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin briefly dropped below $42,000 Monday morning, as the Crypto Fear & Greed Index turned neutral for the first time since November 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week on Crypto Twitter: The ETF Circus Comes to Town]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212824</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212824/this-week-on-crypto-twitter-bitcoin-etf-circus"/>
        <updated>2024-01-14T17:11:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Multiple plot twists upended a week that was already guaranteed to be high octane.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Art Blocks Founder Erick Calderon Approached Printing 'Chromie Squiggle']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212814</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212814/how-art-blocks-founder-erick-calderon-approached-printing-chromie-squiggle"/>
        <updated>2024-01-14T15:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Erick Calderon discussed his premium print run of Chromie Squiggle #8107 at Rug Radio’s R Haus event at Art Basel Miami 2023. Watch the interview now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Bitcoin Flashes and Fades as ETFs Launch—But Ethereum Soars]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212773</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212773/this-week-coins-bitcoin-fanaticism-flashes-fades-etfs-launch-ethereum-soars"/>
        <updated>2024-01-13T21:38:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin's big week was a rollercoaster. Ethereum closed up. And the rest of the top five were largely flat for the past seven days.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Kawailani Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Will Make Workers More Effective But Adapting to Its Rapid Spread Is ‘Scary’: Sam Altman]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212793</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212793/sam-altman-openai-bill-gates-microsoft"/>
        <updated>2024-01-13T20:35:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI CEO Sam Altman sat down with Bill Gates to explore the positive potential and threats of artificial intelligence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Play Super Nintendo and Other Classic Games on Bitcoin—Here’s How]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212729</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212729/you-can-play-super-nintendo-classic-games-bitcoin-heres-how"/>
        <updated>2024-01-13T16:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks to Ordinals, you can find working video games inscribed on the Bitcoin blockchain. Here’s how to play them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nike Will 'Go Way Deeper' Into Video Game Fashion Amid NFT Push]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212723</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212723/nike-will-go-way-deeper-video-game-fashion-amid-nft-push"/>
        <updated>2024-01-13T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nike says it will continue to expand into video game wearables through its .Swoosh platform, but it's unclear if there will be more NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Chair Gary Gensler Recaps Takeover of Agency's Twitter Account]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212765</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212765/sec-chair-gary-gensler-addresses-cyberattack-on-agencys-twitter-account"/>
        <updated>2024-01-13T00:49:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The agency head gave an update on the investigation into a cyberattack that falsely announced Bitcoin ETF approvals earlier this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop Bails on Crypto Gaming, Killing NFT Marketplace]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212761</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212761/gamestop-bails-on-crypto-gaming-killing-nft-marketplace"/>
        <updated>2024-01-13T00:21:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The news comes four months after the storied video game retailer axed its NFT wallet, with GameStop set to exit the space entirely.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Is ’Bigger Than Any Government’: BlackRock CEO Larry Fink]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212727</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212727/bitcoin-bigger-than-any-government-blackrock-ceo-larry-fink"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T23:16:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a Fox Business interview, the former Bitcoin skeptic defended the cryptocurrency as a shield against government manipulation and economic instability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Super Mario AI Hologram Is Creeping People Out in Vegas]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212708</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212708/super-mario-ai-hologram-creeping-people-out-vegas"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T21:21:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The unauthorized AI hologram of gaming icon Super Mario becomes a viral sensation at CES, dubbed an "abomination" by one visitor.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Game Over: More Than 30% of Crypto Games Have Been Discontinued]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212689</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212689/game-over-more-than-30-percent-crypto-games-discontinued"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T19:39:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New research documents a slew of inactive crypto and NFT games that have been abandoned or otherwise inactive for months.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gary Gensler Remains Cagey on Ethereum, Punts on Potential ETF]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212681</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212681/gary-gensler-remains-cagey-ethereum-punts-potential-etf"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T18:45:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On a CNBC segment this morning, the SEC chair also remained vague about Ethereum's status as a security following Bitcoin ETF approvals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Game 'Nyan Heroes' Hits Epic Store Ahead of Airdrop]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212680</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212680/solana-game-nyan-heroes-hits-epic-store-ahead-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T18:17:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nyan Heroes pairs cats and crypto in a Fortnite-like battle royale shooter on Solana, with big moves apparently ahead in 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Plunges on Day Two of ETF Mania as Liquidations Soar]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212671</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212671/bitcoin-plunges-day-two-etf-mania-liquidations-soar"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T17:16:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bitcoin ETF buzz calmed Friday as the leading cryptocurrency dipped down near $43,000. Are traders selling the news after the frenzy?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Genesis Pays $8 Million and Forfeits BitLicense to Settle New York Charges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212656</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212656/genesis-pays-8-million-and-forfeits-bitlicense-to-settle-new-york-charges"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T16:27:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Genesis Trading has had its BitLicense since 2018.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Rallies as BlackRock Boss Eyes ETH ETF After Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212662</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212662/ethereum-rallies-blackrock-boss-eyes-eth-etf-after-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T16:17:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Analysts think an ETH ETF is now a slam dunk, sending Ethereum pumping 18% in the last week amid the Bitcoin ETF rollout in the U.S.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinShares Acquires Valkyrie Funds—And the BRRR Bitcoin ETF With It]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212627</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212627/coinshares-acquires-valkyrie-funds-brrr-bitcoin-etf"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T15:38:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The acquisition includes the Valkyrie Bitcoin Fund, which trades under the BRRR ticker on Nasdaq.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taproot Wizards Launch Quantum Cats Collection As Bitcoin Inscriptions]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212594</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212594/taproot-wizards-launch-quantum-cats-bitcoin-ordinals-collection"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T15:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 3,333-image images on the Bitcoin blockchain cost $66,000 to create.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taki Brings Play-to-Earn Mobile Games to Polygon After Merger, Acquisitions]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212607</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212607/taki-brings-play-earn-mobile-games-polygon-after-merger-acquisitions"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T13:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After launching a social app on Solana, Taki Games has merged with Unite, has a new CEO, and is launching Polygon mobile games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terra Co-Founder Do Kwon Requests SEC Trial Delay So He Can Attend]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212616</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212616/terras-do-kwon-requests-sec-trial-delay-so-he-can-attend"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T13:14:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lawyers for Kwon said that an adjournment to mid-March "would provide a realistic possibility" for him to attend.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elizabeth Warren: SEC 'Wrong on the Law' Over Bitcoin ETF Approval]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212614</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212614/elizabeth-warren-sec-wrong-on-the-law-over-bitcoin-etf-approval"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T10:48:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Senator claimed that the SEC had let crypto "burrow even deeper into our financial system," and pressed for AML rules.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generative Art Across Mediums: Artists Discuss the Evolving Space]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/GK3aN0zo/generative-art-across-mediums-artists-discuss-the-evolving-space</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/GK3aN0zo/generative-art-across-mediums-artists-discuss-the-evolving-space"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T02:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this panel discussion from Rug Radio's R Haus at Art Basel Miami 2023, Sofia Garcia, Ismail Tazi, Emily Edelman, and Aleksandra Art discuss the expanding generative art space—and why "generative" doesn't necessarily have to mean digital.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI-Backed 1X Wants to Put a Humanoid Robot to Work in Your Home]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212584</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212584/household-robots-1x-neo-eve-himanoid-biped"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T01:45:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The robotics company raised $100 million to build NEO, its second bipedal robot design that can perform domestic tasks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These Are All the Bitcoin ETFs That Are Now Trading in the US]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=62912</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/62912/high-profile-bitcoin-etf-applications"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T23:44:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spot Bitcoin ETFs are finally trading in the United States following SEC approval. Here are all the Bitcoin ETFs you can invest in today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves,Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The AI Coin to Rule Them All with Mike Grantis]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rkYpU8TJ/the-ai-coin-to-rule-them-all-with-mike-grantis</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rkYpU8TJ/the-ai-coin-to-rule-them-all-with-mike-grantis"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T18:46:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reza is joined by Mike Grantis from Contango Digital to discuss
- The AI coin to rule them all
- The Solana Ecosystem 
- What's next for Solana airdrops]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conversation With Snowfro: Bringing 'Chromie Squiggle' #8107 to the Physical Space]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DcrU04gG/conversation-with-snowfro-bringing-chromie-squiggle-8107-to-the-physical-space</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DcrU04gG/conversation-with-snowfro-bringing-chromie-squiggle-8107-to-the-physical-space"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Art Blocks founder and CEO and "Chromie Squiggle" project creator Erick "snowfro" Calderon spoke with Benny Redbeard Gross at Rug Radio's R Haus event at Art Basel 2023, to discuss how and why "Chromie Squiggle" NFT #8107 was given a special edition print run in collaboration with Avant Arte.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don't Underestimate Mobile Gaming: Qualcomm's Matthew Grossman]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/34Oil4Qu/dont-underestimate-mobile-gaming-qualcomms-matthew-grossman</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/34Oil4Qu/dont-underestimate-mobile-gaming-qualcomms-matthew-grossman"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Qualcomm product marketing manager Matthew Grossman tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin why mobile esports is exploding in popularity around the world—and dispels some of the misconceptions around mobile gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF: This Is the 'Calm Before the Storm', Says ETF Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/VOX04ytt/bitcoin-etf-this-is-the-calm-before-the-storm-says-etf-analyst</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/VOX04ytt/bitcoin-etf-this-is-the-calm-before-the-storm-says-etf-analyst"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T20:20:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bloomberg Senior ETF Analyst Eric Balchunas joins Farokh Sarmad, Michael Anderson, and Ovie Faruq on the FOMO Hour to share the latest intel on the looming approval for a spot Bitcoin ETF, what might happen when the very different worlds of TradFi and crypto collide, and his insights on “Genslish,” the unique and strategic language of SEC chair Gary Gensler.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Losing 1500 BTC on Mt Gox and the Problem with Women in Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/EfNuNu8a/losing-1500-btc-on-mt-gox-and-the-problem-with-women-in-web3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/EfNuNu8a/losing-1500-btc-on-mt-gox-and-the-problem-with-women-in-web3"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T19:02:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week our host is joined by Brooke Lacey! 

They discuss:  
- Making and losing generational wealth
- Trauma Bond
- Women in Web3
- The Problem with WAGMI]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ESL Faceit Group Exploring Blockchain 'Opportunistically,' Says Exec]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/yvrs4lBx/esl-faceit-group-exploring-blockchain-opportunistically-says-exec</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/yvrs4lBx/esl-faceit-group-exploring-blockchain-opportunistically-says-exec"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T02:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Braithwaite—ESL Faceit Group's VP of Game Ecosystems, Mobile, and Snapdragon Pro Series—shares the esports firm's approach to blockchain technology with GG's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bryan Johnson Explains His Quest for Immortality and Why He Started with the Penis]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tAwP55g9/bryan-johnson-explains-his-quest-for-immortality-and-why-he-started-with-the-penis</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tAwP55g9/bryan-johnson-explains-his-quest-for-immortality-and-why-he-started-with-the-penis"/>
        <updated>2023-12-24T19:38:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Billionaire biohacker Bryan Johnson shared with Decrypt's Jason Nelson why he began his longevity quest and how technology has shaped the endeavor. Johnson also discusses some of his controversial experiments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wildcard's Plans for 2024 with Founders Paul and Katy Bettner]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/TI3aFBhO/wildcards-plans-for-2024-with-founders-paul-and-katy-bettner</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/TI3aFBhO/wildcards-plans-for-2024-with-founders-paul-and-katy-bettner"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T21:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wildcard developers Paul and Katy Bettner tell Decrypt's Kate Irwin about why they see their game as a "Web3 game," not a crypto game, and share why they've stuck with their initial vision despite the challenging broader market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt and Rug Radio Merge to Create Global Web3 Publishing Company]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/VTEBYFD8/decrypt-and-rug-radio-merge-to-create-global-web3-publishing-company</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/VTEBYFD8/decrypt-and-rug-radio-merge-to-create-global-web3-publishing-company"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T17:04:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt and Rug Radio have announced their intent to merge, creating the world’s biggest decentralized publishing company. Codenamed [REDACTED], the alliance is aimed at revolutionizing tech-media, bringing together the forces of content creation and consumption.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>