<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-08-15T14:12:40.498Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-08-15T14:12:40.498Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Crypto Custodian to Court: Prime Trust Files for Bankruptcy Protection]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75538095ee</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/from-crypto-custodian-to-court-prime-trust-files-for-bankruptcy-protection/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T14:08:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the wake of financial upheavals and regulatory hurdles, Prime Trust, a digital currency custodian, has formally sought Chapter 11 bankruptcy protection. This move closely follows the appointment of John Guedry as the company’s overseer, bolstered by a designated committee to steer the restructuring process.
 
Crypto Custodian Prime Trust Files for Chapter 11 Bankruptcy Protection
 
Despite the chaos, Prime Trust pledges to operate with transparency, prioritizing its stakeholders’ best interests. The push for bankruptcy protection marks a new episode in an ongoing drama ignited by claims of financial instability and failures to process customer withdrawals.
 
As the gravity of Prime Trust’s monetary woes intensified, the Nevada Financial Institutions Division stepped in, signaling its pl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Base DeFi Project Suffers $865,000 Exploit, Shares Emergency Program With Users]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755380e854</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/base-defi-project-suffer-865k-exploit-emergency/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T14:06:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rocketswap, a decentralized exchange on the Coinbase native blockchain and Ethereum-based network Base, has just experienced a crypto exploit, losing over $860k of users’ assets. 
 
According to an August 15 post on X by Rocketswap, the incident occurred due to a “brute force hack”  on the server, which contains private keys related to the protocol. Rocketswap posted that this security breach allowed the hackers to gain control of the protocol’s farm feature and transfer out a large volume of users’ assets. 
 
The statement read: 
 

We are sorry to inform you that the team needed to use offline signatures when deploying the launchpad and put the private keys on the server. A brute force hack of the server was detected, and due to the proxy contract used for the farm contract, there were m…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Semilore Faleti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Base DeFi Project Suffers $865,000 Exploit, Shares Emergency Program With Users]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18838454/Base-DeFi-Project-Suffers-865000-Exploit-Shares-Emergency-Program-With-Users</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18838454/Base-DeFi-Project-Suffers-865000-Exploit-Shares-Emergency-Program-With-Users"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T14:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rocketswap, a decentralized exchange on the Coinbase native blockchain and Ethereum-based network Base, has just experienced a crypto exploit, losing over $860k of users’ assets. According to an August 15 post on X by Rocketswap, the incident occurred due to a “brute force hack” on the server,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Perfect storm for undervalued ASICs: Blockstream plans $50M raise to buy miners]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18838432/Perfect-storm-for-undervalued-ASICs-Blockstream-plans-50M-raise-to-buy-miners</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18838432/Perfect-storm-for-undervalued-ASICs-Blockstream-plans-50M-raise-to-buy-miners"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blockstream intends to buy and store ASIC mining hardware ahead of Bitcoin’s halving in 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Star Atlas CEO on Developing an MMO Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/WQCaahmH/star-atlas-ceo-on-developing-an-mmo-game</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/WQCaahmH/star-atlas-ceo-on-developing-an-mmo-game"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T13:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Jason Nelson speaks with Star Atlas Founder and CEO Michael Wagner about the MMO game's approach to development, marketing, and blockchain integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Star Atlas CEO on Developing an MMO Game]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18838462/Star-Atlas-CEO-on-Developing-an-MMO-Game</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18838462/Star-Atlas-CEO-on-Developing-an-MMO-Game"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T13:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Jason Nelson speaks with Star Atlas Founder and CEO Michael Wagner about the MMO game's approach to development, marketing, and blockchain integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto market in early stages of new cycle, Delphi Digital co-founder says]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18838438/Crypto-market-in-early-stages-of-new-cycle-Delphi-Digital-co-founder-says</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18838438/Crypto-market-in-early-stages-of-new-cycle-Delphi-Digital-co-founder-says"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T13:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's mounting evidence suggesting the crypto market is in the early stages of a new cycle, according to Delphi Digital's Kevin Kelly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Edges Higher Following Economic Data; Sei Emerges As Top Gainer]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18838455/Bitcoin-Edges-Higher-Following-Economic-Data-Sei-Emerges-As-Top-Gainer</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18838455/Bitcoin-Edges-Higher-Following-Economic-Data-Sei-Emerges-As-Top-Gainer"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T13:48:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (CRYPTO: BTC) moved slightly higher, with the cryptocurrency prices trading above the $29,300 level on Tuesday. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Bard picks Solana over Cardano; Here is why]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18838411/Google-Bard-picks-Solana-over-Cardano-Here-is-why</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18838411/Google-Bard-picks-Solana-over-Cardano-Here-is-why"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T13:47:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The rise of artificial intelligence (AI) has had a major impact on the cryptocurrency market. AI platforms like OpenAi’s ChatGPT … Continued]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Rise Of Bitcoin Spark: Is It The New Ethereum In The Making?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18838422/The-Rise-Of-Bitcoin-Spark-Is-It-The-New-Ethereum-In-The-Making</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18838422/The-Rise-Of-Bitcoin-Spark-Is-It-The-New-Ethereum-In-The-Making"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T13:44:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Spark is rapidly gaining traction in the crypto domain, challenging the dominance of established cryptocurrencies like Ethereum. This article explores the intricacies of Bitcoin Spark, its comparison with Ethereum, and the reasons behind its rising prominence. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto project using on-chain reputations for governance raises $2 million]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18838388/Crypto-project-using-on-chain-reputations-for-governance-raises-2-million</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18838388/Crypto-project-using-on-chain-reputations-for-governance-raises-2-million"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T13:36:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JKLabs secured a $2 million pre-seed funding from investors like 1kx and Boys Club, as it focuses on improving crypto governance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Did Binance's Listed CYBER and SEI Meet Expectations? Here are the First Price Movements!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18838390/Did-Binances-Listed-CYBER-and-SEI-Meet-Expectations-Here-are-the-First-Price-Movements</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18838390/Did-Binances-Listed-CYBER-and-SEI-Meet-Expectations-Here-are-the-First-Price-Movements"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T13:34:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There were great increases in CYBER and SEI prices, which are listed on the Bitcoin exchange Binance. Here are the details... Continue Reading: Did Binance's Listed CYBER and SEI Meet Expectations? Here are the First Price Movements!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big Questions: Did the NSA create Bitcoin?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18838384/Big-Questions-Did-the-NSA-create-Bitcoin</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18838384/Big-Questions-Did-the-NSA-create-Bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dinari Raises $7.5M for Decentralized Stock Trading Platform]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75538dbc0c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/08/15/dinari-raises-75m-for-decentralized-stock-trading-platform/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T13:26:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Backers for the dShares platform, which will be available ex-US, included a Susquehanna subsidiary.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandy Betz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimized for trading, Sei launches mainnet beta]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18838355/Optimized-for-trading-Sei-launches-mainnet-beta</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18838355/Optimized-for-trading-Sei-launches-mainnet-beta"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T13:23:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mainnet beta will initially launch with 20 applications, with over 250 to come in the near future]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[zkEVM Testnet Goes Live, Traders Now Wonder About IMX’s Price]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18838368/zkEVM-Testnet-Goes-Live-Traders-Now-Wonder-About-IMXs-Price</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18838368/zkEVM-Testnet-Goes-Live-Traders-Now-Wonder-About-IMXs-Price"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T13:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Immutable (IMX) announced on Twitter today that its zkEVM Testnet is officially live. A few months ago, Polygon Labs and Immutable joined forces, unveiling their strategic partnership and the vision to develop the Immutable zkEVM powered by Polygon. Today, the wait is over as the Immutable zkEVM...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Technical Analysis: BTC Unmoved by Better Than Expected US Retail Sales Data]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75538e793c</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-ethereum-technical-analysis-btc-unmoved-by-better-than-expected-us-retail-sales-data/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T13:20:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin mostly consolidated on Tuesday, as traders anticipated the release of July’s retail sales data from the United States. Sales rose by 0.7%, better than the 0.4% expected, and this comes following a 0.2% increase in June. Ethereum also remained unchanged prior to the data.
 
Bitcoin
 
Bitcoin (BTC) was trading in the red for the majority of the day, as price consolidated prior to the release of U.S. retail sales data.
 
After peaking at $29,660.25 to start the week, BTC/USD fell to a low of $29,272.35 earlier in today’s session.
 
Since moving above $30,000 on August 8, the world’s largest cryptocurrency has mostly trended sideways.
 
 
One reason for a lack of direction appears to be due to the relative strength index (RSI) tracking between a support and resistance of its own.
 
The index is currently at a reading of 47.57, and has mostly moved between a floor at 47.00, and ceiling at 49.00 in recent days.
 
For bulls, a breakout above the 49.00 zone will also likely be the straw needed to break the camel’s back.
 
 
Ethereum
 
Ethereum (ETH) has remained largely unchanged in the past few days, rising by 0.11% in the past week.
 
ETH/USD bottomed out at $1,837.21 so far during today’s session, which is almost $20.00 lower than Monday’s high.
 
Price has mostly consolidated around a support point of $1,830 in recent days, however the prospect of a moving average crossover is keeping bullish hopes alive.
 
 
The 10-day (red), and 25-day (blue) moving averages are on the cusp of an upwards crossover, which could likely send prices above $1,900.
 
Similar to BTC, there will first need to be a breakout above a ceiling on the RSI indicator for this to take place.
 
On this occasion the resistance point is at 47.00, and the index is currently tracking at 45.23.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
 Is a bullish run on the cards in the next few weeks? Leave your thoughts in the comments below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BREAKING: Europe Launches First Spot Bitcoin ETF | EP 803]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18838364/BREAKING-Europe-Launches-First-Spot-Bitcoin-ETF-EP-803</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18838364/BREAKING-Europe-Launches-First-Spot-Bitcoin-ETF-EP-803"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T13:20:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In what is certainly an important moment for the industry as a whole, Europe has launched its very first Spot Bitcoin ETF. Called the Jacobi FT Wilshere Bitcoin ETF the service is in regulatory compliance with the Guernsey Financial Services Commission GFSC and has been listed on Euronext...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Adds Support For SEI Listed On Binance Today!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18838350/Coinbase-Adds-Support-For-SEI-Listed-On-Binance-Today</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18838350/Coinbase-Adds-Support-For-SEI-Listed-On-Binance-Today"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T13:20:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A listing news for SEI, which is listed on the Bitcoin exchange Binance, also came from Coinbase. Here are the details... Continue Reading: Coinbase Adds Support For SEI Listed On Binance Today!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China’s new AI regulations begin to take effect]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18838340/Chinas-new-AI-regulations-begin-to-take-effect</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18838340/Chinas-new-AI-regulations-begin-to-take-effect"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T13:16:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Chinese has government loosened its original guidelines for AI it released in April and scheduled them to take effect starting on Aug. 15.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Europe’s First Spot Bitcoin ETF Makes Waves on Euronext Amsterdam]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75538f6110</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/europes-first-spot-bitcoin-etf-makes-waves-in-euronext-amsterdam/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T13:13:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The London-headquartered Jacobi Asset Management has  
introduced Europe's first spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) on Euronext  
Amsterdam. The company obtained approval in 2021 but delayed the launch  
reportedly due to unpredictable circumstances in the digital asset space.
Dubbed the Jacobi FT  
Wilshere Bitcoin ETF, the offering will be regulated by the Guernsey Financial  
Services Commission (GFSC). Listed under the ticker symbol 'BCOIN', the ETF's custody  
is managed by Fidelity Digital Assets, while trading firm Flow Traders assumes  
the role of market maker.
Europe Spearheads Spot  
Bitcoin ETF
The launch positions  
Europe ahead of the US in approving the first spot  
Bitcoin ETF, a step expected  
to potentially facilitate the adoption of Bitcoin among institutional  
in…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AllianceBlock Debuts Nexera Exchange: The On-Chain Limit Order Book Protocol On Arbitrum One]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18838314/AllianceBlock-Debuts-Nexera-Exchange-The-On-Chain-Limit-Order-Book-Protocol-On-Arbitrum-One</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18838314/AllianceBlock-Debuts-Nexera-Exchange-The-On-Chain-Limit-Order-Book-Protocol-On-Arbitrum-One"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T13:07:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Utrecht, Netherlands, August 15th, 2023, Chainwire AllianceBlock today unveiled Nexera Exchange, an innovative new decentralized exchange platform...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Custodian Prime Trust Entangled In Financial Distress, Files Chapter 11 Protection]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7553883273</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-custodian-files-chapter-11-protection/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T13:07:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prime Trust, a prominent name in the world of crypto custodial services, has taken the unexpected step of filing for Chapter 11 bankruptcy protection in Delaware. This move comes after the company encountered a significant shortfall in customer funds.
 
In the filing made on August 15, Prime Trust, LLC, Prime Core Technologies Inc., Prime Digital LLC, and Prime IRA LLC were named as the entities seeking Chapter 11 relief. 
 
 
The company’s decision was prompted by its recognition of a distressing reality: liabilities ranging between $100 million to $500 million, compared to assets estimated at $50 million to $100 million. 
 
This substantial gap underlines the severity of the financial challenges the company is currently facing.
 

 
 
 
 
 
A Bid For Transparency And Redemption
 
Prime T…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to protect your privacy online]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18838300/How-to-protect-your-privacy-online</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18838300/How-to-protect-your-privacy-online"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T13:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover effective strategies to maintain online privacy and learn how to safeguard your personal information while navigating the digital landscape.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Ripple and Amazon Web Services Transform Online Trade with XRP?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18838305/Will-Ripple-and-Amazon-Web-Services-Transform-Online-Trade-with-XRP</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18838305/Will-Ripple-and-Amazon-Web-Services-Transform-Online-Trade-with-XRP"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T13:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Web Services partners with Ripple to integrate XRP, potentially revolutionizing global e-commerce transactions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried's "dark" donations to the GOP came back to haunt him]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18838312/Sam-Bankman-Frieds-dark-donations-to-the-GOP-came-back-to-haunt-him</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18838312/Sam-Bankman-Frieds-dark-donations-to-the-GOP-came-back-to-haunt-him"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T13:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former crypto billionaire Sam Bankman-Fried used millions of dollars in customer deposits to donate to both the Democratic and Republican parties ahead of the US midterm elections last November, according to a fresh indictment (pdf) led by federal prosecutors on Aug. 14 in a New York court.Read more...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 equity trading firm Dinari raises $7.5 million in seed funding]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18838313/Web3-equity-trading-firm-Dinari-raises-75-million-in-seed-funding</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18838313/Web3-equity-trading-firm-Dinari-raises-75-million-in-seed-funding"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T13:01:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 corporate equity trading firm Dinari secured $7.5 million in seed funding. Investors include Third Kind Venture Capital.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Mover Americas: Europe's First Spot Bitcoin ETF Opens in Holland]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755388cfa7</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/08/15/first-mover-americas-hederas-token-gains-on-fed-move/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T13:01:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest price moves in bitcoin (BTC) and crypto markets in context for August 15, 2023. First Mover is CoinDesk’s daily newsletter that contextualizes the latest actions in the crypto markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lyllah Ledesma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LBank Revives IEO: A Look at the IEO Powerhouse LBank and its Historical Yields]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755388f6ce</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/lbank-revives-ieo-a-look-at-the-ieo-powerhouse-lbank-and-its-historical-yields/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T13:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the cryptocurrency market has witnessed a decline for over a year, many investors have chosen to liquidate their assets or move to alternative markets. However, 2023 has painted a different picture, positioning cryptocurrency as one of the best-performing investments. According to CoinMarketCap, the total crypto market capitalization rebounded from a low of $780.9 billion to a staggering $1.2198 trillion. Amid this resurgence, LBank, after a few years of dormancy, has announced the reboot of its IEO. Official participation link: https://www.lbank.com/launchpad-list/pins/
 
With Lbank’s IEO making a comback, let’s dive deep into it’s historical performance to gauge it’s potential.
 
Historical Gains of LBank IEO – 8 IEOs with an Average Surge of 1274%
 
Here’s a breakdown of LBank’s past…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Europe's First Spot Bitcoin ETF Now Listed On Euronext Amsterdam]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75538aa92f</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/markets/europes-first-spot-bitcoin-etf-now-listed-on-euronext-amsterdam"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T12:46:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over a year after it's initial planned launch, Jacobi Asset Management has now officially launched Europe's first spot Bitcoin Exchange-Traded Fund (ETF) on Euronext Amsterdam.



Operating under the ticker BCOIN, the ETF is regulated by the Guernsey Financial Services Commission (GFSC), with Fidelity Digital Assets providing custodial services, while Flow Traders operate as market makers while Jane Street and DRW operate as Authorized Participants. The benchmark for the fund, the FT Wilshire Bitcoin Blended Price Index, is provided by Wilshire Indexes.
“It is exciting to see Europe moving ahead of the US in opening up Bitcoin investing for institutional investors who want safe, secure access to the benefits of digital assets using familiar and regulated structures like our ETF," said Mart…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nik Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your Financial Privacy Is Under Attack: How State-Sponsored Attacks On Bitcoin Are Growing]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75538aa929</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/state-sponsored-attacks-on-bitcoin-privacy-are-growing"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T12:46:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is an opinion editorial by Kudzai Kutukwa, a financial inclusion advocate and Mandela Washington fellow.
Throughout American economic history, there has been a constant drive toward centralization, as evidenced by the many attempts to establish a central bank in the United States. From Alexander Hamilton's “Federalist Papers” to President Andrew Jackson's fierce battle against the Second Bank of the United States and the ultimate creation of the Federal Reserve in 1913, the allure of consolidating financial power has shaped the nation's monetary landscape. 
However, amid the fervor for a centralized monetary authority, there is a cautionary note: Be wary of the erosion of financial privacy. The concentration of financial control leads to less individual sovereignty, as the watchful ey…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kudzai Kutukwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence Trend is Accelerating With ‘Lion’s Share’ in the U.S.: Morgan Stanley]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75538b3958</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/08/15/artificial-intelligence-trend-is-accelerating-with-lions-share-in-the-us-morgan-stanley/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T12:41:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The banking giant said in a report that around 15% of companies quantified a revenue or cost-benefit from applying machine learning in the first half of the year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Canny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dasset Crypto Exchange Crumbles: The Ripple Effects of Regulatory Pressure]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7553744296</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/dasset-crypto-exchange-crumbles-the-ripple-effects-of-regulatory-pressure/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T12:32:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pressure on  
cryptocurrency firms does not seem to decrease. Their condition is not helped  
by the prolonged consolidation of major assets or the tightening regulatory  
screws by governmental financial institutions in the USA and Europe. Problems  
are also visible in Australia and New Zealand, where the Dasset exchange has  
gone into liquidation, and customers cannot retrieve their funds.
Dasset Crypto Exchange Confirms  
Liquidation
According  
to information published yesterday (Monday) by the New Zealand magazine The  
Herald, the country-based exchange has not responded to customer complaints  
about the inability to withdraw funds. The problem is believed to affect at  
least a few dozen people with up to $40,000 in assets on the platform. The  
most affected individual has unsuc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Damian Chmiel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sei Mainnet is Live After Testnet Sees More Than 7.5M Wallets Created]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75537625ea</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/08/15/sei-mainnet-is-live-after-testnet-sees-more-than-75m-wallets-created/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T12:16:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The trading focused layer 1 blockchain is backed by Jump Crypto and Flow Traders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lyllah Ledesma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fintech in the Front, DeFi in the Back—Crypto's Quiet Revolution Is Underway]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152383</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152383/fintech-front-defi-back-cryptos-quiet-revolution-is-underway"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T12:11:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mainstream audiences may never know that the promise of crypto has finally been realized.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX CEO Used $100 Million Of Customers Funds For Politics, US Prosecutors Allege]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755377529f</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ftx-ceo-used-100-million-of-customers/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T12:06:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New criminal charges keep unfolding against former FTX CEO Sam Bankman-Fried in his court case with the US prosecutors. In the latest development, the federal prosecutors filed a new indictment against the former billionaire on Monday, August 14. The filing alleged that Bankman-Fried stole more than $100 million in customers’ funds to fund political campaigns.
 
In addition, the prosecutors have also charged the FTX founder with seven counts of conspiracy and fraud through the new indictment.
 
Bankman-Fried Charged With Violating US Campaign Finance Law
 
Apart from these charges, Sam Bankman-Fried faces multiple counts of fraud, fraud conspiracy, money laundering, and wire fraud, leading to the FTX implosion. The prosecutors also charged him with stealing billions in customers’ funds to …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kent Glory</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Singapore's Central Bank Releases Stablecoin Regulatory Framework]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755377e050</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/08/15/singapores-central-bank-releases-stablecoin-regulatory-framework/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T12:01:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoins must hold minimum base capital 1 million Singapore dollars ($740,000) and provide redemption within no more than five business days of a request.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Secular Investment Case for Bitcoin and Crypto Adoption Remains Intact: Coinbase]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755371e8cf</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/08/15/the-secular-investment-case-for-bitcoin-and-crypto-adoption-remains-intact-coinbase/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T11:43:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The combined effect of expansionary fiscal and monetary policies should support bitcoin long term as a hedge against fiat debasement and profligate spending, the report said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Canny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stanford School Newspaper Highlights the Irony of Sam Bankman-Fried’s Scheduled Stanford Talk on Ethics Amidst Legal Chaos]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755372588d</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/stanford-school-newspaper-highlights-the-irony-of-sam-bankman-frieds-scheduled-stanford-talk-on-ethics-amidst-legal-chaos/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T11:39:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF), a once towering figure in the crypto world and former FTX CEO, was curiously slated to share his insights on tech ethics with Stanford students this winter. In a thorough examination penned by Theo Baker for the Stanford Daily, the details of SBF’s multifaceted relationship with one of the globe’s most respected academic institutions are unraveled.
 
Sam Bankman-Fried’s Tangled Ties With Stanford Law Unveiled Amid Legal Turmoil
 
Per a detailed account in the Stanford Daily, SBF was on the calendar to enlighten the minds of Stanford’s students and faculty on tech ethics during the winter quarter. The excitement was palpable, yet the community was stunned by a sudden twist in fate. November 2022 marked the downfall of SBF’s crypto kingdom, followed by the U.S. gover…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former FTX Exec Declines Testimony, Cites Fifth Amendment Rights]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152527</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152527/former-ftx-exec-declines-testimony-cites-fifth-amendment-rights"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T11:14:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Co-CEO of FTX Digital Markets will invoke his constitutional right against self-incrimination, opting to remain silent throughout the trial.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Recover Ethereum From Old GETH Wallets – KeychainX Expert Explains]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75537dee2c</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/how-to-recover-ethereum-from-old-geth-wallets-keychainx-expert-explains/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T11:08:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recovering an old GETH client can be a daunting task, but with the right hardware, software and information, it is possible. It involves locating the wallet file and cracking the password, using specialized tools such as those developed by the digital assets recovery experts at KeychainX. Once the password is recovered, the wallet can be decrypted and the private key imported to access the stored ETH.
 
Can an Old GETH Wallet Be Recovered?
 
 
 
 
Geth (go-ethereum) is an execution client which has been a core part of Ethereum since its very inception. If you have an old wallet that has been lying around for years and you can’t access it anymore, due to a bug or a missing password, there is still a chance to recover the assets locked inside. Just follow the detailed instructions in this ar…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Europe’s First Bitcoin Spot ETF Launches On Euronext Amsterdam]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75537e1c62</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/europe-first-bitcoin-spot-etf-on-euronext/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T11:07:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a groundbreaking move for the European digital asset market, London-based Jacobi Asset Management has officially listed the continent’s first spot Bitcoin ETF on Euronext Amsterdam. The Jacobi FT Wilshire Bitcoin ETF, trading under the ticker “BCOIN”, represents a significant leap forward for institutional Bitcoin investment in Europe, especially with its unique decarbonisation strategy.
 
The ETF, which has been regulated by the Guernsey Financial Services Commission (GFSC), stands out not only as the first of its kind in Europe but also for its compliance with SFDR Article 8. This compliance is achieved through a pioneering decarbonisation strategy, which includes a verifiable built-in Renewable Energy Certificate (REC) solution. This solution, supplied by digital asset platform Zumo,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FDIC Warns Of Crypto’s Legal And Fraud Risks For US Banks – Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75537e1c5e</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/fdic-warns-of-cryptos-risks-for-us-banks/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T11:07:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrencies have achieved a significant milestone as they found themselves featured within a dedicated segment of the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation, or FDIC, annual risk review, acknowledging the intricate and unprecedented risks associated with digital assets. 
 
This inclusion comes in the wake of a tumultuous period, marked by the March banking crisis that witnessed the abrupt downfall or compelled closure of prominent financial institutions such as Silicon Valley Bank, Silvergate Bank, and Signature Bank, all within a mere week. 
 
The FDIC’s mention of cryptocurrencies in its report reflects the challenging task of evaluating risk in a domain characterized by its ever-evolving nature and rapid technological advancements.
 
 
FDIC Report Identifies Growing Crypto Risks Ami…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Singapore Financial Regulator Issues Key Requirements for Stablecoin Issuers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152517</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152517/singapore-financial-regulator-issues-key-requirements-stablecoin-issuers"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T10:14:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoins issued outside of Singapore or pegged to other currencies will still be subject to the existing token regulatory regime.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meme Coin Base DEX RocketSwap Hit by $866K Exploit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152519</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152519/meme-coin-base-dex-rocketswap-hit-866k-exploit"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T09:52:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The RocketSwap hackers then bridged the stolen amount back to Ethereum and created a meme coin with the loot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jacobi Asset Management Launch Europe's First Bitcoin ETF]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148433</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148433/jacob-asset-management-launch-europe-first-bitcoin-etf"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T07:01:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Europe's inaugural Bitcoin exchange-traded fund went live today on Euronext Amsterdam, beating the U.S. to the punch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance US Seeks Protective Order Against 'Fishing Expedition' by SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152513</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152513/binance-protective-order-sec-fishing-expedition"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T06:29:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto exchange says SEC discovery requests go far beyond the scope agreed upon in the consent order.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt AI, Edited by Ryan Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Custodian Prime Trust Files for Bankruptcy]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152508</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152508/prime-trust-chapter-11-bankruptcy"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T06:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A former Bank of Nevada president will oversee the Chapter 11 process, which may include the sale of all remaining Prime Trust assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt AI, Edited by Ryan Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Achieving the Singularity is 'All About Progress': AI Executive]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152496</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152496/the-singularity-ai-general-artificial-intelligence"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T00:23:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The arrival of the pivotal moment for civilization may arrive ahead of schedule, says SingularityNET COO Janet Adams.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix Starts Streaming Video Games—Here's Why It's a Big Deal]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152490</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152490/netflix-now-streaming-video-games-heres-why-big-deal"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T23:11:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gaming is an enormous industry, and streaming giant Netflix could fuel even further growth by serving on-demand games via nearly any device.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Are 5 Games Building on Ethereum Scaler Immutable zkEVM]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152481</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152481/games-building-on-ethereum-scaler-immutable-zkevm"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T23:02:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Immutable zkEVM's testnet launched today. From strategy games to shooters, here are five of the biggest NFT games coming to the network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried Used $100 Million in Stolen Cash for Political Donations, DOJ Alleges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152483</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152483/sam-bankman-fried-stolen-customer-funds-political-donations-democrats-republicans"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T22:31:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Justice Department claims the disgraced crypto mogul used client funds to “influence cryptocurrency regulation.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FDIC Highlights 'Novel and Complex' Crypto Risks in Annual Review]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152484</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152484/fdic-cryptocurrency-novel-complex-risks"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T22:26:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was the first time the bank regulator dedicated a section to digital assets in its regular risk report.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Sleuth ZachXBT Avoids Lawsuit After Backing Off Claims Against NFT Trader]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152463</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152463/crypto-sleuth-zachxbt-avoids-lawsuit-after-backing-off-claims-against-nft-trader"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T19:26:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jeffrey "Machi Big Brother" Huang has withdrawn his defamation suit against ZachXBT, but only after the sleuth softened his published accusations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Institutional Investors Continue to Bet Big on XRP Following Ripple's Partial SEC Win]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152421</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152421/institutional-investors-continue-bet-big-xrp-following-ripple-partial-sec-win"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T18:50:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Major investors are still showing interest in XRP, pouring cash into it for the 16th week running per data from CoinShares.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Claude AI Developer Anthropic Raises $100M From South Korean Telco Giant SK]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152450</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152450/claude-ai-developer-anthropic-raises-100-million-from-south-korean-telecom-sk"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T18:12:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic’s war chest gets a bit bigger, as firms line up to bet on the OpenAI rival.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miner Hut 8 Shares Plummet 8% After Disappointing Q2 Revenue Figures]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152455</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152455/bitcoin-miner-hut-8-shares-down-58-percent-after-disappointing-quarter"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T17:43:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since last year, Hut 8 has been squeezed between operational issues and rising Bitcoin network difficulty.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aurory's Origin Story: How JRPGs Inspired the Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/O0S201TB/aurorys-origin-story-how-jrpgs-inspired-the-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/O0S201TB/aurorys-origin-story-how-jrpgs-inspired-the-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T16:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Jason Nelson talks to Aurory's Head of Marketing and Business Development Michael Natoli about the origins of the Aurory crypto games at the Solana PlayGG event.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FarmVille Creator Zynga Reveals First Ethereum NFT Game: Sugartown]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152425</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152425/farmville-creator-zynga-reveals-first-ethereum-nft-game-sugartown"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T16:48:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The casual and mobile publisher behind FarmVille and Words With Friends will launch the Ethereum-based Sugartown later this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Rolls Out Crypto Services in Canada]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152424</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152424/coinbase-rolls-out-crypto-services-canada"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T15:57:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company will kick start its launch by offering a free trial for its new subscription service, Coinbase One.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HBAR Surges 16% as FedNow Adds Hedera Project Dropp to 'Service Provider Showcase']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152419</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152419/hbar-surges-fednow-adds-hedera-project-dropp-service-provider-showcase"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T15:08:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Federal Reserve's payment service FedNow has added the Hedera-powered micropayments platform Dropp to its list showcasing service providers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Frontier Fund Launches Accelerator to Boost Ordinals Adoption]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152406</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152406/bitcoin-frontier-fund-launches-accelerator-to-boost-ordinals-adoption"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T14:38:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Led by Bitcoin entrepreneur and influencer Trevor Owens, the fund offers seed investments and mentorship to Ordinals-based startups.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maker Protocol Revenues Hit 2-Year High of $165M as Interest Rates Soar]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152398</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152398/maker-protocol-revenues-hit-2-year-high-165m-interest-rates-soar"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T14:04:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maker protocol's governance move to increase DAI returns and increasing U.S. Treasury yields are boosting the protocol’s revenue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MetaMask, Banxa Roll Out '1-Click' Crypto Buys With Apple Pay]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152393</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152393/metamask-banxa-roll-out-1-click-crypto-buys-apple-pay"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto wallet MetaMask now offers an optimized Apple Pay option thanks to fiat-to-crypto onramp and fintech firm Banxa.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Argentina's Newest Presidential Candidate Javier Milei Is Pro-Bitcoin—What Does That Mean?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152388</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152388/argentina-president-candidate-javier-milei-pro-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T10:33:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Javier Milei is known for being a staunch anti-Central Banker, pro-private sector money, and an alleged promoter of a Ponzi scheme.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meme Coins PEPE and SHIB Rally Double Digits on the Week]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152377</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152377/meme-coins-pepe-shib-rally-double-digits-week"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T09:04:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Popular meme coins PepeCoin and Shiba Inu have both enjoyed significant rallies over the past seven days, each rising more than 15%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zunami Protocol Loses Over $2.1 Million in Price Manipulation Hack]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152366</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152366/zunami-protocol-curve-finance-hack"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T02:36:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The DeFi yield farming aggregator promised "the highest APY on the market."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump, Long Skeptical of Crypto, Holds Up to $500,000 In Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152361</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152361/donald-trump-ethereum-crypto-holdings"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T01:36:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The former president and 2024 Republican frontrunner has been dismissive about the value of cryptocurrency in the past.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Sucks for Sam’ Says Martin Shkreli as Bankman-Fried Is Booked Into Brooklyn Prison]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152355</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152355/sam-bankman-fried-brooklyn-prison-conditions"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T21:26:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Brooklyn jail previously held Ghislaine Maxwell and Martin Shkreli.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former SEC Attorney John Reed Stark Says SEC Will Not Approve a Bitcoin Spot ETF]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152357</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152357/former-sec-attorney-john-reed-stark-bitcoin-spot-etf"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T21:20:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The attorney says a Republican administration after 2024 would be friendlier to ETF applications and roll back enforcement actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week on Crypto Twitter: PayPal Announces Stablecoin While SEC Saves Face in Ripple Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152350</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152350/this-week-on-crypto-twitter-paypal-announces-stablecoin-while-sec-saves-face-in-ripple-lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T20:55:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There were also strong indications of incoming Ethereum Futures ETFs this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Law Professors Scrutinize SEC Notion of ‘Investment Contract’ in Coinbase Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152343</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152343/sec-investment-contract-howey-test-amicus-brief"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T17:57:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The amicus brief included subject expertise from legal scholars at some of the top U.S. law schools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Bring Wall Street Into Crypto? Build Better ‘Piping,’ Says Talos CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152315</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152315/wall-street-crypto-institutional-investors-talos-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-08-12T17:47:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anton Katz says Wall Street firms need tools that better connect them to trading opportunities similar to the ones they use on capital markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aragon Aims to Accelerate DAO Launches With Base]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152299</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152299/aragon-osx-dao-launching-platform-coinbase-base"/>
        <updated>2023-08-12T17:10:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aragon is launching its namesake app and OSx protocol on the new Coinbase blockchain, which can help DAOs get off the ground without developer expertise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paris Hilton Won't Stop Trying to Make 'Sliving' Happen]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152264</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152264/paris-hilton-wont-stop-trying-make-sliving-happen"/>
        <updated>2023-08-12T16:25:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The influencer has launched Slivingland, a Roblox game inspired by a word she's been trying to get off the ground for almost four years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why the MET Is Expanding Into the Metaverse With Roblox]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152282</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152282/the-met-metropolitan-museum-roblox-replica-quest"/>
        <updated>2023-08-12T16:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Metropolitan Museum has launched a quest based app and installed a virtual doppelgänger on the Roblox gaming platform to meet young visitors where they are.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephanie Hirschmiller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chatbot Makers Respond to Accusations That AI Promotes Eating Disorders]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152276</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152276/chatbot-makers-respond-to-accusations-that-ai-promotes-eating-disorders"/>
        <updated>2023-08-12T15:43:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Center for Countering Digital Hate tested the safety guardrails of popular chatbots and found them lacking.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Bitcoin and Ethereum Prices Inch Upwards After PayPal Pitches Stablecoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152271</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152271/this-week-in-coins-bitcoin-and-ethereum-prices-inch-upwards-after-paypal-pitches-stablecoin"/>
        <updated>2023-08-12T15:07:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC this week did a lot of playing for time, but a new note on stablecoins by the Federal Reserve signaled a possible softening on crypto in Washington.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Loan Is Still a Loan Even in DeFi]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152189</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152189/loan-is-still-loan-even-defi"/>
        <updated>2023-08-12T10:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What happens when you mix microfinancing, a motorbike company in Kenya, and decentralized lending? Lots of risk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Hope You Enjoy Prison': Crypto Twitter Reacts as Sam Bankman-Fried's Bail Is Revoked]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152259</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152259/crypto-twitter-reacts-sam-bankman-fried-bail-revoked-ftx"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T23:55:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Disgraced FTX founder and former CEO Sam Bankman-Fried was sent to jail for witness tampering—and crypto personalities didn't hold back.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Degens Allegedly Launched Lil Tay Token Amid Teen Rapper's Death Hoax]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152248</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152248/degens-allegedly-launched-lil-tay-token-amid-teen-rapper-death-hoax"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T23:13:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The internet-famous rapper is apparently alive, but now there’s crypto confusion in the mix thanks to multiple Lil Tay-themed tokens.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Parallel TCG: Inside the Sci-Fi Card Game’s Closed Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/q8YVWJh4/parallel-tcg-inside-the-sci-fi-card-games-closed-beta</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/q8YVWJh4/parallel-tcg-inside-the-sci-fi-card-games-closed-beta"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T15:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin goes hands-on with Parallel’s closed beta on Windows PC to find out what sets it apart from other crypto card-battlers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 Games Need to Compete with All Games, Says Solana Foundation GM]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ud9wTd4s/web3-games-need-to-compete-with-all-games-says-solana-foundation-gm</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ud9wTd4s/web3-games-need-to-compete-with-all-games-says-solana-foundation-gm"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T19:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Foundation's General Manager of Games Johnny Lee tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about Solana's PlayGG conference and shares his take on crypto gaming and the "play-to-earn" concept.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Many Early Blockchain Games Were 'Cash Grabs,' Says Twitch Streamer Alliestrasza]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BA4yE45A/many-early-blockchain-games-were-cash-grabs-says-twitch-streamer-alliestrasza</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BA4yE45A/many-early-blockchain-games-were-cash-grabs-says-twitch-streamer-alliestrasza"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T16:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["I wrote them off," Twitch streamer Alliestrasza said of her initial thoughts on many early blockchain games. She tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how her perspective on Web3 games has evolved over time and now sees blockchain games getting significantly better.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['MetalCore' Game Preview: Hands-on With the 'Titanfall' Meets 'Destiny' NFT Mashup]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/tjK6i7lv/metalcore-game-preview-hands-on-with-the-titanfall-meets-destiny-nft-mashup</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/tjK6i7lv/metalcore-game-preview-hands-on-with-the-titanfall-meets-destiny-nft-mashup"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T19:46:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MetalCore is an upcoming mech shooter developed by Studio 369, and it's being developed on Ethereum scaling network Immutable zkEVM. Decrypt contributor Ryan Gladwin played through the prologue and tested out the recent Alpha 3 online experience to get a sense of the NFT-infused mashup of Titanfall and Destiny.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Give Projects a Chance,' Says Aurory's Michael Natoli on NFT Game Challenges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/nBNKKZdK/give-projects-a-chance-says-aurorys-michael-natoli-on-nft-game-challenges</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/nBNKKZdK/give-projects-a-chance-says-aurorys-michael-natoli-on-nft-game-challenges"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aurory is an NFT-driven game franchise that started life on Solana and is expanding to other chains. Decrypt's Jason Nelson spoke with Aurory Head of Marketing Michael Natoli at Solana's PlayGG event, where Natoli shared his thoughts on the challenges that blockchain games face in reaching players.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Is Only Network Ready for Gaming: Solana Foundation's Johnny Lee]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5OvV3ZXn/solana-is-only-network-ready-for-gaming-solana-foundations-johnny-lee</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5OvV3ZXn/solana-is-only-network-ready-for-gaming-solana-foundations-johnny-lee"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T17:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Foundation General Manager Johnny Lee tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how the Solana network will tackle the scaling problem that blockchain games pose for the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Com2uS Is Going "Full Speed" on Crypto Gaming: Kyu Lee]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pYMZRoYy/com2us-is-going-full-speed-on-crypto-gaming-kyu-lee</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pYMZRoYy/com2us-is-going-full-speed-on-crypto-gaming-kyu-lee"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kyu Lee is the President of game studio Com2uS USA. In an interview, he shares the studio's approach to Web3 and crypto gaming with Decrypt GG's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Discord Game with AI and Blockchain: 'Alchemy: Battle for Ankhos' Creative Lead Alex Finden]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mF18GHGo/building-a-discord-game-with-ai-and-blockchain-alchemy-battle-for-ankhos-creative-lead-alex-finden</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mF18GHGo/building-a-discord-game-with-ai-and-blockchain-alchemy-battle-for-ankhos-creative-lead-alex-finden"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T21:55:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Jason Nelson interviews Alchemy: Battle for Ankhos Creative Director Alex Finden at the Solana PlayGG event in San Diego, California.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Big Respect Between Ethereum and Cosmos Developer Communities': dYdX Foundation CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/XU5MbCGE/big-respect-between-ethereum-and-cosmos-developer-communities-dydx-foundation-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/XU5MbCGE/big-respect-between-ethereum-and-cosmos-developer-communities-dydx-foundation-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T13:24:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CEO of the dYdX Foundation Charles d'Haussy unpacks the decision behind moving one of the largest decentralized exchange protocol's over to its very own chain built on Cosmos. A key driver, he told Decrypt at this year's EthCC event, was that instead of launching on a rollup or another layer-1, launching a fully customized chain will allow dYdX to fine tune the network for its product's needs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Staking Solution Lido 'Had Perfect Product Market Fit' at Launch, Says DAO's Biz Dev Contributor]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/fUHhelhV/ethereum-staking-solution-lido-had-perfect-product-market-fit-at-launch-says-daos-biz-dev-contributor</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/fUHhelhV/ethereum-staking-solution-lido-had-perfect-product-market-fit-at-launch-says-daos-biz-dev-contributor"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T08:43:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marin Tvrdić, a business development contributor to the Lido DAO, sat down with Decrypt during this year's EthCC to break down how the liquid staking protocol has managed such a massive lead, how it plans to keep that lead, and the protocol's new dual-governance tokenomics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's Going to Stop All the DeFi Hacks? 'Standards,' Says OpenZepplin Security Architect]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/aYNuFdAi/whats-going-to-stop-all-the-defi-hacks-standards-says-openzepplin-security-architect</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/aYNuFdAi/whats-going-to-stop-all-the-defi-hacks-standards-says-openzepplin-security-architect"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T08:04:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenZeppelin's security solutions architect Michael Lewellen sat down with Decrypt to discuss how the industry can become a little safer for users at this year's EthCC Paris. The key? Introducing security standards across the industry so folks know what an audit actually means and where risks lie, be it bad faith actors or poor implementation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Ev.io' Game Review: Earn Solana While Blasting Enemies]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/2ZmkuhL2/evio-game-review-earn-solana-while-blasting-enemies</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/2ZmkuhL2/evio-game-review-earn-solana-while-blasting-enemies"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T22:21:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ev.io is a web-based first-person shooter that's free to play, but lets NFT holders earn in-game currency that can be redeemed for Solana (SOL). Decrypt contributor Ryan Gladwin shares his review of the fun throwback to Quake-style blasting, albeit with a modern crypto twist.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Moving Fast and Breaking Things Isn't the Web3 Ethos': MetaMask Product Lead]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/l1EbLgl3/moving-fast-and-breaking-things-isnt-the-web3-ethos-metamask-product-lead</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/l1EbLgl3/moving-fast-and-breaking-things-isnt-the-web3-ethos-metamask-product-lead"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T15:45:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Account abstraction this, smart wallets that. Discussions at EthCC Paris about improving user experience have pointed at industry leader MetaMask as an example of what not to do. But that may soon change, with a host of updates and optimizations coming to crypto's number one wallet, said its product lead Alex Jupiter. It still may take some time, though, before these changes take effect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling Smart Wallets on Starknet 'Was The Winning Combination', Says Argent Co-Founder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/gnBsxw4D/scaling-smart-wallets-on-starknet-was-the-winning-combination-says-argent-co-founder</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/gnBsxw4D/scaling-smart-wallets-on-starknet-was-the-winning-combination-says-argent-co-founder"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T07:35:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Argent co-founder Julien Niset told Decrypt at EthCC Paris that he wants to make crypto wallets disappear. Or at least how they're currently conceived. From clunky seed phrases to a stiff user experience, Argent hopes to make using crypto a little less intimidating and a whole lot more fun.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Mighty Action Heroes' Open Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/litL6kKs/inside-mighty-action-heroes-open-beta</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/litL6kKs/inside-mighty-action-heroes-open-beta"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T18:23:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mighty Action Heroes is the flagship blockchain title from Mighty Bear Games. But is the browser-based battle royale shooter worth checking out? Decrypt's Kate Irwin offers her thoughts and a first look at the upcoming game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>