<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-05-03T02:27:29.528Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-05-03T02:27:29.528Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether Q1 2024 Attestation Reveals Record $4.52 Billion Profits]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742a4535a9</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/tether-q1-2024-attestation-reveals-record-4-52-billion-profits/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T02:24:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tether, one of the largest cryptocurrency companies, has recently released an attestation of its financial activity corresponding to Q1 2024. Tether registered a record-breaking $4.52 billion in profits, and disclosed its net equity levels, reporting $11.37 billion as of March 31, 2024. Tether issued over $12.5 billion USDT during this period. Tether Attestation Registers Record-Breaking […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 May: Four Solana Memecoins That Could Skyrocket 9,000% and Challenge Shiba Inu and Dogecoin]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19456082/3-May-Four-Solana-Memecoins-That-Could-Skyrocket-9000-and-Challenge-Shiba-Inu-and-Dogecoin</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19456082/3-May-Four-Solana-Memecoins-That-Could-Skyrocket-9000-and-Challenge-Shiba-Inu-and-Dogecoin"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T02:11:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB) and Dogecoin (DOGE) are two dog-themed memecoins that went viral and delivered...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC will classify ETH as security and reject spot Ethereum ETFs, says Michael Saylor]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19456081/SEC-will-classify-ETH-as-security-and-reject-spot-Ethereum-ETFs-says-Michael-Saylor</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19456081/SEC-will-classify-ETH-as-security-and-reject-spot-Ethereum-ETFs-says-Michael-Saylor"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T02:09:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Saylor believes that the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) will label Ethereum as a security this summer and consequently deny all spot Ethereum ETF applications. He also claimed that other major cryptos like Binance Coin (BNB), Solana (SOL), Ripple (XRP), and Cardano (ADA)...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MoonPay Expands Crypto Purchasing Options For US Users With PayPal Integration]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742a46b59e</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/moonpay-crypto-options-users-paypal-integration/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T02:08:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a significant development, MoonPay, a crypto payment platform, has announced that users in the United States can now easily buy and sell over 110 cryptocurrencies using PayPal. 
 
The integration, unveiled Thursday, simplifies transactions for new MoonPay users who already have a PayPal account and regularly use it for online transactions. Users can fund their cryptocurrency purchases via their PayPal balance, direct bank withdrawal, or debit card without manually entering payment information.
 
MoonPay And PayPal Join Forces
 
Per the announcement, one of the key advantages of this collaboration is the added layer of security provided by PayPal, which does not disclose full financial details during transactions. MoonPay co-founder and CEO, Ivan Soto-Wright, emphasized the significance …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu: ShibaSwap to operate on Ethereum, Solana: Impact on SHIB?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19456074/Shiba-Inu-ShibaSwap-to-operate-on-Ethereum-Solana-Impact-on-SHIB</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19456074/Shiba-Inu-ShibaSwap-to-operate-on-Ethereum-Solana-Impact-on-SHIB"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T02:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shibaswap would now operate on both the Ethereum and Shibarium networks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Loses Historical Level, Analyst Says “Reclaim And Bounce, Or Die”]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19456066/Bitcoin-Loses-Historical-Level-Analyst-Says-Reclaim-And-Bounce-Or-Die</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19456066/Bitcoin-Loses-Historical-Level-Analyst-Says-Reclaim-And-Bounce-Or-Die"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T02:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An analyst has pointed out how Bitcoin recently closed below a historically important on-chain level, a failure to reclaim which could spell trouble for BTC. Bitcoin Fell Below Short-Term Holder Cost Basis In Latest Crash In a new post on X, Maartunn discussed BTC’s recent close below the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Analyst Is Long On King Crypto As Fed Moves To Unwind Treasury Buybacks: 'QE Is CLose']]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19456078/Bitcoin-Analyst-Is-Long-On-King-Crypto-As-Fed-Moves-To-Unwind-Treasury-Buybacks-QE-Is-CLose</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19456078/Bitcoin-Analyst-Is-Long-On-King-Crypto-As-Fed-Moves-To-Unwind-Treasury-Buybacks-QE-Is-CLose"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T01:45:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (CRYPTO: BTC) analyst Michael van de Poppe takes a bullish stance on the cryptocurrency as the Federal Reserve begins unwinding Treasury buybacks, signaling a potential shift in monetary policy. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JPMorgan Waves Red Flag: Urges Caution As Crypto Market Teeters on Edge]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742a43b5d6</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/jpmorgan-waves-urges-caution-as-crypto-market/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T01:09:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In recent evaluations by JPMorgan analysts, cryptocurrencies’ future appears to be uncertain. Despite the sector’s rapid expansion and increasing mainstream acceptance, the financial giant advises a cautious approach in the short term.
 
This conservative stance stems from “diminishing retail interest” and a “scarcity of positive market catalysts.”
 
 
Analyzing The Shifts: From Enthusiasm To Caution
 
JPMorgan’s scrutiny reveals a marked shift in market dynamics. Over recent weeks, significant selling and profit-taking activities have been observed, particularly from retail investors who seem to be retreating from crypto and equity markets.
 
According to JPMorgan analysts, this trend is corroborated by a notable decrease in net inflows to equity funds, turning negative for the first time…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JPMorgan Waves Red Flag: Urges Caution As Crypto Market Teeters on Edge]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19455971/JPMorgan-Waves-Red-Flag-Urges-Caution-As-Crypto-Market-Teeters-on-Edge</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19455971/JPMorgan-Waves-Red-Flag-Urges-Caution-As-Crypto-Market-Teeters-on-Edge"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T01:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In recent evaluations by JPMorgan analysts, cryptocurrencies’ future appears to be uncertain. Despite the sector’s rapid expansion and increasing mainstream acceptance, the financial giant advises a cautious approach in the short term. This conservative stance stems from “diminishing retail...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Examining MATIC’s future as Polygon records new ATH in key area]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19455966/Examining-MATICs-future-as-Polygon-records-new-ATH-in-key-area</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19455966/Examining-MATICs-future-as-Polygon-records-new-ATH-in-key-area"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T01:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon’s daily active addresses reached an all-time high while MATIC’s price gained bullish momentum]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Day 2: Bitcoin For Corporations | MicroStrategy World 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19452780/Day-2-Bitcoin-For-Corporations-MicroStrategy-World-2024</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19452780/Day-2-Bitcoin-For-Corporations-MicroStrategy-World-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T00:58:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy World: Bitcoin for Corporations Day 2 | Streaming LIVE from Las Vegas, NVJoin leading Fortune 1000 companies to learn from builders and advocates how Bitcoin can supercharge corporations in the 21st century.Day 2 Agenda (PDT):9:00am | Bitcoin: There is No Second Best: Michael...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Holders - Don't Be Fooled]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19455973/Bitcoin-Holders-Dont-Be-Fooled</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19455973/Bitcoin-Holders-Dont-Be-Fooled"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T00:47:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin price news, crypto market updates and altcoins. Particl https://pioneer.particle.network?inviteCode=XP0CLG DRIP dripfi.io/app/?ref=8d7f60e2-e7e8-4066-8bab-66268554bdf0 Adam Livestream https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ROHgrTuw0V8 🔥 GET MY FREE NEWSLETTER 👉...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Economist Alex Krüger Goes ‘Max Long’ on Crypto Positions – Here Are His Altcoin Picks]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19455895/Economist-Alex-Kruger-Goes-Max-Long-on-Crypto-Positions-Here-Are-His-Altcoin-Picks</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19455895/Economist-Alex-Kruger-Goes-Max-Long-on-Crypto-Positions-Here-Are-His-Altcoin-Picks"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T00:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Popular trader and economist Alex Krüger says he’s currently “max long” on the crypto market. Krüger tells his 173,800 followers on the social media platform X that he’s hedged and unhedged multiple times but he’s now max long in “very concentrated positions.” The economist notes that he’s...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin: Longs erase $100M in 1 day, more to come for BTC’s price?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19455900/Bitcoin-Longs-erase-100M-in-1-day-more-to-come-for-BTCs-price</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19455900/Bitcoin-Longs-erase-100M-in-1-day-more-to-come-for-BTCs-price"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T00:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price decline that Bitcoin is facing currently has led to large liquidations of long positions in the past few days.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saylor predicts SEC will designate Ethereum as a security and deny spot ETF applications this summer]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19455902/Saylor-predicts-SEC-will-designate-Ethereum-as-a-security-and-deny-spot-ETF-applications-this-summer</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19455902/Saylor-predicts-SEC-will-designate-Ethereum-as-a-security-and-deny-spot-ETF-applications-this-summer"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T00:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy executive chairman and co-founder Michael Saylor believes the SEC will classify Ethereum as a security this summer and reject the related spot ETF applications filed by various asset managers, including BlackRock. Saylor made the prediction in a social media post on May 2 during a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fantom (FTM) Price Correction Concludes as Buy Signals Emerge]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19455969/Fantom-FTM-Price-Correction-Concludes-as-Buy-Signals-Emerge</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19455969/Fantom-FTM-Price-Correction-Concludes-as-Buy-Signals-Emerge"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T23:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fantom (FTM) price has been consolidating for some time now and could continue. This is because the altcoin has not seen any strong directional bias in weeks. However, a buy signal currently appears on the on-chain metrics, which could help FTM escape consolidation. Buy Singlas Pop Up for Fantom...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jack Dorsey’s Block to use 10% of Bitcoin profit to buy BTC every month]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19455884/Jack-Dorseys-Block-to-use-10-of-Bitcoin-profit-to-buy-BTC-every-month</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19455884/Jack-Dorseys-Block-to-use-10-of-Bitcoin-profit-to-buy-BTC-every-month"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T23:52:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Block, Inc. co-founder Jack Dorsey told shareholders its Bitcoin-buying plan during an earnings call, saying its an “investment in a future where economic empowerment is the norm.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EigenLayer Increases Minimum Airdrop Allocation]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19455907/EigenLayer-Increases-Minimum-Airdrop-Allocation</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19455907/EigenLayer-Increases-Minimum-Airdrop-Allocation"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T23:51:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More than 280,000 users of the restaking protocol will receive an additional 100 EIGEN tokens.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Saylor Delivers Bitcoin Masterclass To Fortune 1000 Companies]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742a4b2d9a</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/michael-saylor-delivers-bitcoin-masterclass-to-fortune-1000-companies"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T23:45:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a Keynote address at MicroStrategy World: Bitcoin for Corporations, MicroStrategy Executive Chairman Michael Saylor delivered a masterclass on corporate finance and the power of bitcoin to supercharge corporate balance sheets. Saylor made a point to emphasize Bitcoin as the single solution for capital appreciation in an inflationary environment.

In his speech, Saylor likened the cost of capital to being the benchmark which a company must surpass to increase its purchasing power, arguing that “Bitcoin is the only asset that exceeds the cost of capital. Another way to say that, is everything else is dilutive.”
Further describing the true cost of capital, he noted that the “S&P is the modern surrogate for the cost of capital… If you had to pick one metric and say, what's the metric that g…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spencer Nichols</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Rides Bitcoin ETF Wave as Profits Soar past $1B in Q1]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742a4b318e</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/coinbase-rides-bitcoin-etf-wave-as-profits-soar-past-1b-in-q1/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T23:45:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase has released its first quarter report for  
2024, showcasing a substantial 72% quarter-on-quarter increase in total revenue  
to $1.6 billion. This surge was accompanied by a notable net income  
of $1,176 billion, representing an increase of 1,588% YoY. This figure represents a turnaround from a net loss of $79 million in the same period last year. Compared to last quarter, Coinbase's net income surged 331%.
The cryptocurrency exchange experienced an uptick in  
its market share across US spot and derivatives trading, along with reaching record highs in Coinbase Prime usage and USDC market capitalization. According to the company, notable international operations significantly contributed to the overall growth.
Impact of Bitcoin ETFs
Coinbase mentioned: "While we cannot attribute…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Massive $43M Crypto Ponzi Scheme Uncovered In New York, Leading To Wire Fraud Arrest]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742a4bcbe7</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/massive-43m-crypto-ponzi-scheme-uncovered-in-ny/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T23:39:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[United States Attorney Damian Williams and FBI Assistant Director James Smith announced the unsealing of an indictment charging Idin Dalpour with wire fraud concerning a multi-year crypto Ponzi scheme that defrauded investors of at least $43 million. 
 
Wire Fraud Indictment Unveils $43M Ponzi Scheme
 
The indictment alleges that from approximately 2020 to April 2024, Dalpour orchestrated a crypto-related Ponzi scheme targeting investors both in the United States and abroad. 
 
Dalpour purportedly solicited investments through an entity he controlled, Entity-1, which claimed to be involved in a Las Vegas hospitality enterprise and a crypto trading venture. 
 
However, instead of utilizing the funds as promised, Dalpour used money from new investors to pay earlier investors, employing a cla…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Only Two Days Left to Earn $FAR Tokens in Farcana Playtest]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19455871/Only-Two-Days-Left-to-Earn-FAR-Tokens-in-Farcana-Playtest</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19455871/Only-Two-Days-Left-to-Earn-FAR-Tokens-in-Farcana-Playtest"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T23:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Farcana, a multiplayer arena hero shooter with a Web3 economy, started its playtest event called Gateway: Showdown on 30th April. This playtest is currently open to all players, which means you can participate simply by signing-up on its official website, and installing the game. Players...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iran and Russia Working on Bilateral CBDC-powered Trade Solutions]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19455906/Iran-and-Russia-Working-on-Bilateral-CBDC-powered-Trade-Solutions</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19455906/Iran-and-Russia-Working-on-Bilateral-CBDC-powered-Trade-Solutions"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T23:30:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Iran and Russia are working on CBDC and “digital financial asset” (DFA)-powered trade solutions, an Iranian official has confirmed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Standard Chartered Warns Bitcoin Price Could Fall to $50K]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742a356133</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/standard-chartered-warns-bitcoin-price-could-fall-to-50k/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T23:23:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Standard Chartered Bank has warned that bitcoin’s price could potentially decline to $50,000. The head of digital asset research at the bank attributed this forecast to a mix of crypto-specific factors and broader macroeconomic influences. Additionally, he warned about the risk of liquidation for some spot exchange-traded fund (ETF) positions, emphasizing that over half of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CRYPTO DIP BUYERS WILL 50X (Secret Altcoin GEMS for max gains)]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19455869/CRYPTO-DIP-BUYERS-WILL-50X-Secret-Altcoin-GEMS-for-max-gains</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19455869/CRYPTO-DIP-BUYERS-WILL-50X-Secret-Altcoin-GEMS-for-max-gains"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T23:21:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[👨‍🌾 SCRAPPY ENTREPRENEURS ONLY!! https://t.me/wagiefarm🔥 Activate Nord VPN for JUST $3 PER MONTH and get access to Threat Protection: https://nordvpn.com/ellio🔥 GET UP TO $200 BY SIGNING UP FOR COINBASE NOW!! http://coinbase-consumer.sjv.io/eKZj26Coinbase New User Incentive is a limited time...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Name Service challenges Unstoppable Domains’ patent]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19455838/Ethereum-Name-Service-challenges-Unstoppable-Domains-patent</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19455838/Ethereum-Name-Service-challenges-Unstoppable-Domains-patent"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T23:15:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Name Service (ENS) has petitioned the United States Patent and Trademark Office (USPTO) to challenge the validity of a patent obtained by Unstoppable Domains (UD) in 2023. ENS claims that UD's patent utilizes technology that ENS had developed and open-sourced.In a statement on social...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Scaling Bitcoin Together” Event Set to Unite Bitcoin Leaders in Hong Kong]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742a364877</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/scaling-bitcoin-together-event-set-to-unite-bitcoin-leaders-in-hong-kong/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T23:14:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. As a part of Bitcoin Asia Week 2024, the “Scaling Bitcoin Together” event will take place on May 11, 2024, in Hong Kong. This event will bring together top blockchain experts to discuss how to grow the Bitcoin ecosystem. The “Scaling Bitcoin Together” aims to foster discussions that propel the development of the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong Bitcoin ETF launch in ‘top 20%’, STRK scam suspect busted: Asia Express]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19455831/Hong-Kong-Bitcoin-ETF-launch-in-top-20-STRK-scam-suspect-busted-Asia-Express</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19455831/Hong-Kong-Bitcoin-ETF-launch-in-top-20-STRK-scam-suspect-busted-Asia-Express"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T23:03:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Hong Kong Bitcoin ETF launch was in the top 20% of launches, and 77% of local crypto holders still plan to invest: Asia Express.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Script State from Lamport Signatures]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742a338179</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/technical/script-state-from-lamport-signatures-"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T22:24:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The last six months or so have seen several proposals for improvements to Bitcoin Script: CAT, 64-bit arithmetic, as well as some older ideas (CTV) and far-future ideas (Chialisp and Simplicity). This activity has largely overshadowed some revolutionary changes in our understanding of the existing Bitcoin Script, changes which form the basis of BitVM but which may also form the basis of other, equally-exciting improvements.
This article tries to summarize and organize research into Script by other people. I make no claim to originality or authorship of anything described here.
Bitcoin Script
As many readers are aware, Bitcoin Script is a simple programming language embedded in the Bitcoin blockchain, which is used to control under what conditions coins may move. By far the most common use …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Poelstra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analyst Identifies Crucial Dogecoin Support At $0.112-$0.123, Will Price Crash Further?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742a3e21bd</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-support-at-0-112-0-123/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T22:01:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin suffered a significant crash in the bloodbath that rocked the crypto market earlier this week, notching double-digit losses in the process. This has sent its support lower, and $0.112-$0.123 is now the level to hold for the meme coin. But what if it falls below this support?
 
Dogecoin Must Hold Support At $0.112-$0.123
 
Crypto analyst YG Crypto, in an analysis, identified $0.112-$0.123 as the major support levels for Dogecoin after the price crash. In the post that was made on X (formerly Twitter), the crypto analyst explained that these levels are important due to the fact that they have prevent massive price crashes for Dogecoin in the past.
 
 
As such, the meme coin needs to maintain above this level to continue its bullish trend. As of the early hours of Thursday, the DOGE …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jito Price Jumps After Topping Solana DeFi Protocols With $1 Billion Locked]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229227</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229227/jito-price-jumps-after-topping-solana-defi-protocols-with-1-billion-locked"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T21:36:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jito Network became the top DeFi protocol on Solana, with liquid staking pool token JitoSOL rising by 8.5%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bulletproof Cadillac, Butler, and $1.5M Titanic Watch: FTX Exec's Lavish Spending Continues]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229212</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229212/ftx-exec-lavish-spending-continues-1-5-million-watch-titanic"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T21:20:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former FTX Europe head Patrick Gruhn is spending his crypto riches— but his fortune is not without controversy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jack Dorsey's Block Adding More Bitcoin to Balance Sheet, Presents Road Map for Others]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742a3b21c8</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2024/05/02/jack-dorseys-block-adding-more-bitcoin-to-balance-sheet-presents-road-map-for-others/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T21:18:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The payments firm announced the news alongside its first quarter earnings report on Thursday afternoon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen  Alpher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JPMorgan: Retail Investors Drive Selloff in Both Crypto and Equity Markets]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742a3b85ad</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/jpmorgan-retail-investors-drive-selloff-in-both-crypto-and-equity-markets/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T21:15:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JPMorgan has highlighted a significant increase in selling and profit-taking across equity and crypto markets, driven largely by retail investors. The global investment bank also observed institutional momentum traders and quantitative funds reducing positions, particularly in stocks, bitcoin, and gold. Insights on Market Trends by JPMorgan JPMorgan, a global investment bank, has provided insights on […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase $1.6 Billion Quarterly Profits Boosted By Stablecoins, Rising Crypto Prices]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229217</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229217/coinbase-first-quarter-profit-report"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T21:10:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The San Francisco-based exchange has reported better-than-expected 2024 Q1 results.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo,André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Time To Buy The Bitcoin Dip? Analyst Upbeat As Federal Reserve Turns Dovish]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742a251d58</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/buy-bitcoin-dip-federal-reserve-turns-dovish/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T21:02:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Bitcoin drops, liquidating leveraged long bets along the way, one analyst, in a post on X, thinks this might be a prime opportunity to accumulate, citing historical patterns of pullbacks followed by impressive recoveries. 
 
Time To Load The Bitcoin Dip?
 
The analyst shared a chart indicating that Bitcoin is within historical retracement ranges. Whenever this happens, prices tend to bounce back sharply, tearing higher, much to the relief of holders.
 
 
 
 
Solid data back this assessment. The analyst said that since Bitcoin bottomed at $15,500 in 2022, there have been four distinct pullbacks, all within the -20% to -23% range. For the savvy, the trader continued, each of these downturns presented an opportunity to accumulate at a discount. 
 
Related Reading: Shiba Inu Fees On Fire: W…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dalmas Ngetich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hybrid L2 Build on Bitcoin Launches Mainnet; US Users Face Geo-Blocking]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742a224db5</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/hybrid-l2-build-on-bitcoin-launches-mainnet-us-users-face-geo-blocking/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T20:20:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The layer-two initiative known as BOB, short for ‘Build on Bitcoin,’ has declared its mainnet operational with over 40 apps launching in the initial phase. Notably, the BOB application that facilitates bridging and access to the ecosystem is geo-blocked in the United States. BOB Mainnet Activates, Project Expects a ‘Bitcoin-Driven Defi Summer’ On May 1, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will the Fed Cut Rates? Crypto and Wall Street Traders Aren’t Betting on It]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229213</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229213/fed-rate-cut-odds-crypto-polymarket-cme-tradfi"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T20:13:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Just cut the rates bro please,” pleaded a down-bad trader on Polymarket.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jack Dorsey’s Block Faces Federal Probe Over Alleged Bitcoin Transactions For Terrorist Groups]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742a2cabfa</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/jack-dorsey-block-federal-probe-crypto-transactions/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T20:01:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to an NBC report, federal prosecutors have initiated an investigation into Block, the financial technology company founded by Twitter co-founder Jack Dorsey, following allegations of compliance failures and links to terrorist networks through alleged crypto transactions. 
 
Notably, a former employee of Block has provided documents to the Southern District of New York, revealing compliance lapses, inadequate customer information collection, and the processing of crypto transactions for sanctioned countries and terrorist groups. 
 
Bitcoin Transactions Linked To Terrorism Revealed
 
Per the report, the former employee disclosed that Block’s units, Square and Cash App, failed to collect sufficient customer information necessary for assessing risks. Additionally, Square processed th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zksnacks to Cease Coinjoin Transactions, Affecting Wasabi, Trezor and Btcpay]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742a284418</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/zksnacks-to-cease-coinjoin-transactions-affecting-wasabi-trezor-and-btcpay/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T19:32:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Thursday, Zksnacks, the developer behind Wasabi Wallet, announced its decision to cease its coinjoin services following regulatory measures in the U.S. The company stated that the wallet will now operate as a standard non-custodial bitcoin wallet without the coinjoin feature. Zksnacks Withdraws Coinjoin Feature from Wasabi Wallet Following intensified regulatory scrutiny in the U.S., […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether Enters Transaction Surveillance Partnership with Chainalysis as Regulatory Pressure Mounts]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742a295543</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/05/02/tether-enters-transaction-surveillance-partnership-with-chainalysis-as-regulatory-pressure-mounts/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T19:24:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The monitoring system would help Tether identify risky crypto addresses that could be used for bypassing sanctions or illicit activities like terrorist financing, the company said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Flashes Bull Flag, Why A 150% Price Jump Is Imminent]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742a2b3ac4</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-flashes-bull-flag-150/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T19:10:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB) could soon witness a significant price rally, with crypto analyst Ali Martinez highlighting a bullish pattern forming on the meme coin’s chart. Shiba Inu’s price could potentially see a 150% gain when this rally happens. 
 
A Bull Flag Is Forming On SHIB’s Chart
 
Martinez mentioned in an X (formerly Twitter) post that Shiba Inu looks to be forming a bull flag on its daily chart. A bull flag is a bullish pattern that indicates that the crypto asset will soon see further moves to the upside. In anticipation of this move, the crypto analyst further revealed that he was placing a buy order around $0.000018343, aiming for a bullish breakout that would send Shiba Inu’s price to $0.000072323. 
 
 

 
 
 
Seeing that a rise to that price level represents about a 150% price gain f…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Transactions Plummet Following Absurd Runes and Halving Surge]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229185</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229185/bitcoin-transaction-fees-fall-after-halving-highs"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T18:50:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cost to send BTC skyrocketed immediately following the halving, but fees have since fallen back to Earth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elizabeth Warren's Latest Crypto Crusade: Bitcoin Mining In Iran]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229189</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229189/elizabeth-warren-iran-bitcoin-mining-terrorism"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T18:39:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The leading crypto critic in the U.S. Senate says the Iranian mining sector supports terrorism.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Messari CEO Criticizes US President’s Crypto Stance, Foresees ‘Mass Wealth Confiscation’ if Biden Gets Reelected]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742a10db94</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/messari-ceo-criticizes-us-presidents-crypto-stance-foresees-mass-wealth-confiscation-if-biden-gets-reelected/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T18:29:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, Messari’s founder and CEO, Ryan Selkis, has expressed strong opinions about the potential impact of a Joe Biden reelection on the cryptocurrency industry in the United States. On Thursday, Selkis voiced his concerns on the social media platform X, stating that a “second Biden term will lead to mass wealth confiscation and crypto seizures.” […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Institutional Selling Behind $57,000 Crash? Data Suggests So]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742a13cfe0</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-institutional-selling-behind-57000-crash/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T18:08:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data shows the Bitcoin Coinbase Premium has been negative for a while now, a sign that institutional selling has been occurring behind the scenes.
 
Bitcoin Coinbase Premium Gap Has Turned Quite Negative Recently
 
As pointed out by CryptoQuant Netherlands community manager Maartunn in a post on X, the Bitcoin Coinbase Premium Gap has been negative for seven straight days.
 
The “Coinbase Premium Gap” is an indicator that keeps track of the difference between the BTC prices listed on the cryptocurrency exchanges Coinbase (USD pair) and Binance (USDT pair). When the value of this metric is positive, it means that the price listed on Coinbase is greater than on Binance right now. Such a trend implies the buying pressure is higher (or alternatively, the selling pressure is lower) on the forme…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mom Sexualizes Herself on Livestream for Son’s Meme Coin—Then Ghosts]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229175</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229175/livemom-livestream-mom-son-meme-coin"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T17:41:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A mom used her boobs to help her son pump a meme coin, called LIVEMOM, to a $300K market cap before the token crashed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETFs Shed $563 Million as BlackRock's IBIT Marks First Daily Loss]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229168</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229168/bitcoin-etfs-shed-563-million-blackrock-ibit-losses"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T16:46:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spot Bitcoin ETFs posted record daily net outflows on Wednesday as BlackRock's IBIT faltered for the very first time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum and Solana Meme Coin Prices Surge Amid Modest Bitcoin Gains]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229150</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229150/ethereum-solana-meme-coins-surge-modest-bitcoin-gains"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T16:29:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin is rising after a rough week, but meme coins like Pepe, Bonk, Dogwifhat, and Dogecoin are the biggest winners today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are Parachains? Polkadot's Secret Weapon Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229149</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-are-parachains-polkadots-secret-weapon-explained"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T15:44:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Polkadot’s parachains offer a unique technical approach to achieving scalability and interoperability for blockchains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will McCurdy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Blogging Protocol Mirror Embraces Farcaster in Social Media Pivot]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229077</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229077/ethereum-blogging-protocol-mirror-farcaster-social-media-pivot"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T15:10:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mirror's team is now building a Farcaster-based social app called Kiosk, while Paragraph will take over Mirror. Collectively, they've raised $15 million.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FBI Arrests Man For Running Alleged $43 Million Crypto Trading Ponzi Scheme]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229132</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229132/fbi-arrests-man-for-running-alleged-43-million-crypto-trading-ponzi-scheme"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T13:21:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Manhattan man allegedly spent $1.7 million of investors' money on gambling debts, $400,000 on Art Direct, and his kids' private school tuition.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana GameShift Adds Google Cloud Integration for Crypto Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229078</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229078/solana-gameshift-google-cloud-integration-crypto-games"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T13:01:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creators building blockchain games with Solana Labs’ GameShift platform will be able to tap into Google Cloud features via the integration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PayPal Expands Crypto Offerings With  MoonPay Integration]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229096</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229096/paypal-adds-moonpay-for-crypto-purchases-debit"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PayPal has linked up with MoonPay to offer its millions of users access to over 100 cryptocurrencies]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Second-Largest European Bank BNP Paribas Bought BlackRock Bitcoin ETF Shares: SEC Filing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229113</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229113/second-largest-european-bank-bnp-paribas-bought-blackrock-bitcoin-etf-shares-sec-filing"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T11:45:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to a 13F report, BNP Paribas purchased IBIT shares in the first quarter of 2024—albeit less than 1 BTC worth at current prices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin and Ethereum Rebound as Interest Rates Remain Unchanged in US]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229103</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229103/bitcoin-and-ethereum-rebound-as-interest-rates-remain-unchanged-in-us"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T10:50:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin and Ethereum are rebounding after a rough couple of days leading up to the Federal Reserve deciding not to change interest rates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy Is Building ‘Decentralized ID’ on Bitcoin Using Ordinals-Like Inscriptions]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229087</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229087/orange-decentralized-identity-ordinals-inscriptions-microstrategy"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T00:25:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Saylor announced the Orange protocol for decentralized identification, hoping to anchor digital identities in the dominant blockchain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build on Bitcoin Launches Mainnet With Over 40 Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229079</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229079/build-on-bitcoin-launches-mainnet-with-over-40-apps"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T23:54:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BOB launches its Bitcoin layer-2 Ethereum rollup, with more to come over the next three weeks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[If the SEC Thinks Ethereum Is a Security, Are ETH ETFs Doomed?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229065</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229065/sec-ethereum-security-eth-etfs-doomed"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T20:54:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s now looking like a long road ahead for ETH to come to Wall Street. But that’s a surprise to few.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ronin's Path From Curated Ethereum Gaming to 'Pervasively Permissionless']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228301</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228301/ronin-path-curated-ethereum-gaming-pervasively-permissionless"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T20:41:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum gaming chain Ronin currently curates the games on its network. But it’s starting to eye up a permissionless future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Notcoin? The Telegram-Based Game, NOT Token, and Future Plans]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=223640</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-notcoin-telegram-based-game-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T19:39:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATED: When is the NOT token actually launching? Here's the latest, along with everything else you need to know about Notcoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery,Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here's How AI Can Help Find Money Laundering on Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229030</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229030/heres-how-ai-can-detect-money-laundering-on-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T18:46:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An Elliptic report shows how MIT-IBM AI Labs used deep learning AI techniques to detect fraud on the world’s dominant blockchain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Trade Sideways as Fed Leaves Interest Rates Untouched]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229041</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229041/bitcoin-ethereum-trade-sideways-as-fed-leaves-interest-rates-untouched"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T18:27:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amid signs of stubborn inflation in the U.S., the central bank kept its key interest rate at its highest level in over 23 years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Could Rebound As ‘Paper Hands’ Investors Flee, Analysts Say]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229046</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229046/bitcoin-paper-hands-correction-glassnode"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T18:18:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Investors often leave during the “local bottom.” and one analyst suggests BTC is reaching that point.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feds Are Investigating Jack Dorsey's Block Over Bitcoin Biz: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229047</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229047/feds-investigating-jack-dorsey-block-bitcoin-biz-report"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T18:06:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jack Dorsey's Block is reportedly under investigation for compliance issues, including with its Bitcoin business.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Hasn't Hit the Bottom Yet, Says Standard Chartered]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229039</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229039/bitcoin-could-fall-to-50000-standard-chartered"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T17:26:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The biggest digital coin still has room to fall, the British firm said in a new report.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Bitcoin Senator' Cynthia Lummis Blasts DOJ Stance on Private Crypto Wallets]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229020</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229020/bitcoin-senator-cynthia-lummis-blasts-doj-stance-crypto-wallets"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T17:09:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lummis argued the Department of Justice's position on self-custody "contradicts existing Treasury guidance" and "violates the rule of law."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF Leader BlackRock Leads $47M Funding Round in Securitize]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228992</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228992/bitcoin-etf-blackrock-leads-47-million-funding-round-securitize"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T16:48:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock’s BUIDL fund, created with Securitize, has $375 million in assets under management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Redstone Network Launches to Power Fully On-Chain Ethereum Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229005</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229005/redstone-network-launches-fully-on-chain-ethereum-games"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T16:01:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Powered by the Optimism OP Stack, Redstone enables “autonomous worlds” and other intriguing new types of on-chain Ethereum games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether Netted $4.52 Billion Q1 Profit Thanks To Bitcoin Gains]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228991</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228991/tether-netted-4-52-billion-q1-profit-thanks-to-bitcoin-gains"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T15:42:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tether’s Bitcoin investment is paying off, achieving much greater profit than the company’s immense bond portfolio.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BNB Chain's $1M Meme Innovation Contest Is 'Unleashing Meme Coin Creativity']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228494</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228494/bnb-chains-1m-meme-innovation-contest-is-unleashing-meme-coin-creativity"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T15:40:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The competition aims to encourage developers to create, launch and trade their meme coins on BNB Chain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Ethereum Founder Vitalik Buterin Keeps His Crypto Safe]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228946</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228946/how-ethereum-founder-vitalik-buterin-keeps-crypto-safe"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T14:38:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Decentralize your own security," says Ethereum founder Vitalik Buterin—but he doesn't use a cold wallet for his own personal crypto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Do A Little With Mike Demarais]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ajrh0oiK/we-do-a-little-with-mike-demarais</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ajrh0oiK/we-do-a-little-with-mike-demarais"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T15:11:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mike dropped knowledge bombs from years of building in the trenches alongside some deep cuts on the early Williamsburg crypto mafia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eth Rally Fails]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Gj7TMrbP/eth-rally-fails</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Gj7TMrbP/eth-rally-fails"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T12:45:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto falls, ETH/BTC rally again marks mini sell-off. Yen carry-trade implosion linked to worries. ETH gas fees hit 6-month lows. 3rd straight week of institutional outflows. Slowing BTC ETF flows are just a pause: Bernstein. BTC now on track for 5 red weeks in a row. BTC may have topped, could hit $35k: Brandt. ETFs may become big sellers: Bianco. Consensys list 4 reasons ETH isn’t a security. Rumours continue to grow of EigenLayer airdrop. Perp DEX volumes continue fall, GMX underperforms. Wallets begin to block US users after Samourai case. WLD in reported partnership talks with OpenAI. Large unlocks this week for SUI, PYTH & MEME.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Sasha Stiles’ Experiential, AI-Infused NFT Drop with Bang & Olufsen]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/6Vi2IgYj/inside-sasha-stiles-experiential-ai-infused-nft-drop-with-bang-olufsen</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/6Vi2IgYj/inside-sasha-stiles-experiential-ai-infused-nft-drop-with-bang-olufsen"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T22:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At a launch party for the collection in New York’s SoHo neighborhood, the artist broke down her latest art experiment, “Four Core Texts,” with Decrypt’s Sander Lutz.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interview: How 'Notcoin' Will Evolve After the NOT Token Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PprnGP14/interview-how-notcoin-will-evolve-after-the-not-token-launch</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PprnGP14/interview-how-notcoin-will-evolve-after-the-not-token-launch"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Open Builders founder Sasha Plotvinov speaks with Decrypt's Sander Lutz at Token 2049 Dubai about how he envisions Notcoin's expansion and evolution after the token drop—into something akin to the "Netflix of social, viral games."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Magic Runes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IGWg0R64/magic-runes</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IGWg0R64/magic-runes"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T13:59:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC stables at $66k, liquidations in narrow range. BTC funding again turns negative in bullish sign. ETFs net inflow after Grayscale moves to lower fees. BTC demand 5x vs supply post-halving: Bitfinex. SOL congestion issue now largely solved. Two SEC lawyers resign after ‘gross abuse of power’. Ripple fights to lower $2bn SEC fine. SAFE trades at $2.8bn FDV after OKX lists. MANEKI hits $150m on first day, China memes pump. Memecoins are ‘black hole you can’t ignore’. DeGods up 20%, may switch back to SOL. Magic Eden launches Runes platform ahead of time.  Louis Vuitton gifts Pharrell jacket to NFT holders. Melania Trump launches necklace with SOL NFTs. Hoodie Punk trades for $620K.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Luxury Watches, Designer Shoes Will Soon Trade Like NFTs: Arianee CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/CSNQG2md/luxury-watches-designer-shoes-will-soon-trade-like-nfts-arianee-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/CSNQG2md/luxury-watches-designer-shoes-will-soon-trade-like-nfts-arianee-ceo"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arianee CEO Pierre-Nicolas Hurstel sat down with Rug Radio founder Farokh and Decrypt’s Sander Lutz at NFT Paris to discuss everything from the future of on-chain luxury to the secret hack to finding the best restaurants in France.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notcoin's Co-Creator Explains the Game's Token Delay—And When to Expect NOT Now]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/7Zx33xo5/notcoins-co-creator-explains-the-games-token-delayand-when-to-expect-not-now</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/7Zx33xo5/notcoins-co-creator-explains-the-games-token-delayand-when-to-expect-not-now"/>
        <updated>2024-04-22T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Notcoin co-creator Sasha Plotvinov spoke with Decrypt's Sander Lutz at Token 2049 Dubai to discuss why the NOT token launch was pushed back from the original 4/20 target, when to expect the listing, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TON’s Justin Hyun Breaks Down The Importance of USDT Coming to Telegram]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ODQI6ACA/tons-justin-hyun-breaks-down-the-importance-of-usdt-coming-to-telegram</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ODQI6ACA/tons-justin-hyun-breaks-down-the-importance-of-usdt-coming-to-telegram"/>
        <updated>2024-04-19T10:14:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Token 2049 in Dubai, The Open Network’s director of investments sat down with Decrypt’s Sander Lutz to discuss what he sees as the game-changing integration of USDT onto TON, and his plans for getting Telegram’s 900 million users to start using crypto in the immediate future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Influencer Ansem Explains His Meme Coin Thesis and Why He’s Bullish on Bitcoin Runes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/u9DHFoK0/crypto-influencer-ansem-explains-his-meme-coin-thesis-and-why-hes-bullish-on-bitcoin-runes</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/u9DHFoK0/crypto-influencer-ansem-explains-his-meme-coin-thesis-and-why-hes-bullish-on-bitcoin-runes"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T21:56:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ansem, the crypto trader who's amassed a sizable following on the back of meme coin Dogwifhat (WIF) and other calls, chats with Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz at Token 2049 Dubai about his meme coin thesis, why he's bullish on Bitcoin Runes, and what he sees ahead for the crypto markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Sander Lutz Braves the Dubai Floods for a Crypto Conference]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/mtjVHGa3/decrypts-sander-lutz-braves-the-dubai-floods-for-a-crypto-conference</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/mtjVHGa3/decrypts-sander-lutz-braves-the-dubai-floods-for-a-crypto-conference"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T21:33:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz reports from Dubai amid a historic storm that flooded the famed city, trudging through the streets to complete his essential task: Attending the Token 2049 crypto conference.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gold Beats Its All Time High]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/6ULgUKVk/gold-beats-its-all-time-high</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/6ULgUKVk/gold-beats-its-all-time-high"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T09:53:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) maintains its trend of reaching higher lows amidst choppy market conditions. Exchange-traded funds (ETFs) witness another influx of $125 million. There's anticipation of Hong Kong approving ETFs for both Bitcoin and Ethereum (ETH) come Monday. Notable institutional investor BlackRock shows interest in Bitcoin. Recent filings reveal increased Bitcoin purchases by banks. A Bitcoin-friendly political party secures victory in the South Korean election. Analyst Kang predicts Bitcoin could surge to $80-100k by May. Meanwhile, Ethereum sees accumulation by stablecoin whales on the rise. A new Ethereum Improvement Proposal (EIP) aims to streamline signing requests. Solana (SOL) experiences a resurgence in activity, reaching yearly highs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NASA’s Next Deep Space Mission Won’t Use Artificial Intelligence]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/0WGP33Rp/nasas-next-deep-space-mission-wont-use-artificial-intelligence</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/0WGP33Rp/nasas-next-deep-space-mission-wont-use-artificial-intelligence"/>
        <updated>2024-04-13T18:42:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Thursday, Decrypt Media visited NASA's Jet Propulsion Laboratory in Pasadena, CA to meet with the Engineering team behind the Europa Clipper before its launch to Jupiter's Europa moon in October.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Do A Little with Weesh]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LnaOT9bF/we-do-a-little-with-weesh</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LnaOT9bF/we-do-a-little-with-weesh"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T07:46:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week’s episode, we did a little something different. We took the man who is usually behind the camera and put him in front of it. We sat down with our producer Weesh to dive into how in fell in love with art and became a collector, how he met Andy and fun childhood memories together, his biggest wins in crypto, and so much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside VanEck’s Crypto Takeover of the New York Stock Exchange]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9YAY4wGD/inside-vanecks-crypto-takeover-of-the-new-york-stock-exchange</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9YAY4wGD/inside-vanecks-crypto-takeover-of-the-new-york-stock-exchange"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T14:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worlds collide as Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz heads to the floor of the NYSE to witness a special closing bell ceremony hosted by VanEck in honor of Web3. Featuring Choose Rich Nick, VanEck Head of Web3 Matt Bartlett, and more!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wormhole Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9SNiIVfU/wormhole-wednesday</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9SNiIVfU/wormhole-wednesday"/>
        <updated>2024-04-07T17:42:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC hits $64.5K then rebounds, SOL outperforms. Government sends $2B BTC to Coinbase to sell. Funding rates stay low after sweep lower. ETFs see small inflow, Ark outflow more than GBTC. Wormhole W launches at $15B FDV. BTC ‘inflection point’ if it follows rates or gold. Gold & BTC very correlated for the last year. Expect slower ETF volume this month: Bloomberg. BTC 2x and 3x levered ETFs launch yesterday. BTC ETFs now half the size of gold.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>