<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-05-01T21:13:01.602Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-05-01T21:13:01.602Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto exchange Poloniex settles case with US OFAC for this violation]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18238800/Crypto-exchange-Poloniex-settles-case-with-US-OFAC-for-this-violation</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18238800/Crypto-exchange-Poloniex-settles-case-with-US-OFAC-for-this-violation"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T21:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Poloniex, a crypto exchange, settled its ongoing case with the OFAC as of 1 May 2023. The exchange will be paying over $7 million as a fine to the law enforcement department.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Central Banker's Confession On Bitcoin | Dr. David Andolfatto]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18238799/Central-Bankers-Confession-On-Bitcoin-Dr-David-Andolfatto</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18238799/Central-Bankers-Confession-On-Bitcoin-Dr-David-Andolfatto"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T21:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dr. David Andolfatto is the professor and chair of the economics department at the Miami Herbert Business School at the University of Miami. He was the very first central banker to ever give a public presentation on bitcoin. In this conversation, we talk about bitcoin, federal reserve,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Liquid staking solutions now have more TVL than DEXs: DefiLlama]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18238802/Liquid-staking-solutions-now-have-more-TVL-than-DEXs-DefiLlama</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18238802/Liquid-staking-solutions-now-have-more-TVL-than-DEXs-DefiLlama"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From April 13 to May 1, TVL on decentralized exchanges declined by $1.66 billion while it increased on liquid staking protocols by $280 million.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Saylor's MicroStrategy Books a Much Smaller Bitcoin Impairment Charge]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18238787/Michael-Saylors-MicroStrategy-Books-a-Much-Smaller-Bitcoin-Impairment-Charge</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18238787/Michael-Saylors-MicroStrategy-Books-a-Much-Smaller-Bitcoin-Impairment-Charge"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T20:53:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amid BTC's big rally, the company's impairment loss narrowed to $18.9 million in the first quarter from $197.6 million in the fourth quarter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Dips, Equities Trade Sideways Ahead of Fed Rate Decision]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18238786/Crypto-Dips-Equities-Trade-Sideways-Ahead-of-Fed-Rate-Decision</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18238786/Crypto-Dips-Equities-Trade-Sideways-Ahead-of-Fed-Rate-Decision"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T20:50:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Markets are hoping for some confirmation rate hikes are on the pause]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Falters As President Biden Admits US Banking Sector Is Weak]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7512a7b076</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-falters-as-president-biden-admits-us-banking-sector-is-weak/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T20:35:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. President Joe Biden, speaking at the National Small Business Week on May 1, has admitted that the United States banking system is fragile. In a recent statement, the Head of State revealed that the government will institute measures to ensure its financial system remains “sound and safe.” 
 
Despite Biden’s comments, Bitcoin and most cryptocurrencies remain lower. Bitcoin is down 4% in the last 24 hours and roughly 10% from April 2023 highs, trading at $28,100.
 
Banks Collapsing In The United States, President Biden’s Assurance
 
The president’s comments follow the collapse of the First Republic Bank, the third major bank to collapse in less than two months. 
 
The bank’s failure saw the stock’s price crash in late April 2023 as Bitcoin prices powered higher, charting as high as $30,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dalmas Ngetich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Republic Closure Contradicts Anti-crypto Narrative]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18238763/First-Republic-Closure-Contradicts-Anti-crypto-Narrative</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18238763/First-Republic-Closure-Contradicts-Anti-crypto-Narrative"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T20:32:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Regulators have questioned crypto’s role in the banking crisis failures, but with First Republic, the bank seems to have fallen without the help of digital assets]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Falters As President Biden Admits US Banking Sector Is Weak]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18238762/Bitcoin-Falters-As-President-Biden-Admits-US-Banking-Sector-Is-Weak</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18238762/Bitcoin-Falters-As-President-Biden-Admits-US-Banking-Sector-Is-Weak"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T20:30:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. President Joe Biden, speaking at the National Small Business Week on May 1, has admitted that the United States banking system is fragile. In a recent statement, the Head of State revealed that the government will institute measures to ensure its financial system remains “sound and safe.”...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scientists in Texas developed a GPT-like AI system that reads minds]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18238764/Scientists-in-Texas-developed-a-GPT-like-AI-system-that-reads-minds</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18238764/Scientists-in-Texas-developed-a-GPT-like-AI-system-that-reads-minds"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study demonstrates how the tech underlining ChatGPT can decode brain scans; recent AI progress indicates this could have implications for blockchain and Web3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Digital Currency Group at Risk of $630 Million Default]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18238785/Digital-Currency-Group-at-Risk-of-630-Million-Default</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18238785/Digital-Currency-Group-at-Risk-of-630-Million-Default"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Digital Currency Group can exacerbate fiat crisis if it fails to raise liquidity before Genesis loan deadline.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sotheby's Launches On-Chain NFT Marketplace for Secondary Art Sales]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=138514</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/138514/sothebys-launches-on-chain-nft-marketplace-for-secondary-art-sales"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T20:29:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Famed auction house Sotheby's now supports secondary NFT sales, letting collectors list and make offers on work from select artists.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Republic's Failure Shows the Limits of Fed Bank Programs]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18238755/First-Republics-Failure-Shows-the-Limits-of-Fed-Bank-Programs</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18238755/First-Republics-Failure-Shows-the-Limits-of-Fed-Bank-Programs"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T20:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[European Union pushes forward with first AI framework: Law Decoded, April 24–May 1]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18238745/European-Union-pushes-forward-with-first-AI-framework-Law-Decoded-April-24May-1</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18238745/European-Union-pushes-forward-with-first-AI-framework-Law-Decoded-April-24May-1"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T20:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stabilizing the Banking System: Biden Reassures Public Amid First Republic Bank Collapse, but Warns of National Debt Default]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7512a1717e</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/stabilizing-the-banking-system-biden-reassures-public-amid-first-republic-bank-collapse-but-warns-of-national-debt-default/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T20:18:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amid the collapse of the second, third, and fourth largest banks in American history, U.S. president Joe Biden reassured the public that the country’s banking system remains sturdy. However, the president also acknowledged the “threat by the speaker of the House to default on the national debt.”
 
Biden Expresses Confidence in American Banking System Despite First Republic Bank Collapse
 
Biden’s recent statements were made following California’s financial regulators seizing First Republic Bank and placing it under the control of the U.S. Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation (FDIC). After the bank’s seizure, it was then sold to JPMorgan Chase, the largest bank in the United States, which pledged to cover all deposits, including the uninsured.
 
Biden expressed his approval of the governme…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mawson Infrastructure Signs Agreement For 24MW Ohio Facility That Will Come Online In Q3 2023]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7512a2bebd</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/mawson-infrastructure-signs-agreement-for-24mw-ohio-facility"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T20:05:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The site could potentially bring Mawson’s capacity in the area up to 290MW and increase deployable hash rate to 1.0 EH/s
Digital infrastructure provider Mawson Infrastructure Group Inc. (Mawson) has signed an agreement for a new site in Corning, Ohio, with an initial capacity of 24MW.
According to a press release, the site, signed on a long-term lease, has an additional 26MW of potential capacity upside, subject to further infrastructure investment, which would take the total site to 50MW. 
The site is expected to go live in Q3 2023 and will initially host 12 modular data centers (MDCs) and 7,056 miners. The new site will expand Mawson's potential capacity to up to 290MW, highlighting the company's focus on the Pennsylvania and Ohio region.
Mawson's CEO James Manning said, “This is the first of several smaller sites the Mawson team has been working on, with a focus to deploy low cost, quick to market mining facilities.” COO Liam Wilson added, “We are actively planning for the halving event, and plan to have the most efficient fleet possible — as always, focusing on shareholders return on capital. We are focused on this region for various reasons and look forward to seeing which ASIC units perform best before ordering in bulk.”
The new site is an addition to the existing 240MW of capacity that Mawson has online and under development in the surrounding area. The company's goal is to provide a possible increase in deployable hashrate of up to 1.0 EH/s. Mawson's infrastructure includes a proprietary modular data center (MDC) design that aims to reduce deployment time and capital expenditure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BtcCasey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Poloniex will pay $7.6M settlement to US authorities for 'apparent violations' of sanctions]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18238721/Poloniex-will-pay-76M-settlement-to-US-authorities-for-apparent-violations-of-sanctions</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18238721/Poloniex-will-pay-76M-settlement-to-US-authorities-for-apparent-violations-of-sanctions"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T20:02:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OFAC said Poloniex allowed users in Crimea, Cuba, Iran, Sudan and Syria to conduct digital asset trades, deposits and withdrawals between January 2014 and November 2019.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Billionare Ray Dalio Predicts US Government Will Turn Money Printers Back On To Fund National Deficit]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18238702/Billionare-Ray-Dalio-Predicts-US-Government-Will-Turn-Money-Printers-Back-On-To-Fund-National-Deficit</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18238702/Billionare-Ray-Dalio-Predicts-US-Government-Will-Turn-Money-Printers-Back-On-To-Fund-National-Deficit"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T20:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Billionaire investor Ray Dalio believes that the US government will turn the money printers back on to save the country from defaulting on its massive debt. In a recent interview with YouTuber Chris Williamson, Dalio says that the US government will likely resort to currency debasement to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Weak, Bring on FOMC]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18238726/Crypto-Weak-Bring-on-FOMC</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18238726/Crypto-Weak-Bring-on-FOMC"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T19:58:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[🚀 Learn Technical Analysis with The Chart Guys! 🚀https://www.chartguys.com/trading-community-membershipOur goal is to review and discuss the most recent price action in the market in a manner that makes it useful to you. Using Technical Analysis, we perform an indepth review of the action in the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analyst Nicholas Merten Says Bitcoin Getting ‘Really Scary for the Bulls’ As BTC Clings to $28,000 – Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18238703/Analyst-Nicholas-Merten-Says-Bitcoin-Getting-Really-Scary-for-the-Bulls-As-BTC-Clings-to-28000-Heres-Why</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18238703/Analyst-Nicholas-Merten-Says-Bitcoin-Getting-Really-Scary-for-the-Bulls-As-BTC-Clings-to-28000-Heres-Why"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T19:55:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A widely followed crypto analyst says that Bitcoin (BTC) is giving reason for its bulls to start getting concerned. In a new DataDash update, Nicholas Merten tells his 512,000 YouTube subscribers that things are “getting scary” for BTC bulls as its weekly price action starts to look exhausted at...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple-SEC Meeting That Could Change Everything: Will It Actually Happen?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18238696/Ripple-SEC-Meeting-That-Could-Change-Everything-Will-It-Actually-Happen</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18238696/Ripple-SEC-Meeting-That-Could-Change-Everything-Will-It-Actually-Happen"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T19:41:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rumors of a secret meeting between blockchain giant Ripple and the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) sent the XRP community into a frenzy]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Godfather of AI’ Leaves Google to Save Us From AI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=138515</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/138515/geoffrey-hinton-quits-google-ai-godfather-danger-warning"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T19:39:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence pioneer Geoffrey Hinton fears that the race to advanced AI will carry humanity over a cliff.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Godfather of AI’ Leaves Google to Save Us From AI]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18238692/Godfather-of-AI-Leaves-Google-to-Save-Us-From-AI</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18238692/Godfather-of-AI-Leaves-Google-to-Save-Us-From-AI"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T19:39:42.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russia Defies Sanctions With Crypto For Cross-Border Transactions]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7512adc402</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/russia-defies-sanctions-crypto-for-cross-border/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T19:36:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While the United States regulators have continued to see cryptocurrency as a major threat, other countries, such as Russia, are beginning to pay attention to the technology’s potential while experimenting with its potential.
 
In recent years, sanctions have become an increasingly common tool countries use to exert pressure on their political rivals. The impact of these measures has been significant for Russia, as several rounds of economic sanctions have targeted it in response to the invasion of Ukraine. 
 
However, despite its challenges, Russia is now looking to use cryptocurrency to help it bypass these restrictions and conduct cross-border transactions.
 
Crypto As A Tool For Cross-Border For Cross-Border Transactions
 
Speaking at a recent conference, Deputy Finance Minister Alexei …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How will Arbitrum [ARB] benefit from GMX’s expanding activity? According to…]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18238678/How-will-Arbitrum-ARB-benefit-from-GMXs-expanding-activity-According-to</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18238678/How-will-Arbitrum-ARB-benefit-from-GMXs-expanding-activity-According-to"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T19:30:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arbitrums' overall activity surges as GMX dominates the perpetual contracts market. However, ARB token's price continues to fall.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russia Defies Sanctions With Crypto For Cross-Border Transactions]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18238679/Russia-Defies-Sanctions-With-Crypto-For-Cross-Border-Transactions</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18238679/Russia-Defies-Sanctions-With-Crypto-For-Cross-Border-Transactions"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T19:30:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While the United States regulators have continued to see cryptocurrency as a major threat, other countries, such as Russia, are beginning to pay attention to the technology’s potential while experimenting with its potential. In recent years, sanctions have become an increasingly common tool...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Litecoin (LTC) Price Dips as Miners Sell Large Amounts of Coins, What’s Next?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18238698/Litecoin-LTC-Price-Dips-as-Miners-Sell-Large-Amounts-of-Coins-Whats-Next</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18238698/Litecoin-LTC-Price-Dips-as-Miners-Sell-Large-Amounts-of-Coins-Whats-Next"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T19:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Does Magic Eden Vet Web3 Games?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ogci0VQ6/how-does-magic-eden-vet-web3-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ogci0VQ6/how-does-magic-eden-vet-web3-games"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Magic Eden Chief Gaming Officer Chris Akhavan tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about how the NFT marketplace vets potential Web3 games for its platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bushi Puts a Samurai Twist on Overwatch's Hero Combat]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=138479</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/138479/bushi-puts-a-samurai-twist-on-overwatchs-hero-combat"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T19:18:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PREVIEW: This early alpha shoot-’em-up shows promise, as Bushi combines a unique aesthetic with rapid-fire acrobatics and combat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Exchange Poloniex Agrees to $7.6M Fee to Settle Sanctions Violation Charges]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7512aa50ee</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/05/01/crypto-exchange-poloniex-agrees-to-76m-fine-settle-sanctions-violation-charges/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T18:53:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto exchange Poloniex will remit $7.59 million to settle sanctions violations allegations with the U.S. Treasury Department's Office of Foreign Asset Control (OFAC), the sanctions watchdog announced Monday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Talent Co. And Summer Of Bitcoin Announce Summer 2023 Bitcoin Industry Apprenticeship Program]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7512abb18b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/summer-2023-bitcoin-industry-apprenticeship-program-announced"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T18:39:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The program, aimed at college students, seeks to provide industry exposure and networking opportunities with Bitcoin-focused companies.
Bitcoin Talent Co. and Summer of Bitcoin have announced their partnership to launch the Summer 2023 Bitcoin Industry Apprenticeship (BIA) Program for undergraduate and graduate students from universities in North America and Europe.
The program is expected to provide students with hands-on experience in the Bitcoin industry, industry exposure, skill development, an in-depth understanding of Bitcoin and networking opportunities. Applications for the program will run from June 12 to August 25.
According to the press release, the program will "unlock additional opportunities for students to spend time learning from and contributing to the operations of venture-funded Bitcoin companies." 
The BIA Program is expected to provide students with practical skills that can be applied to various industries and fields, while also helping them establish professional relationships with Bitcoin-focused companies.
As the macroeconomic and geopolitical backdrop continues to highlight the importance of bitcoin, this partnership is aiming to be an opportunity to dedicate one's career to the growth of the industry.
"Over 30% of interns graduating from university have been offered full-time roles after participating in Summer of Bitcoin's previous open-source internship programs," the press release said. Companies interested in partnering with the program and offering internship opportunities, as well as students interested in pursuing summer internships, can visit www.bitcointalent.co/bitcoin-industry-apprenticeship-program for more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BtcCasey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Crypto Venture Giant Responds To Proposed Regulation In The U.K.]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75129451a7</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-giant-responds-proposed-regulation-in-the-uk/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T18:34:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brian Quintenz, Head of Policy for crypto venture firm a16, posted a reply to the United Kingdom Treasury’s consultation on their new regulatory framework. The financial watchdog opened this process last week after announcing their “Future Financial Services Regulatory Regime for Cryptoassets.” 
 
 
As Bitcoinist reported last week, the U.K. Treasury and the Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) want to launch a “robust” crypto regulatory framework. In that sense, the regulators seek input from key industry players on the proposal to “ensure the right regulatory regime.”
 
 
U.K. Wants To Overhaul Crypto Regulation
 
In their response to the consultation process, a16z and its Head of Policy applauded the initiative and the U.K. effort to listen to the nascent industry. In the U.S. and other ma…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reynaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Erases April Gains After Slumping More Than 5% in a Day]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=138505</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/138505/bitcoin-erases-april-gains-price-down"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T18:24:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin had been on a roll last month but is now down significantly from when it pushed towards $31,000.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Network Fees Surge 153% in 30 Days, While Arbitrum Daily Transactions Outpace ETH Following Shapella Upgrade]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7512965717</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ethereum-network-fees-surge-153-in-30-days-while-arbitrum-daily-transactions-outpace-eth-following-shapella-upgrade/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T18:15:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum network fees have experienced a significant upswing following the implementation of the Shapella upgrade on April 12th. In the last 30 days, onchain fees have soared by over 153%, from a prior rate of $4.65 per transfer to a current average of $11.80 per transaction. The data highlights a substantial surge in the costs associated with Ethereum network transactions, indicating a notable increase in onchain activity.
 
Onchain Fees on Ethereum Network Soar by 153% in a Month, While Arbitrum’s Daily Transactions Exceed ETH Post-Shapella Upgrade
 
Over the past month, Ethereum network fees have witnessed a material surge, with the cost of onchain transfers surging from $4.65 per transaction on April 1, to an average of 0.0064 ether or $11.80 per transfer at present. The data reveals a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Set New Record of Daily Transactions the Same Day the U.S. Government Quietly Engineered a Bank Buyout]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e751297bf86</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/05/01/bitcoin-set-new-record-of-daily-transactions-the-same-day-the-us-government-quietly-engineered-a-bank-buyout/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T18:02:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The events are unconnected, but crypto has a role to play in the wider political realignment questioning the sanctity of central banks and established powers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Kuhn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are Bitcoin Investors Leaving American Exchanges? Here’s What Data Says]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7512931872</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-investors-leaving-american-exchanges-data/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T17:34:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data shows the Bitcoin exchange reserve ratio for US versus offshore platforms has continued to decline recently. Here’s what this tells us.
 
Bitcoin Exchange Reserve Ratio Has Been Falling For A While Now
 
As explained by an analyst in a CryptoQuant post, the BTC reserve of the US-based exchanges is going down. The “exchange reserve” is an indicator that measures the total amount of Bitcoin that’s currently sitting in the wallets of a centralized exchange or a group of such platforms.
 
The metric of interest here is not actually the exchange reserve, but the “exchange reserve ratio.” As this indicator’s name implies, it tells us about the ratio between the exchange reserves of two given sets of platforms. In the context of the current discussion, the two sets of exchanges are …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hououin Kyouma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paysenger Launches IDO as the Platform Looks to Solve the Challenges of AI-Generated Art]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75129e6615</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/paysenger-launches-ido-as-the-platform-looks-to-solve-the-challenges-of-ai-generated-art/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T17:05:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. The rise of AI-generated art has created ethical concerns and challenges within the art community, as many artists perceive these tools as undermining their skills and exploiting their work for profit. Paysenger, a groundbreaking blockchain-based collaboration platform for content creators, fans, and brands, is poised to tackle these issues with its native token, EGO, and AI integration.
 
Paysenger introduces a personalized AI model that allows artists to create unique, AI-generated art in their distinctive style. This exclusive, artist-specific AI model uses the artist’s social account for validation and access. By combining personalized AI models, blockchain technology, and NFTs, Passenger aims to revolutionize the art world and foster new opportunities for artists and br…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Now Use Your JPEGs to Borrow Ethereum on NFT Marketplace Blur]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=138498</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/138498/you-can-now-use-your-jpegs-borrow-ethereum-nft-marketplace-blur"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T17:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The leading NFT marketplace by trading volume just launched zero-fee, perpetual loans via the new Blend peer-to-peer protocol.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sotheby's Launches On-Chain Secondary NFT Marketplace]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75129f322f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/web3/2023/05/01/sothebys-launches-on-chain-secondary-nft-marketplace/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T16:58:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sotheby’s Metaverse will now offer fully on-chain secondary transactions via Ethereum and Polygon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rosie Perper</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 Gaming Reigns Supreme In Crypto, Raises Over $7 Billion In Record Time]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75129a6241</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/web3-gaming-reigns-supreme-raises-over-7-billion/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T16:32:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 gaming has emerged as the hottest sector in the crypto world, raising over $7 billion in funding over the past 18 months. This is more than any other crypto sector in the industry, highlighting the immense potential and popularity of the gaming sector in the crypto ecosystem.
 
Web3 gaming is a relatively new concept that combines blockchain technology and gaming to create a new form of gaming experience. This innovative approach allows gamers to create, own, and trade in-game assets using cryptocurrency, adding an extra layer of excitement and engagement to traditional gaming.
 
The Rise Of Web3 Gaming
 
The $7 billion in funding has been raised by a diverse range of web3 gaming projects, from massive multiplayer online games to decentralized gaming platforms. This funding has enable…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFT Marketplace Blur Launches Peer-to-Peer Lending Platform, Blend]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e751284e661</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/web3/2023/05/01/nft-marketplace-blur-launches-peer-to-peer-lending-platform-blend/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T16:12:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Short for Blur Lending, Blend will allow collectors to buy blue-chip NFTs with a smaller up-front payment, similar to a down payment on a house.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cam Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Firm FARE Protocol Raises $6.2M Ahead of Token Launch]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e751286584d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/05/01/crypto-firm-fare-protocol-raises-62m-ahead-of-token-launch/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T16:01:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fundraise was led by C Squared Ventures and Goat Capital, the firm co-founded by Twitch founder Justin Kan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandy Betz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biggest Movers: LTC Back Under $90.00, as SOL Extends Declines]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e751280a5e0</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/biggest-movers-ltc-back-under-90-00-as-sol-extends-declines/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T15:43:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Litecoin fell below the $90.00 level on Monday, as sentiment in cryptocurrency markets remained mostly bearish. The global market cap is down 1.87% at the time of writing, which seems to be a result of the upcoming Federal Reserve interest rate decision. Solana was also in the red today.
 
Litecoin (LTC)
 
Litecoin (LTC) was down for a second straight session on Monday, as markets prepared for the upcoming United States Federal Reserve policy decision.
 
LTC/USD dropped to low at $86.83 earlier in today’s session, which comes 24 hours after trading at a high of $91.39.
 
Today’s drop in price has pushed litecoin to its weakest point since last Wednesday, when the token was at a low of $84.21.
 
 
Looking at the chart, Monday’s move came as the relative strength index (RSI) fell to a support level at 44.00.
 
At the time of writing, the index is tracking at 44.80, with an upcoming ceiling of 50.00 a potential target for bulls.
 
Should this point be hit, there is a strong possibility that LTC will move back above the $90.00 mark.
 
 
Solana (SOL)
 
In addition to litecoin, solana (SOL) was another notable mover on Monday, as the token fell for a third consecutive day.
 
Following a high of $23.93 on Sunday, SOL/USD slipped to a bottom of $22.05 earlier in the day.
 
This bearish spell started after bulls were unable to force a breakout beyond a ceiling at the $24.00 mark.
 
 
One of the catalysts for this was the RSI, which also failed to surge past a key resistance level at 55.00
 
As of writing, price strength is tracking at 48.58, with the next visible floor at the 45.00 zone.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
Will solana fall below $20.00 this week? Let us know your thoughts in the comments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Bans Justin Sun From Farming SUI Following Large Deposits]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75128105fb</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/binance-bans-justin-sun-farming-sui-large-deposits/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T15:40:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Binance team has issued a warning and ban on Justin Sun from farming SUI tokens following large TUSD transfer deposits he made on the platform earlier today.
 
The SUI layer 1 blockchain, which has been under development for a while now, gained massive attention and interest from the crypto community following the announcement of its mainnet launch scheduled on May 3, 2023.
 
Not just that, news of the SUI token introduction on the Binance launchpool also sparked the interests of crypto investors, which may likely include that of the TRON Founder, who deposited a significant volume of the token required to farm SUI tokens.
 
Binance Takes Drastic Measures To Secure SUI On Launchpool
 
Binance exchange made an announcement yesterday on its official website and socials, introducing the S…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mudiaga Iritare</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Charlie Munger Raises Concerns Over Troubled Commercial Property Loans at US Banks]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7512881648</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/charlie-munger-raises-concerns-over-troubled-commercial-property-loans-at-us-banks/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T14:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Charlie Munger, the vice chairman of Berkshire Hathaway, stated in a recent interview that American banks are burdened with poor-quality commercial real estate loans. His comments arrive amid the collapse of three major U.S. banks and the expected seizure of First Republic Bank by the federal government. Despite the potential challenges, Munger emphasized that the current situation is not as severe as the 2008 financial crisis, stating that “it’s not nearly as bad as it was in 2008.”
 
U.S. Banks Saddled With Poor-Quality Commercial Real Estate Loans, According to Charlie Munger’s Latest Interview
 
The renowned investor and vice chairman of Berkshire Hathaway, Charlie Munger, spoke to the Financial Times (FT) in an interview published on April 30, 2023, where he discussed potential issues…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Slaps Coinme With $4M Fine For Misleading Investors]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75128875ad</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/sec-coinme-4m-fine/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T14:41:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has served a $4 million fine to Coinme over its initial coin offering (ICO) of UpToken. 
 
Based on the SEC’s order, the UPToken ICO, which Coinme and its subsidiary conducted from October 2017 to December 2017, was an investment contract based on the Howey test.
 
The SEC also believes that the company’s offer of unregistered securities to crypto investors and traders was “misleading,” necessitating the fine.
 
SEC Serves Coinme $4 Million In Fines
 
Recently, the SEC stated that Coinme’s misleading marketing strategy violated securities laws as Coinme did not register the tokens as securities, and the company did not qualify for an exemption from registration requirements.
 
According to the SEC’s filing, the company raised about $3.6 milli…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Dambel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Unlocks 1 Billion XRP From Escrow Wallet Amid Price Change]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7512703b7f</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ripple-unlocks-1-billion-xrp-from-escrow/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T13:38:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple has released 1 billion locked XRP tokens from an unknown wallet. According to the whale-tracking site Whale Alert, Ripple released the tokens in two transactions of 500 million XRP each. 
 
The recent action follows Ripple’s monthly routine when it unlocks tokens from a pre-timed Escrow system. Ripple designed its Escrow system to lock some amounts of XRP in a smart contract over a pre-programmed time. This system creates a predictable and stable XRP circulating supply.
 
The California-based fintech company has practiced this system monthly since 2018, except in November 2022.
 
Ripple Mobilizes Locked XRP Tokens For its ODL Services
 
Whale Alert captured the transaction on May 1 and highlighted the two transactions simultaneously. In detail, the first transaction, tagged “Escrow …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Dambel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Are Ordinals? A Beginner's Guide to Bitcoin NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=121590</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-are-ordinals-a-beginners-guide-to-bitcoin-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T13:26:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bitcoin community has gone wild over Ordinal Inscriptions, but what is the new thing taking over Crypto Twitter?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Justin Sun Calls $56M Token Transfer to Binance an 'Oversight', Requests Full Refund]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=138471</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/138471/justin-sun-calls-56m-token-transfer-binance-oversight-requests-full-refund"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T12:02:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CZ flagged Sun's $56 million token transfer to Binance, suggesting the Tron founder would use it to farm a soon-to-be-launched token.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gemini Warns Barry Silbert's Digital Currency Group of $630M Default Risk]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=138453</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/138453/gemini-warns-barry-silbert-digital-currency-group-630m-default-risk"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T11:01:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DCG “risks defaulting on its obligations” if it's unable to pay the $630 million debt made to bankrupt Genesis, said Gemini.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PEPE Coin Enters Market’s Top 100 Cryptocurrencies, Soaring 111% Overnight]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=138454</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/138454/pepe-coin-enters-markets-top-100-cryptocurrencies-soaring-overnight"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T10:41:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The newly-launched meme coin PEPE has taken crypto by storm after hitting a market capitalization of $540 million.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ohio Man Steals $21M in Bitcoin From Brother, Gets Four Years in Prison]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=138445</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/138445/ohio-man-steals-bitcoin-from-brother-prison"/>
        <updated>2023-04-30T21:17:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gary James Harmon will spend four years in prison after stealing crypto assets that law enforcement tried to seize from his brother.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Proof’s Kevin Rose on Building in the NFT Bear Market: ‘Holy Shit Has It Been Tough’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=138446</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/138446/proofs-kevin-rose-building-nft-bear-market-holy-shit-been-tough"/>
        <updated>2023-04-30T21:10:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One year after the Moonbirds NFT drop, Rose discusses Proof’s renewed art focus and the “weird dynamic” of running Web3 projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Transactions Soar as Ordinals Barrel Past 2.5 Million, Notch Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=138438</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/138438/bitcoin-transactions-soar-as-ordinals-barrell-past-2-5-million-notch-daily-record"/>
        <updated>2023-04-30T19:06:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bump in inscriptions comes as text-based content solidifies its dominance on Ordinals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interview: Kevin Rose on the 'Weird Dynamic' of Building an NFT Project]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rb2MhkWH/interview-kevin-rose-on-the-weird-dynamic-of-building-an-nft-project</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rb2MhkWH/interview-kevin-rose-on-the-weird-dynamic-of-building-an-nft-project"/>
        <updated>2023-04-30T18:49:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Proof co-founder and CEO Kevin Rose chats with Decrypt Culture Editor Andrew Hayward during NFT NYC 2023 to discuss his startup's reaffirmed focus on digital art and collectors, the challenges of building in the NFT market, and what he's learned in the last year since the buzzy Moonbirds drop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Bored Ape Creator Yuga Labs Plans to Get to the 'Otherside']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=138402</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/138402/bored-ape-yacht-club-yuga-labs-otherside-playtest"/>
        <updated>2023-04-30T18:24:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After the Otherside Second Trip playtest, Yuga execs reflect on building in public and how they aim to bring the Web3 metaverse game to life.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week on Crypto Twitter: Tornado Cash Dev Alex Pertsev Returns! CZ Says He’s Not That Rich]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=138409</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/138409/this-week-on-crypto-twitter-tornado-cash-alex-pertsev-cz-rich"/>
        <updated>2023-04-30T18:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Industry lawyers and advisors made a killing from the horrorshow that was “Crypto Winter” 2022.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Everyone Is Keeping a Close Eye on Mt. Gox, US Gov Bitcoin Wallets]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=138356</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/138356/why-everyone-is-keeping-a-close-eye-on-mt-gox-us-gov-bitcoin-wallets"/>
        <updated>2023-04-30T12:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Investors are keeping their eyes on these unorthodox HODLers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Italy Welcomes ChatGPT Back After Ban Over AI Privacy Concerns]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=138362</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/138362/italy-welcomes-chatgpt-back-after-ban-over-ai-privacy-concerns"/>
        <updated>2023-04-29T23:23:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The restoration comes after OpenAI added several new privacy features to its AI chatbot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Bluesky Invite Codes as Chrissy Teigen Joins Decentralized Twitter Rival]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=138250</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/138250/how-get-bluesky-code-chrissy-teigen-aoc-join-decentralized-twitter-rival"/>
        <updated>2023-04-29T20:13:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The decentralized social app backed by Jack Dorsey is still in the invite-only stage. Here’s how you can join the conversation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alys Key</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Bitcoin, ICP and Solana Lead Small Market-Wide Rally]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=138385</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/138385/this-week-in-coins-bitcoin-icp-solana-rally-regulation"/>
        <updated>2023-04-29T17:22:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Small gains across the board this week after First Republic Bank’s shares nosedived following publication of its latest quarterly report.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lightning Labs Aims to Help 'Bring Bitcoin to Billions' With Latest Upgrade]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=138381</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/138381/lightning-labs-bitcoin-billions-update"/>
        <updated>2023-04-29T16:46:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The tech startup aims to continue to make it easier for people to use the Lightning Network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alyssa Hertig</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How MMORPG Mirandus is Managing its Web3 Elements]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XETXOt0k/how-mmorpg-mirandus-is-managing-its-web3-elements</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XETXOt0k/how-mmorpg-mirandus-is-managing-its-web3-elements"/>
        <updated>2023-04-29T16:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gala Games Cofounder Michael McCarthy says an "unbelievable" amount of Mirandus conversations are about its approach to Web3 and crypto transactions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Gmoney Is Buying Twitter Blue Checks for NFT Brand 9dcc's Top Supporters: ‘I Like to Fuck Around and Find Out’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=138373</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/138373/why-gmoney-buying-twitter-blue-checks-nft-brands-9dcc-top-supporters"/>
        <updated>2023-04-29T16:17:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The founder of apparel brand 9dcc isn’t worried about Twitter pushing back. “If anything, they’d want to encourage it,” he told Decrypt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gary Gensler Says SEC Believes Ethereum Is Not a Security—At MIT in 2018]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=138334</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/138334/gary-gensler-sec-ethereum-not-security-mit-2018"/>
        <updated>2023-04-28T21:44:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC had a very different take on the second biggest cryptocurrency back in 2018, according to Gary Gensler.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here's How Much Money FTX Really Has Left]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=138337</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/138337/heres-how-much-money-ftx-really-has-left"/>
        <updated>2023-04-28T20:45:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Of $86M the firm has spent so far, $67 million alone has gone towards its legal fees.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former OpenAI Researcher: There’s a 50% Chance AI Ends in 'Catastrophe']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=138310</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/138310/openai-researcher-chance-ai-catastrophe"/>
        <updated>2023-04-28T20:40:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paul Christiano ran the language model alignment team at OpenAI. He's not so sure this all won't end very badly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Battle Royale Shooter 'Grit' Plays Like a Wild West PUBG—With NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=138320</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/138320/gala-games-nft-shooter-grit-feels-like-wild-west-pubg"/>
        <updated>2023-04-28T20:36:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PREVIEW: Shove the Red Dead comparisons aside. Gala Games' Grit is a game all on its own, with a battle royale focus and optional NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adidas and Pharrell Release Digital Clothing for Doodles NFT Holders]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=138290</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/138290/adidas-pharrell-release-digital-clothing-doodles-nft-holders"/>
        <updated>2023-04-28T18:21:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Musician Pharrell Williams headlines the Doodles NFT bundle with digital and physical gear from Adidas, Human Made, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Fortnite, League of Legends Exec Joins Otherside Creator Yuga Labs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=138280</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/138280/ex-fortnite-league-legends-exec-joins-otherside-creator-yuga-labs"/>
        <updated>2023-04-28T15:32:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The $4B startup behind the Bored Ape Yacht Club is snagging top game industry talent as it prepares to launch its Otherside metaverse game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Azra Games's Creative Process?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zyYFJkg0/what-is-azra-gamess-creative-process</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zyYFJkg0/what-is-azra-gamess-creative-process"/>
        <updated>2023-04-28T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azra Games CEO Mark Otero tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about Azra's creative process to game development and storytelling.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Berenberg Analysts: Bitcoin 'Could Rally' Near Next Year's Halving Event]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=138269</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/138269/berenberg-analysts-bitcoin-could-rally-near-next-years-halving-event"/>
        <updated>2023-04-28T15:20:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Analysts suggest the next Bitcoin halving event could, yet again, bring the leading cryptocurrency out of its crypto winter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miner Bitfarms Hits New Hashrate High Amid Argentine Expansion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=138268</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/138268/bitcoin-miner-bitfarms-hits-new-hashrate-high-argentine-expansion"/>
        <updated>2023-04-28T13:53:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More than 2,000 new miners were activated earlier this week, with the firm aiming for even further expansion by year's end.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alys Key</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon Lending Protocol 0VIX Pauses Protocol After $2M Exploit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=138262</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/138262/polygon-lending-protocol-0vix-pauses-protocol-exploit"/>
        <updated>2023-04-28T13:23:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The attackers manipulated the price of Aavegotchi's native token, before looting relevant lending pools for at least $2 million on 0VIX.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AOC, Hollywood Stars Are 'Skeeting' on Bluesky]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=138238</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/138238/aoc-hollywood-stars-are-skeeting-bluesky"/>
        <updated>2023-04-28T10:49:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Instead of "tweeting," the influx of new Bluesky users has coined a new term for sharing their thoughts on the decentralized social media app.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CFTC Cracks its 'Largest Fraud' Case Involving Bitcoin, Orders Offender to Pay $3.4B Penalty]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=138244</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/138244/cftc-cracks-largest-fraud-involving-bitcoin-orders-offender-pay-3-4b-penalty"/>
        <updated>2023-04-28T10:01:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CFTC has just won a record $3.4 billion penalty payment in a Bitcoin-related fraud case, according to an order from a Texas judge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beleaguered Bitcoin Miner Greenidge Inks Deal with Core Scientific]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=138214</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/138214/new-york-bitcoin-miner-greenidge-announces-expansion-following-hard-times"/>
        <updated>2023-04-28T00:44:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As recently as January, Greenidge looked as if it was going to go bust. It claims to have turned a page.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bored Ape Creator Yuga Labs Dominates NFT Sales With 35% Share]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=138219</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/138219/bored-ape-yacht-club-creator-yuga-labs-dominates-nft-sales-35-share"/>
        <updated>2023-04-27T23:40:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bored Ape Yacht Club, CryptoPunks, and other projects tallied over one-third of total NFT sales volume between Q4 2022 and Q1 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why 'Napoleon Dynamite' Star Jon Heder and a 'Workaholics' Co-Creator Are Bringing Hollywood to Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=138213</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/138213/why-napoleon-dynamite-star-jon-heder-workaholics-co-creator-bringing-hollywood-web3"/>
        <updated>2023-04-27T23:08:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Traditional television is old, slow, and corporate," Dominic Russo said. He and Heder tell Decrypt why creators are embracing Web3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FBI Searches Home of Former FTX Exec and Sam Bankman-Fried Ally]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=138216</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/138216/fbi-searches-home-former-ftx-executive-ryan-salame"/>
        <updated>2023-04-27T22:29:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authorities are reportedly looking at $24 million worth of political donations made by Ryan Salame while at the collapsed exchange.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bank of Korea Edges Closer to Being Able to Investigate Crypto Firms: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=138208</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/138208/bank-of-korea-edges-closer-to-being-able-to-investigate-crypto-firms-report"/>
        <updated>2023-04-27T20:50:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Korean regulators said they worry it will signal "virtual asset markets and businesses are treated the same as financial markets and institutions."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase CEO Follows Through With Stock Sale, COIN Investors Unfazed]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=138205</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/138205/coinbase-ceo-follows-through-with-stock-sale-coin-investors-unfazed"/>
        <updated>2023-04-27T20:35:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto entrepreneur wants to donate money to biohacking technology causes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFT Games After Axie Infinity's Fall Will Be Made for Gamers, Not Degens: Aqua CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=138197</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/138197/nft-games-after-axie-infinitys-fall-made-gamers-not-degens-aqua-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-04-27T20:34:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Next-generation Web3 games are being built right now, but the Aqua marketplace team believes developers need help holding onto players.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aurory Is 'Pokemon Meets The Matrix,' Says Executive Producer]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/AotiTeMz/aurory-is-pokemon-meets-the-matrix-says-executive-producer</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/AotiTeMz/aurory-is-pokemon-meets-the-matrix-says-executive-producer"/>
        <updated>2023-04-27T20:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Aurory Web3 game's Executive Producer Jonathan Campeau tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin at the 2023 Game Developer's Conference about the game and what it's like to play.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: Marco Santori]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JDZuMy3q/gm-marco-santori</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JDZuMy3q/gm-marco-santori"/>
        <updated>2023-04-27T18:53:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's no doubt that the SEC dealt Kraken—and the outlook for crypto staking products in the U.S.—a big blow when it announced a $30 million settlement and ordered the company to stop offering the service to its customers in the states in February. Now Marco Santori, the company's chief legal officer, says the exchange is eager to move on from it. That means reckoning with a really challenging regulatory environment and growing its customer base overseas. And as Santori quips: "Kraken's master account application has not yet been rejected."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brycent on Web3 Games and the Problem with 'NFT Value']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/P97zCeID/brycent-on-web3-games-and-the-problem-with-nft-value</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/P97zCeID/brycent-on-web3-games-and-the-problem-with-nft-value"/>
        <updated>2023-04-26T15:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XSET gamer and content creator Brycent tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the problem with gaming NFTs—and what needs to happen instead in the next generation of Web3 games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a Yogurt Shop Started Mark Otero's Video Game Career]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/nZzUeNAR/how-a-yogurt-shop-started-mark-oteros-video-game-career</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/nZzUeNAR/how-a-yogurt-shop-started-mark-oteros-video-game-career"/>
        <updated>2023-04-26T13:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azra Games CEO Mark Otero tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about his career developing eight RPG games and being acquired by Electronic Arts before getting into Web3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain Games Will Shed Their 'Well-Deserved' Bad Reputation In 2023, Says Solana Games Lead]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/HrFRBQIL/blockchain-games-will-shed-their-well-deserved-bad-reputation-in-2023-says-solana-games-lead</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/HrFRBQIL/blockchain-games-will-shed-their-well-deserved-bad-reputation-in-2023-says-solana-games-lead"/>
        <updated>2023-04-26T13:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Foundation's General Manager of Games Johnny Lee tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about his predictions for Web3 gaming in 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We're Going to Stop Calling it Web3 Gaming, Says Magic Eden Chief Gaming Officer]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/VMeXv9Mb/were-going-to-stop-calling-it-web3-gaming-says-magic-eden-chief-gaming-officer</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/VMeXv9Mb/were-going-to-stop-calling-it-web3-gaming-says-magic-eden-chief-gaming-officer"/>
        <updated>2023-04-25T23:13:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Magic Eden Chief Gaming Officer Chris Akhavan talks Web3 adoption and Web3's reputation problem with Decrypt's Kate Irwin. Also, he shares his stance on the word "NFT."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ava Labs' Ed Chang on the Future of Web3 Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Wdrl0iqp/ava-labs-ed-chang-on-the-future-of-web3-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Wdrl0iqp/ava-labs-ed-chang-on-the-future-of-web3-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-04-25T20:26:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the Game Developer's Conference in San Francisco, Ava Labs' Head of Gaming Ed Chang spoke with Decrypt's Kate Irwin about Ava Labs' approach to Web3 gaming, building games on Avalanche, and gave his thoughts on what the coming months and years will look like for the ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Dying in this game is different than other games,' Says Lead Mirandus Dev]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/GbkRmy1x/dying-in-this-game-is-different-than-other-games-says-lead-mirandus-dev</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/GbkRmy1x/dying-in-this-game-is-different-than-other-games-says-lead-mirandus-dev"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T17:53:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gala Games Cofounder and Mirandus Developer Michael McCarthy tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about Mirandus' hardcore fantasy world and its high stakes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: Arthur Hayes Says Crypto Failures Are A Sign of The System Cleansing Itself]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZHyccGKp/gm-arthur-hayes-says-crypto-failures-are-a-sign-of-the-system-cleansing-itself</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZHyccGKp/gm-arthur-hayes-says-crypto-failures-are-a-sign-of-the-system-cleansing-itself"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T13:47:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arthur Hayes says the speed at which projects like Terra grow and implode is a feature of the crypto industry, not a bug. He founded crypto exchange Bitmex in 2014 and then became the original crypto bad boy. In 2021 the DOJ charged him in with violating the U.S. Bank Secrecy Act for not implementing an anti-money laundering program at Bitmex. He plead guilty and was sentenced to two years probation and six months of home detention. In fact, he was still sporting an ankle bracelet on a recent cover of New York Magazine. Now he's living in Singapore, offering up his views on the crypto industry with long form, meme-filled essays, and still thinks the crypto industry will save investors from what he calls a broken banking system. "I don't care if you're capitalist or you're a communist. Everybody put on a lot of debt. We've passed the point where that debt is becoming useful," he said. "And therefore everyone is going to take an L unless they get some crypto or some gold—some hard asset that's outside of the traditional banking system."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brycent on Meeting Gary Vaynerchuk through Web3 Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/xL8pz64R/brycent-on-meeting-gary-vaynerchuk-through-web3-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/xL8pz64R/brycent-on-meeting-gary-vaynerchuk-through-web3-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T22:23:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XSET gamer and content creator Brycent tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about how entrepreneur and VeeFriends creator Gary Vaynerchuk first reached out to him.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: Anthony Scaramucci Is More Bullish on Bitcoin Than Ever]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PqLOXL47/gm-anthony-scaramucci-is-more-bullish-on-bitcoin-than-ever</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PqLOXL47/gm-anthony-scaramucci-is-more-bullish-on-bitcoin-than-ever"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T18:58:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthony Scaramucci of hedge fund SkyBridge Capital got burned by Sam Bankman-Fried: he co-hosted SALT conferences with FTX and sold a 30% stake in SkyBridge to FTX Ventures. And yet "The Mooch" tells Dan Roberts and Stacy Elliott "I'm more bullish now than I have ever been" on crypto as an investment case. He discusses his frustration with SBF, how wrong he thinks politicians like Elizabeth Warren and Gary Gensler are about crypto and how to regulate it, what he sees happening next with adoption, and talks about Trump. Watch and make sure to subscribe to the gm podcast on Apple or Spotify.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Chief Legal Officer: The Problem With SEC's Howey Test Isn't Its Age]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/woZFLgib/coinbase-chief-legal-officer-the-problem-with-secs-howey-test-isnt-its-age</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/woZFLgib/coinbase-chief-legal-officer-the-problem-with-secs-howey-test-isnt-its-age"/>
        <updated>2023-04-10T16:25:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Chief Legal Officer Paul Grewal discussed the "Howey Test," which the SEC uses as its yard stick for whether a crypto asset should be regulated as a security, and told Decrypt's Stacy Elliott and Dan Roberts the issue with it isn't that it's old (the case is from 1946) but how it's being applied to modern technology. Watch and make sure to subscribe to the gm podcast on Apple or Spotify.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized Pictures Plots Its Next Web3 Grant for Filmmakers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/WlVsgaOs/decentralized-pictures-plots-its-next-web3-grant-for-filmmakers</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/WlVsgaOs/decentralized-pictures-plots-its-next-web3-grant-for-filmmakers"/>
        <updated>2023-04-08T13:15:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leo Matchett from Web3 film funding platform Decentralized Pictures tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson at Outer Edge LA about DCP's just announced iPhone Filmmaking Initiative, which will support aspiring filmmakers who create a short film on their iPhones, and will be determined via DCP's crypto-native on-chain voting system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 YouTuber CryptoStache: Gaming Will Be the Catalyst That Takes NFTs Mainstream]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Exb7eWKj/web3-youtuber-cryptostache-gaming-will-be-the-catalyst-that-takes-nfts-mainstream</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Exb7eWKj/web3-youtuber-cryptostache-gaming-will-be-the-catalyst-that-takes-nfts-mainstream"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T02:51:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 gaming YouTuber CryptoStache talks to Decrypt's Jason Nelson at Outer Edge LA about why Web3 gaming will bring NFTs mainstream, the partnerships that prove it's already happening, how gamers will change their tune on NFTs, and how the terminology is likely to change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fordefi Aims to Dramatically Simplify the Institutional Crypto Wallet]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/LGxyFJP5/fordefi-aims-to-dramatically-simplify-the-institutional-crypto-wallet</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/LGxyFJP5/fordefi-aims-to-dramatically-simplify-the-institutional-crypto-wallet"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T02:39:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Steve H., VP of sales from Fordefi, which raised $18 million in funding last year, tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson at Outer Edge LA how Fordefi uses multi-party computation to make signing transactions on an institutional crypto wallet much simpler—no seed phrase needed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: Canadian Bitcoin Miner Hut 8 Is Heading West]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5AGD2ifd/gm-canadian-bitcoin-miner-hut-8-is-heading-west</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5AGD2ifd/gm-canadian-bitcoin-miner-hut-8-is-heading-west"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T21:40:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Toronto-based Bitcoin mining company Hut 8 recently announced a merger with U.S. Bitcoin Corp that will take it into Texas, Nebraska, and New York. Hut 8 CEO Jaime Leverton joined Dan Roberts and Stacy Elliott to talk expanding into the U.S., dealing with regulatory pushback post-FTX, why Texas is such a hotspot, and where she'd like to expand globally down the road (the climates may surprise you). Watch and make sure to subscribe to the gm podcast on Apple or Spotify.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>