<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-12-30T11:11:54.206Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-12-30T11:11:54.206Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Indian Exchanges in Crisis Talks After Govt Blocks Binance, Kucoin]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19141314/Indian-Exchanges-in-Crisis-Talks-After-Govt-Blocks-Binance-Kucoin</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19141314/Indian-Exchanges-in-Crisis-Talks-After-Govt-Blocks-Binance-Kucoin"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T10:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto exchanges in India have reportedly convened for emergency meetings. The crisis talk came after the Indian government moved to block Binance, Kucoin, Huobi, and Kraken. Indian exchanges heavily rely on Binance for liquidity, creating a tight situation. Prominent crypto exchanges in India...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlocking tokens: Crypto projects to release over $150M in January 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19141303/Unlocking-tokens-Crypto-projects-to-release-over-150M-in-January-2024</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19141303/Unlocking-tokens-Crypto-projects-to-release-over-150M-in-January-2024"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T10:55:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto enthusiasts and investors brace themselves as Token Unlock, a prominent tracker of locked tokens, reveals details of upcoming token unlocks slated for the first week of January 2024. This disclosure shines a spotlight on the significant value of tokens worth more than $150.84 million set...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Launches AI-Powered Copilot App for iOS and iPadOS Users]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19141304/Microsoft-Launches-AI-Powered-Copilot-App-for-iOS-and-iPadOS-Users</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19141304/Microsoft-Launches-AI-Powered-Copilot-App-for-iOS-and-iPadOS-Users"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T10:51:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has expanded its AI-powered capabilities by launching the Copilot app for Apple iOS and iPadOS users. The application, formerly known as Bing Chat, is now available for download on the Apple App Store, providing users with an innovative chat assistant experience. Copilot distinguishes...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin to Reach New Important ATHs in 2024, Samson Mow Believes]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19141310/Bitcoin-to-Reach-New-Important-ATHs-in-2024-Samson-Mow-Believes</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19141310/Bitcoin-to-Reach-New-Important-ATHs-in-2024-Samson-Mow-Believes"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T10:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of Bitcoin maximalists, Samson Mow, has shared his bullish Bitcoin predictions for upcoming 2024 year]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fidelity’s 2024 Crypto Outlook: Bull Runs, Halvings, and Regulatory Shifts]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19141302/Fidelitys-2024-Crypto-Outlook-Bull-Runs-Halvings-and-Regulatory-Shifts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19141302/Fidelitys-2024-Crypto-Outlook-Bull-Runs-Halvings-and-Regulatory-Shifts"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T10:44:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fidelity Investments’ analysis for the upcoming year focuses on five critical themes that could shape the future of crypto investments. These themes range from macroeconomic factors like Federal Reserve policies to specific crypto events such as the Bitcoin halving, offering a comprehensive view...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[S15 E1: Max Hillebrand & Lando Rothbardian on Integrating ShopInBit's "Buy Anything" Into Wasabi Wallet]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19141292/S15-E1-Max-Hillebrand-Lando-Rothbardian-on-Integrating-ShopInBits-Buy-Anything-Into-Wasabi-Wallet</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19141292/S15-E1-Max-Hillebrand-Lando-Rothbardian-on-Integrating-ShopInBits-Buy-Anything-Into-Wasabi-Wallet"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T10:43:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wasabi Wallet now offers a "Buy Anything" button that lets you buy physical items with greater privacy?! How does that even work? ZK Snacks CEO Max Hillebrand & ShopInBit CEO Lando Rothbardian join the show to explain everything about this integration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Monero Lead Maintainer Calls on Binance to Take a Stance on Privacy Coin Issue]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7487cbde32</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/former-monero-lead-maintainer-calls-on-binance-to-take-a-stance-on-privacy-coin-issue/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T10:43:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ricardo Spagni, the former lead maintainer of Monero, one of the most used privacy coins in the cryptocurrency market, has called on Binance to take a stance on the issue of privacy coins. Spagni stated that avoiding taking sides in the process is a disservice to the whole industry and that any protocol-level changes to make Monero compliant are “unnecessary.”
Former Monero Lead Dev Ricardo ‘Fluffypony’ Spagni Calls on Binance to Stand for Privacy Coins
Ricardo “Fluffypony” Spagni, the former lead maintainer of Monero, has called on Binance to change its position on delisting privacy-focused coins. In a recent X post, Spagni criticizes Binance’s stance, which could lead to the delisting of these currencies in January.
Supported by a report produced by consulting firm Perkinscoie, which sta…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Contemplates Layoffs as AI Advances in Ad Sales Division]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19141295/Google-Contemplates-Layoffs-as-AI-Advances-in-Ad-Sales-Division</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19141295/Google-Contemplates-Layoffs-as-AI-Advances-in-Ad-Sales-Division"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T10:41:02.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nigeria’s Yellow Card anticipates crypto boom post-CBN ban lift]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19141280/Nigerias-Yellow-Card-anticipates-crypto-boom-post-CBN-ban-lift</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19141280/Nigerias-Yellow-Card-anticipates-crypto-boom-post-CBN-ban-lift"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T10:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Bard picks 4 commodities to buy for start of 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19141284/Google-Bard-picks-4-commodities-to-buy-for-start-of-2024</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19141284/Google-Bard-picks-4-commodities-to-buy-for-start-of-2024"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T10:34:56.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BREAKING: Crypto Will DOUBLE In 2024, BIG Money Coming To Crypto & Elon Musk Twitter & Dogecoin]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19141296/BREAKING-Crypto-Will-DOUBLE-In-2024-BIG-Money-Coming-To-Crypto-Elon-Musk-Twitter-Dogecoin</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19141296/BREAKING-Crypto-Will-DOUBLE-In-2024-BIG-Money-Coming-To-Crypto-Elon-Musk-Twitter-Dogecoin"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T10:30:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Its about that time again, it looks like we have some brand new expectations for the cryptocurrency market in 2024 and I think people will like what they hear. A major world power might be getting ready to introduce their OWN Spot cryptocurrency ETFs and Elon Musk spoke and people got...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No Encore: FTX Maestro Sam Bankman-Fried Escapes Second Criminal Trial]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7487b5938d</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/sam-bankman-fried-escapes-second-criminal-trial/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T10:23:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The meteoric rise and catastrophic crash of FTX, once a cryptocurrency empire helmed by the seemingly benevolent “King of Crypto” Sam Bankman-Fried, is a story far too complex to encapsulate in a single headline. While his conviction on charges of defrauding customers marks a significant milestone, the echoes of this financial earthquake will resonate for years to come.
 
FTX’s Fallout: Investor Losses, Regulatory Scrutiny
 
With the goal of saving time, the government told US District Judge Lewis Kaplan in a letter on Friday that it would not be bringing a second set of charges against Bankman-Fried for conspiracy to bribe foreign officials, bank fraud, and running an unlicensed money transmitting business.
 
The judge is permitted to consider a substantial portion of the evidence that wi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These 3 coins came back from the dead in 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19141254/These-3-coins-came-back-from-the-dead-in-2023</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19141254/These-3-coins-came-back-from-the-dead-in-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T10:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trader Predicts ‘Fireworks’ for Blue-Chip Altcoin if Critical Support Area Is Reclaimed, Updates Bitcoin Outlook]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19141257/Trader-Predicts-Fireworks-for-Blue-Chip-Altcoin-if-Critical-Support-Area-Is-Reclaimed-Updates-Bitcoin-Outlook</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19141257/Trader-Predicts-Fireworks-for-Blue-Chip-Altcoin-if-Critical-Support-Area-Is-Reclaimed-Updates-Bitcoin-Outlook"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T10:15:59.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Indonesian authorities shut down Bitcoin mining operations over electricity theft]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19141237/Indonesian-authorities-shut-down-Bitcoin-mining-operations-over-electricity-theft</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19141237/Indonesian-authorities-shut-down-Bitcoin-mining-operations-over-electricity-theft"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T10:08:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, Indonesian police authorities have taken decisive action against a network of Bitcoin mining operations, accusing their organizers of stealing nearly $1 million of electricity. The North Sumatra Police Force spearheaded the crackdown on this multi-site Bitcoin mining operation,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former FTX CEO Sam Bankman-Fried is unlikely to face a second trial]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19141216/Former-FTX-CEO-Sam-Bankman-Fried-is-unlikely-to-face-a-second-trial</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19141216/Former-FTX-CEO-Sam-Bankman-Fried-is-unlikely-to-face-a-second-trial"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T09:58:11.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Bulls Break Rank as Current Uptrend Gets Rejected]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19141222/XRP-Bulls-Break-Rank-as-Current-Uptrend-Gets-Rejected</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19141222/XRP-Bulls-Break-Rank-as-Current-Uptrend-Gets-Rejected"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T09:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XRP price slips amid waning buying interest, is year-end rally still possible?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BSV Skyrockets 110% Weekly and Taps $100, BTC Struggles Below $42K (Weekend Watch)]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19141206/BSV-Skyrockets-110-Weekly-and-Taps-100-BTC-Struggles-Below-42K-Weekend-Watch</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19141206/BSV-Skyrockets-110-Weekly-and-Taps-100-BTC-Struggles-Below-42K-Weekend-Watch"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T09:48:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BSV has trumped all other top 100 crypto assets in terms of weekly gains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US prosecutors water down FTX Ex-CEO SBF’s second trial probability: no new evidence]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19141177/US-prosecutors-water-down-FTX-Ex-CEO-SBFs-second-trial-probability-no-new-evidence</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19141177/US-prosecutors-water-down-FTX-Ex-CEO-SBFs-second-trial-probability-no-new-evidence"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T09:23:28.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Critic Jamie Dimon’s JPMorgan to Buy BTC on Behalf of BlackRock’s ETF]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19141172/Bitcoin-Critic-Jamie-Dimons-JPMorgan-to-Buy-BTC-on-Behalf-of-BlackRocks-ETF</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19141172/Bitcoin-Critic-Jamie-Dimons-JPMorgan-to-Buy-BTC-on-Behalf-of-BlackRocks-ETF"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T09:15:04.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analyst Insights on Diverse Rulings- Ripple’s XRP and Terraform’s LUNA]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19141153/Analyst-Insights-on-Diverse-Rulings-Ripples-XRP-and-Terraforms-LUNA</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19141153/Analyst-Insights-on-Diverse-Rulings-Ripples-XRP-and-Terraforms-LUNA"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T08:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Judge Jed S. Rakoff ruled Terraform Labs’ four tokens, including LUNA and UST, as unregistered securities. Attorney Rispoli commented that XRP would have also been deemed a security if Judge Rakoff ruled it. The attorney highlighted the necessity of Congress’ action for unbiased ruling in the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developer Alerts Ledger Live Software Could Be Tracking User IDs, Apps and Balances]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7487be8717</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/developer-alerts-ledger-live-software-could-be-tracking-user-ids-apps-and-balances/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T08:41:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rektbuilder, a developer, has stated that cryptocurrency hardware wallet company Ledger can track user identities, apps, and even cryptocurrency balances in the device through the use of Ledger Live, its wallet management software. The developer discovered this behavior while working on Lecce Libre, a lighter, less intrusive software for the hardware wallet.
Ledger Live Sends User Information to Ledger, Developer Alleges
Developer Rektbuilder alerted about the information that Ledger, the hardware wallet manufacturer, receives through its wallet management program Ledger Live. According to his findings, the software embeds checks for the ID of each device when installing or updating apps and firmware.
The developer, currently working on “Lecce Libre,” a less intrusive and lighter app to ma…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BNB Chain’s 2023: Revolutionizing Web3 Development with opBNB and Greenfield]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19141126/BNB-Chains-2023-Revolutionizing-Web3-Development-with-opBNB-and-Greenfield</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19141126/BNB-Chains-2023-Revolutionizing-Web3-Development-with-opBNB-and-Greenfield"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T08:32:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The year 2023 marked a significant milestone in the evolution of blockchain technology and Web3 development, particularly for BNB Chain. The launch of opBNB and Greenfield has not only enriched the BNB Chain ecosystem but also significantly lowered the entry barriers to Web3 development. The...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fidelity, Others Amend Spot Bitcoin ETF Forms On Deadline Day – Details]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7487bfff07</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/fidelity-others-amend-bitcoin-etf-on-deadline-day/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T08:24:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the last few weeks, there have been notable developments in the spot Bitcoin ETF saga in the US, with asset managers revising their application forms following dialogue with the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). 
 
On December 29, which marked the final day for S-1 amendments, Fidelity Investments, alongside six other asset managers, namely VanEck, Bitwise, WisdomTree, Invesco, BlackRock, and Valkyrie, all updated their ETF applications with the SEC in what seems like a preparatory move for an approval by the US securities regulator.
 
 
Fidelity Offers Lowest Sponsor Fee In Incentive Competition Among Asset Managers
 
In its S-1 form update, Fidelity Investments revealed more information on its proposed spot Bitcoin ETF, notably announcing Jane Street Capital as an authorize…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Semilore Faleti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC’s Cash Only Restriction for Spot Bitcoin ETF Is Nonsense, Says Vaneck Director]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7487a08793</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/secs-cash-only-restriction-for-spot-bitcoin-etf-is-nonsense-says-vaneck-director/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T06:40:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A director of digital assets strategy at asset management firm Vaneck says the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC)’s cash-only requirement for spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) is “nonsense.” He predicted that it would not hold out for long since publicly listed companies already hold billions of dollars in bitcoin on their balance sheets.
 
‘The Cash-Only Create/Redeem Requirement for the Bitcoin ETPs Is Kabuki Theatre’
 
Gabor Gurbacs, director of Digital Assets Strategy at asset management firm Vaneck, thinks it’s “nonsense” for the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to require spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) issuers to use the cash creation method instead of the in-kind model for their crypto exchange-traded products (ETPs). The executive stated on …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia Makes a Slower GPU for China Under New U.S. Trade Restrictions]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211222</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211222/nvidia-rtx-4090d-gpu-chinese-market"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T05:08:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new GPU specifically designed for the Chinese market won’t be a top performer, but will still be good enough for gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[India Cracks Down on Offshore Crypto Exchanges — Blocks Binance, 8 Other Platforms]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7487a9a527</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/india-cracks-down-on-offshore-crypto-exchanges-blocks-binance-8-other-platforms/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T04:38:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Indian government has directed the Ministry of Electronics and Information Technology to bar access to offshore cryptocurrency exchanges deemed illegal within the country. The nine affected crypto platforms include Binance, Kucoin, Huobi, Kraken, and Bitfinex. The Ministry of Finance also revealed that 31 crypto service providers have registered with the country’s Financial Intelligence Unit to date.
 
India Blocks 9 Offshore Crypto Platforms
 
India’s Ministry of Finance announced Thursday that the Financial Intelligence Unit India (FIU IND) has issued “compliance Show Cause Notices” to nine offshore crypto service providers. The Indian government brought crypto service providers into the ambit of the country’s Anti Money Laundering/Counter Financing of Terrorism (AML-CFT) framework i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Expert Analysis: Pro-XRP Lawyer Challenges Stablecoin Securities In Terraform Labs Case]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7487906abd</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/pro-xrp-lawyer-challenges-stablecoin-securities/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T03:04:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent ruling by US District Judge Jed Rakoff, the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) emerged victorious in the Terraform Labs case, causing concern and unease within the cryptocurrency community over the classification of stablecoins.This has led legal experts to question the ruling and its implications.
 
The case centered around Do Kwon, a cryptocurrency entrepreneur, and his company Terraform Labs, who were found to have violated US law by failing to register two digital currencies that eventually collapsed in 2022. The TerraUSD stablecoin and Luna (LUNC) were at the heart of the SEC’s allegations.
 
Doubts On Stablecoin’s Security Status
 
Pro-XRP lawyer Jeremy Hogan took to social media, expressing skepticism over the classification of stablecoins as securities. 
 
Jere…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Lawmakers Seek to Fire SEC Chair Gary Gensler in 2024]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7487924639</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/us-lawmakers-seek-to-fire-sec-chair-gary-gensler-in-2024/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T02:38:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two U.S. lawmakers have joined forces in an effort to fire Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Chairman Gary Gensler. “2024 would be a great time to fire Gary Gensler, pass the SEC Stabilization Act, [and] hold the SEC accountable for its corruption,” Congressman Warren Davidson announced.
 
‘2024 Would Be a Great Time to Fire Gary Gensler’
 
Representatives Warren Davidson (R-OH) and Tom Emmer (R-MN) are seeking to remove Gary Gensler as the chairman of the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). Congressman Davidson wrote on social media platform X Thursday:
 

2024 would be a great time to fire Gary Gensler, pass the SEC Stabilization Act, hold the SEC accountable for its corruption, and end the accredited investor rule that protects deal flow for the donor class.
 
Davidson introduced the SEC Stabilization Act earlier in June to fire Gensler as the chair of the securities regulator. He previously explained that the bill would “remove the role of chairman,” noting: “It would preserve the current commissioners but it would add a sixth commissioner so there would be no more than three from any one political party.”
 
Congressman Emmer has also repeatedly criticized Gensler for his enforcement-centric approach to regulating the crypto industry. He wrote on X Thursday: “Gensler’s SEC sides with Wall Street, not Main Street. I’m proud to join Warren Davidson as a co-lead on his bill, the SEC Stabilization Act, so we can fire Gary Gensler.”
 
Davidson is also against the Federal Reserve launching a digital dollar. In an X post on Tuesday, the lawmaker called for the ban of central bank digital currencies. He opined:
 

Central bank digital currency (CBDC) poses an existential threat to western civilization. Sound money serves as a stable store of value and an efficient means of exchange. CBDC consummates the corruption of money into a dystopian tool for coercion & control. Ban them.
 
Do you think SEC Chair Gary Gensler should be fired? Let us know in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ESL Faceit Group Exploring Blockchain 'Opportunistically,' Says Exec]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/yvrs4lBx/esl-faceit-group-exploring-blockchain-opportunistically-says-exec</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/yvrs4lBx/esl-faceit-group-exploring-blockchain-opportunistically-says-exec"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T02:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Braithwaite—ESL Faceit Group's VP of Game Ecosystems, Mobile, and Snapdragon Pro Series—shares the esports firm's approach to blockchain technology with GG's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOJ Halts Second Trial Against FTX’s Bankman Fried, Citing Sufficiency of Initial Evidence and ‘Public Interest’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74879e8be9</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/doj-halts-second-trial-against-ftxs-bankman-fried-citing-sufficiency-of-initial-evidence-and-public-interest/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T01:37:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Dec. 29, 2023, past 6 p.m. Eastern Time (ET), the Department of Justice (DOJ) conveyed in a letter to Judge Lewis Kaplan its decision to not move forward with a subsequent trial against Sam Bankman-Fried, the ex-CEO of FTX.
 
FTX’s Bankman Fried Avoids Second Trial
 
According to several reports on Friday evening, prosecutors have decided against pursuing a second trial against Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF). Matthew Russell Lee of the Inner City Press disclosed the update on X, posting a snapshot of the DOJ’s letter and also distributing it on his Patreon.
 
“So no evidence and cross examination about the campaign finance and China bribe counts, no getting to the bottom of who took the money,” Russell Lee wrote on Friday. “It is known that officials in the Bahamas, whose request to drop these…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Founder Sam Bankman-Fried Won't Face Second Criminal Trial, U.S. Prosecutors Say]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748798858b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-news/2023/12/30/ftx-founder-sam-bankman-fried-wont-face-second-criminal-trial-us-prosecutors-say/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T01:10:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The lawyers said much of the evidence they planned to introduce in the second trial was already introduced in the first case and can be considered in the sentencing planned for March 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Napolitano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Invesco, Fidelity, BlackRock, Others Dot Their Bureaucratic I's as Likely SEC Action on Spot Bitcoin ETF Looms]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74879b076f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-news/2023/12/29/invesco-fidelity-blackrock-others-dot-their-bureaucratic-is-as-likely-sec-action-on-spot-bitcoin-etf-looms/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T00:37:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock, Fidelity and Invesco want all their ducks in a row should the SEC grant approvals early in the new year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Senate Ethics Committee Urged to Investigate Senator Elizabeth Warren on Misleading Crypto Statements]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74879b1054</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/senate-ethics-committee-urged-to-investigate-senator-elizabeth-warren-on-misleading-crypto-statements/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T00:36:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CEO of the Chamber of Digital Commerce says the Senate Ethics Committee should launch a full investigation on Senator Elizabeth Warren for making false and misleading statements about crypto. “Senator Elizabeth Warren has misled the American people as well as the U.S. Congress on multiple fronts,” she stressed.
 
‘Senate Ethics Committee Should Launch a Full Investigation’
 
Chamber of Digital Commerce founder and CEO Perianne Boring slammed U.S. Senator Elizabeth Warren (D-MA) for making false and misleading statements regarding cryptocurrency in an interview with Fox Business on Thursday.
 
“Senator Elizabeth Warren has misled the American people as well as the U.S. Congress on multiple fronts,” the Chamber of Digital Commerce chief began. “First, she’s misled us to believe that cryp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP And Dogecoin Flip Solana, Avalanche To Be Among Most Liquid Cryptocurrencies]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74879b6c89</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/xrp-dogecoin-flip-solana-avalanche-most-liquid/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T00:32:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An analysis by blockchain analytics platform Kaiko revealed that XRP and Dogecoin (DOGE) are among the top four most liquid cryptocurrencies, only trailing Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH). 
 
This finding challenges the conventional wisdom that market capitalization is a wholesome metric for evaluating a cryptocurrency’s price, and thus, liquidity.
 
 
Assessing Crypto Liquidity: What Factors Were Considered?
 
In their report, Kaiko argues that liquidity, which measures how easily an asset can be traded, is a more accurate representation of a cryptocurrency’s true worth. Market capitalization and fully diluted value, according to Kaiko, provide an incomplete picture of a cryptocurrency’s value proposition. 
 
To measure market capitalization, the asset’s price and tokens in circulation p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dalmas Ngetich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JPMorgan CEO's Bitcoin Bashing Is a 'Do as I Say, Not as I Do' Situation]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748787f515</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/12/29/jpmorgan-ceos-bitcoin-bashing-is-a-do-as-i-say-not-as-i-do-situation/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T23:35:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jamie Dimon's bank agreed to play a key role with BlackRock's proposed bitcoin ETF, just weeks after he told U.S. senators: "I've always been deeply opposed to crypto, bitcoin, etc."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Baker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VanEck Joins Bitcoin ETF Ad War With New Teaser Trailer]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211215</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211215/vaneck-joins-bitcoin-etf-ad-war-with-new-teaser-trailer"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T23:06:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The investment firm teased the as-of-yet non-existent financial product days before the latest of several supposed deadlines the SEC faces to approve one.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Founder Vitalik Buterin Shares Thoughts On The Current State Of Web3]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748782d331</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-founder-vitalik-buterin-web3/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T23:01:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent blog post titled “Make Ethereum Cypherpunk Again” the founder of Ethereum, Vitalik Buterin has expressed his thoughts on the current state of the Web3 ecosystem.
 
Ethereum Founder Voices Concerns Over Faded Web3 Vision
 
In a blog post published on December 28, Ethereum Founder, Vitalik Buterin reflected on his past experiences from a decade ago where he witnessed Bitcoin’s steady adoption and integration into daily life activities. In this reflection, Buterin highlighted the transformative vision he visualizes of the Web3 ecosystem.
 
“The reason why I bring these memories up is that they remind me of a deeper vision underlying crypto: we are not here to just create isolated tools and games, but rather build holistically toward a more free and open society and economy, where …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Best Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlimited Innovations vs. 2,500 Swimming Pools — AI Faces Similar Environmental Backlash as Bitcoin Mining]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74878cc945</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/unlimited-innovations-vs-2500-swimming-pools-ai-faces-similar-environmental-backlash-as-bitcoin-mining/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T22:38:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In recent years, attention has centered on bitcoin mining, particularly its energy usage in securing the network and validating transactions through proof-of-work (PoW). As generative artificial intelligence (AI) emerges as a major force in technology, it’s encountering similar environmental concerns. Moreover, advocates of bitcoin are drawing parallels between the criticisms of AI’s energy demands and those directed at cryptocurrency mining.
 
Eco-Impact of AI: Facing the Environmental Challenges of Innovation
 
Although AI has generally received acclaim in the press, its consumption of electricity and water has recently sparked considerable debate. Numerous online articles decry the significant resources AI utilizes, including a Rolling Stone piece alleging that “Microsoft’s global water…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Crypto King” Tom Emmer Mounts Offensive Against SEC Chair Gary Gensler With Ouster Bill]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74878d5b99</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-king-challenges-sec-chair-gary-gensler/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T22:31:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US Congressman Tom Emmer, known for his digital asset expertise and pro-cryptocurrency stance and dubbed the “Crypto King” of Congress, has taken a bold step by introducing the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Stabilization Act.
 
The legislation, co-led by Emmer, aims to remove SEC Chairman Gary Gensler from his position, citing concerns over his regulatory actions in the digital asset sector.
 
Emmer Alleges Gensler Targets Crypto Industry Unfairly
 
Since assuming the role in 2021 during President Biden’s administration, Chairman Gensler has faced persistent criticism from Congressman Tom Emmer regarding the SEC’s approach to cryptocurrency regulation. 
 
Emmer alleges that Gensler shares an anti-crypto sentiment with billionaire Warren Buffett and has been disproportionately ta…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock Bitcoin ETF Names JP Morgan, Jane Street as Authorized Participants]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211208</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211208/blackrock-bitcoin-etf-jp-morgan-jane-street"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T21:37:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The amendment is one of the last steps in the application process, experts say.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock, Valkyrie Name Authorized Participants Including JPMorgan for Bitcoin ETF]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74878b2738</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/12/29/blackrock-names-jp-morgan-jane-street-as-authorized-participants-for-bitcoin-etf/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T21:27:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock will use J.P. Morgan and Jane Street as their authorized participants. Valkyrie has also named Jane Street in addition to Cantor Fitzgerald.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Argentina’s President Javier Milei Sends Omnibus Bill to Congress, Seeking Legislative Powers]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7487750c6f</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/argentinas-president-javier-milei-sends-omnibus-bill-to-congress-seeking-legislative-powers/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T21:06:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Argentina’s President Javier Milei has sent a massive new bill to Congress to adopt a scheme of regulations to advance his goal of modernizing the Argentine state. If approved, the bill would allow Milei to legislate by executive order on certain emergency areas and privatize state companies, among other aspects.
 
Javier Milei Proposes Omnibus Bill to Obtain Legislative Faculties
 
Argentina’s President Javier Milei has continued pressing on in his transformative goals for the country. The so-called libertarian has sent a massive omnibus bill to Congress, which touches on or modifies 20 laws. The bill, titled “Law of Bases and Starting Points for the Freedom of Argentines,” seeks to continue with the ostensibly libertarian reform of the Argentine state, touching on subjects like personal …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Chainlink Nightmare: Investor Duped Out Of $4.66 Million In Cunning Phishing Scam]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7487757b6c</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/chainlink-nightmare-investor-duped-phishing-scam/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T21:02:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Chainlink (LINK) crypto investor has recently suffered a catastrophic loss due to a sophisticated phishing attack. The victim, who had been trading and accumulating LINK tokens, was duped into approving a fraudulent transaction, resulting in the loss of roughly $4.66 million.
 
The Chainlink Investor Phishing Attack: A Detailed Breakdown
 
The investor, over a period starting from June 7, 2022, to October 14, 2023, had built up a portfolio of 290,750 LINK tokens valued at $2.26 million. Interestingly, the savvy trading strategies allowed the investor to profit nearly $2.4 million.
 
 
However, this financial success turned sour when the investor clicked on a phishing link, unwittingly authorizing a malicious transaction.
 
According to analytics firm Lookonchain’s report, the victim’s er…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Free Money': These Are the Hottest Airdrops Around Right Now]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209179</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209179/free-money-hottest-airdrops-around-right-now"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T20:50:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATED: More and more airdrops are coming, including from Jupiter, Portal, Blast, and Frame, plus Solana Saga owners can claim more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Got 'Worthless' NFTs? This Startup Buys JPEGs for a Penny to Harvest Tax Losses]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211186</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211186/got-worthless-nfts-startup-buys-jpegs-penny-harvest-tax-losses"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T19:16:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unsellable says it has helped NFT collectors realize $4.2 million worth of tax losses to date by buying up their illiquid assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Token ORDI Surges to New High, Nearing Top 50 Coins]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211185</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211185/bitcoin-token-ordi-surges-new-high-nearing-top-50-coins"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T18:44:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price of ORDI, the biggest token minted on the Bitcoin network, is surging again today—and is one of this week's best-performers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF Race Could Get Tighter After This Deadline]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211188</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211188/bitcoin-etf-race-amendment-deadline"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T18:14:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fund managers vying to release a spot Bitcoin ETF have until today to file a key amendment to their applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gamers Bash Xbox for Controversial Art Apparently Made by AI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211178</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211178/gamers-bash-xbox-controversial-art-apparently-made-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T16:54:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aiming to promote the human creativity behind indie games, Xbox instead enrages gamers by apparently using AI-generated art.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These Are the High-Profile Spot Bitcoin ETF Applications Currently in Play]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=62912</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/62912/high-profile-bitcoin-etf-applications"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T15:30:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. SEC has dragged its heels on approval of a Bitcoin spot ETF—but analysts are optimistic that there's light at the end of the tunnel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin: Web3 Vision Has 'Faded' Due to Rising Transaction Fees]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211148</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211148/vitalik-buterin-web3-vision-has-faded-due-to-rising-transaction-fees"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T13:12:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Degen gamblers" have become "the only audience that remains willing to pay" when transaction fees soar, Buterin said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche Foundation to Invest in Meme Coin Collection]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211145</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211145/avalanche-foundation-to-invest-in-meme-coin-collection"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T10:50:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price of Avalanche-based meme coins including Husky Avax and Coq Inu rose by double-digits on the news.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Ernie Bot from Baidu Reaches 100 Million Users in China]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211138</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211138/baidu-ernie-bot-ai-chatbot-china"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T02:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Baidu's conversational AI demonstrates swift traction at home, even as it looks to close the gap globally.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Most Powerful Generative AI Text Tools of 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211128</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211128/decrypt-emerge-best-large-language-models-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T01:02:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whatever your style, there will always be a Large Language Model (LLM) out there for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Judge Sides With SEC Over Do Kwon, Says UST, LUNA Are Securities]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211129</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211129/judge-sides-with-sec-over-do-kwon-says-ust-luna-are-securities"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T23:49:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The summary judgment removes one of the biggest questions looming over Kwon’s trial, which will now focus solely on allegations of fraud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GG's 2023 Year in Review: Stories That Rocked the Gaming World]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211122</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211122/ggs-2023-year-review-stories-rocked-gaming-world"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T22:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From layoffs to GTA 6 and Microsoft acquiring Activision, these are the stories that defined 2023 in gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[India Will Block Binance, Kraken, and Other Exchanges in Crypto Crackdown]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211114</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211114/india-block-binance-kraken-other-exchanges-crypto-crackdown"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T20:32:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[India's Financial Intelligence Unit said the crypto exchanges were operating illegally in the country. Now their websites will be blocked.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$14 Billion in Bitcoin Options Expire Tomorrow—Here’s Why It Matters]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211113</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211113/14-billion-bitcoin-options-expire-tomorrow-why-it-matters"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T19:40:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's $14 billion worth of Bitcoin options expiring on Friday. The split between puts and call shows investors are feeling bullish.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Traders May Be Lining Up to 'Sell the News' on ETF Approval]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211108</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211108/bitcoin-traders-sell-news-etf-approval"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T18:37:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price of Bitcoin could plunge if a spot exchange-traded fund (ETF) is approved in the U.S. in January, CryptoQuant claims.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blast Deposits Top $1.1 Billion Ahead of Ethereum L2 Launch and Airdrop]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211107</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211107/blast-deposits-top-1-1-billion-ahead-ethereum-l2-launch-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T18:11:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Paradigm-backed Ethereum scaler’s rollout has been controversial, but that isn’t stopping users from buying in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Dips Below $100 as Meme Coin Trading Reverses Course]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211101</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211101/solana-dips-below-100-meme-coin-trading-bonk"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T16:51:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SOL may have burned a little too hot a little too fast, now falling 7% in 24 hours.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cathie Wood's ARK Sells Remaining GBTC Shares, Buys $100M in Bitcoin Futures ETF]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211088</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211088/cathie-woods-ark-sells-remaining-gbtc-shares-buys-100m-in-bitcoin-futures-etf"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T13:52:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The asset manager offloaded 2.25 million GBTC shares and purchased 4.32 million shares of the ProShares Bitcoin Strategy ETF.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PancakeSwap's CAKE Jumps 7% on Proposal to Slash Token Supply by 300 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211085</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211085/pancakeswaps-cake-jumps-5-on-proposal-to-slash-token-supply-by-300-million"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T10:45:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PancakeSwap's CAKE token jumped by 4% following the proposal, which would see its maximum supply reduced from 750 million to 450 million.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Dumps Millions in Ethereum After Disastrous NFT Redux]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211064</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211064/trump-dumps-millions-in-eth-after-disastrous-nft-redux"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T00:53:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The former president has cashed out $2.4 million worth of ETH in the last three weeks, Arkham reports.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Biggest Space Stories of 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211059</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211059/the-biggest-space-stories-of-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T23:53:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even amid an avalanche of AI news, space exploration still managed to make headlines this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Biggest Crypto Airdrops of 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211031</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211031/biggest-crypto-airdrops-2023-arbitrum-blur-celestia-jito"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T23:03:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The top token handouts of the year netted users over $4.5 billion worth of free crypto. Here are 2023's biggest crypto airdrops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Gaming Predictions: Will 2024 Be the Breakout Year?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210772</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210772/crypto-gaming-predictions-2024-breakout-year"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T22:29:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto industry leaders remain optimistic about the future of blockchain gaming. Here's what they expect in 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brakes on Bonk: Solana Meme Coin Down 56% From All-Time High]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211030</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211030/bonk-solana-based-meme-coin-slows-down"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T21:41:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The meme token is now well below the all-time high it touched two weeks ago.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Game On: The Hottest Upcoming Gaming Token Airdrops]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211029</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211029/game-on-hottest-upcoming-gaming-token-airdrops"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T21:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From Portal to Saga, these are the token airdrops that crypto gamers should be paying close attention to right now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI Trained AI Models on Copyrighted Work, Says NYT Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211006</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211006/openai-trained-ai-models-on-copyrighted-work-says-nyt-lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T19:02:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Current methods for training AI on copyrighted work means “less journalism will be produced, and the cost to society will be enormous,” says the NYT.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PlayStation Plus: Latest Free PS5 Games to Download]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207958</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207958/playstation-plus-latest-free-ps5-games-download"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATED: Sony's next batch of free PS5 games for PlayStation Plus subscribers has been announced. Here's what you can grab soon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Jumps, But the Real Winners Are Optimism, Arbitrum, and Polygon]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210990</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210990/ethereum-jumps-real-winners-optimism-arbitrum-polygon"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T18:18:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum is up significantly today, but the tokens behind projects that make the ecosystem faster and cheaper to use are doing even better.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Year in Bitcoin: ETFs, Ordinals and What Comes Next]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210926</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210926/year-in-bitcoin-etfs-ordinals-what-comes-next"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T18:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin was in survival mode at the start of the year and then made a massive comeback.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's 2023 NFT Project of the Year: Pudgy Penguins]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210727</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210727/decrypts-nft-project-year-2023-pudgy-penguins"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T17:34:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum collection Pudgy Penguins thrived in Crypto Winter and now is gliding to new heights on the back of mainstream market toys.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xai Gaming Token Airdrop Delayed—Here's When It's Coming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210989</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210989/xai-gaming-token-airdrop-delayed-heres-when-coming"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T17:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arbitrum's "layer-3" gaming network is pushing back its XAI airdrop. Here's why, and who’s eligible for the rescheduled launch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy Boosts Its Bitcoin Holdings to $8 Billion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210969</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210969/microstrategy-boosts-its-bitcoin-holdings-to-8-billion"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T16:11:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company has spent $5.9 billion to build its BTC treasury.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Got a Solana Saga Before They Sold Out? Here Are All the Airdrops You Can Claim]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210634</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210634/solana-saga-airdrops-tokens-nfts-you-can-claim"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T15:49:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATED: Our list has been updated with even more airdrops, NFTs, and other perks for Solana Saga owners. Check out the latest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘We’re Living Longer, But We’re Living Longer, Sicker’: Rejuve CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210928</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210928/were-living-longer-but-were-living-longer-sicker-rejuve-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-12-26T22:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A SingularityNET spinoff hopes to leverage AI and blockchain to crowdsource better health and longevity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Slips Standalone Copilot AI App Into Android Store]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210918</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210918/microsoft-slips-standalone-copilot-app-for-android-into-google-app-store"/>
        <updated>2023-12-26T22:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a late Christmas gift to generative AI fans, the Redmond-based tech giant released a free mobile app to rival popular paid options.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wildcard's Plans for 2024 with Founders Paul and Katy Bettner]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/TI3aFBhO/wildcards-plans-for-2024-with-founders-paul-and-katy-bettner</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/TI3aFBhO/wildcards-plans-for-2024-with-founders-paul-and-katy-bettner"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T21:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wildcard developers Paul and Katy Bettner tell Decrypt's Kate Irwin about why they see their game as a "Web3 game," not a crypto game, and share why they've stuck with their initial vision despite the challenging broader market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt and Rug Radio Merge to Create Global Web3 Publishing Company]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/VTEBYFD8/decrypt-and-rug-radio-merge-to-create-global-web3-publishing-company</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/VTEBYFD8/decrypt-and-rug-radio-merge-to-create-global-web3-publishing-company"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T17:04:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt and Rug Radio have announced their intent to merge, creating the world’s biggest decentralized publishing company. Codenamed [REDACTED], the alliance is aimed at revolutionizing tech-media, bringing together the forces of content creation and consumption.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['If You Play Well, You're Gonna be Rewarded': How FPS Web3War is Bringing 'Skill-to-Earn' to Crypto Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Jl5AEFuD/if-you-play-well-youre-gonna-be-rewarded-how-fps-web3war-is-bringing-skill-to-earn-to-crypto-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Jl5AEFuD/if-you-play-well-youre-gonna-be-rewarded-how-fps-web3war-is-bringing-skill-to-earn-to-crypto-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T10:20:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roll1ng Thund3rz co-founder Valentin Cobelea and Zilliqa CEO Matt Dyer joined Decrypt to discuss how the new FPS game Web3War is shaking up the crypto gaming space with a novel "skill to earn" mechanic that rewards players for high-quality gameplay.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating peaceful money & taking over your local government w/ Joseph Schiarizzi]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zb0VG27G/creating-peaceful-money-taking-over-your-local-government-w-joseph-schiarizzi</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zb0VG27G/creating-peaceful-money-taking-over-your-local-government-w-joseph-schiarizzi"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T23:23:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week our host Reza Jafery is joined by Joseph Schiarizzi, founder of OpenDollar and prolific solidity developer. 


We discuss: 
- Onchain beer
- Taking over your local government
- His Emmy and 3 patents?!?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INTERVIEW: Ember Sword CEO Says NFT Games Are More 'Transparent']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/M9OHCVpA/interview-ember-sword-ceo-says-nft-games-are-more-transparent</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/M9OHCVpA/interview-ember-sword-ceo-says-nft-games-are-more-transparent"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T21:58:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ember Sword CEO Mark Laursen shares why some big game studios "irk" him—and why he got into game development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Director Jordan Bayne on the State of Film3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZLoEDkL9/director-jordan-bayne-on-the-state-of-film3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZLoEDkL9/director-jordan-bayne-on-the-state-of-film3"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T00:11:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the 2023 Film3 Summit, Jordan Bayne—director and founder of The Squad—spoke with Decrypt's Sander Lutz about how the Film3 world has progressed over the last year and what decentralized technologies can offer to creators that want to buck the Hollywood system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Questions With SCENE: Phil Mohun]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TwOjXfOR/5-questions-with-scene-phil-mohun</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TwOjXfOR/5-questions-with-scene-phil-mohun"/>
        <updated>2023-12-01T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bright Moments co-founder Phil Mohun joins 5 Questions With SCENE to recount some favorite moments from the road, including negotiating with Patagonian gauchos, falling in love with Tokyo, and gaining a newfound appreciation for shrooms chocolate bars.

Shot and edited by Vincent Roazzi Jr.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>