<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-06-16T02:40:30.902Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-06-16T02:40:30.902Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alt coins are just another fiat currency! #bitcoin #crypto #shorts]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18584728/Alt-coins-are-just-another-fiat-currency-bitcoin-crypto-shorts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18584728/Alt-coins-are-just-another-fiat-currency-bitcoin-crypto-shorts"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T02:14:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alt coins and fiat are basically the same.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Court Will Rule on Terraform Labs' Push to Dismiss SEC Lawsuit Within a Month]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18584709/US-Court-Will-Rule-on-Terraform-Labs-Push-to-Dismiss-SEC-Lawsuit-Within-a-Month</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18584709/US-Court-Will-Rule-on-Terraform-Labs-Push-to-Dismiss-SEC-Lawsuit-Within-a-Month"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T01:57:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Was UST a security because it was designed for practical uses rather than as an investment?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mercedes-Benz Is Adding ChatGPT to Cars for AI Voice Commands]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144872</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144872/mercedes-benz-adding-chatgpt-cars-ai-voice-commands"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T01:55:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The luxury automaker is set to integrate OpenAI's ChatGPT chatbot into its Mercedes-Benz User Experience (MBUX) feature in the U.S.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mercedes-Benz Is Adding ChatGPT to Cars for AI Voice Commands]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18584696/Mercedes-Benz-Is-Adding-ChatGPT-to-Cars-for-AI-Voice-Commands</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18584696/Mercedes-Benz-Is-Adding-ChatGPT-to-Cars-for-AI-Voice-Commands"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T01:55:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The luxury automaker is set to integrate OpenAI's ChatGPT chatbot into its Mercedes-Benz User Experience (MBUX) feature in the U.S.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Firm Abra Said to be Insolvent in Texas State Regulators’ Cease-and-Desist Order]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757ee5d0ff</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/crypto-firm-abra-said-to-be-insolvent-in-texas-state-regulators-cease-and-desist-order/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T01:40:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to an emergency cease-and-desist order from the Texas State Securities Board, the cryptocurrency firm Abra is “insolvent or nearly insolvent.” The filing alleges that a group of state securities regulators has been investigating Abra, and the working group interviewed William Barhydt, the company’s founder, in March 2023.
 
Texas State Regulators Issue Cease-and-Desist Order, Citing Insolvency Claims Against Crypto Firm Abra
 
The Texas State Securities Board (TSSB) has issued an emergency cease-and-desist order against the company Abra and its network of subsidiaries. The notice alleges that Abra and its affiliate companies are “collectively insolvent or nearly insolvent.” The order also named Plutus Financial, Plutus Lending, Abra Boost, and the firm’s founder, William John “Bi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase doubles USDC rewards to 4% amid SEC scrutiny on staking services]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18584674/Coinbase-doubles-USDC-rewards-to-4-amid-SEC-scrutiny-on-staking-services</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18584674/Coinbase-doubles-USDC-rewards-to-4-amid-SEC-scrutiny-on-staking-services"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T01:26:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase said in a June 15 tweet that it now offers 4% rewards on USDC. Coinbase’s newly increased reward rate means that the company has approximately doubled its previously offered returns on USD Coin (USDC). As recently as June 9, the company’s website said that customers could only earn 2%...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin edges up after slump, Ether little-changed, other top 10 tokens continue bumpy ride]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18584676/Bitcoin-edges-up-after-slump-Ether-little-changed-other-top-10-tokens-continue-bumpy-ride</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18584676/Bitcoin-edges-up-after-slump-Ether-little-changed-other-top-10-tokens-continue-bumpy-ride"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T01:24:33.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlockFi Sues State Commission for Not Accepting Its Surrendered License]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144879</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144879/blockfi-sues-connecticut-banking-commission"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T01:23:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bankrupt crypto exchange wants to surrender its license, but regulators are insisting on what BlockFi says would be an expensive court proceeding.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is USDT About to Depeg?! #shorts]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18584660/Is-USDT-About-to-Depeg-shorts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18584660/Is-USDT-About-to-Depeg-shorts"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T01:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ukraine Wants to Tax Crypto Gains at 18% from 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18584661/Ukraine-Wants-to-Tax-Crypto-Gains-at-18-from-2024</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18584661/Ukraine-Wants-to-Tax-Crypto-Gains-at-18-from-2024"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T01:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ukrainian regulators are prepared to start taxing crypto gains at 18% from 2024, with lawmakers set to vote on proposals this fall. Per Forbes Ukraine, the National Commission for Securities and the Stock Market is set to unveil a draft law, which will be set before lawmakers at the next...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Mover Asia: Hong Kong as Crypto Hub? The City's Strict Banking Requirements May Be an Obstacle]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757ee2a242</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/06/16/first-mover-asia-hong-kong-as-crypto-hub-the-citys-strict-banking-requirements-may-be-an-obstacle/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T00:42:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Hong Kong-based entrepreneur says that while the digital assets regulation is "overall friendly," banking regulations will make the industry's growth there difficult. ALSO: Bitcoin surges post-BlackRock iShares ETF filing but the rally sputters.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds, James Rubin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analyzing the state of Arbitrum since its mega AirDrop event in March]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18584634/Analyzing-the-state-of-Arbitrum-since-its-mega-AirDrop-event-in-March</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18584634/Analyzing-the-state-of-Arbitrum-since-its-mega-AirDrop-event-in-March"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T00:30:55.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinEx Exchange Banned In New York, Authorities Recover $1.7 Million]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757eecf7a1</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/coinex-banned-in-new-york-recover-1-7-million/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T00:14:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Attorney General Letitia James has issued a ban on CoinEx, a Hong Kong-based cryptocurrency exchange, prohibiting its operations within the state of New York. The ban follows an announcement on June 15 revealing that the exchange’s funds, totaling over $1.7 million, were seized.
 
The seizure was conducted due to allegations of CoinEx’s failure to register as a securities and commodities brokerage, as required by regulation in the United States. A proposed settlement was recently filed in a New York state court in Manhattan, awaiting the judge’s approval.
 
 
The settlement outlines the terms and conditions for CoinEx, the Hong Kong-based cryptocurrency exchange. Specifically, the exchange would be barred from offering, selling, or purchasing securities and commodities in New York.
 
Furth…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>anushsamal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Mover Asia: Hong Kong as Crypto Hub? The City's Strict Banking Requirements May Be an Obstacle]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18584624/First-Mover-Asia-Hong-Kong-as-Crypto-Hub-The-Citys-Strict-Banking-Requirements-May-Be-an-Obstacle</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18584624/First-Mover-Asia-Hong-Kong-as-Crypto-Hub-The-Citys-Strict-Banking-Requirements-May-Be-an-Obstacle"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T00:08:19.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Dollar Dominance Is Coming to an End, Time For Chinese Yuan To Advance Has Arrived: CEO of Russia’s Second-Largest Bank]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18584616/US-Dollar-Dominance-Is-Coming-to-an-End-Time-For-Chinese-Yuan-To-Advance-Has-Arrived-CEO-of-Russias-Second-Largest-Bank</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18584616/US-Dollar-Dominance-Is-Coming-to-an-End-Time-For-Chinese-Yuan-To-Advance-Has-Arrived-CEO-of-Russias-Second-Largest-Bank"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T00:04:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The chief executive of Russia’s second-largest bank says that the US dollar is on the verge of losing its role as the world’s dominant currency amid the rise of the Chinese yuan. In a new interview with Reuters, VTB Bank CEO Andrey Kostin says the move by the United States and its allies to block […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Benjamin Cowen Predicts Collapse in Ethereum (ETH) Against Bitcoin (BTC) – Here’s His Outlook]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18584600/Benjamin-Cowen-Predicts-Collapse-in-Ethereum-ETH-Against-Bitcoin-BTC-Heres-His-Outlook</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18584600/Benjamin-Cowen-Predicts-Collapse-in-Ethereum-ETH-Against-Bitcoin-BTC-Heres-His-Outlook"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T00:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Widely followed crypto analyst Benjamin Cowen is warning of a possible Ethereum (ETH) collapse relative to Bitcoin (BTC) as the altcoin markets continue to flash signs of weakness. In a new strategy session, Cowen tells his 783,000 YouTube subscribers that the ETH/BTC pair could drop more than...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinEx Exchange Banned In New York, Authorities Recover $1.7 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18584613/CoinEx-Exchange-Banned-In-New-York-Authorities-Recover-17-Million</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18584613/CoinEx-Exchange-Banned-In-New-York-Authorities-Recover-17-Million"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T00:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock Files Bitcoin ETF Application, Leveraging Coinbase Custody]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757eef3efc</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/markets/blackrock-nears-filing-bitcoin-etf-application-leveraging-coinbase-custody"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T23:50:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock, the worlds largest asset manager, has filed an application for a spot Bitcoin ETF (exchange-traded fund). 
In their pursuit of a Bitcoin ETF, BlackRock has chosen Coinbase Custody as their trusted custodial solution. The proposed ETF will be benchmarked against indices provided by CF Benchmarks. The indices will be comprised of price data from six exchanges: Coinbase, Kraken, Gemini, Bitstamp, itBit, and LMAX Digital.
It is worth noting that the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), the regulatory authority responsible for overseeing ETFs in the United States, has thus far rejected every application for a spot bitcoin ETF. Nevertheless, the commission has granted approval for several bitcoin futures ETFs, which have been successfully introduced for trading.
BlackRock's filing for a spot Bitcoin ETF signals a turning point in the industry, as a prominent player in the traditional financial space acknowledges the potential of Bitcoin. If approved, the Bitcoin ETF would open doors to a new wave of adoption and provide investors with an unprecedented opportunity to participate in the Bitcoin market through a regulated and accessible investment vehicle.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nik Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Token Sale Ahead: Celsius to Convert Customer ‘Altcoins’ to BTC and ETH]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757ee86f48</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/token-sale-ahead-celsius-to-convert-customer-altcoins-to-btc-and-eth/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T23:37:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amid the regulatory crackdown in the United States, the bankrupt crypto lender Celsius has announced that all of its customers’ “altcoins” will be converted to bitcoin (BTC) and ethereum (ETH). Over $215 million worth of coins such as CEL, ADA, LINK, LTC, and others will be sold beginning on July 1, 2023.
 
Celsius Plans to Convert 15 Different Tokens to Bitcoin and Ethereum
 
In mid-February 2023, Celsius announced it would be acquired by Novawulf Digital Management to execute the reorganization plan. The firm filed its plan on June 15, and as per the latest revisions, customers who possess “altcoins” will have their balances converted to BTC and ETH on July 1. The only accounts exempted from this conversion are the “custody and withhold accounts.”
 
“Celsius will be selling all altcoins …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Korean crypto contagion, Bank of China on Ethereum, HK’s exchange red carpet: Asia Express]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18584587/Korean-crypto-contagion-Bank-of-China-on-Ethereum-HKs-exchange-red-carpet-Asia-Express</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18584587/Korean-crypto-contagion-Bank-of-China-on-Ethereum-HKs-exchange-red-carpet-Asia-Express"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T23:33:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong lays out welcome mat for exchanges, Korean crypto lender contagion, Do Kwon banged up abroad, Bank of China’s Ethereum debt note.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mark Cuban Predicts Crypto Apocalypse: 90% Of Companies Will Go Broke]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757eea8462</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/billionaire-mark-cuban-predicts-crypto-apocalypse/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T23:15:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tech behemoth Mark Cuban and former Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) official John Reed Stark engaged in a heated exchange over the ongoing regulatory crackdown on the crypto industry. 
 
The discussion was sparked by the recent temporary restraining order (TRO) hearing against Binance, which sought to freeze all of the exchange’s U.S. assets.
 
 
Cuban And Stark Clash Over Judge’s Remarks In Binance Case
 
Cuban argued that not all crypto businesses with tokens or considering using tokens are large “enterprises,” as Stark had assumed. He pointed out that most crypto applications are small, with only a few people involved. 
 
He also shared his experience of a small company that had called the SEC for guidance on getting registered. The response they received was to review some cas…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock applies for spot Bitcoin ETF — a US first if approved]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18584558/BlackRock-applies-for-spot-Bitcoin-ETF-a-US-first-if-approved</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18584558/BlackRock-applies-for-spot-Bitcoin-ETF-a-US-first-if-approved"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T23:03:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The investment firm joins a long line of applicants; ARK is among those still waiting to hear from the SEC, and Grayscale has appealed its rejection.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alchemy's ChatGPT Plugin Enables Easier Blockchain Analysis Via AI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144856</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144856/alchemy-chatgpt-ai-plugin-enables-easier-blockchain-analysis"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T23:02:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alchemy’s new GPT-4 plugin harnesses the power of AI to deliver user-friendly, real-time blockchain analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alchemy's ChatGPT Plugin Enables Easier Blockchain Analysis Via AI]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18584563/Alchemys-ChatGPT-Plugin-Enables-Easier-Blockchain-Analysis-Via-AI</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18584563/Alchemys-ChatGPT-Plugin-Enables-Easier-Blockchain-Analysis-Via-AI"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T23:02:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alchemy’s new GPT-4 plugin harnesses the power of AI to deliver user-friendly, real-time blockchain analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["AI Is Game-Changing But Needs Fact-Checking": AlchemyAI Project Lead]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/HXlThlXv/ai-is-game-changing-but-needs-fact-checking-alchemyai-project-lead</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/HXlThlXv/ai-is-game-changing-but-needs-fact-checking-alchemyai-project-lead"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this interview, Decrypt's Jason Nelson chats with Alchemy product manager and AlchemyAI project lead Elan Halpern on blockchain analysis using ChatGPT, what AI means for better user experience, and the need to fact-check AI. Halpern also gives a demo of the new AlchemyAI ChatGPT plugin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["AI Is Game-Changing But Needs Fact-Checking": AlchemyAI Project Lead]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18584572/AI-Is-Game-Changing-But-Needs-Fact-Checking-AlchemyAI-Project-Lead</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18584572/AI-Is-Game-Changing-But-Needs-Fact-Checking-AlchemyAI-Project-Lead"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Banned In New York, CoinEx Returns $1.7 Million to Settle Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144820</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144820/banned-in-new-york-coinex-returns-1-7-million-to-settle-lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T22:50:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New York Attorney General Letitia James announced a $1.7 million settlement with Hong Kong-based CoinEx over securities violations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do Kwon to Remain in Custody While Montenegro Courts Consider Extradition Request: Report]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757ed69d59</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/06/15/do-kwon-to-remain-in-custody-while-montenegro-courts-consider-extradition-request-report/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T22:32:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Courts in the country approved bail for the Terraform Labs founder, but a South Korea extradition request is set to keep him in jail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandali Handagama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aptos’ latest milestone could leave investors craving for more because…]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18584530/Aptos-latest-milestone-could-leave-investors-craving-for-more-because</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18584530/Aptos-latest-milestone-could-leave-investors-craving-for-more-because"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T22:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prometheum: What You Need to Know About the SEC’s Poster Child for Crypto Compliance]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144833</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144833/prometheum-sec-poster-child-crypto-compliance"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T22:21:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prometheum's co-CEO gave remarks on Capitol Hill that mirrored the SEC's stance. Now industry observers are poring over the startup’s paper trail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prometheum: What You Need to Know About the SEC’s Poster Child for Crypto Compliance]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18584522/Prometheum-What-You-Need-to-Know-About-the-SECs-Poster-Child-for-Crypto-Compliance</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18584522/Prometheum-What-You-Need-to-Know-About-the-SECs-Poster-Child-for-Crypto-Compliance"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T22:21:52.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Dominance Spikes To 47.6% As Holders Ditch Altcoins For BTC]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757ed039e3</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-dominance-spikes-47-6-ditch-altcoins-btc/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T22:16:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data shows that Bitcoin dominance has risen to a value of 47.6% as investors have been rotating their altcoins into BTC.
 
Bitcoin Dominance Has Gone Up By 7.6% Since The Start Of 2023
 
As the on-chain analytics firm Glassnode pointed out, alts are being constantly rotated into the original cryptocurrency. The “dominance” here refers to the percentage of the total cryptocurrency market cap that the market cap of Bitcoin alone accounts for.
 
When the value of this metric goes up, it means that the market share of the cryptocurrency is growing right now. Such a trend can indicate that investors prefer to invest in the asset over the current altcoins.
 
On the other hand, decreasing values of the indicator can be a sign that the holders are relatively losing interest in BTC as the market ca…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hououin Kyouma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain Analytics Firm Chainalysis Urges Crypto Firms to Start MiCA Preparations Now]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18584513/Blockchain-Analytics-Firm-Chainalysis-Urges-Crypto-Firms-to-Start-MiCA-Preparations-Now</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18584513/Blockchain-Analytics-Firm-Chainalysis-Urges-Crypto-Firms-to-Start-MiCA-Preparations-Now"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T22:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking: Blackrock Reveals Plan To Take Over Bitcoin & Crypto Industry]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18584514/BREAKING-BLACKROCK-REVEALS-PLAN-TO-TAKE-OVER-BITCOIN-CRYPTO-INDUSTRY</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18584514/BREAKING-BLACKROCK-REVEALS-PLAN-TO-TAKE-OVER-BITCOIN-CRYPTO-INDUSTRY"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T22:08:50.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Allowing Users to Earn Digital Assets Drive Wider Cryptocurrency Adoption?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757ed25e37</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/innovation/will-allowing-users-to-earn-digital-assets-drive-wider-cryptocurrency-adoption/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T21:56:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrencies  
have received a lot of interest in recent years because they provide a  
decentralized and digital form of money. However, widespread acceptance continues  
to be a struggle. Allowing consumers to earn digital assets is one potential  
method for increasing cryptocurrency adoption.
In this  
article, we will look at how to earn digital assets and how it affects bitcoin  
acceptance. We will examine whether allowing users to earn digital assets may  
expedite the general acceptance of cryptocurrencies, from the benefits for  
individuals to the ramifications for businesses and the wider crypto ecosystem.
The Current  
State of Cryptocurrency Adoption
Despite substantial  
progress, cryptocurrency use remains mostly limited to tech-savvy individuals  
and early adopters. V…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FM Contributors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Jumps Past $25.7K After BlackRock iShares ETF Filing]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757ed34a82</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/06/15/bitcoin-jumps-past-257k-after-blackrock-ishares-etf-filing/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T21:47:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The largest cryptocurrency rose more than 1.3% in the hour after the announcement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Rubin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sotheby's Second 3AC NFT Sale Nets $10.9M, With 'The Goose' Alone Netting $6.2M]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757ed34a7f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/web3/2023/06/15/sothebys-second-3ac-nft-sale-nets-109m-with-the-goose-alone-netting-62m/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T21:47:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ringers #879, a seminal NFT artwork often referred to as "The Goose," far outpaced estimates and sold for $tk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rosie Perper</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[House Financial Services Republicans Blast SEC’s Proposed Rule, State Gensler Is Pushing ‘His Own Personal Views Regarding Digital Assets’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757edc699f</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/house-financial-services-republicans-blast-secs-proposed-rule-state-gensler-is-pushing-his-own-personal-views-regarding-digital-assets/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T21:37:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Republicans of the House Financial Services Committee have criticized U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Chair Gary Gensler, stating he is using Rule 3b-16 amendments to impose his views on cryptocurrency assets. In a letter sent to the SEC, republicans push back against the new proposed definition of “exchange” and its implications.
Financial Services Committee Republicans Push Back Against SEC’s Proposed Ruleset
Republicans of the House Financial Services Committee are pushing back against the proposed amendments to Rule 3b-16 presented by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) that expands the definition of “exchange.”
The group, comprising Chair Patrick McHenry and 28 other representatives, sent a letter on June 13 criticizing the implications of the approval of t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitch's New Favorite Game 'Only Up' Is Loaded With Goblintown NFT Art]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144815</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144815/twitch-new-game-only-up-goblintown-nft"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T21:31:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More than 100,000 simultaneous viewers watched streamers play clumsy climbing game Only Up, which is packed with Goblintown references.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock Files Bitcoin ETF Application With the SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144782</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144782/blackrock-filing-bitcoin-etf-application-soon-reports"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T21:28:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock, with Coinbase as its partner, has submitted an application for a spot Bitcoin ETF following a Thursday morning report.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock's iShares Files Paperwork for Spot Bitcoin ETF]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757edd6cb0</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/06/15/blackrocks-ishares-files-paperwork-for-spot-bitcoin-etf/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T21:27:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC has rejected numerous attempts by other fund companies to launch a spot bitcoin ETF.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen  Alpher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celsius Cleans House: All Altcoins To Be Sold For Bitcoin And Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757ede9720</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/celsius-cleans-house-all-altcoins-to-be-sold/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T21:17:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Defunct crypto lender Celsius Network has proposed a joint reorganization plan to resolve its outstanding claims and interests under Chapter 11 of the Bankruptcy Code.
 
As part of this plan, Celsius has requested court approval to convert all altcoin holdings, except those designated for Withhold or Custody accounts, to Bitcoin and Ethereum. According to the filing, the conversion will be done using commercially reasonable efforts to maximize value. If the plan is approved, Celsius will begin converting the altcoins on July 1. 
 
 
Celsius Customers Alert
 
For several reasons, celsius’ move to convert all altcoins to Bitcoin and Ethereum is strategic. Firstly, it allows the company to streamline operations by focusing on the two most popular and valuable cryptocurrencies. 
 
This will si…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jack Dorsey's Block Bitcoin Wallet Opens Beta, Announces Coinbase Support]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144825</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144825/jack-dorseys-block-bitcoin-wallet-opens-beta-announces-coinbase-support"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T21:05:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitkey will allow beta users to withdraw Bitcoin from Coinbase and Cashapp using "copy and paste."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Regains Ground to Reach $25.2K, but Investors Remain Jittery About U.S. Economy, Monetary Policy]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757eda393f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/06/15/bitcoin-regains-ground-to-reach-252k-but-investors-remain-jittery-about-us-economy-monetary-policy/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T20:44:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tether’s USDT stablecoin loses its $1 peg, while other major cryptos spend their day in red territory.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Rubin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dmitri Cherniak's 'The Goose' NFT Sells at Sotheby's Auction for $5.4M]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757edaa2db</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/web3/2023/06/15/dmitri-cherniaks-the-goose-nft-sells-at-sothebys-auction-for-54m/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T20:40:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NFT was purchased by 3AC co-founders Su Zhu and Kyle Davies in August 2021 for about 1,800 ETH – worth roughly $5.8 million at the time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rosie Perper</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MakerDAO Hikes DAI Savings Rate, Ousts Paxos Dollar, Curbs Gemini Dollar in Reserve]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757edaa2cc</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/06/15/makerdao-hikes-dai-savings-rate-ousts-paxos-dollar-curbs-gemini-dollar-in-reserve/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T20:40:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The move could redefine baseline interest rates in the DeFi space, spurring higher stablecoin lending rates and making leverage more expensive, one analyst noted.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFT Artwork Owned by Three Arrows Capital Sells for $6.2 Million at Sotheby's]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144816</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144816/nft-artwork-owned-three-arrows-capital-sells-6-2-million-sothebys"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T20:37:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ringers #879, a.k.a. "The Goose," sold for over $6.2 million with fees at today's Sotheby's Grails: Part II live auction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong Authorities Encourage Major Banks To Embrace Crypto Clients]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757ec55126</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/hong-kong-authorities-encourage-embrace-crypto/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T20:17:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to reports, the Hong Kong Monetary Authority (HKMA), the regulatory body overseeing banking activities in the region, has allegedly been encouraging major banks such as HSBC and Standard Chartered to establish relationships with cryptocurrency exchanges.
 
This push to embrace the crypto sector comes despite the heightened regulatory scrutiny faced by the industry on a global scale. This initiative aims to position Hong Kong as a prominent global hub for the cryptocurrency industry.
 
 
However, the sector still grapples with challenges arising from significant collapses that have occurred in the past. A report dated June 15 revealed that three sources with knowledge of the matter disclosed that the Hong Kong Monetary Authority (HKMA) raised queries during a May meeting with UK-b…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>anushsamal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trade like a pro: Choose PrimeXBT crypto futures]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757ec55122</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/trade-like-a-pro-choose-primexbt-crypto-futures/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T20:17:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a professional trader, you’re always on the lookout for platforms that offer cutting-edge tools, a wide range of instruments, and high liquidity. PrimeXBT, a rapidly growing cryptocurrency trading platform, has become a preferred choice for many seasoned traders. 
 
With a broad range of features tailored to suit the needs of pros, PrimeXBT presents a compelling case. Let’s explore why this platform is a top choice for professional crypto futures trading.
 

 
PrimeXBT crypto futures advantages
 
Right off the bat, PrimeXBT stands out with its advanced trading tools and user-friendly interface. While the platform is straightforward enough for beginners, it truly shines when experienced traders leverage its advanced functionalities. 
 
One of the main advantages that PrimeXBT offers is i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Every CEX Needs a DEX]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757ec54dee</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/06/15/every-cex-needs-a-dex/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T20:17:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralization used to be a cherished principle, it’s now a competitive necessity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergey Gorbunov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[As Crypto Burned Stateside, NFT Believers Partied Through the Night in Lisbon]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144748</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144748/crypto-burned-stateside-nft-believers-partied-through-night-lisbon"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T19:22:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC's actions against the largest crypto exchanges were barely a footnote during the NFT extravaganza at NFC Lisbon in Portugal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former FTX Ventures Head Amy Wu Turns to AI After Being 'Duped' by SBF]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144795</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144795/former-ftx-ventures-head-amy-wu-turns-to-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T18:26:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite a dark episode at FTX Ventures, Wu has now joined Menlo Ventures to help spearhead its investments in AI and consumer tech.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Colombia’s Central Bank Taps Ripple to Pilot CBDC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144799</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144799/colombia-central-bank-ripple-cbdc"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T18:15:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Colombia already makes use of Ripple's technology for land distribution efforts in the country.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Devs Cry Foul on Uniswap v4 'Open Source' Promises]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144802</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144802/ethereum-devs-cry-foul-on-uniswap-v4-open-source-promises"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T17:54:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's a few licenses that Ethereum devs consider the mark of a truly open source project. The one Uniswap chose for its v4 isn't one of them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD Debuts AI Chip to Challenge Nvidia]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144788</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144788/amd-debuts-ai-chip-to-challenge-nvidia"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T17:29:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company's new MI300X AI Chip will be a direct competitor to the dominance of Nvidia's H100.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Heads East as Huobi HK Launches Trading Service in Hong Kong]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142955</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142955/crypto-heads-east-as-huobi-hk-launches-trading-service-in-hong-kong"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T17:25:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Huobi has joined the Hong Kong Virtual Assets Consortium (HKVAC), while its Hong Kong arm now offers crypto spot trading and virtual asset custody.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Whale Moves $1.2 Million After 13 Years of Inactivity]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144786</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144786/bitcoin-whale-moves-million-after-13-years"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T16:53:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some long-term investors are moving their stashes after years of remaining dormant.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arbitrum's New 'Layer-3' Xai Network Is Built to Power Web3 Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144775</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144775/arbitrums-new-layer-3-xai-network-built-power-web3-games"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T16:01:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dedicated gaming network Xai is launching with support from Offchain Labs, with games like Final Form and LAMOverse up first.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fedi's Bitcoin Federations Could Onboard Next 1 Billion Users, Says CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144599</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144599/fedis-bitcoin-federations-could-onboard-next-1-billion-users-says-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T14:21:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fedi CEO Obi Nwosu has big plans for kickstarting Bitcoin adoption via a unique, Lightning-powered community app called "Federations."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cyber Criminals Are Turning to Crypto Mining Pools to Wash Ill-Gotten Funds: Chainalysis]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144762</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144762/cyber-criminals-are-turning-crypto-mining-pools-wash-ill-gotten-funds-chainalysis"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T13:01:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ransomware actors are increasingly trying to pass off their own funds as proceeds received from cryptocurrency mining, claims Chainalysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Artificial Intelligence (AI) Take Over Your Job?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137047</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/will-artificial-intelligence-take-over-your-job-decryptu"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T10:39:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jobs requiring human ingenuity or creativity, or which rely heavily on social and emotional skills, might be the safest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Reiff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum, Cardano, and Dogecoin Lead Weekly Crypto Losses]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144741</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144741/ethereum-cardano-dogecoin-lead-weekly-crypto-losses"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T09:59:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After the largest altcoins, Bitcoin is also shedding value as the crypto market continues to digest yesterday’s fed notes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried Trial Can Proceed on Original Charges Only, Says DoJ]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144740</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144740/sam-bankman-fried-trial-can-only-proceed-original-charges-says-doj"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T09:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Government is willing to wait a bit longer to try the FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried on several additional counts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alys Key</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether CTO Says 'Let Them Come' as Stablecoin's Dollar Peg Wobbles]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144735</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144735/tether-cto-says-let-them-come-stablecoin-peg-wobbles"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T08:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the market's largest stablecoin waffling, the Tether CTO took to Twitter to assure investors that redemptions won't be a problem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Take AI Warnings Seriously, Says UN Secretary-General]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144692</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144692/take-ai-warnings-seriously-un-secretary-general"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T23:54:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The official called for the creation of something akin to the International Atomic Energy Agency to regulate AI tech.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Republicans Continue to Defend Crypto in Latest Letter to SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144671</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144671/republicans-continue-to-defend-crypto-in-letter-to-sec"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T23:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[House Financial Services Committee leaders warned that the SEC’s suggested new definition of “exchange” would hurt innovation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Bad Like Brooklyn Dancehall' Brings Shaggy and Jamaican Culture to Tribeca]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144614</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144614/bad-like-brooklyn-dancehall-brings-shaggy-jamaican-culture-tribeca"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T22:54:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The documentary, executive produced by musician Shaggy, debuted at the Tribeca Film Festival with help from Decentralized Pictures.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Gold Rush: Generative AI Poised to Pump $4.4 Trillion Into Global Economy Annually]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144684</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144684/ai-gold-rush-generative-ai-4-trillion-into-global-economy-annually"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T22:53:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Generative AI could be a major player in the AI industry as a whole, which could be worth $15.7 trillion by 2030.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Miami's 'Bitcoin Mayor' Will Challenge Donald Trump for US President]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144682</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144682/miamis-bitcoin-mayor-files-to-run-for-u-s-president"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T22:08:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Francis X. Suarez has been an outspoken advocate of cryptocurrency since taking office in 2017.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Leaders Praise Draft GOP Bill, Dems Raise Concerns]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144663</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144663/crypto-leaders-praise-draft-gop-bill-dems-raise-concerns"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T21:37:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Congress invited crypto executives to testify on a bill that some say may undermine the SEC]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Lender Delio Freezes Withdrawals Citing 'Market Volatility']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144675</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144675/crypto-lender-delio-freezes-withdrawals-citing-market-volatility"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T21:01:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Delio is the second South Korean platform to suspend withdrawals this week after Haru Invest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prime Trust Partner Banq Files for Bankruptcy Following BitGo Deal]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144672</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144672/prime-trust-partner-banq-files-for-bankruptcy-following-bitgo-acquisition-deal"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T20:55:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prime Trust is set to be acquired by BitGo after a period of "garbage" spending last summer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unleash ChatGPT: The Top 7 Plugins You Should Know in 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144661</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144661/unleash-chatgpt-the-top-7-plugins-you-should-know-in-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T20:32:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT plugins integrate other apps into the OpenAI chatbot, enhancing it with diverse, user-friendly AI features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fractal Is Like an Arcade, Says Twitch Co-Founder Justin Kan]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/6r6Mdwt6/fractal-is-like-an-arcade-says-twitch-co-founder-justin-kan</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/6r6Mdwt6/fractal-is-like-an-arcade-says-twitch-co-founder-justin-kan"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Justin Kan was a co-founder of Twitch and now works on Fractal, a Web3 gaming startup. Kan tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about his new company and what he's up to.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Mobile Puzzle Game Earns You Bitcoin or Ethereum for Playing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144601</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144601/this-mobile-puzzle-game-earns-you-bitcoin-ethereum-playing"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T20:23:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[REVIEW: Stack sats or eke out ETH in Ethereum Blast, a solid but simplistic (and ad-heavy) iOS and Android puzzle game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Trade Sideways as Fed Skips Rate Hike]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144620</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144620/bitcoin-ethereum-trade-sideways-fed-skips-rate-hike"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T19:48:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s the first time the Fed has not raised rates at a meeting in 18 months.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Set to Leave Cyprus Ahead of MiCA Legislation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144595</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144595/binance-moves-to-deregister-cyprus-entity-ahead-of-mica-legislation"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T19:13:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The exchange said it's looking to focus elsewhere in Europe—and “will continue to comply with applicable laws of the European Union."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['NFTs Can't Scale' in Current Form, Say Superduper Co-founders]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144579</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144579/nfts-cant-scale-current-format-say-superduper-founders"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T16:44:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At this year’s NFC, the Superduper founders stressed that getting NFTs to mass adoption won’t be easy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Hard Fork to Stave Off SEC? Devs Say It's Not Happening]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144576</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144576/solana-hard-fork-devs-say-its-not-happening"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T15:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“I work on the largest Solana project, with more than 10 developers, and nobody is discussing [a hard fork]” said Matías Kudelski, a cyber security researcher who audits Solana’s code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Firms Should Start Preparing for MiCA ‘Now–Maybe Even Yesterday’: Chainalysis]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144572</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144572/crypto-firms-should-start-preparing-mica-now-maybe-even-yesterday-chainalysis"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T13:49:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MiCA comes into effect next year, but that doesn't mean crypto firms should wait to become compliant, said Chainalysis' EU policy lead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alys Key</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are NFTs the Next SEC Target?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/YaGgY87J/are-nfts-the-next-sec-target</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/YaGgY87J/are-nfts-the-next-sec-target"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T20:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin discusses the current regulatory climate in the U.S. with Gala Games' President of Blockchain Jason Brink.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Collab.Land Co-Founder Said There Was No ‘Aha Moment’ When Launching DAO Toolkit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/kcBRKFGk/collabland-co-founder-said-there-was-no-aha-moment-when-launching-dao-toolkit</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/kcBRKFGk/collabland-co-founder-said-there-was-no-aha-moment-when-launching-dao-toolkit"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T09:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CCO and co-founder of Collab.Land Anjali Young explained at this year’s NFC Lisbon the origins of the crypto community tool kit, which industry niches are turning to its suite of products, and what’s next for the project since its token distribution event last February.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Buying a Slice of H.R. Giger's 'Alien' Is Fine Art, Not Memorabilia: Particle CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/VACG0WVg/buying-a-slice-of-hr-gigers-alien-is-fine-art-not-memorabilia-particle-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/VACG0WVg/buying-a-slice-of-hr-gigers-alien-is-fine-art-not-memorabilia-particle-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T08:49:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With H.R. Giger's original "Alien" statue on full display at this year's NFC Lisbon, Particle CEO Harold Eytan told Decrypt that owning an NFT-ified slice of the piece isn't just for fans of the iconic creature and movie series but also for fine art collectors. Interested in owning a piece? Be prepared to cough up half an ETH for one of the 500 tranches of the digitized sculpture.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Community Co-Creation 'Is a Big Step for Fashion Brands' Entering the Metaverse: BNV Founder and CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/z6NSMnNm/community-co-creation-is-a-big-step-for-fashion-brands-entering-the-metaverse-bnv-founder-and-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/z6NSMnNm/community-co-creation-is-a-big-step-for-fashion-brands-entering-the-metaverse-bnv-founder-and-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T08:49:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The founder and CEO of metaverse fashion platform BNV Richard Hobbs said big brands are still nervous to let fans and community members customize their favorite garments. Still, he believes that as long as you can meet a firm's commercial bottom lines while stirring engagement, there's nothing to lose.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Standard Crypto VC Co-Founder on NFTs and Their Stigma in Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/bmtrrLio/standard-crypto-vc-co-founder-on-nfts-and-their-stigma-in-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/bmtrrLio/standard-crypto-vc-co-founder-on-nfts-and-their-stigma-in-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T18:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alok Vasudev is a co-founder of venture capital firm Standard Crypto. In an interview with Decrypt's Kate Irwin, he shares his thoughts on NFT marketing, NFT utility in gaming, and the stigma that pervades the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ava Labs Announces Avalanche Arcad3 for Game Developers at 3XP]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XPHp9r4j/ava-labs-announces-avalanche-arcad3-for-game-developers-at-3xp</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XPHp9r4j/ava-labs-announces-avalanche-arcad3-for-game-developers-at-3xp"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T15:21:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ava Labs Head of Gaming Ed Chang shares news with Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the crypto firm's latest push to help traditional game developers break into blockchain gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Like a Middle Finger to Western Culture’: YuYu Unpacks Inspiration Behind NFT Expo GAG]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Vuoplr6a/like-a-middle-finger-to-western-culture-yuyu-unpacks-inspiration-behind-nft-expo-gag</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Vuoplr6a/like-a-middle-finger-to-western-culture-yuyu-unpacks-inspiration-behind-nft-expo-gag"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T13:33:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At this year’s NFC Lisbon, multimedia artist and photographer YuLiang "YuYu" Liu broke down how themes from traditional painting and BDSM informed his latest NFT exhibition called “GAG.” He also shared exclusively with Decrypt a yet-to-be-launched drop for fans of his work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Competition Was Rather Low' in Mobile Wallet Space, Says Zerion Head of Growth]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/vCg8O2oy/competition-was-rather-low-in-mobile-wallet-space-says-zerion-head-of-growth</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/vCg8O2oy/competition-was-rather-low-in-mobile-wallet-space-says-zerion-head-of-growth"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T13:33:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zerion's move to launch a mobile-first crypto wallet not only helped NFT users swap jpegs on the go but was also a play to get away from crypto's desktop-centric user experience. And with such little competition, Zerion's head of growth Alexander Guy told Decrypt at NFC Lisbon it's managed to rake in 150,000 funded wallets. Next step? Taking on MetaMask and contending as a browser-extension wallet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘We’ve Never Seen Anything Like This in VR’, Says The Sandbox COO on Apple’s Vision Pro Headset]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/GQ29RaHw/weve-never-seen-anything-like-this-in-vr-says-the-sandbox-coo-on-apples-vision-pro-headset</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/GQ29RaHw/weve-never-seen-anything-like-this-in-vr-says-the-sandbox-coo-on-apples-vision-pro-headset"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T13:33:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Sandbox COO Sebastien Borget told Decrypt at this year’s NFC Lisbon that despite the high price point, Apple’s new VR headset is nonetheless “groundbreaking.” And though the tech giant never used the term “metaverse” in its reveal, Borget is sure that the technology will be key in growing participation in various digital worlds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Gala Safe? Gala Games Head of Blockchain on GALA, Crypto, and SEC Regulatory Turmoil]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5bcrE8nL/is-gala-safe-gala-games-head-of-blockchain-on-gala-crypto-and-sec-regulatory-turmoil</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5bcrE8nL/is-gala-safe-gala-games-head-of-blockchain-on-gala-crypto-and-sec-regulatory-turmoil"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T15:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gala Games President of Blockchain shares his thoughts on the GALA token upgrade and the latest SEC turmoil with Decrypt's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Artists Adopting NFTs Has Been ‘Really Market Dependent’, Says NFT Club Berlin’s Rebekka Revel]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/QKlIVlj3/artists-adopting-nfts-has-been-really-market-dependent-says-nft-club-berlins-rebekka-revel</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/QKlIVlj3/artists-adopting-nfts-has-been-really-market-dependent-says-nft-club-berlins-rebekka-revel"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T15:07:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Getting non-crypto artists to make the leap into Web3 comes in ebbs and flows according to the market’s bear and bull waves, says co-founder of NFT Club Berlin and Superteam Germany Rebekka Revel. But she’s hoping to change that by changing the narrative around digital collectibles, regardless of the market, one word at a time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big Brands Exploring Web3 to ‘Scale Up Their Super-fan Base’: Superduper Co-founder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/he6UzJwz/big-brands-exploring-web3-to-scale-up-their-super-fan-base-superduper-co-founder</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/he6UzJwz/big-brands-exploring-web3-to-scale-up-their-super-fan-base-superduper-co-founder"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T14:49:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Co-founder and co-CEO of Web3 media brand Superduper Dom Smith says big brands are eager to enter the space—they just don’t know how. Still, they all maintain a thesis of turning their communities into “super fans” that generate value for users as well as a firm’s bottom line.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How 1 Simple Question Kickstarted Performance Artist Foodmasku's Plunge Into NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/w86DMn3p/how-1-simple-question-kickstarted-performance-artist-foodmaskus-plunge-into-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/w86DMn3p/how-1-simple-question-kickstarted-performance-artist-foodmaskus-plunge-into-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T10:10:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As his food mask creations went viral on the Internet during the COVID lockdowns, reposted on TikTok and Instagram without his consent, he soon asked: "How do I protect my digital files?" Performance artist Foodmasku describes at this year's NFC Lisbon how that simple question spiraled into a minting collection after collection of his edible works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arianee CEO Pegs Wine and Spirits as Next 'Exciting' Industry to Make Web3 Leap]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Bo2NeG9Z/arianee-ceo-pegs-wine-and-spirits-as-next-exciting-industry-to-make-web3-leap</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Bo2NeG9Z/arianee-ceo-pegs-wine-and-spirits-as-next-exciting-industry-to-make-web3-leap"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T09:28:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CEO and co-founder of Arianee Pierre Nicolas Hurstel unpacks the wide spectrum of digital collectibles from 10,000 PFP collections to access passes for exclusive events. And with an unannounced big brand soon joining, Hurstel revealed at NFC Lisbon which kind of NFTs big brands are moving towards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why 'Words With Friends' Creator Paul Bettner is 'Allergic' to Pay-to-Win NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JkfOleb4/why-words-with-friends-creator-paul-bettner-is-allergic-to-pay-to-win-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JkfOleb4/why-words-with-friends-creator-paul-bettner-is-allergic-to-pay-to-win-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T20:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Words With Friends and Wildcard creator Paul Bettner tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about his perspective on what to do when NFTs become in-game characters and assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitch Co-Founder Justin Kan: 18 Months is 'Several Decades' in Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rKVvsPFb/twitch-co-founder-justin-kan-18-months-is-several-decades-in-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rKVvsPFb/twitch-co-founder-justin-kan-18-months-is-several-decades-in-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fractal and Twitch co-founder Justin Kan gives Decrypt's Kate Irwin an update on all things Fractal and his perspective on blockchain technology in gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Playing for Money in Web3 Games Not 'Durable,' Says Fractal's Justin Kan]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MQG3SaBM/playing-for-money-in-web3-games-not-durable-says-fractals-justin-kan</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MQG3SaBM/playing-for-money-in-web3-games-not-durable-says-fractals-justin-kan"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twitch and Fractal co-founder Justin Kan and Fractal co-founder Dan Borstelmann share their perspectives on Web3 gaming's changing landscape with Decrypt's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Cyber Cafe to Web3: How Everquest Dev Jeffrey Butler Got Into Game Development]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/hRlI4WXe/from-cyber-cafe-to-web3-how-everquest-dev-jeffrey-butler-got-into-game-development</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/hRlI4WXe/from-cyber-cafe-to-web3-how-everquest-dev-jeffrey-butler-got-into-game-development"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T14:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everquest developer turned Avalon Chief Product Officer Jeffrey Butler tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how he got into game development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>