<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-09-19T12:28:58.708Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-09-19T12:28:58.708Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How big is Bitcoin in Lugano? Decentralize with Cointelegraph goes to BTC school]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18913406/How-big-is-Bitcoin-in-Lugano-Decentralize-with-Cointelegraph-goes-to-BTC-school</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18913406/How-big-is-Bitcoin-in-Lugano-Decentralize-with-Cointelegraph-goes-to-BTC-school"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T12:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adam Back, Paolo Ardoino and enthusiastic students from all over the world share insights on Bitcoin school as well as crypto adoption in Switzerland.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Altcoin Made a New Announcement, Its Price Mobilized!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18913410/This-Altcoin-Made-a-New-Announcement-Its-Price-Mobilized</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18913410/This-Altcoin-Made-a-New-Announcement-Its-Price-Mobilized"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T12:11:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This altocin listed on Binace launched its new application, its price moved upwards. Here are the Details... Continue Reading: This Altcoin Made a New Announcement, Its Price Mobilized!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Standard Chartered’s Zodia Custody Crypto Custody Firm Begins Offering Yield on Crypto Holdings]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18913368/Standard-Chartereds-Zodia-Custody-Crypto-Custody-Firm-Begins-Offering-Yield-on-Crypto-Holdings</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18913368/Standard-Chartereds-Zodia-Custody-Crypto-Custody-Firm-Begins-Offering-Yield-on-Crypto-Holdings"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T12:07:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinspeaker Standard Chartered’s Zodia Custody Crypto Custody Firm Begins Offering Yield on Crypto Holdings Zodia Custody will now offer yield on digital assets to institutional clients in addition to providing its custody services. Standard Chartered’s Zodia Custody Crypto Custody Firm Begins...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale CEO: Crypto Has Become Non-Partisan in Washington]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18913377/Grayscale-CEO-Crypto-Has-Become-Non-Partisan-in-Washington</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18913377/Grayscale-CEO-Crypto-Has-Become-Non-Partisan-in-Washington"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T12:07:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale CEO Michael Sonnenshein has affirmed his company’s willingness to work with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to actualize a spot Bitcoin ETF conversion. Speaking about his recent meeting with the lawmakers in Washington D.C., Sonnenshein said crypto in Washington has...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock Bitcoin ETF Will Bring New Money: Arca CIO]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75479ad654</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/blackrock-bitcoin-etf-new-money-arca-cio"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T12:06:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There may be over 10 financial giants filing to launch a Bitcoin ETF, but according to one analyst, BlackRock's application may be the one to watch.
In a CNBC video released Monday, Arca Chief Investment Officer Jeff Dorman called BlackRock's filing "much more important" than the other prospective offerings. To date, other applicants include Fidelity, Digital Currency Group, and most recently Franklin Templeton, which joined the race just last week.
"If Blackrock has an ETF, you know that they are going to win. They have the marketing and distribution to put new people into Bitcoin," Dorman said.
According to the CNBC, BlackRock, one of the world's largest asset management firms, has been closely monitoring the cryptocurrency market for some time, even quietly exploring ways to incorporate Bitcoin into its investment strategies. 
This prospective move by BlackRock could signal a major vote of confidence in the cryptocurrency and might encourage other institutional investors to follow suit.
Elsewhere in the video, experts shed light on how a spot Bitcoin ETF could provide traditional investors with a regulated and accessible gateway into the cryptocurrency market. Experts believe that once the SEC approves a Bitcoin ETF, it will likely attract a broad spectrum of investors, from retail traders to institutional players, who have been waiting for a regulated vehicle to enter the crypto space.
Already, Bitcoin Futures ETFs are publicly traded, though these funds notably do not buy or sell Bitcoin on the open market.
Finally, the experts noted Bitcoin's broader narrative as a decentralized digital currency and store of value, as well as how the upcoming halving, in which the rewards Bitcoin pays out to the miners that secure the protocol will be reduced, could put a positive pressure on its price dynamics.
Taken together, the CNBC report was confident enough to declare a "next bull market" may soon be in store.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reed Macdonald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet the grifter cast of Killer Whales, ‘Web3’s answer to Shark Tank’]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18913373/Meet-the-grifter-cast-of-Killer-Whales-Web3s-answer-to-Shark-Tank</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18913373/Meet-the-grifter-cast-of-Killer-Whales-Web3s-answer-to-Shark-Tank"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T12:05:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Killer Whales is billed as 'Shark Tank for Web3,' but the judges it's chosen have enjoyed far from spotless crypto careers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GRVT raises funds at $39 million valuation to build hybrid crypto exchange]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18913374/GRVT-raises-funds-at-39-million-valuation-to-build-hybrid-crypto-exchange</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18913374/GRVT-raises-funds-at-39-million-valuation-to-build-hybrid-crypto-exchange"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T12:05:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GRVT (pronounced "gravity"), a crypto project that is building a hybrid exchange, raised $7.1 million in pre-seed and seed funding.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto venture market is painfully slow]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18913375/The-crypto-venture-market-is-painfully-slow</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18913375/The-crypto-venture-market-is-painfully-slow"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T12:01:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto VC Mike Dudas discusses the current slowdown in the crypto venture market, citing decreased user engagement and unrealistic valuation expectations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimism Announces Third Round Of Token Airdrop Worth $26 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18913325/Optimism-Announces-Third-Round-Of-Token-Airdrop-Worth-26-Million</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18913325/Optimism-Announces-Third-Round-Of-Token-Airdrop-Worth-26-Million"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T12:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum layer-2 scaling solution Optimism has announced a new airdrop of OP tokens worth $26 million to active governance participants. This airdrop tagged Airdrop 3 marks the third round and will distribute 19.4 million OP tokens to 31,000 unique addresses. The developers aim to boost...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Missionaries, mercenaries, and pragmatists: Alex Tapscott’s new book brings the case for Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18913370/Missionaries-mercenaries-and-pragmatists-Alex-Tapscotts-new-book-brings-the-case-for-Web3</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18913370/Missionaries-mercenaries-and-pragmatists-Alex-Tapscotts-new-book-brings-the-case-for-Web3"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T12:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No newcomer to the world of blockchain and cryptocurrencies, Alex Tapscott, has a decorated history in the blockchain world. He has co-authored an international bestseller on the subject, founded a blockchain research think tank, and, as Managing Director at Ninepoint Partners, Tapscott has...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Proposed Ethereum standard aims to verify security audits on-chain]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18913338/Proposed-Ethereum-standard-aims-to-verify-security-audits-on-chain</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18913338/Proposed-Ethereum-standard-aims-to-verify-security-audits-on-chain"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T12:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A newly proposed standard aims to enhance Ethereum smart contract security by allowing anyone to verify audit information on-chain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Over 50% of US Bitcoin Miners to Back New Policy Group]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18913324/Over-50-of-US-Bitcoin-Miners-to-Back-New-Policy-Group</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18913324/Over-50-of-US-Bitcoin-Miners-to-Back-New-Policy-Group"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alchemy Pay co-founder launches $60 million VC fund with former Lightspeed, Harmony execs as partners]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18913339/Alchemy-Pay-co-founder-launches-60-million-VC-fund-with-former-Lightspeed-Harmony-execs-as-partners</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18913339/Alchemy-Pay-co-founder-launches-60-million-VC-fund-with-former-Lightspeed-Harmony-execs-as-partners"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T11:58:47.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The SBF Trial: How Did We Get Here?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754784a8cb</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/09/19/the-sbf-trial-how-did-we-get-here/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T11:54:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried stands accused of committing wire fraud and conspiracy to commit several other types of frauds. His once-mighty crypto exchange, FTX, collapsed in dramatic fashion nearly a year ago, shedding billions in value. And in two weeks, he’ll begin his effort to convince a jury of his peers that he didn’t commit any of many alleged crimes while running the company.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De, Danny Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Sues SBF’s Parents Over Breaches of Fiduciary Duties and Unjust Enrichment]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18913312/FTX-Sues-SBFs-Parents-Over-Breaches-of-Fiduciary-Duties-and-Unjust-Enrichment</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18913312/FTX-Sues-SBFs-Parents-Over-Breaches-of-Fiduciary-Duties-and-Unjust-Enrichment"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T11:48:36.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Whale of This Altcoin Made a Large Purchase from Binance! There was a sudden jump in price!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18913319/The-Whale-of-This-Altcoin-Made-a-Large-Purchase-from-Binance-There-was-a-sudden-jump-in-price</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18913319/The-Whale-of-This-Altcoin-Made-a-Large-Purchase-from-Binance-There-was-a-sudden-jump-in-price"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T11:48:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new whale, known by the short address 0x0ba, purchased $2.2 million worth of tokens from the Bitcoin exchange Binance. Continue Reading: The Whale of This Altcoin Made a Large Purchase from Binance! There was a sudden jump in price!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Synthetix Founder Kain Warwick Says US Courts Will Sort Out Crypto Regulation Battles – Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18913316/Synthetix-Founder-Kain-Warwick-Says-US-Courts-Will-Sort-Out-Crypto-Regulation-Battles-Heres-Why</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18913316/Synthetix-Founder-Kain-Warwick-Says-US-Courts-Will-Sort-Out-Crypto-Regulation-Battles-Heres-Why"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T11:45:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Synthetix (SNX) founder Kain Warwick thinks it is nearly impossible for decentralized finance (DeFi) projects to avoid regulatory risk in the US. In July, Warwick founded Infinex, a decentralized perpetual exchange that uses Synthetix for its liquidity. He acknowledges that there is regulatory...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pro-Crypto Nonprofit Advocates for Regulatory Clarity Ahead of Gary Gensler SEC Testimony]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18913322/Pro-Crypto-Nonprofit-Advocates-for-Regulatory-Clarity-Ahead-of-Gary-Gensler-SEC-Testimony</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18913322/Pro-Crypto-Nonprofit-Advocates-for-Regulatory-Clarity-Ahead-of-Gary-Gensler-SEC-Testimony"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T11:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In anticipation of Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Chair Gary Gensler’s forthcoming congressional testimony, pro-crypto nonprofit Stand With Crypto has initiated an ad campaign. The organization, established by Coinbase, the largest US-based crypto exchange, aims to amplify the voices...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Cut as New York Cracks Crypto Whip: Which Tokens Made It?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18913311/XRP-Cut-as-New-York-Cracks-Crypto-Whip-Which-Tokens-Made-It</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18913311/XRP-Cut-as-New-York-Cracks-Crypto-Whip-Which-Tokens-Made-It"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T11:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NYDFS has significantly reduced the number of approved cryptocurrencies, triggering pushback from the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Debanking Row Revived By UK Regulator Review]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197760</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197760/debanking-row-revived-by-uk-regulator-review"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T11:44:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Financial Conduct Authority is reported to have found no evidence of politically-motivated account closures.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alys Key</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Embracing Tokenization Now Is a Strategic Move for the Future’ — Metatime CEO Yusuf Sevim]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7547861320</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/embracing-tokenization-now-is-a-strategic-move-for-the-future-metatime-ceo-yusuf-sevim/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T11:44:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While tokenization of real-world assets (RWAs) like gold and real estate is a prospect that unnerves stakeholders in traditional financial systems, according to Yusuf Sevim, the co-founder of the decentralized protocol Metatime, this can potentially bring with it “immense benefits.” Enhanced liquidity for real estate markets is one benefit that accrues to players in the traditional financial services industry if they embrace the tokenization of RWAs, Sevim argued.
 
Overcoming Trust and Regulatory Issues
 
The co-founder also told Bitcoin.com News that embracing tokenization now “is a strategic move for the future” and one that aligns with what he described as “the inevitable shift towards decentralized finance.” However, Sevim said the prospect of the tokenization of RWAs becoming widespr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Market Today: Bitcoin, Solana, eCash Break Resistance in Bullish Move]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18913288/Crypto-Market-Today-Bitcoin-Solana-eCash-Break-Resistance-in-Bullish-Move</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18913288/Crypto-Market-Today-Bitcoin-Solana-eCash-Break-Resistance-in-Bullish-Move"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T11:40:28.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong looks to release stablecoin regulations by mid-2024, lawmaker says]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18913285/Hong-Kong-looks-to-release-stablecoin-regulations-by-mid-2024-lawmaker-says</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18913285/Hong-Kong-looks-to-release-stablecoin-regulations-by-mid-2024-lawmaker-says"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T11:34:24.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Stabilizes at $26,500 After Hitting September Highs: Eyes on Federal Reserve’s FOMC Meeting]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18913289/Bitcoin-Stabilizes-at-26500-After-Hitting-September-Highs-Eyes-on-Federal-Reserves-FOMC-Meeting</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18913289/Bitcoin-Stabilizes-at-26500-After-Hitting-September-Highs-Eyes-on-Federal-Reserves-FOMC-Meeting"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T11:33:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) concluded the week ending on September 17th with a price of approximately $26,500,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TikTok Faces Challenge As Elon Musk Crypto Scams Multiply]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754787b578</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/tiktok-elon-musk-crypto-scams-multiply/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T11:32:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TikTok, the wildly popular video-sharing platform, is currently grappling with an onslaught of fraudulent cryptocurrency giveaways that prey on users’ trust in themes related to Elon Musk, his electric vehicle and aerospace companies SpaceX and Tesla. 
 
A recent report from Bleeping Computer sheds light on these deceptive schemes, revealing the tactics employed by scammers to pilfer unsuspecting victims’ cryptocurrency holdings.
 
 
The Ingenious Scam on TikTok
 
The scammers behind these cryptocurrency giveaway scams ingeniously lure users into registering accounts on counterfeit cryptocurrency exchange websites. Their ploy typically involves a request for a small cryptocurrency deposit, purportedly to activate the user’s account. 
 
However, once deposited, these funds vanish into the h…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Udao Announces First Public Presale For Revolutionary Web3 Skills Economy Platform]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7547826c14</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/udao-announces-first-public-presale-for-revolutionary-web3-skills-economy-platform/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T11:14:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. Switzerland – September 19, 2023 – Udao, a global Web 3.0 platform designed to empower users to learn new skills and match them to relevant job opportunities, announces its first public presale event. This provides an opportunity to everyone to engage in the Web 3.0 transformation of the education sector.
 
To participate in the Udao presale, mark your calendars for the Super Early Bird Days, taking place from September 25 to October 5, 2023. Detailed information can be found on the Udao’s website.
 
Facing the Global Skills Crisis 
 
In today’s rapidly changing world, there is an ever growing gap between skill supply and demand in the dynamic labor market.
 
Consider the findings from the renowned experts:
 
 
There are 1 billion people worldwide who need to reskill very so…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OneCoin Money Laundering Lawyer Denied New Trial]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754783089d</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/onecoin-money-laundering-lawyer-denied-new-trial/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T11:09:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mark Scott,  
the lawyer convicted of laundering $400 million from the infamous OneCoin  
fraud, has been denied a motion for a new trial despite revelations of false  
testimony during his 2019 trial. United States District Judge Edgardo Ramos  
made the decision during a hearing held on September 18.
Scott's  
Claim of Unawareness in OneCoin Fraud
Scott,  
aged 54, had argued that he was unaware of OneCoin's fraudulent nature when he  
played a pivotal role in setting up a fund that facilitated money laundering  
for OneCoin's Founder, Ruja 'Cryptoqueen' Ignatova. 
In  
November 2019, he was found guilty of money laundering and bank fraud  
conspiracy, ultimately amassing $50 million through a fraudulent fund  
responsible for processing payments and transactions linked to the OneCoin  
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tareq Sikder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Bankruptcy Estate Sues Sam Bankman-Fried's Parents Over Millions in ‘Misappropriated’ Funds]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197755</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197755/ftx-bankruptcy-estate-sues-sam-bankman-frieds-parents-over-millions-in-misappropriated-funds"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T10:53:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The legal action seeks to recover millions of dollars in allegedly misappropriated funds from the parents of FTX's former CEO.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Setback as Judge Denies Immediate Access to Binance US Software]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197756</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197756/sec-setback-as-judge-denies-immediate-access-to-binance-us-software"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T10:41:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A federal judge has denied the SEC's request to access the software powering Binance US, the American arm of the crypto exchange.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Hussey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US SEC Commissioner Urges Crypto Firms To Not Give Up The Fight]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7547888607</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/sec-commissioner-crypto-firms/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T10:31:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pro-Crypto US SEC Commissioner Hester Pierce has urged crypto firms not to back down in the push for regulatory clarity amidst the US Securities and Exchange Commission’s (SEC) continued clampdown on several notable digital asset companies. 
 
Regulatory Uncertainty “Shall Pass”
 
Despite the not-so-cordial relationship that may exist between the SEC and stakeholders in the crypto industry, Pierce believes there is a need for collaboration as these stakeholders need to discuss with the commission the right approach to regulating the industry. This may prompt the Commission to have “a change of heart,” according to her.
 
 
In an interview with Cointelegraph, Pierce stated, “Don’t give up on the United States. This too shall pass, the confusion shall pass,” in a direct address to crypto com…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JPEX Drama Shows Need for Crypto Regime, Hong Kong Leader Says]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754776eb49</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/09/19/jpex-drama-shows-need-for-crypto-regime-hong-kong-leader-says/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T09:46:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The territory’s leader urged investors to use licensed platforms and promised more education about crypto risks]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack Schickler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Citigroup Unveils Token Services for Institutional Clients]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754776eb3d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/09/19/citigroup-unveils-token-services-for-institutional-clients/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T09:46:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a pilot, Citi used smart contracts to serve the same purpose as bank guarantees and letters of credit working with shipping company Maersk and a canal authority.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMC Preview: Bitcoin And Crypto Eye The Fed’s Next Move]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754770f34f</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/fomc-preview-bitcoin-crypto-fed-next-move/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T09:32:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anticipation builds in both the traditional financial as well as Bitcoin and crypto sectors as the Federal Reserve’s FOMC rate decision looms this Wednesday at 2:00 pm ET. Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell will address the public, shedding light on the decision, 30 minutes post-announcement.
 
Reviewing The Macro Economic Landscape
 
The recent months have witnessed a rekindling of inflation. Data reveals that July experienced a year-over-year inflation increase of +3.2%, with August climbing even higher to 3.7% YoY. This surge was underscored by August’s significant +0.6% month-over-month inflation growth, marking the year’s largest.
 
On the labor market front, there have been hints of a slowdown. An unsettling leap in unemployment figures, moving from 3.5% in July to 3.8% in August, s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Staked Ether Experiences $573M in Inflows This Month]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7547719e36</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/09/19/binance-staked-ether-experiences-573m-in-inflows-this-month/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T09:27:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance's staked ether token (BETH) experienced $573 million in deposits across two single days in September, more than quadrupling total value locked to $731 million, DefiLlama data show.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JPEX's Legal Woes Could Signal Trouble for Hong Kong Crypto]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75477d868d</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/jpexs-legal-woes-could-signal-trouble-for-hong-kong-crypto/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T08:58:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After just  
three months of easing cryptocurrency regulations in Hong Kong, authorities are  
already discussing tightening them again. In the wake of alleged fraud at JPEX,  
an unlicensed cryptocurrency exchange in the Chinese special administrative  
region, authorities are taking stringent measures to regulate digital assets.  
Six individuals have been arrested, and the Securities and Futures Commission  
(SFC) has received many complaints against the platform, leading to calls for  
tighter supervision.
Unlicensed Crypto Operations  
under Fire in Hong Kong
The SFC had  
already warned the public about JPEX's unlicensed status before the arrests  
were made. Over 1,400 complaints have been lodged against the exchange,  
implicating more than HKD 1 billion ($127.9 million) in losses.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Damian Chmiel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK Crime Bill Lets Cops Freeze Crypto Faster, Channels Tainted Assets to Public Funding]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75477e5a21</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/09/19/uk-crime-bill-lets-cops-freeze-crypto-faster-channels-tainted-assets-to-public-funding/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T08:51:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Economic Crime and Corporate Transparency Bill set to become law later this year removes some legislative hurdles that slow local cops from freezing crypto linked to crime.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camomile Shumba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain Data Visualization Startup Bubblemaps Secures $3.2M in Seed Funding]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754778b01a</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/blockchain-data-visualization-startup-bubblemaps-secures-3-2m-in-seed-funding/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T08:34:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paris-based Bubblemaps, a firm specializing in blockchain data visualization, announced on Monday that it had secured $3.2 million in seed funding from a group of investors. Bubblemaps stated that the newly acquired funds would be directed toward a mission to increase access to blockchain data, serving both individuals and institutions.
 
Bubblemaps Raises $3.2M to Boost Blockchain Data Access
 
Bubblemaps secured $3.2 million in a seed funding round, with INCE Capital leading the investment effort. Other contributors to the fundraising initiative included Cronos Chain, Avalanche, V3ntures, Momentum 6, Lbank, Stake Capital, and others.
 
“We’ve successfully raised €3M to accelerate blockchain data innovation,” announced Bubblemaps on the social media platform X.
 
The platform offers users vibrant bubble visualizations linked to onchain data for blockchains, decentralized finance (defi), and non-fungible tokens (NFTs). Bubblemaps dubs the platform the “first supply auditing tool for defi tokens and NFTs.” Bubblemaps has established partnerships with various blockchain projects, including Polygon, Fantom, Cronos, BNB, Arbitrum, and Avalanche.
 
 
In the past two years, companies specializing in blockchain and crypto-related analytics have secured substantial investments. In August 2021, Messari raised $21 million, while just a few months earlier in May, Coin Metrics obtained $15 million. February 2022 witnessed Dune Analytics raising $69.4 million, and the preceding month, Cryptoslam secured $9 million.
 
What do you think about Bubblemaps raising $3.2 million? Share your thoughts and opinions about this subject in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Dominance Returns Above 50% As Altcoins Encounter Resistance]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7547790d49</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-dominance-returns-above-50/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T08:31:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With a market valuation of almost $520 billion and a current price of $26,690, Bitcoin has reclaimed the limelight. It now accounts for more than half of the entire cryptocurrency market.
 
This turning point is important because it occurs at a time when many alternative cryptocurrencies are stagnating or declining. It’s worth noting, though, that Bitcoin is still nearly 5% lower than its June high and 23% below than its January 2022 peak, despite the recent uptick.
 
Looking at the market more broadly, the alpha coin’s market dominance ranged between nearly 40% and 49% for more than two years before it finally reached the 52% level in June, when asset manager BlackRock’s application for a spot BTC exchange-traded fund sparked expectations about releasing significant inflows into the asset…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aligning with MiCA: Malta Proposes Changes in Its Crypto Rules]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7547679bfb</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/aligning-with-mica-malta-proposes-changes-in-its-crypto-rules/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T07:40:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malta’s Financial Services Authority (MFSA) has moved towards aligning the island’s existing cryptocurrency regulations with Europe’s Markets in Crypto-Assets (MiCA) regulations, which will come into effect in December 2024. The MFSA has launched a public consultation until 29 September on the proposed changes.
Crypto Regulations in Malta
Malta was one of the early jurisdictions to adopt crypto regulations with the establishment of its Virtual Financial Assets (VFA) framework in 2018, aiming to attract companies in the booming industry to the island. Although some big names initially moved to Malta, the program failed to attract the masses.
Now, the proposed changes to align its requirements with MiCA will ease many existing rules. One of the highlighted changes is removing the systems aud…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arnab Shome</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sino Global, Coinbase and Libra Alums Start $60 Million Web3 Fund]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75476f0587</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/09/19/sino-global-coinbase-and-libra-alums-start-60-million-web3-fund/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T06:37:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oak Grove Ventures will focus on early-stage investments in Web3, artificial intelligence and biotechnology.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP, Dogecoin And Litecoin Removed From New York’s Crypto Greenlist]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75476fab12</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/xrp-dogecoin-ltc-removed-new-york-crypto-greenlist/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T06:31:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a notable development, the New York Department of Financial Services (NYDFS) has undertaken a substantial revision of its virtual currency framework, resulting in XRP, Dogecoin, Litecoin, among others being removed from the state’s “greenlist”. Late Monday’s announcement signified a pivotal alteration to the list that enumerates approved tokens for DFS-licensed firms.
 
Prior, this greenlist boasted 25 tokens, including heavyweight names such as Bitcoin, Ethereum, Dogecoin, Litecoin, XRP, and the emergent PayPal Dollar. However, post yesterday’s overhaul, the roster has been notably truncated, spotlighting only eight tokens. Remarkably Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) are the only non-pegged coins, besides Gemini Dollar (GUSD), GMO JPY (GYEN), GMO USD (ZUSD), Pax Gold (PAXG), Pax Dollar…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Sues Sam Bankman-Fried's Parents, Aims to Recover "Millions of Dollars"]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754768eb9a</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/ftx-sues-sam-bankman-frieds-parents-aims-to-recover-millions-of-dollars/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T06:20:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bankruptcy estate of FTX has sued Joseph Bankman and Barbara Fried, parents of the collapsed crypto exchange's Founder and former CEO, Sam Bankman-Fried, to recover "millions of dollars in fraudulently transferred and misappropriated funds," Coindesk initially reported.
Joseph Bankman and Barbara Fried Received Tens of Millions of Dollars
According to a court filing yesterday (Monday), the crypto exchange and its sister companies have paid tens of millions to the Bankman and Fried and other organizations associated with them.
"FTX Trading paid $18,914,327.82, inclusive of taxes, fees, and costs, for Blue Water, to which Bankman and Fried received title, as well as various expenses related to Blue Water totaling more than $90,000," the filing, redacted in parts, stated, which is only on…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arnab Shome</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bank of Russia Governor Elvira Nabiullina: ‘Cash Is Not Going Away’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7547553654</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bank-of-russia-governor-elvira-nabiullina-cash-is-not-going-away/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T05:38:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elvira Nabiullina, Governor of the Bank of Russia, talked about the future of cash in the context of the digital ruble pilot currently being executed in the country. Nabiullina explained that physical money was not disappearing and that the future implementation of the digital ruble was directed to offer payment options to users.
Bank of Russia Governor Elvira Nabiullina: ‘People Should Be Able to Choose How to Make Payments’
Elvira Nabiullina, Governor of the Bank of Russia, explained that the institution had no intention of eliminating cash in the context of the tests being conducted with the digital ruble, Russia’s central bank digital currency (CBDC). In a press conference on September 15 after a meeting with the bank’s board of directors, Nabiullina explained that the institution was …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Updates its SEO Playbook for Content Generated With AI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197743</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197743/google-seo-algorithm-update-ai-generated-content"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T02:56:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has dropped “content written by people” and now says it  looks for quality content—no matter how it was generated.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Y3K Innovation Summit Demystifies AI and Blockchain for Marginalized Communities]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197715</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197715/y3k-innovation-summit-usc-demystifies-ai-blockchain-for-marginalized-communities"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T02:27:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hosted at USC, the event focused on equal access to emerging tech, offering hands-on experiences with Web3 technology.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PayPal Shares First PYUSD Report as Stablecoin Market Fades to $131 Billion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197688</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197688/paypal-pyusd-report-stablecoins-131-billion"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T23:16:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PYUSD’s $44 million market capitalization suggests the stablecoin’s initial adoption has been slow so far.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How ‘Spiderchain’ Plans to Build Ethereum on Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197687</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197687/how-spiderchain-plans-to-build-ethereum-on-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T22:47:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following weeks of debate about Bitcoin drivechains, a similar project to unlock the network’s programming potential is picking up steam.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[End of Crypto 'Capitulation Phase' May Be Near: CoinShares Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197677</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197677/end-of-crypto-capitulation-phase-may-be-near-coinshares-analyst"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T21:27:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Token prices rose but institutions continue to sell digital assets, which for James Butterfill is an indicator of a change in phases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Earn Bitcoin by Playing Minecraft]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197638</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/how-earn-bitcoin-playing-minecraft-satlantis-guide"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T21:18:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Satlantis server on Minecraft pays out real Bitcoin for playing. Here's how to get started, begin earning, and cash out your winnings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SoftBank Mulls Big Investment in OpenAI Following ARM IPO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197633</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197633/softbank-mulls-big-investment-in-openai-following-arm-ipo"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T21:08:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CEO of the Japanese multinational firm chats frequently with both Sam Altman and ChatGPT.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miner Hut 8 Inches Toward Merger With USBTC as Court Approves Deal]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197631</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197631/bitcoin-miner-hut-8-inches-toward-merger-with-usbtc-as-court-approves-deal"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T20:19:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hut 8 Corp stands to be one of the largest Bitcoin miners across the continent, but the deal isn't finalized yet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring the 'Shared Vocabulary' of Generative Art's History]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156690</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156690/exploring-the-shared-vocabulary-of-generative-arts-history"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T19:40:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new exhibition in London highlights the connections between the early pioneers of generative art and their modern counterparts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mila Kunis' Stoner Cats Banned From NFT Marketplaces After SEC Charges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197622</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197622/mila-kunis-stoner-cats-trading-banned-nft-marketplaces-sec"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T19:32:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenSea and Rarible both confirmed that they blocked Stoner Cats NFT trades, while Blur shows no active listings after the SEC settlement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['House of Mirrors': SEC Demands Urgent Inspection of Binance US Assets]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197620</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197620/sec-demands-binance-us-inspection-in-house-of-mirrors-case"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T19:18:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The top regulator has slammed Binance US in Monday court documents for allegedly not cooperating.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Elder Scrolls VI Isn't Coming to PlayStation 5, Won't Release Before 2026]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197609</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197609/the-elder-scrolls-vi-isnt-coming-playstation-5-wont-release-before-2026"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T17:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unlike Skyrim, The Elder Scrolls VI isn't planned for PlayStation. Instead, it'll be a PC and Xbox exclusive, like Starfield.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Citigroup Will Let Rich Clients Use Private Blockchain to Transfer Assets]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197602</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197602/citigroup-launches-smart-contract-digital-token-service-for-institutions"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T17:15:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Citigroup is allowing big money clients to transform their deposits into digital tokens.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rising From Ashes: Berlin Bitcoin Veteran Bitwala Makes Surprise Comeback]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197596</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197596/rising-from-ashes-berlin-crypto-veterans-bitwala-make-surprise-comeback"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T16:59:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once known as Nuri, Berlin-based cryptocurrency startup Bitwala is relaunching under its old name—but German users will have to wait.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here's How Much Bitcoin We Earned Playing Minecraft]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/z8rit7yN/heres-how-much-bitcoin-we-earned-playing-minecraft</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/z8rit7yN/heres-how-much-bitcoin-we-earned-playing-minecraft"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T16:49:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can now mine Bitcoin in Minecraft. Decrypt contributor Ryan S. Gladwin shows us how.

Satlantis website: https://satlantis.net/
Minecraft server address: play.satlantis.net]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deepfake Pornography: Is Consent Over Your Image a Lost Cause?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197592</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/deepfake-pornography-is-consent-over-your-image-a-lost-cause"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T14:28:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For many in the areas of cybersecurity, social justice, privacy law, and other fields, deepfake pornography is one of the greatest threats to emerge from the AI era.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Reiff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong Influencer Arrested Over JPEX Exchange Promotion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197573</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197573/hong-kong-influencer-arrested-over-jpex-exchange-promotion"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T12:55:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joseph Lam’s arrest followed the suspension of trading on crypto exchange JPEX, which regulators allege was operating without a license.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Hussey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain's Unseen Backbone Securing Billions of Dollars in Value]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154993</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154993/blockchains-unseen-backbone-securing-billions-of-dollars-in-value"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T12:01:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chronicle Protocol aims to redefine the oracle space with Scribe, when it launches to the public this month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elizabeth Warren's Digital Asset Anti-Money Laundering Act Gets Nine New Sponsors]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197565</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197565/elizabeth-warrens-digital-asset-anti-money-laundering-act-gets-nine-new-sponsors"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T10:53:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Warren's controversial Digital Asset Anti-Money Laundering Act has received support from nine more U.S. senators.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Europe is ‘Eating America’s Lunch’: U.S. Held Back by Bitcoin ETF Paralysis]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197538</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197538/europe-is-eating-americas-lunch-u-s-held-back-by-bitcoin-etf-paralysis"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T01:10:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Europe is probably a bit ahead of the game,” says a Swiss CEO. "The U.S. still has work to do.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nature, Not Humans, Should Be the Model for AI, Says Artist Collective]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197514</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197514/ai-agi-nature-fungi-plants-not-humans-theta-noir"/>
        <updated>2023-09-17T23:22:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Challenging conventional AI ethics, Theta Noir believes AI should mimic nature's sustainability rather than human excess.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Celebrities Settle Lawsuits Over FTX Deals]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197509</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197509/first-celebrities-settle-lawsuit-over-ftx-deals"/>
        <updated>2023-09-17T23:05:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Among those who agreed to settle were Jacksonville Jaguars quarterback Trevor Lawrence, and YouTube influencers Tom Nash and Kevin Paffrath.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PolkaWorld Hits Pause as Founder Faults Polkadot Governance Change]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197507</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197507/polkaworld-hits-pause-as-founder-faults-polkadot-governance-change"/>
        <updated>2023-09-17T22:42:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the center of the controversy is a new structure that grants every token holder a vote.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week on Crypto Twitter: Idris Elba Falls Flat, and Are We Near the End of Binance?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197480</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197480/this-week-on-crypto-twitter-idris-elba-stellar-binance-executive-turnover"/>
        <updated>2023-09-17T18:16:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several crypto Twitter heads remarked on the shifty personnel changes over at Binance this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prosecutors Say SBF’s Lawyers Are Trying to Taint Juror Pool]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197479</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197479/prosecutors-say-sbfs-lawyers-are-trying-to-taint-juror-pool"/>
        <updated>2023-09-17T17:56:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ahead of Sam Bankman-Fried's trial, the government objects to voir dire questions from the defense.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Steady Week for Bitcoin and Ethereum, Toncoin Balloons 23%]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197429</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197429/this-week-in-coins-bitcoin-steady-ethereum-invlationary-toncoin-rises"/>
        <updated>2023-09-16T19:16:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not even a big-budget Idris Elba commercial could save Stellar’s XLM from taking a nose dive.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Metaverse Token Coming From Animoca Game Studio]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197441</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197441/bitcoin-metaverse-token-coming-from-animoca-game-studio"/>
        <updated>2023-09-16T19:15:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animoca Brands' Darewise subsidiary will launch a metaverse token via Bitcoin Ordinals to power an ecosystem led by the game Life Beyond.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Billionaire Mark Cuban Loses $870,000 In Crypto Scam]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197439</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197439/mark-cuban-crypto-scam-metamask-hack"/>
        <updated>2023-09-16T19:01:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The owner of the Dallas Mavericks lost roughly $870,000, although the figures could have been much worse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Did Google Ban AI Artists from Running Stable Diffusion on Its Cloud?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197428</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197428/google-colab-stable-diffusion-web-ui-ban"/>
        <updated>2023-09-16T18:33:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Users have claimed that Google banned them from Colab after they tried to run Stable Diffusion with the famous WebUI popularized by A1111.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some Celebrities Are Embracing AI to Stay Ahead of Deepfake Makers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197412</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197412/celebrities-using-ai-to-get-ahead-of-deepfakes"/>
        <updated>2023-09-16T17:39:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prominent actors are reportedly using Metaphysic Pro to take ownership of the data needed to reproduce their likenesses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is KYC? How Crypto Exchanges Prevent Money Laundering]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=112290</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-kyc-how-crypto-exchanges-prevent-money-laundering"/>
        <updated>2023-09-16T09:51:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Know-your-customer (KYC) requirements are a growing part of Web3, as crypto becomes more integrated with the existing financial system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korea’s Lazarus Group Has Stolen $240M in Crypto in Just 104 Days: Elliptic]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197407</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197407/north-korea-lazarus-hacks-240m-crypto-just-104-days-elliptic"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T22:20:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adding to the tally is the $54 million hack of crypto exchange CoinEx, which blockchain sleuths at Elliptic now believe Lazarus was likely behind.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nouns Fork: Disgruntled NFT Holders Exit With $27 Million From Treasury]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197400</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197400/nouns-fork-disgruntled-nft-holders-exit-27-million-from-treasury"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T21:28:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Nouns NFT collective on Ethereum, which is building open-source IP by funding creative projects, fractures after a widely supported fork.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Judge Grants SEC’s Motion to Unseal Key Documents in Binance Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197396</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197396/judge-sec-unseal-key-documents-binance-lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T21:20:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The judge’s approval follows accusations that Binance US exhibited a “lack of transparency” in the SEC’s investigation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Gemini Poised to Take On AI Titans OpenAI and Microsoft]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197378</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197378/google-gemini-poised-to-take-on-ai-titans-openai-and-microsoft"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T19:58:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has reportedly started testing its most advanced AI model to date, Gemini, which it says has impressive multimodal capabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[London Design Museum Lets Visitors Test Iconic Runway Looks via AR]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197360</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197360/london-design-museum-lets-visitors-test-iconic-runway-looks-ar"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T19:41:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An augmented reality experience developed by Snapchat maker Snap is part of the museum's new "Rebel: 30 Years of London Fashion" exhibit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephanie Hirschmiller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gods Unchained's Daniel Paez on the Future of NFT Gaming Interoperability]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/obt7FGYr/gods-unchaineds-daniel-paez-on-the-future-of-nft-gaming-interoperability</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/obt7FGYr/gods-unchaineds-daniel-paez-on-the-future-of-nft-gaming-interoperability"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T20:27:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daniel Paez, executive producer on NFT card-battling game Gods Unchained, speaks with Decrypt Culture Editor Andrew Hayward about what the future of NFT game interoperability will really look like—and what it won't.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Mino Games is Using Artificial Intelligence]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/SrT1Afj7/how-mino-games-is-using-artificial-intelligence</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/SrT1Afj7/how-mino-games-is-using-artificial-intelligence"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T22:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mino Games CEO Sasha McKinnon tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about how the studio's upcoming game Dimensionals will use real-time AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INTERVIEW: How Will Aurory Use NFTs and Crypto?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qv3VwNmM/interview-how-will-aurory-use-nfts-and-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qv3VwNmM/interview-how-will-aurory-use-nfts-and-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T15:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Natoli, Aurory's Head of Marketing and Business Development, tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how the Aurory games will use NFTs and crypto and shares the studio's broader stance on the tech.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Cloud's James Tromans on the Intersection of AI and Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OeD4uoLj/google-clouds-james-tromans-on-the-intersection-of-ai-and-web3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OeD4uoLj/google-clouds-james-tromans-on-the-intersection-of-ai-and-web3"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google's Global Head of Google Cloud for Web3 James Tromans sat down with Decrypt's Jason Nelson to discuss how AI can help Web3 companies come to market faster and the real value of Web3 tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastering NFT Trading - Degen U]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/HQGt1Vrq/mastering-nft-trading-degen-u</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/HQGt1Vrq/mastering-nft-trading-degen-u"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T07:08:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Take Degen U's new course, Mastering NFT Trading, and earn an on-chain certificate. A top instructor will help you identify trends, seize the right moment to trade, weed out scams—and have fun while doing it!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Space Nation CEO on Working With 'Independence Day' Director Roland Emmerich]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LpznLhtx/space-nation-ceo-on-working-with-independence-day-director-roland-emmerich</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LpznLhtx/space-nation-ceo-on-working-with-independence-day-director-roland-emmerich"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T17:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jerome Wu, CEO of Space Nation, tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the upcoming Space Nation Online game in development and shares details on Space Nation Cofounder Roland Emmerich's role in the project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GAME REVIEW: Champions Arena from Gala Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qUE1RlDx/game-review-champions-arena-from-gala-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qUE1RlDx/game-review-champions-arena-from-gala-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Champions Arena is a turn-based fantasy RPG from Gala Games, where characters can become NFTs and crypto can be used to purchase gems, one of the game's synthetic currencies. Decrypt's Kate Irwin takes us inside the game for her thoughts on the fun, mobile-first title.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apex Legends Voice Actor Ben Prendergast on the Future of Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/X3RKdsaG/apex-legends-voice-actor-ben-prendergast-on-the-future-of-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/X3RKdsaG/apex-legends-voice-actor-ben-prendergast-on-the-future-of-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T18:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Voice actor Ben Prendergast, who's voiced characters in games like Apex Legends and God of War Ragnarok, shares his opinions on the tech space's history of "bubbles" and whether blockchain gaming has a future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Future of AI Stardom and Robotics With SingularityNET COO Janet Adams and Desdemona]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yVQaZI71/the-future-of-ai-stardom-and-robotics-with-singularitynet-coo-janet-adams-and-desdemona</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yVQaZI71/the-future-of-ai-stardom-and-robotics-with-singularitynet-coo-janet-adams-and-desdemona"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T16:45:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this interview, SingularityNET COO Janet Adams explains the intricate details that went into creating the Desdemona robot AI from Hanson Robotics and future plans for the AI Diva.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto a 'No-Brainer' for Video Games, Says Mino Games CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rdynom8C/crypto-a-no-brainer-for-video-games-says-mino-games-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rdynom8C/crypto-a-no-brainer-for-video-games-says-mino-games-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T18:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mino Games CEO Sasha MacKinnon, developer of the upcoming Dimensionals game, tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the studio's approach to digital collectibles.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Wagner's 'Controversial Take' on Crypto in Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tc2nKeqA/michael-wagners-controversial-take-on-crypto-in-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tc2nKeqA/michael-wagners-controversial-take-on-crypto-in-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T16:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Solana's PlayGG, Star Atlas CEO Michael Wagner shares his "controversial take" on crypto in games, shares the challenges of developing the upcoming scifi game, and how crypto's volatility has changed his perspective with Decrypt's Jason Nelson.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>