<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-02-24T10:16:36.850Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-02-24T10:16:36.850Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Gets Court Approval to Sell AI Firm Stake]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19276596/FTX-Gets-Court-Approval-to-Sell-AI-Firm-Stake</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19276596/FTX-Gets-Court-Approval-to-Sell-AI-Firm-Stake"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T10:11:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FTX wins court nod to sell AI startup stake, plans full customer payback]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uniswap's New Plan Boosts Token Prices by 60%]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19276587/Uniswaps-New-Plan-Boosts-Token-Prices-by-60</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19276587/Uniswaps-New-Plan-Boosts-Token-Prices-by-60"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T10:04:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Uniswap's governance proposal spikes UNI prices, promising rewards for token holders]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT and Gemini stumble, Nvidia wins, and a look at Sam Altman: AI news roundup]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19276583/ChatGPT-and-Gemini-stumble-Nvidia-wins-and-a-look-at-Sam-Altman-AI-news-roundup</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19276583/ChatGPT-and-Gemini-stumble-Nvidia-wins-and-a-look-at-Sam-Altman-AI-news-roundup"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It wasn’t the best week for AI chatbots, which were making high-profile mistakes in both text and video. But Nvidiajoined the $2-trillion club, as Wall Street’s favorite AI chipmaker beat sky-high earnings expectations and the stock kept rallying. And we take a look at the life of OpenAI CEO Sam...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Riot platforms report surge in Bitcoin production amid rising revenue]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19276567/Riot-platforms-report-surge-in-Bitcoin-production-amid-rising-revenue</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19276567/Riot-platforms-report-surge-in-Bitcoin-production-amid-rising-revenue"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T09:58:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Riot Platforms, a prominent player in the Bitcoin mining sector, has revealed a substantial uptick in its production for 2023. According to the company’s recent report published on Feb. 22, 2024, Riot Platforms recorded a 19% increase in the number of Bitcoins mined compared to the previous...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale eyes Ethereum’s growth post-Dencun technological boost]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19276562/Grayscale-eyes-Ethereums-growth-post-Dencun-technological-boost</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19276562/Grayscale-eyes-Ethereums-growth-post-Dencun-technological-boost"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T09:55:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent analysis by Grayscale, a leading digital currency asset manager, the forthcoming Dencun upgrade for Ethereum has been identified as a significant factor contributing to the recent uptick in Ether (ETH) prices. According to a report published on February 23 by William Ogden Moore, a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uniswap (UNI) Soars 76% as Price Hits Multi-Year High, Reason Uncovered]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19276564/Uniswap-UNI-Soars-76-as-Price-Hits-Multi-Year-High-Reason-Uncovered</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19276564/Uniswap-UNI-Soars-76-as-Price-Hits-Multi-Year-High-Reason-Uncovered"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T09:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase on Grayscale Ethereum Spot ETF Application: “ETH Is a Commodity, Not a Security”]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74dbc71769</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/coinbase-on-grayscale-ethereum-spot-etf-application-eth-is-a-commodity-not-a-security/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T09:36:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase has answered the SEC request for comments on the proposed rule change to list the ETH Grayscale Fund as a spot ETF. Coinbase stated that ether was a commodity, and its status has been publicly recognized in a variety of circumstances by U.S. agencies and courts. Coinbase Supports Ethereum Grayscale Fund Conversion as a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zcash Jumps 20% After Grayscale's Privacy-Based ETF Move]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19276547/Zcash-Jumps-20-After-Grayscales-Privacy-Based-ETF-Move</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19276547/Zcash-Jumps-20-After-Grayscales-Privacy-Based-ETF-Move"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T09:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is Zcash?Zcash is a special kind of digital money, created in 2016, that focuses a lot on keeping things private and secure. It uses complex math to make sure transactions are secret. One cool thing is zk-SNARKs, a technology that checks transactions without telling everyone who's involved....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Judge Approves Binance’s $4.3 Billion Plea Agreement – Details]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74dbc03d07</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/us-judge-approve-binance-4-3-billion-plea-agreement/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T09:24:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to the latest report, Binance Holdings Ltd. will pay one of the largest corporate penalties in United States history after a judge approved the company’s plea agreement. This comes months after the cryptocurrency exchange and its former CEO and founder Changpeng Zhao pleaded guilty to anti-money laundering infringements, bringing a close to a long-term investigation by the Department of Justice (DOJ) and other regulatory bodies.
 
Binance Accepts Full Responsibility For Its Past Actions: Defense Attorney
 
In a Seattle court hearing on Friday, February 23, US District Judge Richard Jones approved the plea agreement for the world’s largest cryptocurrency exchange. The deal entails Binance’s payment of a $4.3 billion penalty, the appointment of a new CEO, and the institution of a c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Opeyemi Sule</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analyst Forecasts $40 Target For Chainlink (LINK)]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19276550/Analyst-Forecasts-40-Target-For-Chainlink-LINK</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19276550/Analyst-Forecasts-40-Target-For-Chainlink-LINK"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T09:20:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chainlink (LINK) continues to remain among the headlines following a negative performance, which saw the token’s price decline by 7.63% in the last week based on data from CoinMarketCap. However, despite this discouraging price loss, investors and market experts appear to remain bullish on the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Price Prediction as SOL Drops Below $100 Support – Here’s the Next Level to Watch]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19276594/Solana-Price-Prediction-as-SOL-Drops-Below-100-Support-Heres-the-Next-Level-to-Watch</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19276594/Solana-Price-Prediction-as-SOL-Drops-Below-100-Support-Heres-the-Next-Level-to-Watch"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T09:19:42.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Never-Before Seen Emails Satoshi Nakamoto Sent During the Months He Founded Bitcoin Revealed]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19276527/New-Never-Before-Seen-Emails-Satoshi-Nakamoto-Sent-During-the-Months-He-Founded-Bitcoin-Revealed</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19276527/New-Never-Before-Seen-Emails-Satoshi-Nakamoto-Sent-During-the-Months-He-Founded-Bitcoin-Revealed"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T09:17:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some previously unseen emails belonging to Bitcoin founder Satoshi Nakamoto were published in court. Continue Reading: New Never-Before Seen Emails Satoshi Nakamoto Sent During the Months He Founded Bitcoin Revealed]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance founder’s fate hangs in the balance amid legal turmoil]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19276514/Binance-founders-fate-hangs-in-the-balance-amid-legal-turmoil</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19276514/Binance-founders-fate-hangs-in-the-balance-amid-legal-turmoil"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T09:07:20.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Trading vs Crypto Investing: Key Differences Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19276485/Crypto-Trading-vs-Crypto-Investing-Key-Differences-Explained</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19276485/Crypto-Trading-vs-Crypto-Investing-Key-Differences-Explained"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T08:49:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Digital currencies are becoming popular daily, whether investing in crypto or trading. These currencies use encryption demand and supply currency units and verify fund transfers. They operate independently of a central bank. In crypto investing, you purchase cryptocurrencies expecting the price...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK business registry approves controversial ERC20 wallet drainer]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19276477/UK-business-registry-approves-controversial-ERC20-wallet-drainer</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19276477/UK-business-registry-approves-controversial-ERC20-wallet-drainer"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T08:43:33.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Banking customers lose nearly $500M to scammers: Reports]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19276470/Banking-customers-lose-nearly-500M-to-scammers-Reports</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19276470/Banking-customers-lose-nearly-500M-to-scammers-Reports"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T08:35:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Federal Trade Commission (FTC) has released a damning report revealing that US banks failed to prevent scammers from making away with almost $500 million of their customers’ money in 2023. The report sheds light on the pervasive nature of fraud, with a staggering $10 billion stolen by...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Request Made for Binance’s Changpeng Zhao to Surrender Passports Before Sentencing]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19276593/Request-Made-for-Binances-Changpeng-Zhao-to-Surrender-Passports-Before-Sentencing</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19276593/Request-Made-for-Binances-Changpeng-Zhao-to-Surrender-Passports-Before-Sentencing"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T08:30:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The United States Attorney's Office has made a formal request to a federal judge seeking additional travel restrictions for Changpeng Zhao, commonly known as CZ, the former CEO of Binance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uniswap Skyrockets 80% as Bitcoin Stalls at $51K (Market Watch)]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19276464/Uniswap-Skyrockets-80-as-Bitcoin-Stalls-at-51K-Market-Watch</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19276464/Uniswap-Skyrockets-80-as-Bitcoin-Stalls-at-51K-Market-Watch"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T08:22:09.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fear and Greed Index at Extreme Greed – This Fractal Suggests Correction Incoming]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19276484/Fear-and-Greed-Index-at-Extreme-Greed-This-Fractal-Suggests-Correction-Incoming</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19276484/Fear-and-Greed-Index-at-Extreme-Greed-This-Fractal-Suggests-Correction-Incoming"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T08:18:11.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Rich Dad Poor Dad' Author Reveals His Possible Actions Should Bitcoin Crash]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19276446/Rich-Dad-Poor-Dad-Author-Reveals-His-Possible-Actions-Should-Bitcoin-Crash</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19276446/Rich-Dad-Poor-Dad-Author-Reveals-His-Possible-Actions-Should-Bitcoin-Crash"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T08:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Airdrop timing secrets unveiled-CoinGecko]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19276444/Airdrop-timing-secrets-unveiled-CoinGecko</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19276444/Airdrop-timing-secrets-unveiled-CoinGecko"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T08:10:05.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Pre-Halving Rally Has Only Just Started, Says Crypto Analyst – Here’s His Outlook]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19276441/Bitcoin-Pre-Halving-Rally-Has-Only-Just-Started-Says-Crypto-Analyst-Heres-His-Outlook</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19276441/Bitcoin-Pre-Halving-Rally-Has-Only-Just-Started-Says-Crypto-Analyst-Heres-His-Outlook"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T08:04:36.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fluidkey Launches to Tackle the Transaction Privacy Issues on EVM Chains]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74dbb064ab</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/fluidkey-launches-to-tackle-the-transaction-privacy-issues-on-evm-chains/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T06:35:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fluidkey has announced it has opened its Optimism-based alpha to more users, allowing them to test their private solutions. Fluidkey seeks to solve the transaction privacy problem in EVM chains by leveraging ENS and stealth addresses, allowing users to use a new self-custodial asset for each payment, and segregating these movements to avoid linkability. Fluidkey […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four Spot Bitcoin ETFs Now Available To Clients Of $30 Billion RIA Firm]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74dbbd7ec4</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-etfs-now-to-clients-of-30-billion-ria-firm/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T05:37:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to a recent Bloomberg report, Carson Group, an Omaha, Nebraska-based registered investment advisor (RIA) with a substantial $30 billion on its platform, announced the approval of four of the ten newly launched Bitcoin ETFs.
 
Among the approved ETFs are BlackRock’s iShares Bitcoin Trust (IBIT), managing $6.6 billion, and Fidelity’s Wise Origin Bitcoin Fund (FBTC), with $4.8 billion in assets. These two products have experienced the highest investor inflows so far. Additionally, smaller offerings from Bitwise and Franklin Templeton made the cut.
 
Carson Group Approves Bitcoin ETFs
 
Grant Engelbart, Vice President and Investment Strategist at Carson Group, stated that the firm prioritized “significant asset growth” and trading volume when selecting IBIT and FBTC. 
 
Meanwhile, Bi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase CEO Says No Access Block in Nigeria, Platform Operating Normally]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74dbba1102</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/coinbase-ceo-says-no-access-block-in-nigeria-platform-operating-normally/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T04:41:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong has dismissed reports of his cryptocurrency exchange being blocked by Nigerian authorities. He emphasized that Coinbase products are fully operational in Nigeria without any interruptions. “We have not received any outreach or communication from officials in Nigeria,” the Coinbase executive affirmed. Meanwhile, Binance has reportedly admitted that some users in Nigeria […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3,248 ETH Stolen In Axie Infinity Co-Founder Hack – Here Are The Details]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74dba506e0</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/axie-infinity-co-founder-hack-here-are-the-details/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T04:05:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Thursday night, the Axie Infinity co-founder suffered a hack that included a large amount of ETH being withdrawn from the wallet and sent to Tornado Cash. The suspicious activity was revealed by a blockchain investigator, who alerted of the compromised whale wallet over the Ronin bridge.
 
Related Reading: Massive Crypto Breach: Hackers Extract $26 Million In BTC And ETH From This Exchange
 
Almost $10 Million In Stolen Funds
 
Web3 security platform Ancilia was the first to inform of an alleged security breach over the Ronin Bridge. At the time, 2,790 ETH had been withdrawn and deposited to Tornado Cash.
 
Aleksander Larsen, one of the Co-Founders of Sky Mavis, Axie Infinity, and Ronin Network, clarified that neither the Ronin bridge nor the chain had been compromised.
 
The Axie Infin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rubmar Garcia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump Acknowledges Bitcoin’s Popularity — Says BTC Has Taken on ‘a Life of Its Own’ and ‘I Can Live With It’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74dba2154b</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/donald-trump-acknowledges-bitcoins-popularity-says-btc-has-taken-on-a-life-of-its-own-and-i-can-live-with-it/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T03:02:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. presidential candidate and former President Donald Trump has acknowledged the growing popularity of bitcoin, stating that “a lot of people are doing it” and the crypto has taken on “a life of its own.” Trump further shared: “More and more I’m seeing people wanting to pay bitcoin and you’re seeing something that’s interesting so […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase CEO Dispels Rumours: No Government Ban On Nigerians From The Crypto Exchange]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74dbac757b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/coinbase-ceo-dispels-rumours-no-ban-crypto-exchange/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T02:34:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase, a prominent crypto exchange headquartered in the United States, has debunked allegations that it was instructed by the Nigerian government to prevent its citizens from using its crypto trading services.
 
The denial came directly from Coinbase’s CEO, Brian Armstrong, who addressed the issue through a post on X. Armstrong clarified that Coinbase’s services are still operational in Nigeria, with no interruptions reported.
 
 
Armstrong emphasized that Coinbase has not been approached or contacted by Nigerian officials regarding such directives.
 
 
This is inaccurate WRT Coinbase as far as I can tell. 
Coinbase products are still operating (no interruption) 
We haven’t received any outreach or communication from officials in Nigeria
 
— Brian Armstrong  (@brian_armstrong) February …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Must Pay $4.3 Billion In Federal Case as CZ Awaits Sentencing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=218833</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/218833/judge-approves-binances-plea-deal-with-4-3-billion-fine-as-cz-awaits-sentencing"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T01:55:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Federal prosecutors called the criminal fine and financial penalty "the largest enforcement action" in the agency's history.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US District Judge Sanctions Binance’s $4.3 Billion Plea Deal]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74dba8c969</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/us-district-judge-sanctions-binances-4-3-billion-plea-deal/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T01:41:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Holdings is set to pay $4.3 billion in fines following the approval of its plea agreement with prosecutors by U.S. District Judge Richard Jones on Friday. Beyond the financial settlement, a third party will oversee Binance’s operations for a duration of five years. Historic $4.3 Billion Binance Settlement Approved by Seattle Judge Binance, the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Falls Out Of Top 10 Crypto, Are Meme Coins No Longer A Threat?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74dbabe902</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-out-of-top-10-crypto/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T01:05:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin has seen abysmal performance in the last year, even while the likes of Bitcoin and Ethereum went on to hit new yearly highs. On the back of this poor performance, other altcoins have been creeping up in their market cap to challenge Dogecoin’s position in the top 10 cryptocurrencies by market cap list. And now, after another week of stalling behind the market, Dogecoin has lost its position on this list.
 
Dogecoin Loses 10th Spot To Tron (TRX)
 
Justin Sun’s Tron and its native TRX token have been on a bullish run over the last year. It has risen almost 200% from its 2023 lows of $0.05, and this has sent its market cap rocking. At the same time, the Dogecoin price has failed to follow this growth path, and has instead stalled.
 
 
The result of Dogecoin’s sluggish performance is …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Best Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Bitcoin Miners Sue Biden Administration In Battle Over Regulation]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74db916ca6</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/us-bitcoin-miners-sue-biden-administration/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T00:05:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Thursday, February 22, Bitcoin miner Riot Platforms, along with industry groups Texas Blockchain Council (TBC) and the Chamber of Digital Commerce, initiated legal action against key agencies of the Biden-Harris Administration. The lawsuit targets the US Department of Energy (DOE), the US Energy Information Administration (EIA), and the Office of Management and Budget (OMB), challenging the administration’s recent steps to gather detailed energy consumption data from the cryptocurrency mining sector.
 
The legal complaint arises from a January decision by the OMB, which approved an emergency request by the EIA to collect data on energy usage from 82 Bitcoin mining operations, including that of Riot Platforms. This move has been criticized by the plaintiffs and supported by United States…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Looking at Kraken's Motion to Dismiss an SEC Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74db91c44c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/02/23/looking-at-krakens-motion-to-dismiss-an-sec-lawsuit/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T00:01:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's some familiar arguments, and they all point to one conclusion: This is going to take a while.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Satoshi Nakamoto to Martti Malmi: The Correspondence That Shaped Bitcoin’s Early Days]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74db9f332c</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/satoshi-nakamoto-to-martti-malmi-the-correspondence-that-shaped-bitcoins-early-days/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T23:08:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a series of insightful emails between Martti Malmi and Satoshi Nakamoto, the foundational discussions shaping the early development of Bitcoin are revealed. These exchanges offer a rare glimpse into the critical thinking and technical challenges overcome in the cryptocurrency’s infancy. Blueprints of a Digital Revolution: Nakamoto’s Conversations With Sirius The dialogue initiated in May […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Sellers Have Returned On Coinbase, Price Decline To Continue?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74db9fccb5</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-sellers-returned-coinbase-price-decline/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T23:02:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data shows the Bitcoin Coinbase Premium Index has turned negative once more, a sign that could prove to be bearish for the asset’s price.
 
Bitcoin Coinbase Premium Index Has Dipped Into Red Territory
 
As pointed out by an analyst in a post on X, selling pressure on Coinbase has risen recently. The indicator of interest here is the “Coinbase Premium Index,” which measures the percentage difference between the Bitcoin prices listed on cryptocurrency exchanges Coinbase and Binance.
 
When the value of this metric is positive, it means that the price listed on Coinbase is greater than that on Binance right now. Such a trend implies either the buying pressure on the former is higher than the latter or the selling pressure is lower.
 
 
On the other hand, a negative value implies Coinbase may …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Patterns That Led To 28,000% Rally In 2020 Have Returned]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74db8619b8</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-patterns-28000-rally/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T22:04:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin is once again on the radar of crypto investors after multiple important patterns have made their way to the fore. This was pointed out by crypto analyst Ali Martinez, who identified multiple patterns similar to what was seen in 2020 that could result in a parabolic rally.
 
Dogecoin Chart Looks Similar To 2020
 
2020 was a pivotal year for Dogecoin as it was the setup that led to one of the most impressive rallies in crypto history. It also shares a similarity with 2024 as it was also a year when the Bitcoin halving took place, leading to an incredibly bullish one year for the space.
 
 
It seems Dogecoin is looking toward a repeat of this rally as similar patterns are beginning to form once more. According to crypto analyst Ali Martinez, the present performance of the meme coin d…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$30 billion RIA Platform Carson Group Approves To Offer Spot Bitcoin ETFs To Clients]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74db878b50</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/30-billion-ria-platform-carson-group-approves-to-offer-spot-bitcoin-etfs-to-clients"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T21:52:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Carson Group, a significant $30 billion registered investment adviser (RIA) platform, has recently announced its approval to offer four spot Bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) to its clients, according to a Bloomberg report. Out of the recent batch of US-listed spot Bitcoin ETFs, Carson Group has greenlit BlackRock’s iShares Bitcoin Trust, Fidelity Wise Origin Bitcoin Fund, Bitwise Bitcoin ETF, and the Franklin Bitcoin ETF.

JUST IN - $30 billion RIA platform Carson Group has approved to offer these four spot #Bitcoin ETFs to their clients:
- BlackRock
- Franklin
- Bitwise
- Fidelity
— Bitcoin Magazine (@BitcoinMagazine) February 23, 2024
  
  
  
Grant Engelbart, Carson Group's vice president and investment strategist, highlighted the criteria for selection, emphasizing the "significant…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nik Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The New Satoshi Emails: 120 Pages Detailing Work on Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74db878b3f</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/newly-revealed-satoshi-email-correspondence-with-martti-malmi"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T21:52:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Satoshi Nakamoto's earliest collaborator Martii 'Sirius' Malmi has released his entire email correspondence with Bitcoin's creator.
Spurred by an ongoing lawsuit in the U.K., the new emails are the most significant addition to the canon of what we know about Bitcoin's still anonymous creator. 
Here are the most important new findings.
EMAIL #1: SATOSHI'S BITCOIN SCALING ASSUMPTIONS
 
                         
                         
                         
                     
                    
When asked how Bitcoin might scale in the future, Satoshi theorized the network might have a maximum of 100,000 nodes. 
Here he goes into the calculations assessing the economics of bandwidth costs to nodes (read: miners) in propagating transactions across the network, the economic costs tha…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pete Rizzo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Judge Signs Off on Binance's $4.3B Plea Deal With U.S. Prosecutors]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74db8197c9</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/02/23/judge-signs-off-on-binances-43b-plea-deal-with-us-prosecutors/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T21:34:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A federal judge approved the U.S. Department of Justice's $4.3 billion fine on Binance after the crypto exchange pleaded guilty to violating anti-money laundering laws last November.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does the Bitcoin Halving Still Matter in 2024?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74db838be0</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/does-the-bitcoin-halving-still-matter-in-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T21:17:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every four years, the Bitcoin halving occurs, meaning that the amount of new coins issued through mining rewards is cut in half. When Bitcoin first launched, mining rewards were 50 BTC. Currently, that figure is 6.25 BTC, and after the next halving, it will be reduced to 3.125 BTC.
 The halving occurs every 210,000 blocks rather than on pre-specified dates, but this corresponds to a roughly four-year cycle, which means that the next reduction in issuance should reach us this April. Notably, a glance at BTC’s price action since inception reveals a repeating pattern of vertical gains, deep corrections, and drawn-out recoveries, and this sequence appears to correspond closely with the halvings, leading among bitcoin traders to an entrenched belief in halving-driven movements.
 However, as Bit…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam White</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miners Face Adapt or Perish Scenario as Halving Approaches in Under 60 Days]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74db8c1123</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-miners-face-adapt-or-perish-scenario-as-halving-approaches-in-under-60-days/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T21:12:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data indicates that we’re 96% through the journey to the next Bitcoin halving event, with under two months remaining until the reward for mining a block is reduced from 6.25 to 3.125 bitcoins. Although it’s still premature to pinpoint the precise date—given the average ten-minute interval between blocks—the event is anticipated to take place in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Halving and BTC Price: Will This Time Be Different?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=218809</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/218809/bitcoin-halving-btc-price-etfs-this-time-different"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T20:59:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin is in a different place than it was four years ago, the last time the cryptocurrency underwent a halving. Here’s what you need to know.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Now Move Brave Browser Rewards On-Chain With a Solana Wallet]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=218813</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/218813/brave-browser-bat-rewards-solana-on-chain-transfer"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T20:50:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The popular web browser now allows BAT transfers to self-custody Solana wallets—and the team hasn't ruled out other blockchain integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Tokens Resist Cooling Crypto Market as Bitcoin, Ethereum Wobble]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=218767</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/218767/ai-tokens-resist-cooling-crypto-market-as-bitcoin-ethereum-wobble"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T19:41:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin and Ethereum may be near a small correction just days after posting big gains in intra-day and intra-week sessions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designer Stephy Fung: 'Taking a Stand' For Digital Fashion With New SYKY Collection]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=218766</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/218766/designer-stephy-fung-taking-a-stand-for-digital-fashion-with-new-syky-collection"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T18:42:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 'Four Dragons' collection from digital fashion collective SYKY celebrates the Chinese Year of the Dragon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['No Guarantee' Bitcoin Halving Will Be Favorable for Miners: Riot Platforms]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=218786</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/218786/no-guarantee-bitcoin-halving-favorable-miners-riot-platforms"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T18:21:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Experts warn that miners should get "ready to shut down unprofitable machines" after the Bitcoin halving cuts rewards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Portal Fever: Record $8.6 Billion Staked for Binance Rewards Ahead of Game Token Airdrop]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=218764</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/218764/portal-record-binance-launchpool-gaming-token-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T18:06:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance reports record-breaking demand for the Portal staking pools ahead of the cross-chain gaming token's listing next week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improbable Chief Product Officer: Web3 Games Need to Put Experience, Game Logic Onchain]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/26stQqOi/improbable-chief-product-officer-web3-games-need-to-put-experience-game-logic-onchain</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/26stQqOi/improbable-chief-product-officer-web3-games-need-to-put-experience-game-logic-onchain"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T17:49:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Improbable's Rob Whitehead joined Decrypt's Stephen Graves at NFT Paris to talk about the metaverse technology firm's collaborations with blue-chip NFT collections, and how adding tens of thousands of players to a game will work in practice.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uniswap Price Skyrockets After Foundation Proposes Long-Awaited Staking Rewards]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=218760</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/218760/uniswap-price-skyrockets-proposal-uni-staking-rewards"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T17:43:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized exchange Uniswap may soon have an upgrade to reward holders of governance tokens. The price of UNI has surged as a result.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xai Gaming Token Hits All-Time High, Ronin Still Recovering After Founder’s Wallets Drained]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=218759</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/218759/xai-gaming-token-high-ronin-recovering-founder-hack"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T16:44:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ronin (RON) is gradually rebounding after Axie Infinity co-founder Jeff Zirlin’s wallets were hacked, while XAI jumped to a new peak.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AVAX Dips as Avalanche Network Faces Block Production Halt]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=218758</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/218758/avalanche-network-block-production-halt-avax-dips"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T16:26:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The suspected “esoteric bug” has not helped AVAX performance, which is down for the fifth day in a row this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Softens His Bitcoin Stance: 'A Lot of People Are Doing It']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=218739</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/218739/trump-bitcoin-stance"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T14:08:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I can "live with it one way or the other," he told Fox News during an interview this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin Wary of Pushing Too Much Complexity to Ethereum L2s]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=218531</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/218531/vitalik-buterin-ethereum-l2-complexity"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T12:37:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An L1 consensus failure might create a day of panic for devs, but "with an L2 bug, people could permanently lose lots of money." he said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$3 Billion in Bitcoin Options Expire Today—Here’s Why It Matters]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=218707</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/218707/3-billion-bitcoin-options-expire-today"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T10:33:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today’s $3 billion expiry is nothing compared to the open interest accumulating for March expiry—right before the Bitcoin halving.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can Robot Lawn Mowers Run ‘Doom’? Yes Indeed]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=218679</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/218679/can-robot-lawn-mowers-run-doom-yes"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T05:02:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Rip, shear, mow, and tear." Husqvarna and id Software are teaming up to release a version of Doom that plays on Wi-Fi lawn mowers in April.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Axie Infinity’ Founder’s Ronin Wallets Hacked for $9.5 Million in Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=218694</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/218694/axie-infinity-founder-hacked-9-5-million-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T04:32:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jeff “Jiho” Zirlin tweeted that his personal wallets on the Ronin chain were compromised as funds were taken and sent to Tornado Cash.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Can Now Sell Its $1B Stake in Anthropic to Repay Creditors]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=218675</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/218675/ftx-anthropic-ai-shares-sell-bankruptcy-recovery"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T02:09:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The value of the AI company's shares held by FTX has doubled since the last time a sale was contemplated.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken Decries ‘Expansive New Theory’ Behind SEC Lawsuit, Calls for Dismissal]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=218673</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/218673/kraken-motion-to-dismiss-sec-case-securities"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T01:37:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto exchange says Gary Gensler's agency is trying to “commandeer expansive new authority over the U.S. economy.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Kawailani Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Block Says Its Bitcoin Bets, Boosted By the Cash App, Yielded $207M In Gains]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=218666</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/218666/block-cash-app-square-bitcoin-earnings-growth"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T01:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Jack Dorsey-led payment provider notched a 90% year-over-year increase in Bitcoin gross profit, driving its stock up in after-hours trading.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin, Nvidia Hit Record Highs as AI Hype Fuels Crypto and Stock Market Rally]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=218642</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/218642/worldcoin-wld-nvidia-nvda-all-time-high-crypto-ai-stock-rally"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T00:12:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company that wants to scan your eyeballs for some cash is flying high, along with other projects connected with artificial intelligence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PancakeSwap Launching 'Nemesis Downfall' Shooter With Crypto Rewards]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=218657</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/218657/pancakeswap-nemesis-downfall-shooter-crypto-rewards"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T23:53:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[First-person shooter Nemesis Downfall is PancakeSwap's third game, offering ND token rewards on BNB Chain in its upcoming open beta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reddit Signs Deal with Google for AI Model Training]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=218619</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/218619/reddit-google-ai-model-training-visibility-ipo"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T23:28:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The social news platform deepens its relationship with the search giant, trading access to its vast trove of user-generated content for greater visibility.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase, a16z Take SEC to Court Over 'Unlawful' Crypto Overreach]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=218567</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/218567/coinbase-a16z-take-sec-court-unlawful-crypto-overreach"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T22:51:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A coalition of crypto giants including Coinbase and Andreessen Horowitz filed suit against the SEC in Texas, seeking regulatory clarity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No, Google Is Not Shutting Down Gmail]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=218613</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/218613/no-google-is-not-shutting-down-gmail"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T22:08:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Twitter hoax is sparking some panic and some schadenfreude over Google's mixed record on services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Kawailani Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Starknet Price Jumps After Ethereum Scaler Bows to Pressure Over Token Unlock Schedule]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=218626</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/218626/starknet-ethereum-scaler-revises-token-unlock-schedule"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T21:51:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[StarkWare announced Thursday that it will gradually allocate Starknet tokens to contributors and investors following backlash.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘We're Promising Nothing’: Telegram Game Notcoin Has 25 Million Players and a Soon-to-be-Real Token]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=218610</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/218610/telegram-game-notcoin-25-million-players-token"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T21:48:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Notcoin players have mined trillions of virtual coins by tapping in Telegram. Co-creator Sasha Plotvinov explains what comes next.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Notcoin? Co-Creator Sasha Plotvinov Explains the Viral Telegram Game and Token]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/nEJVx7Nn/what-is-notcoin-co-creator-sasha-plotvinov-explains-the-viral-telegram-game-and-token</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/nEJVx7Nn/what-is-notcoin-co-creator-sasha-plotvinov-explains-the-viral-telegram-game-and-token"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T21:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Notcoin, a simple clicker-style game within messaging app Telegram, has racked up over 25 million players since the start of 2024 and plans to convert the trillions of virtual coins mined so far into a real crypto token on The Open Network. Open Builders founder Sasha Plotvinov joins Decrypt's Andrew Hayward to explain the viral phenomenon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reddit Files to Go Public, Says It Invested in Bitcoin and Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=218602</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/218602/reddit-files-go-public-invested-bitcoin-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T20:56:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Social media site Reddit wants to go public, an SEC filing shows. It also reveals that the company has Bitcoin and Ethereum.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stable Diffusion 3 Is Here—And the AI Image Generator Blows Away MidJourney, Dall-E 3 and Google ImageFX]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=218577</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/218577/stable-diffusion-3-review-comparison-midjourney-dall-e-imagefx"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T20:38:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest open-source model from Stability AI excels at prompt adherence and can understand natural language instead of keywords and tags.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Inventor Satoshi Nakamoto Emails Revealed in Court]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=218575</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/218575/bitcoin-inventor-satoshi-nakamoto-emails-revealed"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T19:44:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fresh Satoshi Nakamoto lore emerges as cypherpunk Adam Back shares 2008-2009 emails with the Bitcoin inventor.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Says It's Still Accessible in Nigeria Despite Reported Crypto Ban]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=218565</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/218565/coinbase-accessible-nigeria-crypto-ban"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T18:27:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nigerian authorities are reportedly blocking citizens' access to popular crypto trading platforms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Backs Grayscale's Ethereum ETF: 'Virtually Identical' to Bitcoin ETFs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=218562</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/218562/coinbase-backs-grayscale-ethereum-etf-push-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T18:17:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Citing Ethereum's technical configuration and market capitalization, Coinbase believes the SEC should approve an ETH spot ETF.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Pirate Nation' Studio Reveals Network for Fully On-Chain Games on Arbitrum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=218554</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/218554/pirate-nation-arbitrum-gaming-multichain-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T17:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Proof of Play’s Multichain network will power fully on-chain games, starting with Pirate Nation, but will open up to other developers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Serotonin CEO: Luxury Brands Can Make Metaverse 'Beautiful and Fulfilling']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=218509</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/218509/serotonin-ceo-luxury-brands-metaverse"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T14:34:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Luxury brands gathered at Decrypt and Rug Radio's R HAUS in Paris to discuss the future of Web3 luxury and fashion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Fair Value of Bitcoin Is Still Zero,' Say European Central Bank Officials]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=218508</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/218508/fair-value-of-bitcoin-is-still-zero-ecb"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T13:05:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This isn't a new sentiment. In November 2022 the same authors declared that Bitcoin was on the "road to irrelevance."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond $69K: What’s the Real Price Bitcoin Has to Reach to Beat Its All-Time High?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=218301</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/218301/bitcoin-inflation-real-price-all-time-high"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T12:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A single Bitcoin doesn’t buy what it used to. Here’s how the asset fares when measured up against inflation in the U.S. economy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Flat Ahead of New US Jobless Claims and Housing Data]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=218500</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/218500/bitcoin-flat-us-jobless-claims-housing-reports"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T10:09:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even with good news in equities markets, $53,000 "will likely be a tough resistance to break" for Bitcoin, said a Bitbank analyst.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Pixels' Founder Luke Barwikowski on the Game's Wild Rise and Ronin Move]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/3GbWbSMh/pixels-founder-luke-barwikowski-on-the-games-wild-rise-and-ronin-move</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/3GbWbSMh/pixels-founder-luke-barwikowski-on-the-games-wild-rise-and-ronin-move"/>
        <updated>2024-02-17T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ahead of the PIXEL token launch, Pixels game founder Luke Barwikowski joins Decrypt's Andrew Hayward to discuss the hectic last few months—and why the game migrated between Ethereum scaling networks, from Polygon to Ronin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Arbitrum Won the 'ApeChain' Vote for an ApeCoin Ethereum Scaler]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QnxP7O5A/how-arbitrum-won-the-apechain-vote-for-an-apecoin-ethereum-scaler</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QnxP7O5A/how-arbitrum-won-the-apechain-vote-for-an-apecoin-ethereum-scaler"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Offchain Labs co-founder and CEO Steven Goldfeder joined Rug Radio's "FOMO Hour" to discuss the ApeCoin DAO's vote to create an Ethereum layer-2 gaming network on Arbitrum for the Bored Ape Yacht Club ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recommend-To-Earn: Tokenizing Travel Recommendations with Sam Simmons]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LATf5OYs/recommend-to-earn-tokenizing-travel-recommendations-with-sam-simmons</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LATf5OYs/recommend-to-earn-tokenizing-travel-recommendations-with-sam-simmons"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T19:24:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reza is joined by Sam Simmons, founder of MintPass. 


They discuss:
- The Parallels between Professional Poker and Crypto
- The profitability of Ethics
- The "Recommend-To-Earn" economy]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Collected: Grant Riven Yun's Journey Through Art and Medicine]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/xXQ3TeOk/the-collected-grant-riven-yuns-journey-through-art-and-medicine</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/xXQ3TeOk/the-collected-grant-riven-yuns-journey-through-art-and-medicine"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T13:36:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Collected's Rachel Wilkins joins digital artist Grant Riven Yun to explore his remarkable journey blending art with medical studies, to achieve over $2 million in sales.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nifty Island Co-Founder on Why Play-to-Airdrop Is the Game's 'Booster Rocket']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TsLkobIU/nifty-island-co-founder-on-why-play-to-airdrop-is-the-games-booster-rocket</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TsLkobIU/nifty-island-co-founder-on-why-play-to-airdrop-is-the-games-booster-rocket"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T22:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nifty Island co-founder Charles Smith joins Decrypt Culture Editor Andrew Hayward to discuss the game's play-to-airdrop campaign, why token incentives are so important to getting crypto games off the ground, and how the team plans to sustain its growth going forward.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pixels: The Hot Crypto Game and Airdrop Explained in One Minute or Less]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/0Es4KAu9/pixels-the-hot-crypto-game-and-airdrop-explained-in-one-minute-or-less</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/0Es4KAu9/pixels-the-hot-crypto-game-and-airdrop-explained-in-one-minute-or-less"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T16:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rug Radio Creator and crypto influencer AshleyDCan explains the popular Ronin farming game Pixels and details around the upcoming PIXEL token airdrop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Scaler Blast Explained in One Minute or Less]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/bTBCaI8S/ethereum-scaler-blast-explained-in-one-minute-or-less</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/bTBCaI8S/ethereum-scaler-blast-explained-in-one-minute-or-less"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rug Radio Creator and crypto influencer AshleyDCan explains Ethereum layer-2 scaling network Blast, from the creators of top NFT marketplace Blur, including its upcoming airdrop and how to participate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pixels Founder: Why PIXEL Token Launch Feels Like 'Day One' for Ronin Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/E9zZ9yHc/pixels-founder-why-pixel-token-launch-feels-like-day-one-for-ronin-game</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/E9zZ9yHc/pixels-founder-why-pixel-token-launch-feels-like-day-one-for-ronin-game"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T23:50:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Luke Barwikowski, founder of farming game Pixels on Ronin, joins Decrypt Culture Editor Andrew Hayward to discuss the incoming launch of the PIXEL token and why he sees it as such a turning point for the rising blockchain game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Animoca’s Yat Siu: How Crypto Gaming Gains Mass Adoption]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/i5oROwec/animocas-yat-siu-how-crypto-gaming-gains-mass-adoption</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/i5oROwec/animocas-yat-siu-how-crypto-gaming-gains-mass-adoption"/>
        <updated>2024-02-10T17:18:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yat Siu, CEO and co-founder of Animoca Brands, joins the FOMO Hour to discuss his view of the Web3 gaming space, how 2024 is already shaping up to be a big year for crypto gaming, the importance of education in the Web3 space, and much, much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shrapnel STX1 Early Access Gameplay]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/SryOJzgn/shrapnel-stx1-early-access-gameplay</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/SryOJzgn/shrapnel-stx1-early-access-gameplay"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T17:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gameplay footage from the STX1 early access gameplay demo of Shrapnel, a first-person shooter built on Avalanche.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Farcaster: Has Decentralized Social Media Finally Arrived?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/SQxXd8cV/farcaster-has-decentralized-social-media-finally-arrived</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/SQxXd8cV/farcaster-has-decentralized-social-media-finally-arrived"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T21:30:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rug Radio creator Benjamin White digs into the rise of Farcaster, the decentralized social media platform that's challenging Twitter following the launch of its Frames feature. Is this the decentralized social media app that finally clicks with the masses?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Gmoney Took Out a $1 Million Loan on a CryptoPunks NFT]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mIE20tcG/why-gmoney-took-out-a-1-million-loan-on-a-cryptopunks-nft</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mIE20tcG/why-gmoney-took-out-a-1-million-loan-on-a-cryptopunks-nft"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T00:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pseudonymous NFT collector and entrepreneur Gmoney joined Rug Radio's live "FOMO Hour" show to discuss why he took out a $1 million loan on one of the most recognizable CryptoPunks NFTs around.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Hunger Games: Explained in One Minute or Less]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/9R1qQMVk/solana-hunger-games-explained-in-one-minute-or-less</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/9R1qQMVk/solana-hunger-games-explained-in-one-minute-or-less"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T16:58:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rug Radio Creator and crypto influencer AshleyDCan explains the latest sensation taking over timelines on Crypto Twitter, Solana Hunger Games. The new "crypto AR" game from GG.zip is backed by Delphi and plans to launch in the spring. Here's what going on, explained in one minute or less.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Questions With SCENE: Gala Marija Vrbanic]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/UcfnncpU/5-questions-with-scene-gala-marija-vrbanic</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/UcfnncpU/5-questions-with-scene-gala-marija-vrbanic"/>
        <updated>2024-02-04T03:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tribute Brand founder and CEO Gala Marija Vrbanic joins 5 Questions With SCENE to discuss not just fashion, but graffiti crimes, fishless aquariums, and the apparently emergent sport of wind chasing.

Video shot and edited by Vincent Roazzi Jr.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Is Everyone Talking About Jupiter on Solana?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/EiN2WqlF/why-is-everyone-talking-about-jupiter-on-solana</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/EiN2WqlF/why-is-everyone-talking-about-jupiter-on-solana"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T19:04:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rug Radio Creator and crypto influencer AshleyDCan explains why the crypto world can't stop talking about Solana's Jupiter. What is JUP? Who qualified for the airdrop? And will there be another round?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jupiter Founder Meow Unloads on the Solana Airdrop 'FUD']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/YSpISivs/jupiter-founder-meow-unloads-on-the-solana-airdrop-fud</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/YSpISivs/jupiter-founder-meow-unloads-on-the-solana-airdrop-fud"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T18:35:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meow, the pseudonymous founder of Solana DEX aggregator Jupiter, made a surprise appearance today on Rug Radio's "FOMO Hour" to address the JUP airdrop "FUD,"  and explain why he believes the backlash to the team's launch liquidity pool is unfounded.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Future is Multichain w/ Jason Trikakis from Holograph]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QGJdd57G/the-future-is-multichain-w-jason-trikakis-from-holograph</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QGJdd57G/the-future-is-multichain-w-jason-trikakis-from-holograph"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T16:21:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reza is joined by Jason from Holograph.xyz

They dive into the multichain future and what that means for NFTs, DeFi, RWAs, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Generative AI Makes for a More Inclusive Metaverse in 'Avalon']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/J5j39bBG/how-generative-ai-makes-for-a-more-inclusive-metaverse-in-avalon</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/J5j39bBG/how-generative-ai-makes-for-a-more-inclusive-metaverse-in-avalon"/>
        <updated>2024-01-31T04:31:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avalon Chief Product Officer Jeffrey Butler speaks with Decrypt reporter Jason Nelson about the use of generative AI within the upcoming game and how it will help players from anywhere and everywhere truly see themselves represented in the online world.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>