<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-04-19T14:14:06.944Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-04-19T14:14:06.944Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Price Prediction For May. Will Shanghai Split Boost ETH, or is Metacade a Better Investment Option?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18147652/Ethereum-Price-Prediction-For-May-Will-Shanghai-Split-Boost-ETH-or-is-Metacade-a-Better-Investment-Option</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18147652/Ethereum-Price-Prediction-For-May-Will-Shanghai-Split-Boost-ETH-or-is-Metacade-a-Better-Investment-Option"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T14:07:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum is well-regarded as a crypto stalwart across the industry and ultimately remains the leading provider of blockchain network services for a host of decentralized apps (dApps), DeFi, and GameFi platforms. Ethereum news is buzzing with the platform’s now completed Shanghai update hot on...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Karate Combat Secures $18 Million for Crypto-Driven Martial Arts]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137185</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137185/karate-combat-18-million-fundraise-investors-crypto-martial-arts-game"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cash infusion will help the crypto league launch Karate Combat apps on iOS and Android.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Karate Combat Secures $18 Million for Crypto-Driven Martial Arts]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18147656/Karate-Combat-Secures-18-Million-for-Crypto-Driven-Martial-Arts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18147656/Karate-Combat-Secures-18-Million-for-Crypto-Driven-Martial-Arts"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cash infusion will help the crypto league launch Karate Combat apps on iOS and Android.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Exchange Zipmex Files For An Extension On The Moratorium]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18147632/Crypto-Exchange-Zipmex-Files-For-An-Extension-On-The-Moratorium</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18147632/Crypto-Exchange-Zipmex-Files-For-An-Extension-On-The-Moratorium"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to an announcement, the struggling cryptocurrency exchange Zipmex has requested a two-month extension to the moratorium period set by the Singapore court overseeing its bankruptcy reorganization. The […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US judge rejects Do Kwon’s request to block SEC from accessing documents]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18147624/US-judge-rejects-Do-Kwons-request-to-block-SEC-from-accessing-documents</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18147624/US-judge-rejects-Do-Kwons-request-to-block-SEC-from-accessing-documents"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T13:55:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. District Court Judge Jed Rakoff denied Do Kwon’s request to block the SEC from accessing documents related to Terraform Labs (TFL) and Luna Foundation Guard (LFG) on April 14, according to court filings. The SEC recently requested the Monetary Authority of Singapore to provide documents...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin plunges toward $29,000, Coinbase leads drop in crypto stocks alongside traditional markets]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18147630/Bitcoin-plunges-toward-29000-Coinbase-leads-drop-in-crypto-stocks-alongside-traditional-markets</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18147630/Bitcoin-plunges-toward-29000-Coinbase-leads-drop-in-crypto-stocks-alongside-traditional-markets"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T13:53:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto prices fell across the board on Wednesday in tandem with stocks like Coinbase and MicroStrategy. Bitcoin declined below $30,000.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will the Latest Move in the FTX Lawsuit Spark an Anti-Regulatory Backlash?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18147612/Will-the-Latest-Move-in-the-FTX-Lawsuit-Spark-an-Anti-Regulatory-Backlash</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18147612/Will-the-Latest-Move-in-the-FTX-Lawsuit-Spark-an-Anti-Regulatory-Backlash"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T13:35:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lawyers for plaintiffs in the FTX lawsuit have just served NBA star Shaquille O’Neal with papers naming him as a defendant. However, this latest development has drawn mixed reactions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Australia surges in crypto ATM adoption]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18147590/Australia-surges-in-crypto-ATM-adoption</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18147590/Australia-surges-in-crypto-ATM-adoption"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T13:35:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Australia has been on a crypto ATM installation spree, taking it to the third spot in the world in terms of global ATM machines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Discloses X Takeover To Twitter Partners, Implications For Dogecoin]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7519389032</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/elon-musk-x-takeover-twitter-dogecoin/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T13:34:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On his way to transforming Twitter into the “‘Everything App,” Dogecoin aficionado Elon Musk has emailed Twitter’s business partners to inform them that the company behind the social media app is now operating under the name X Corp. As Bitcoinist reported, this news has already been leaked by court documents from Twitter’s case against political activist Laura Loomer last week.
 
The documents revealed that Twitter was already fully acquired by the Elon Musk owned X Corp. on April 4, which is part of the parent company called X Holdings Corp. Remarkably, Musk incorporated three holding companies called X Holdings I, II and III as early as April 2022 to prepare Twitter acquisition.
 
Yesterday, Tuesday, Twitter sent an email to its partners, Forbes reports. It says, “Twitter, Inc. has been …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dan Tapiero on Growth Investing in 2023 (EP.418)]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18147616/Dan-Tapiero-on-Growth-Investing-in-2023-EP418</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18147616/Dan-Tapiero-on-Growth-Investing-in-2023-EP418"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T13:30:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dan Tapiero, the founder of 10T Holdings and 1 Round Table Partners joins the show. In this episode we discuss: The performance of Bitcoin as a macro asset over the past year. The current regulatory environment and how the USA is losing its lead versus other countries in the digital asset...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From SNL and The Tonight Show to Sotheby’s:  NFT Creator Bryan Brinkman]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18147591/From-SNL-and-The-Tonight-Show-to-Sothebys-NFT-Creator-Bryan-Brinkman</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18147591/From-SNL-and-The-Tonight-Show-to-Sothebys-NFT-Creator-Bryan-Brinkman"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bryan Brinkman (of SNL and The Tonight Show) reveals that the secret to being a successful NFT creator involves spending just one-third of the time on art.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin crashes into deep correction amid ‘cascade of liquidations’]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18147568/Bitcoin-crashes-into-deep-correction-amid-cascade-of-liquidations</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18147568/Bitcoin-crashes-into-deep-correction-amid-cascade-of-liquidations"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T13:27:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) experienced a significant drop in value on Wednesday, April 19, as a deep correction in the markets occurred. … Continued]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin backlash against NYT continues with #StopThePresses]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18147573/Bitcoin-backlash-against-NYT-continues-with-StopThePresses</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18147573/Bitcoin-backlash-against-NYT-continues-with-StopThePresses"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T13:26:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NYT's anti-Bitcoin-mining article has presented its critics with an open goal to demand it cease its wasteful printing of newspapers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Discloses X Takeover To Twitter Partners, Implications For Dogecoin]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18147559/Elon-Musk-Discloses-X-Takeover-To-Twitter-Partners-Implications-For-Dogecoin</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18147559/Elon-Musk-Discloses-X-Takeover-To-Twitter-Partners-Implications-For-Dogecoin"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T13:25:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On his way to transforming Twitter into the “‘Everything App,” Dogecoin aficionado Elon Musk has emailed Twitter’s business partners to inform them that the company behind the social media app is now operating under the name X Corp. As Bitcoinist reported, this news has already been leaked by...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Blasts Off With 14% Climb Ahead Of Maiden Starship Launch]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75193a1e8f</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-blasts-off-14/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T13:25:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin enthusiasts are figuratively over the moon, and not just because of the meme-inspired cryptocurrency’s soaring value – they’re now eagerly eyeing the cosmos as well. 
 
Nothing, not even the sheer scale of Elon Musk’s SpaceX Starship, can dampen their excitement as they look towards the heavens with hopes of seeing the colossal spacecraft take off.
 
Starship, the biggest rocket ever built, has captured the attention of space enthusiasts worldwide, and its upcoming launch has sent ripples of excitement throughout the Dogecoin community. 
 
As the countdown to the launch continues, the current DOGE price is also on the rise, adding to the already electrifying atmosphere surrounding this historic event.
 
 

 
 
Dogecoin Sees Gains Despite Delayed Starship Launch
 
Despite the delay…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BREAKING: Asian Countries Are Secretly Stacking Bitcoin | EP 721]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18147574/BREAKING-Asian-Countries-Are-Secretly-Stacking-Bitcoin-EP-721</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18147574/BREAKING-Asian-Countries-Are-Secretly-Stacking-Bitcoin-EP-721"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T13:22:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kingdom of Bhutan secretly invests millions in Bitcoin and Bitcoin 2023 recently announced a governor from the country of Indonesia✓ SUBSCRIBE - https://bit.ly/3QbgqTQ✓ LEAVE A LIKE ✓ COMMENT Join our Telegram, Give us Memes to Review!► https://t.me/SimplyBitcoinTVBITCOIN CONFRENCE DISCOUNTS►...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prosecutors Seek Seven-Year Prison Sentence for Reggie Fowler in Crypto Shadow Bank Case]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75193a93ae</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/04/19/prosecutors-seek-seven-year-prison-sentence-for-reggie-fowler-in-crypto-shadow-bank-case/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T13:22:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The former footballer pleaded guilty to bank and wire fraud charges over operating Crypto Capital Corp., the shadow bank that lost Bitfinex's millions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandali Handagama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Blasts Off With 14% Climb Ahead Of Maiden Starship Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18147558/Dogecoin-Blasts-Off-With-14-Climb-Ahead-Of-Maiden-Starship-Launch</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18147558/Dogecoin-Blasts-Off-With-14-Climb-Ahead-Of-Maiden-Starship-Launch"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T13:21:57.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Renowned Analyst Explains When Bitcoin (BTC) Price Will Reach $100,000]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18147613/Renowned-Analyst-Explains-When-Bitcoin-BTC-Price-Will-Reach-100000</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18147613/Renowned-Analyst-Explains-When-Bitcoin-BTC-Price-Will-Reach-100000"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T13:20:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PlanB, the analyst behind the Stock-to-Flow model, predicts Bitcoin will break the $100,000 mark after the 2024 halving, despite his history of contentious and sometimes inaccurate predictions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Technical Analysis: BTC Nears Breakout Below $29,000 on Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75193be7f4</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-ethereum-technical-analysis-btc-nears-breakout-below-29000-on-wednesday/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T13:14:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin fell to a one-week low on Apr. 19, as markets moved into consolidation following a recent bull run. Following today’s red wave, prices neared a breakout below the $29,000 level earlier in the session. Ethereum also declined, falling below $2,000.
 
Bitcoin
 
Bitcoin (BTC) moved lower on Wednesday, as markets began to consolidate following recent gains in price.
 
Following a high of $30,470.30 on Tuesday, BTC/USD dropped to a bottom at the $29,102.17 mark earlier in the day.
 
The low sent bitcoin to its lowest point since April 10, which is when price was last below $29,000.
 
 
Bitcoin chart by TradingView
 

 
 

 
Overall, it appears that today’s sell-off took place as the 14-day relative strength index (RSI) fell below a floor at 59.00.
 
At the time of writing, the index is tracking at 54.97, with the next visible point of support at the 55.00 mark.
 
Should this level be hit, there is a good chance that BTC will be trading around a floor at $28,600.
 
 
Ethereum
 
In addition to BTC, Wednesday’s red wave also pushed ethereum (ETH) lower, with the price dropping below $2,000.
 
ETH/USD hit a low of $1,967.17 earlier today, which comes less than 24 hours after it traded at a peak of $2,121.53.
 
The move came as ethereum fell below its recent price floor at the $2,030 level, with some eyeing a lower floor at $1,830.
 
 
Ethereum chart by TradingView
 

 
 

 
Ultimately, ETH was relatively overbought in recent days, with the RSI hitting a reading above 75.00 to start the week.
 
This led to bears reentering the market, which have now pushed price strength to a current reading at 55.00
 
A floor at 51.00 could be the target for sellers, which would almost certainly see ETH trading under $1,900.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
 What is behind today’s red wave? Leave your thoughts in the comments below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gary Gensler: The SEC Will Not Change its Attitude Toward Crypto Exchanges]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18147548/Gary-Gensler-The-SEC-Will-Not-Change-its-Attitude-Toward-Crypto-Exchanges</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18147548/Gary-Gensler-The-SEC-Will-Not-Change-its-Attitude-Toward-Crypto-Exchanges"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T13:12:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to Gensler, crypto platforms are “just a bunch of intermediaries” that must comply with existing law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Sets Sights on UK Crypto Hub As Regulatory Uncertainty Looms at Home in the US]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18147521/Coinbase-Sets-Sights-on-UK-Crypto-Hub-As-Regulatory-Uncertainty-Looms-at-Home-in-the-US</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18147521/Coinbase-Sets-Sights-on-UK-Crypto-Hub-As-Regulatory-Uncertainty-Looms-at-Home-in-the-US"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T13:04:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amid swirling regulatory uncertainty in the United States, top American crypto exchange Coinbase is emphasizing its efforts to make inroads in the United Kingdom. While visiting London this week for UK FinTech Week 2023, Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong and met with MP Andrew Griffith, the UK’s...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Wealth Manager Onramp Taps CoinDesk Indices to Create Customized Portfolios]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e751925e748</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/04/19/dnpcrypto-wealth-manager-onramp-taps-coindesk-indices-to-create-customized-portfolios/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T13:01:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The partnership will provide advisors with a wider range of options for shaping successful portfolios.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aoyon Ashraf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Wallet Firm Trezor Adds Privacy-Enhancing 'CoinJoin' Feature to Bitcoin Transactions]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137055</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137055/crypto-wallet-firm-trezor-adds-privacy-enhancing-coinjoin-feature-bitcoin-transactions"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T13:01:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The popular Bitcoin privacy-preserving technique is now available on Trezor hardware wallets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Square Enix Teams With Elixir to Bring Web3 Games to Mainstream Audiences]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137140</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137140/square-enix-teams-with-elixir-to-bring-web3-games-to-mainstream-audiences"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Final Fantasy developer is continuing its push into Web3 via the Elixir launcher, which already offers an Epic Games Store integration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Square Enix Teams With Elixir to Bring Web3 Games to Mainstream Audiences]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18147512/Square-Enix-Teams-With-Elixir-to-Bring-Web3-Games-to-Mainstream-Audiences</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18147512/Square-Enix-Teams-With-Elixir-to-Bring-Web3-Games-to-Mainstream-Audiences"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Final Fantasy developer is continuing its push into Web3 via the Elixir launcher, which already offers an Epic Games Store integration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Connecting DeFi: How multichain token systems can improve liquidity]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18147503/Connecting-DeFi-How-multichain-token-systems-can-improve-liquidity</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18147503/Connecting-DeFi-How-multichain-token-systems-can-improve-liquidity"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T13:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Multichain token systems can move tokens between different blockchains, allowing users to access liquidity across multiple markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chainstack launches Subgraphs, an on-chain indexing tool for 13 blockchains]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18147520/Chainstack-launches-Subgraphs-an-on-chain-indexing-tool-for-13-blockchains</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18147520/Chainstack-launches-Subgraphs-an-on-chain-indexing-tool-for-13-blockchains"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T13:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By providing a single access point for data across all supported protocols with Subgraphs, Chainstack aims to help teams begin using the indexer through a hosted service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EU’s Crypto Licensing Regime Set for Approval as Lawmakers Signal Support]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7519212b8e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/04/19/eus-crypto-licensing-regime-set-for-approval-as-lawmakers-signal-support/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T12:40:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leaders of the European Parliament’s largest political groupings indicated they’ll support the landmark MiCA law ahead of a vote Thursday]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack Schickler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AIDOGE Triggers Arbitrum Meme Coin Bull Run, Here’s Coins To Look At]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7519227412</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/aidoge-triggers-meme-coin-bull-run/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T12:32:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The success of AIDOGE on the Arbitrum network has brought about a new meme season on the Ethereum Layer 2 blockchain. The result of its rally has been multiple new coins coming out of the blockchain as they try to leverage this newfound liquidity. In this report, we take a look at some of the promising meme coins that have been making a splash.
 
PufDAO (PUF)
 
For PufDAO (PUF), this meme coin was launched two days ago and it seems to play into the 4/20 meme on Twitter. However, unlike other 4/20 meme coins that have arisen during this time, PUF has seen a reasonable level of success.
 
 
After launching at a price of $0.0000002101, the meme coin knocked off two zeroes by early Wednesday to reach an all-time high of $0.00002123, according to data from Dextools. This put its market cap at i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Best Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Mover Americas: Bitcoin Slides Toward $29K]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75192c4851</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/04/19/first-mover-americas-bitcoin-slides-toward-29k/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T12:20:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest price moves in bitcoin (BTC) and crypto markets in context for April 19, 2023. First Mover is CoinDesk’s daily newsletter that contextualizes the latest actions in the crypto markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lyllah Ledesma, Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hard-Wallet Maker Ledger, Crypto Custodian Etana Target Institutions With Regulated Custody]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75192c483f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/04/19/hard-wallet-maker-ledger-crypto-custodian-etana-target-institutions-with-regulated-custody/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T12:20:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The companies are looking to make it easier for institutions to hold digital assets and bolster investor confidence in the market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Napolitano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Protocol Fetch.ai Offering AI Trading Tools for Decentralized Exchanges]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75192c482f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/04/19/crypto-protocol-fetchai-introduces-ai-trading-tools-for-decentralized-exchanges/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T12:20:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fetch.ai's aim is to facilitate peer-to-peer trading between DeFi users using AI-powered software "agents."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Puts Power In The Hands Of The Workers]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75192ea76a</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/bitcoin-unites-workers-of-the-world"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T12:05:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A former communist party member on how Bitcoin may help avoid the violence that historically accompanies economically-induced social unrest.
 
         
         
         
         
    
This is an opinion editorial by Frank Kashner, founder of UnChainDemocracy.org.
In 1971, I joined a communist party while working in the factory of the highest-paid General Electric (GE) defense plant in the country. I was repulsed by pictures of our military dropping napalm on Vietnamese children, convinced that the justifications of our government were lies, and I was drawn to the idea that “the working class” would soon take over the world and create a utopia. 
The group that I joined was split off from the American Communist Party. It was supposed to be “democratic and centralist.” I quit the group af…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Frank Kashner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PEPE Holder Turns $250 into $1M in Four Days. But Can They Sell It?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137203</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137203/pepe-holder-turns-250-into-1m-in-four-days-but-can-they-sell-it"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T12:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A memecoin investor has turned $250 into $1.02 million—but liquidity issues could prevent them from realizing that profit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong Court Declares Crypto as Property in Case Involving Defunct Gatecoin]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75192844c0</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/04/19/hong-kong-court-declares-crypto-as-property-in-case-involving-defunct-gatecoin/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T11:54:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ruling would give Hong Kong liquidators more clarity on how to treat crypto assets caught up in winding down procedures, law firm Hogan Lovells said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandali Handagama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russia Developing Payment Gateways With Partners Like Turkey, Mulling Crypto Settlements]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e751928b658</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/russia-developing-payment-gateways-with-partners-like-turkey-mulling-crypto-settlements/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T11:51:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bank of Russia is building a system of gateways with foreign payment networks and is now working with Turkey in this field. Russia’s monetary authority would also allow the experimental use of cryptocurrencies in foreign economic activities, its head was quoted as saying.
 
Russia’s Central Bank ‘Actively Working’ With Turkey on New Payment Gateways
 
The Central Bank of Russia (CBR) is developing payment gateways with foreign payment systems and is actively working with Turkey in this area, Governor Elvira Nabiullina said at a meeting with lawmakers in the State Duma, the lower house of Russian parliament.
 
Russians visiting Turkey have been experiencing problems with payments since Visa and Mastercard suspended Russian operations as part of sanctions over the war in Ukraine. Starting fr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lubomir Tassev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Over $250 Million in Liquidations as Bitcoin, Ethereum Slip]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137198</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137198/250-million-in-liquidations-as-bitcoin-ethereum-slip"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T11:16:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin dropped to just over $29,000 overnight, while Ethereum slumped by 6% on the day to slip below $2,000.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinEx Charity’s Effort to Support Education Is Appreciated by Kacuv]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7519169ae9</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/coinex-charitys-effort-to-support-education-is-appreciated-by-kacuv/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T11:13:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. Recently, CoinEx Charity has kicked off its second educational welfare program in Türkiye. In the first program, all the students receiving donations have continued their studies in the new semester. Since last year, CoinEx Charity has participated in the Umudum Scholarship Program initiated by the local charity organization Kacuv in Türkiye, offering support in tuition to 50 local impoverished students.
 
The Umudum Scholarship Program provides scholarships for students in preschools, primary schools, secondary schools, and universities in Türkiye who need financial support to continue their studies. This program aims to boost students’ learning motivation and ensure that their education is not interrupted due to financial difficulties.
 
CoinEx Charity’s Effort to Support …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinDesk Winds Down Ethereum Validator ‘Zelda,’ and We Now Wait for Money Back]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e751916d1f0</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/04/19/coindesk-winds-down-validator-zelda-as-ethereum-enables-staking-withdrawals/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T11:11:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CoinDesk set up its own Ethereum validator, fondly nicknamed “Zelda,” in 2020 to witness firsthand the blockchain’s landmark shift to an energy-efficient proof-of-stake consensus mechanism from its original proof-of-work – the same one used by Bitcoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bradley Keoun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Service Providers Licensing Begins in UAE]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7519132231</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/cryptocurrency-service-providers-licensing-begins-in-uae/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T10:43:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The  
Securities and Commodities Authority (SCA), which oversees financial markets in  
the United Arab Emirates (UAE), announced this week that it has begun accepting  
license applications for cryptocurrency services. 
This  
follows the approval of regulations governing the market and is another step  
towards making the UAE an 'Oasis' for digital asset companies.
Virtual Asset Service  
Providers Licensing Begins in UAE
In 2022,  
the UAE Cabinet passed Resolution No. 111, which granted the SCA authority to  
issue decisions governing virtual asset transactions and license virtual asset  
service providers (VASPs).
All  
UAE-based companies offering virtual asset services, except those licensed to  
operate in economic-free zones, must adhere to the SCA's decisions and submit  
their l…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Damian Chmiel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chip Giant Intel Abandons Bitcoin ASIC Production]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75191e6227</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/chip-giant-intel-abandons-bitcoin-asic-production/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T10:22:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After announcing the production of bitcoin application-specific integrated circuits (ASICs), Intel, the world’s largest semiconductor chip manufacturer by revenue, appears to be abandoning its blockchain chip production. On Tuesday, a spokesperson for the chip manufacturer explained that Intel has “end-of-lifed the Intel Blockscale 1000 Series ASIC.”
 
Intel Spokesperson Discloses Company Has End-of-Lifed the Blockscale 1000 Series ASIC
 
In February 2022, the California-based technology company Intel made headlines when it announced its plan to create “energy-efficient accelerators,” or ASIC technology, to contribute to the development of blockchain technologies. Later that month, at the 2022 International Solid-State Circuits Conference (ISSCC), the company unveiled the Bonanza Mine BMZ1…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Institutions Flock to Ether After Shapella Upgrade]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75191ecb21</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/04/19/institutions-flock-to-ether-after-shapella-upgrade/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T10:19:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Open interest in CME futures has risen to the highest level since March 2022, indicating an influx of institutional traders to the crypto market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These Are The Key Takeaways For Ripple And XRP From The Gensler Hearing]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75191871dd</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/key-takeaways-ripple-xrp-gensler-hearing/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T10:08:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The course of yesterday’s congressional hearing of US Securities and Exchange Commission chairman Gary Gensler before the House Financial Services Committee can undoubtedly be seen as an indirect triumph for Ripple, XRP investors and the entire crypto industry. Gensler was confronted with tough questions right from the start, which he tremulously dodged, just to avoid giving any regulatory clarity.
 
Partly with shaking hands and in broken speech, Gensler only stammered in response to aggressive questions from Committee Chairman Patrick McHenry, Warren Davidson and Tom Emmer (all Republicans), among others. Davidson asked the most important question of the day for the XRP community: whether he believes XRP is a security.
 
Interestingly, Gensler refused to give a yes or no answer. Instead,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Will Hit $100,000 This Year, Artificial Intelligence And These Experts Predict]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7519010510</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-will-hit-100000-this-year/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T09:09:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since its launch in 2009, Bitcoin, the first decentralized cryptocurrency in the world, has had its own ups and downs.
 
Many have questioned the viability and future of the cryptocurrency industry in the wake of its spectacular ascent and catastrophic falls. Nevertheless, despite the ambiguity, the alpha coin has persisted in its growth, and experts anticipate that the digital asset will experience tremendous growth in 2023.
 
ChatGPT Sees Bitcoin Reaching $100K This Year
 
According to ChatGPT, a linguistic model built on data patterns and analysis, Bitcoin will achieve its highest price to date in 2023, peaking at between $100,000 and $120,000.
 
The outlook is supported by a number of elements, such as the present optimistic market trend, rising levels of mainstream use, and rising ins…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Brief History of Artificial Intelligence (AI): From Turing to IoT]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137088</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/a-brief-history-of-artificial-intelligence-ai-from-turing-to-iot"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T09:06:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence (AI) as a concept dates back to ancient times, but modern AI began in the mid-20th century with pioneers like Alan Turing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Reiff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong Is Vying To Be The Next Crypto Hub]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137144</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137144/hong-kong-is-vying-to-be-the-next-crypto-hub"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T04:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong has historically provided fertile soil to grow financial institutions. Can it also make magic for crypto firms?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shuyao Kong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Frontiers: Jeremy Booth Lassos More Western Artists Into Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137149</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137149/new-frontiers-jeremy-booth-lassoing-more-western-artists-web3"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T23:18:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NFT artist announced the Western Art Dept, an initiative to bring more traditional Western-themed artists into the Web3 space.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Hacker Has Stolen $10 Million in Ethereum and No One Knows How]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137167</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137167/hacker-stolen-10-million-ethereum-no-one-knows-how"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T23:09:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A hacker has been targeting OG crypto users since December, draining their wallets and leaving experts baffled.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Oasis Tribute Album Sparks Debate Over Copyright and the Future of Music]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137160</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137160/ai-oasis-aisis-breezer-liam-gallagher-music-copyright"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T23:05:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI revives Oasis’ distinctive sound, raising complicated questions about the intersection of creativity and technology.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Did Gary Gensler Pull a Kim Kardashian by 'Shilling' Algorand?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137142</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137142/gary-gensler-kim-kardashian-shilling-algorand"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T22:14:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Years before the SEC labeled it a security, Gensler called Algorand “great technology” and “brilliant work.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gensler Is Driving Crypto to Communist China, Says Republican Congressman]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137127</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137127/gensler-driving-crypto-china-republican-tom-emmer"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T19:29:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GOP lawmakers blasted the SEC Chairman today during a hearing, with Rep. Tom Emmer (R-MN) the most scathing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Upgrade Could Make It Harder for Governments to Censor Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137130</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137130/this-upgrade-could-make-it-harder-for-governments-to-censor-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T19:24:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The more influential Bitcoin becomes, the greater the risk of attack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alyssa Hertig</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Drops More NFTs—And Now the First Batch Is Plummeting in Price]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137120</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137120/trump-drops-more-nfts-price-plummeting"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T17:32:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trump wants “‘NICE GUY’ CREDIT” after dropping more $99 NFTs, but his first set of collectibles have fallen by over 50% on the secondary market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lack of Crypto Compliance Is SEC's Fault, Say Republican Lawmakers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137089</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137089/lack-crypto-compliance-is-sec-fault-say-republican-lawmakers"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T14:48:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The letter accuses the agency boss of cramming the digital assets industry into an improper regulatory framework.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jeremy Cowart to Create 10,000 Photo NFTs in 20 Minutes—In Front of an Audience]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137064</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137064/jeremy-cowart-create-10000-photo-nfts-live-20-minutes-audience"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T14:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Award-winning photographer Jeremy Cowart will produce the NFTs live in Nashville, in partnership with OpenSea and Transient Labs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gala v2 Airdrop Announced: What You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137065</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137065/gala-v2-airdrop-announced-what-you-need-know"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T12:43:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GALA holders are scheduled for an airdrop in May but should be wary of keeping their funds in exchanges, liquidity pools, or smart contracts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Artificial Intelligence Can Revolutionize Supply Chain Optimization]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137050</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/how-artificial-intelligence-can-revolutionize-supply-chain-optimization"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T11:30:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A look at how AI can be used to take on—and improve—the optimization of a supply chain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Reiff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK ‘Moving Fast’ on Crypto Regulations, Says Coinbase CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137045</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137045/uk-moving-fast-crypto-regulations-says-coinbase-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T11:06:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amid the latest crypto crackdown in the United States, Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong appears to be turning to the UK and Europe.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly,Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Granted Access to Singapore Records for Terra's Do Kwon]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137043</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137043/sec-granted-access-singapore-records-terra-do-kwon"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T09:44:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A judge rejected Do Kwon's request to block SEC access to documents related to Terraform Labs’ activities in Singapore.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can AI Save Journalism From Fake News? Not Yet, But These Tools Can Help]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137012</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137012/ai-journalism-fake-news-checker-detector-fact-check"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T03:51:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The advent of accessible AI makes it easier than ever to create fake images. But AI language tools can also help debunk false information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Bumped to the Back Seat as AI Investments Accelerate]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137033</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137033/vc-investors-shift-gears-favor-ai-over-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T03:27:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mysten Labs CEO Evan Cheng says AI’s broad consumer appeal has VCs shifting gears.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nike Unveils First .Swoosh NFT Digital Sneaker Drop]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137011</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137011/nike-unveils-first-swoosh-nft-collection-for-members"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T00:25:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The “Our Force 1" collection will potentially consist of hundreds of thousands of virtual pairs of the brand’s iconic Air Force 1 sneaker.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paxful CEO Says Users Can Withdraw Funds—But They Say Otherwise]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137000</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137000/paxful-ceo-ray-yousseff-claims-withdrawals-available-users-disagree"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T23:21:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paxful customers are angry that they still cannot withdraw their funds while the company's ex-boss claims otherwise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google CEO: We’re Not Ready for Advanced AI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=136993</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/136993/google-ceo-we-are-not-ready-for-advanced-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T22:04:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Experts warn that AI could harm humans but also say the future may be brighter than we think.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Labels Algorand and Five Other Tokens as Securities in Bittrex Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=136990</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/136990/sec-bittrex-lawsuit-algorand-five-tokens-securities"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T21:23:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A legal expert said the coins’ inclusion resembles another SEC lawsuit brought against a former Coinbase employee.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Starbucks Odyssey Launch ‘Getting Closer’ With New NFTs, Rewards]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=136984</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/136984/starbucks-odyssey-nft-rewards-launch"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T20:22:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The coffee giant will drop its second NFT collection this week, and teased the public rollout for its Web3 platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Fund Inflows Top $100M in One Week as Investors 'Flee to Safety']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=136977</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/136977/bitcoin-funds-100m-investors-safe-haven"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T20:03:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Big investors continue to feel optimistic about Bitcoin, according to a Monday CoinShares report, with over $104 million of inflows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Charges Bittrex, Former CEO for Operating Unregistered Securities Exchange]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=136973</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/136973/sec-charges-bittrex-former-ceo-operating-unregistered-securities-exchange"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T15:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The lawsuit also names six tokens as securities, including Algorand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EU Lawmakers Call for 'Human-centric, Safe and Trustworthy' AI Development]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=136964</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/136964/eu-lawmakers-call-human-centric-safe-trustworthy-ai-development"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T15:12:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Politicians working on the EU’s response to AI development want the bloc to work with the U.S. on a "human-centric" solution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alys Key</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Australians Lost $148M in Crypto to Scammers in 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=136948</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/136948/aussies-lost-148-million-crypto-scammers-2022"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T13:19:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scams continued to plague Australians in 2022, with crypto payments seeing a hefty uptick compared to the previous year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bittrex Faces Potential Enforcement Action From The SEC: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=136947</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/136947/bittrex-faces-potential-enforcement-action-sec-report"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T11:23:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC has reportedly told the Seattle-based Bittrex of a potential enforcement action against the crypto exchange.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shaq Finally Served in FTX Lawsuit After Months of ‘Running’, Say Lawyers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=136940</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/136940/shaq-finally-served-ftx-lawsuit-after-months-running-say-lawyers"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T10:48:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shaq has finally been served after allegedly “running” from legal complaints over his promotion of the fallen crypto exchange FTX.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alys Key</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is zkEVM? The Zero-Knowledge Proof's Role in Smart Contracts]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=136938</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-zkevm"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T10:09:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The emerging zkEVM ecosystem will allow the Ethereum blockchain to bolster secure transaction scalability — while preserving key functions and features of its virtual machine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kade Garrett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Tapers Gains After 12% Rise Post-Shanghai]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=136933</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/136933/ethereum-tapers-gains-rise-post-shanghai"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T09:17:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Significant withdrawals after the Shanghai upgrade and the dollar's strength may be weighing on the second-largest cryptocurrency.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFT NYC Again Showcased the Resilience of Web3 Culture]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=136810</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/136810/nft-nyc-2023-gmoney-ordinals-bitcoin-wrangler"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T01:50:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From an NFT scavenger hunt to NFT-enabled physical fashion, there was a lot to like at NFT NYC, even amid an extended bear market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: Anthony Scaramucci Is More Bullish on Bitcoin Than Ever]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PqLOXL47/gm-anthony-scaramucci-is-more-bullish-on-bitcoin-than-ever</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PqLOXL47/gm-anthony-scaramucci-is-more-bullish-on-bitcoin-than-ever"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T18:58:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthony Scaramucci of hedge fund SkyBridge Capital got burned by Sam Bankman-Fried: he co-hosted SALT conferences with FTX and sold a 30% stake in SkyBridge to FTX Ventures. And yet "The Mooch" tells Dan Roberts and Stacy Elliott "I'm more bullish now than I have ever been" on crypto as an investment case. He discusses his frustration with SBF, how wrong he thinks politicians like Elizabeth Warren and Gary Gensler are about crypto and how to regulate it, what he sees happening next with adoption, and talks about Trump. Watch and make sure to subscribe to the gm podcast on Apple or Spotify.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Chief Legal Officer: The Problem With SEC's Howey Test Isn't Its Age]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/woZFLgib/coinbase-chief-legal-officer-the-problem-with-secs-howey-test-isnt-its-age</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/woZFLgib/coinbase-chief-legal-officer-the-problem-with-secs-howey-test-isnt-its-age"/>
        <updated>2023-04-10T16:25:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Chief Legal Officer Paul Grewal discussed the "Howey Test," which the SEC uses as its yard stick for whether a crypto asset should be regulated as a security, and told Decrypt's Stacy Elliott and Dan Roberts the issue with it isn't that it's old (the case is from 1946) but how it's being applied to modern technology. Watch and make sure to subscribe to the gm podcast on Apple or Spotify.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized Pictures Plots Its Next Web3 Grant for Filmmakers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/WlVsgaOs/decentralized-pictures-plots-its-next-web3-grant-for-filmmakers</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/WlVsgaOs/decentralized-pictures-plots-its-next-web3-grant-for-filmmakers"/>
        <updated>2023-04-08T13:15:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leo Matchett from Web3 film funding platform Decentralized Pictures tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson at Outer Edge LA about DCP's just announced iPhone Filmmaking Initiative, which will support aspiring filmmakers who create a short film on their iPhones, and will be determined via DCP's crypto-native on-chain voting system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 YouTuber CryptoStache: Gaming Will Be the Catalyst That Takes NFTs Mainstream]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Exb7eWKj/web3-youtuber-cryptostache-gaming-will-be-the-catalyst-that-takes-nfts-mainstream</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Exb7eWKj/web3-youtuber-cryptostache-gaming-will-be-the-catalyst-that-takes-nfts-mainstream"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T02:51:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 gaming YouTuber CryptoStache talks to Decrypt's Jason Nelson at Outer Edge LA about why Web3 gaming will bring NFTs mainstream, the partnerships that prove it's already happening, how gamers will change their tune on NFTs, and how the terminology is likely to change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fordefi Aims to Dramatically Simplify the Institutional Crypto Wallet]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/LGxyFJP5/fordefi-aims-to-dramatically-simplify-the-institutional-crypto-wallet</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/LGxyFJP5/fordefi-aims-to-dramatically-simplify-the-institutional-crypto-wallet"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T02:39:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Steve H., VP of sales from Fordefi, which raised $18 million in funding last year, tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson at Outer Edge LA how Fordefi uses multi-party computation to make signing transactions on an institutional crypto wallet much simpler—no seed phrase needed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: Canadian Bitcoin Miner Hut 8 Is Heading West]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5AGD2ifd/gm-canadian-bitcoin-miner-hut-8-is-heading-west</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5AGD2ifd/gm-canadian-bitcoin-miner-hut-8-is-heading-west"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T21:40:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Toronto-based Bitcoin mining company Hut 8 recently announced a merger with U.S. Bitcoin Corp that will take it into Texas, Nebraska, and New York. Hut 8 CEO Jaime Leverton joined Dan Roberts and Stacy Elliott to talk expanding into the U.S., dealing with regulatory pushback post-FTX, why Texas is such a hotspot, and where she'd like to expand globally down the road (the climates may surprise you). Watch and make sure to subscribe to the gm podcast on Apple or Spotify.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: Kevin Owocki Wants to Regenerate DeFi]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/knbMLd17/gm-kevin-owocki-wants-to-regenerate-defi</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/knbMLd17/gm-kevin-owocki-wants-to-regenerate-defi"/>
        <updated>2023-04-01T14:23:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Move over, DeFi—ReFi is coming? Gitcoin founder Kevin Owocki has stepped away from DeFi grant-giving machine Gitcoin as it fully decentralizes and is now focused on regenerative finance (huh?) and ReFi incubator Supermodular. He aims to "regenerate the regenerators." He explained it all to Dan Roberts and Liam Kelly, and also talks DAO structure, crypto factions, NFT use cases, his book "Greenpilled," and much more. Watch and make sure to subscribe to the gm podcast on Apple or Spotify.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Aurory's Head of Production Left Ubisoft for Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PqJHF0N9/why-aurorys-head-of-production-left-ubisoft-for-web3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PqJHF0N9/why-aurorys-head-of-production-left-ubisoft-for-web3"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T21:24:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aurory executive producer and head of production Jonathan Campeau tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin at GDC about how the first-generation of Web3 games came out of DeFi and are now evolving.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['We Don't Really Do the Corporate Thing Very Well' Says Jason Brink on Gala Games Approach]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/EDzHoKrt/we-dont-really-do-the-corporate-thing-very-well-says-jason-brink-on-gala-games-approach</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/EDzHoKrt/we-dont-really-do-the-corporate-thing-very-well-says-jason-brink-on-gala-games-approach"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T21:14:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With roughly 50 video games in its pipeline, Gala Games is all-in on Web3. Gala's President of Blockchain Jason Brink told Decrypt's Kate Irwin at GDC about the studio's ethos and weighs in on the different approaches to Web3 gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: Coinbase's Top Lawyer Gets Real on SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mB7DMx7l/gm-coinbases-top-lawyer-gets-real-on-sec</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mB7DMx7l/gm-coinbases-top-lawyer-gets-real-on-sec"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T16:36:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paul Grewal is the Chief Legal Officer at Coinbase and a former U.S. magistrate judge in Northern California. He gave Dan Roberts and Stacy Elliott his candid takes on Sam Bankman-Fried and FTX, the SEC's crackdown on staking, the sanctioning of Tornado Cash, and more alpha on how Coinbase is approaching the current unfriendly US regulatory environment. Watch and make sure to subscribe to the gm podcast on Apple or Spotify.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Founder of Rotten Tomatoes Says Web3 Entertainment Isn’t Nearly Entertaining Enough Yet]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/ri2LLifZ/the-founder-of-rotten-tomatoes-says-web3-entertainment-isnt-nearly-entertaining-enough-yet</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/ri2LLifZ/the-founder-of-rotten-tomatoes-says-web3-entertainment-isnt-nearly-entertaining-enough-yet"/>
        <updated>2023-03-25T02:44:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rotten Tomatoes founder Patrick Lee, who has led companies at the intersection of technology and entertainment from Web1 to Web3, spoke to Decrypt's Sander Lutz at Outer Edge LA about the current state of decentralized gaming, film and television.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: How Gnosis Has Endured and Evolved]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Kxfs2Dmd/gm-how-gnosis-has-endured-and-evolved</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Kxfs2Dmd/gm-how-gnosis-has-endured-and-evolved"/>
        <updated>2023-03-24T20:58:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gnosis first launched in 2015 as a decentralized prediction market built on Ethereum. Now it's a DAO, a multi-sig wallet, a staking chain, and a vibrant community with its own GNO governance token. Co-founder and COO Friederike Ernst talked to Dan Roberts and Stacy Elliott about the careful evolution of Gnosis, decentralization impostors, account abstraction, DeFi UX failures, why Ethereum is the "Manhattan of crypto," and much more. Watch and make sure to subscribe to the gm podcast on Apple or Spotify.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Justin Aversano's Inspiration for Tarot-Themed NFT Photo Series 'Smoke and Mirrors']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/dkWNFMPb/justin-aversanos-inspiration-for-tarot-themed-nft-photo-series-smoke-and-mirrors</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/dkWNFMPb/justin-aversanos-inspiration-for-tarot-themed-nft-photo-series-smoke-and-mirrors"/>
        <updated>2023-03-24T20:03:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Justin Aversano, best known for his high-selling "Twin Flames" NFT photo series, joined Decrypt’s Andrew Hayward ahead of the upcoming L.A. exhibition for his new Ethereum NFT project "Smoke and Mirrors." He shared the wild inspiration behind the tarot-themed collection, and why—despite his growing profile—he opted not to exhibit at a major brand-name gallery.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Midnight Society’s Rob Bowling Talks Deadrop Launch and Working With Dr. Disrespect]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/yIc3fKH2/midnight-societys-rob-bowling-talks-deadrop-launch-and-working-with-dr-disrespect</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/yIc3fKH2/midnight-societys-rob-bowling-talks-deadrop-launch-and-working-with-dr-disrespect"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T21:28:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former "Call of Duty" developer Rob Bowling, now head of Midnight Society Studio, checked in with Decrypt's Kate Irwin at GDC and shared some behind-the-scenes statistics on how players are enjoying "Deadrop." The game saw 90,000 player hours over the weekend, with 97 minutes average play time per player, and their community size tripled in just a few days.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>