<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-10-24T05:18:24.218Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-10-24T05:18:24.218Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2024 Presidential Election Predictions: Ripple CEO Highlights Risks for the Crypto Market]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20081640/2024-Presidential-Election-Predictions-Ripple-CEO-Highlights-Risks-for-the-Crypto-Market</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20081640/2024-Presidential-Election-Predictions-Ripple-CEO-Highlights-Risks-for-the-Crypto-Market"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T05:11:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ahead of the 2024 U.S. general election early next month, top crypto executives, led by Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse, have expressed their willingness to work with the next government to streamline the inevitable mainstream adoption of digital assets and web3 protocols. Speaking at the DC...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 GameFi Sector Expected To Hit $301.5 Billion By 2030 – Report]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77ba2b6f8e</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/web3-gamefi-sector-expected-to-hit-301-5-billion-by-2030-report/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T05:10:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recent Nansen report revealed that the Game Finance (GameFi) sector is expected to see major growth by the decade’s end, driven by decentralized economic systems, the rise of AAA games in Web3, and the popularity growth of role-playing games (RPG).
 
 
What’s Behind Web3 GameFi’s Growth
 
Blockchain analytics firm Nansen revealed that the Web3 GameFi sector is set for major growth throughout the decade, with projections suggesting a 68% compound annual growth rate (CAGR) from 2024 to 2030.
 
This potential surge could see the sector reach $301.5 billion in the next six years, driven by decentralization, true asset ownership, in-game economies, and growing community engagement. Per the report, the decentralized nature of the blockchain offers players true ownership of in-game assets like …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rubmar Garcia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Facing a Major Breakout or Breakdown? Here’s What Experts Are Saying!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20081633/XRP-Facing-a-Major-Breakout-or-Breakdown-Heres-What-Experts-Are-Saying</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20081633/XRP-Facing-a-Major-Breakout-or-Breakdown-Heres-What-Experts-Are-Saying"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T05:06:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple’s XRP is facing a whirlwind of developments that could shape its future in the crypto landscape. From CEO Brad Garlinghouse’s bold revelations to XRP’s fluctuating price trends, there’s a lot brewing in the world of Ripple. Here’s a look at the key events that are catching the attention...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Faces Challenges as It Lags Behind Gold, Says Bloomberg Strategist]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20081503/Bitcoin-Faces-Challenges-as-It-Lags-Behind-Gold-Says-Bloomberg-Strategist</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20081503/Bitcoin-Faces-Challenges-as-It-Lags-Behind-Gold-Says-Bloomberg-Strategist"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T05:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mike McGlone, Bloomberg Intelligence's chief commodity strategist, recently shared insights on Bitcoin, gold, and their relationship with copper via his X account.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BitBoy Crypto foresees XRP flipping ETH by 2025 – Here’s why]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20081516/BitBoy-Crypto-foresees-XRP-flipping-ETH-by-2025-Heres-why</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20081516/BitBoy-Crypto-foresees-XRP-flipping-ETH-by-2025-Heres-why"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T05:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here's why BitBoy believe XRP could flip ETH by 2025 and front a 30X price rally to $15.6.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA) Struggles to Build Bullish Momentum: Will It Turn Around?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20081470/Cardano-ADA-Struggles-to-Build-Bullish-Momentum-Will-It-Turn-Around</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20081470/Cardano-ADA-Struggles-to-Build-Bullish-Momentum-Will-It-Turn-Around"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T04:58:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano price started a fresh decline below the $0.3550 zone. ADA is consolidating above $0.3400 and might attempt a recovery wave. ADA price started a downward move below the $0.3500 support level. The price is trading below $0.3550 and the 100-hourly simple moving average. There was a break...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOJ Warns Musk Over $1M Voter Giveaway in Swing States]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20081466/DOJ-Warns-Musk-Over-1M-Voter-Giveaway-in-Swing-States</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20081466/DOJ-Warns-Musk-Over-1M-Voter-Giveaway-in-Swing-States"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T04:54:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Department of Justice has warned Elon Musk’s America PAC that his $1 million giveaway to registered voters in swing states may violate federal law. Musk pledged to donate $1 million daily to randomly selected voters who sign his PAC’s petition supporting the First and Second Amendments....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[El Salvador President Nayib Bukele Donates 2 Bitcoins to Fund 1,000 Schools in Honduras]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20081465/El-Salvador-President-Nayib-Bukele-Donates-2-Bitcoins-to-Fund-1000-Schools-in-Honduras</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20081465/El-Salvador-President-Nayib-Bukele-Donates-2-Bitcoins-to-Fund-1000-Schools-in-Honduras"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T04:52:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Salvadoran President Nayib Bukele announced a donation of 2 bitcoins, valued at $133,000, to support the construction of 1,000 schools in Honduras. This donation is part of El Salvador’s ongoing initiative, where the government has been purchasing 1 BTC daily since March 16. Currently, the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Denmark to Tax Crypto Unrealized Gains Starting 2026]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20081464/Denmark-to-Tax-Crypto-Unrealized-Gains-Starting-2026</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20081464/Denmark-to-Tax-Crypto-Unrealized-Gains-Starting-2026"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T04:50:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Denmark is set to introduce a groundbreaking 42% tax on unrealized cryptocurrency gains beginning January 1, 2026. The tax will apply to assets like Bitcoin, including those acquired as far back as 2009. This move aims to treat cryptocurrencies like traditional investment assets, such as stocks...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Dips Below $67K—Is a Crash to $60K Coming?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20081452/Bitcoin-Dips-Below-67KIs-a-Crash-to-60K-Coming</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20081452/Bitcoin-Dips-Below-67KIs-a-Crash-to-60K-Coming"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T04:45:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s (BTC) price is cooling off after a spectacular rally to $69,000 last week, with analysts predicting more downward movement before a potential rebound. The leading cryptocurrency is down 4% for the week, encountering resistance as short-term sentiment turns bearish due to a bearish...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uncharted Territory: Bitcoin’s Mining Difficulty Reaches New Extremes]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77ba178856</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/uncharted-territory-bitcoins-mining-difficulty-reaches-new-extremes/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T04:32:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s difficulty has soared once again at block height 866,880, reaching a record-breaking 95.67 trillion. Meanwhile, the network’s computational power is keeping pace, operating at a blazing 729.13 exahash per second (EH/s) at the time of reporting. In the coming days, it’ll be fascinating to watch how the combination of increased difficulty and dipping prices […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple News: Will the SEC’s Civil Appeal Be Dismissed? XRP Community Celebrates]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20081405/Ripple-News-Will-the-SECs-Civil-Appeal-Be-Dismissed-XRP-Community-Celebrates</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20081405/Ripple-News-Will-the-SECs-Civil-Appeal-Be-Dismissed-XRP-Community-Celebrates"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T04:12:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ongoing legal battle between Ripple and the SEC has captured significant attention on social media, with new claims emerging almost daily. Recently, some discussions have centered around procedural aspects of the case. Key Claims Regarding the SEC’s Civil Appeal According to recent claims,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Freedom! Nigerian Court Clears Binance Exec, Orders Immediate Release]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77ba11ef94</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/freedom-nigerian-court-clears-binance-exec-orders-immediate-release/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T04:11:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tigran Gambaryan, a Binance executive who had been detained since February, has been officially cleared of all charges by the Nigerian government.
 
The Economic and Financial Crimes Commission (EFCC) requested the withdrawal of the case at the Federal High Court in Abuja during a court session on October 23, 2024.
 
This announcement was made during the session. Gambaryan, the chief of financial crime compliance at Binance and a US citizen, was previously accused of money laundering and currency manipulation. However, these accusations have been dismissed.
 
 
BREAKING: Nigerian Government Drops All Money Laundering Charges Against Binance Executive Gambaryan | Sahara Reporters https://t.co/K1fNs5KVmo pic.twitter.com/5oJ0YfImpP
 
— Sahara Reporters (@SaharaReporters) October 23, 2024
 

 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BRICS Summit 2024: China, Russia, Iran Urge for Crypto Payments in De-Dollarization Effort]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20081415/BRICS-Summit-2024-China-Russia-Iran-Urge-for-Crypto-Payments-in-De-Dollarization-Effort</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20081415/BRICS-Summit-2024-China-Russia-Iran-Urge-for-Crypto-Payments-in-De-Dollarization-Effort"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T04:04:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the sixteenth annual BRICS Summit in Kazan, Russia, several leading members discussed cryptocurrency’s role in de-dollarization. The Presidents of Russia, China, and Iran all stressed the need for new digital platforms. The core of this de-dollarization effort is BRICS Pay, a payment solution...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BTC Holder Metaplanet Raises $66M Through Stock Acquisition Rights Exercise]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20081282/BTC-Holder-Metaplanet-Raises-66M-Through-Stock-Acquisition-Rights-Exercise</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20081282/BTC-Holder-Metaplanet-Raises-66M-Through-Stock-Acquisition-Rights-Exercise"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T04:01:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest capital raise makes money available for more Bitcoin buys, with the company already holding over 861 BTC worth $57.3 million.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Layer 2 Base Mainnet Will Introduce Fault Proof on October 30]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20081221/Layer-2-Base-Mainnet-Will-Introduce-Fault-Proof-on-October-30</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20081221/Layer-2-Base-Mainnet-Will-Introduce-Fault-Proof-on-October-30"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T03:42:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Layer 2 Base mainnet will introduce fault proofs on October 30, allowing users to challenge invalid transactions without relying on third parties.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla Q3 Earnings Report Confirms its Bitcoin Holdings Remain Intact]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20081414/Tesla-Q3-Earnings-Report-Confirms-its-Bitcoin-Holdings-Remain-Intact</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20081414/Tesla-Q3-Earnings-Report-Confirms-its-Bitcoin-Holdings-Remain-Intact"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T03:42:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla’s Q3 earnings report confirms that its Bitcoin holdings remained unchanged throughout the year despite recent speculations. The company continues to hold 11,509 BTC, currently valued at around $765 million. This means Tesla is still the fourth-largest Bitcoin holder among publicly traded...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global Finance Faces a Shift as Mbridge Digital Currency Platform Challenges US Dollar]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77ba1cdd79</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/global-finance-faces-a-shift-as-mbridge-digital-currency-platform-challenges-us-dollar/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T03:40:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The People’s Bank of China emphasized the Mbridge platform’s role in improving cross-border payments through the use of central bank digital currencies (CBDCs), aiming to reduce inefficiencies and avoid new barriers. The platform, which targets underserved regions like ASEAN, could reshape global finance and challenge the U.S. dollar’s dominance while requiring careful coordination to maintain […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[El Salvador's President Nayib Bukele Donates Bitcoin To Support Funding For 1,000 Schools Through Charity Run]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20081241/El-Salvadors-President-Nayib-Bukele-Donates-Bitcoin-To-Support-Funding-For-1000-Schools-Through-Charity-Run</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20081241/El-Salvadors-President-Nayib-Bukele-Donates-Bitcoin-To-Support-Funding-For-1000-Schools-Through-Charity-Run"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T03:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[El Salvador president Nayib Bukele donated Bitcoin (CRYPTO: BTC) to well-known philanthropist Shin Fujiyama to help raise funds to build schools in the Central American nation of Honduras. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Massive DOGE Rally Incoming? Analyst Forecasts Parabolic 5,220% Surge]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20081298/Massive-DOGE-Rally-Incoming-Analyst-Forecasts-Parabolic-5220-Surge</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20081298/Massive-DOGE-Rally-Incoming-Analyst-Forecasts-Parabolic-5220-Surge"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T03:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A popular cryptocurrency analyst has recently suggested that the price of the meme-inspired cryptocurrency Dogecoin ($DOGE) could see a massive price increase in the near future, based on historical data. The pseudonymous analyst going by Zer0 on the microblogging platform X (formerly known as...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple ‘made a mistake’ not talking to regulators early, says CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20081189/Ripple-made-a-mistake-not-talking-to-regulators-early-says-CEO</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20081189/Ripple-made-a-mistake-not-talking-to-regulators-early-says-CEO"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T03:12:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple should have engaged with US regulators a lot earlier, says the firm’s CEO Brad Garlinghouse, who added it’s now “trying to make up for lost time.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple CEO Confident That A Spot XRP ETF Is Inevitable]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20081187/Ripple-CEO-Confident-That-A-Spot-XRP-ETF-Is-Inevitable</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20081187/Ripple-CEO-Confident-That-A-Spot-XRP-ETF-Is-Inevitable"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T03:10:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse believes a spot XRP ETF is inevitable, citing strong demand for cryptocurrency ETFs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP News : Why CEO Of Ripple Was De-Banked]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20081045/XRP-News-Why-CEO-Of-Ripple-Was-De-Banked</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20081045/XRP-News-Why-CEO-Of-Ripple-Was-De-Banked"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T02:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple’s CEO, Brad Garlinghouse, dropped a bit of a bombshell recently. At DC Fintech Week, he shared that he was personally de-banked by Citigroup Inc., a bank he’s been with for 25 years. Why? Because of his ties to cryptocurrency. It’s not just him though. This reflects a growing trend where...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best VPNs for Crypto Trading: Online Security and Privacy Assurance]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20081043/Best-VPNs-for-Crypto-Trading-Online-Security-and-Privacy-Assurance</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20081043/Best-VPNs-for-Crypto-Trading-Online-Security-and-Privacy-Assurance"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T02:54:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If your crypto portfolio is worth at least $100, you should care about the security of your assets. Every crypto trader, especially active in the DeFi space, should pay attention to their security and privacy to forestall cybercriminals. Something as common as a VPN (Virtual Private Network) can...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Number of Bitcoin Whales Jumps to Highest Since January 2021]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77ba19585c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/10/24/number-of-bitcoin-whales-jumps-to-highest-since-january-2021/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T02:51:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whale Entities are clusters of crypto wallet addresses held by a single network participant holding least 1,000 BTC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Senator Claims BRICS Push to Ditch US Dollar Could Boost USD Global Dominance]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77ba1a4aef</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/senator-claims-brics-push-to-ditch-us-dollar-could-boost-usd-global-dominance/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T02:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Senator Bill Hagerty has warned of growing efforts by BRICS nations to bypass the U.S. dollar’s dominance but argued this could ultimately strengthen the status of the dollar as the world’s reserve currency. He emphasized the need for a regulatory framework to boost demand for U.S. treasuries and stablecoins, while his stablecoin legislation aims […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Base, Arbitrum, And Ethereum L2s Will Have To Buy Decentralization, Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77ba04dbaa</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/base-arbitrum-ethereum-l2s-buy-decentralization/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T02:12:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After years of refinement, Ethereum, the world’s largest smart contracts platform, is scaling. However, it does not scale in the way most decentralization purists desire. The network, trying to accommodate all its users, now relies mainly on off-chain solutions using roll-up techniques to process more transactions and relieve the mainnet.
 
The Ethereum Layer-2 Boom
 
The result has seen a boom with layer-2 platforms. According to L2Beat, all these off-chain solutions scaling Ethereum manage over $37 billion worth of assets. The largest of them all is Arbitrum, which controls more than $13 billion.
 
 
Despite the boom, the question of decentralization still lingers. Arbitrum, Base, and other layer-2s on Ethereum might be gaining traction, but most have yet to decentralize.
 
 
For example…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dalmas Ngetich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bounces Above $67,000 as Traders Navigate a ‘Liquidity Hunt’ Post-Surge]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287980</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287980/bitcoin-bounces-back-above-67000-as-traders-navigate-liquidity-hunt-post-surge"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T02:12:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin has steadied above $67,000, with experts predicting a retest of $70,000 as the U.S. election and upcoming NFP data shape market bias.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Sinclair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brazil Calls for Unified BRICS Financial System, Challenging Western Hegemony]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77ba07b6b3</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/brazil-calls-for-unified-brics-financial-system-challenging-western-hegemony/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T01:40:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brazilian President Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva has urged the creation of a unified financial system among BRICS nations. He emphasized the need for alternative monetary relations. Egyptian President Abdel Fattah el-Sisi echoed this sentiment, advocating for financial settlements in national currencies, stressing cooperation within BRICS. Lula Champions Unified BRICS Financial System Brazilian President Luiz […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Avg Profitability Index Hits 200% – Active Profit-Taking On The Horizon?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77ba01e947</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-avg-profitability-index-hits-200-active-profit-taking-on-the-horizon/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T01:14:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following the Federal Reserve’s decision to cut interest rates in September, Bitcoin has been volatile yet predominantly bullish. Analysts and investors are now waiting patiently for the next leg up, as BTC recently stopped at the $69,400 mark and is finding strong support around $66,000. This level is key, as it could determine Bitcoin’s next price movement.
 
 
Key data from CryptoQuant reveals that the Bitcoin Average Profitability Index is currently at 202%, indicating that the price is roughly twice the realized price. This metric provides confidence to investors and traders who expect Bitcoin to continue rising. 
 
With profitability still well below levels that typically trigger mass profit-taking, it suggests more room for BTC to grow before significant selling pressure emerges. 
 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Villafuerte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Privacy Bill Aims to End Government’s Grip on Americans’ Financial Data]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77ba0cdb21</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/new-privacy-bill-aims-to-end-governments-grip-on-americans-financial-data/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T00:38:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Saving Privacy Act, aimed at curbing federal surveillance of Americans’ financial data, is gaining momentum. Backers argue the government has overreached, violating privacy rights without effectively targeting criminals. Provisions include repealing key financial reporting laws and strengthening Fourth Amendment protections. Supporters highlight the need to protect personal financial data while enabling authorities to pursue […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla Holds Bitcoin Steady After BTC Wallet Transfers Spark Speculation]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77ba0a6d21</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/tesla-holds-bitcoin-steady-after-btc-wallet-transfers-spark-speculation/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T23:35:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla has reported stable bitcoin holdings for Q3 2024, despite transferring its 11,509 BTC to new wallets. The move, which sparked speculation but did not signal a sale, suggests routine security measures. Tesla posted $25.2 billion in revenue and $2.7 billion in profits, driven by record vehicle deliveries and a 52% surge in energy storage. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tudor-Jones Bullish on BTC, Dollar keeps Rising, GOAT hits $750M]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/J2wZRRcf/tudor-jones-bullish-on-btc-dollar-keeps-rising-goat-hits-750m</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/J2wZRRcf/tudor-jones-bullish-on-btc-dollar-keeps-rising-goat-hits-750m"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T23:31:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All roads lead to inflation, own BTC: Tudor-Jones. Saylor plans to give away BTC ‘to civilisation’. India considering banning crypto for CBDC. Metaplanet raises $66m, likely to buy BTC. Peter Todd goes into hiding after Satoshi claims. SEC makes crypto examination priority in 2025. SOL again flips ETH for 24hr fees. AVAX release debit card for payments. Nigeria drops charges against Binance exec. Vitalik writes about future of The Verge for ETH. Buenos Aires builds decentralised ZK ID solution. Azura launches DeFi trading platform. Farcaster makes just $10k in October. LINK announces private transactions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Clash: Vitalik Buterin Labels Michael Saylor’s Bitcoin Comments ‘Batshit Insane’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77bbf40196</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/buterin-labels-saylors-bitcoin-comments-batshit-insane/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T23:19:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The remarks made by a popular executive from a Bitcoin development company, advocating for large financial institutions to take custody of Bitcoin, disappointed the cryptocurrency community.
 
MicroStrategy CEO Michael Saylor is now at the center of strong criticisms after saying that it would be better for Bitcoin to be in the custody of “too big to fail” banks than self-custody.
 
 
The Contentious Remark
 
Saylor, in a podcast interview, dissuaded investors and traders from the Bitcoin self-custody approach while putting forward the idea of custodianship through large financial institutions like banks.
 
He believes that large and established financial institutions can better serve Bitcoin holders because they are designed to secure financial assets.
 
 
In the said interview, Saylor de…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vietnam Unveils Ambitious Strategy to Become Regional Blockchain Hub]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77bbf07b0b</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/vietnam-unveils-ambitious-strategy-to-become-regional-blockchain-hub/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T22:35:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Vietnamese government has unveiled a strategy to make Vietnam a leader in blockchain technology in Southeast Asia. The strategy includes building blockchain brands, establishing testing centers, and developing human resources. The government aims to achieve these goals through a five-step action plan, which includes legal reforms, ecosystem development, and international collaboration. Boosting Vietnam’s Blockchain […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple CEO Says Kamala Harris Taking 'Nuanced' Approach to Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287968</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287968/ripple-ceo-nuanced-crypto-approach-kamala-harris"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T22:30:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brad Garlinghouse painted Kamala Harris as a savvy Silicon Valley insider with a "nuanced" approach to crypto, while saying Donald Trump came out "aggressively" on the subject.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ECB’s Anti-Bitcoin Propaganda Debunked In Scathing Academic Rebuttal]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77bbf1f016</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ecb-anti-bitcoin-propaganda-debunked/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T22:21:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a response to the latest anti-Bitcoin paper by the European Central Bank (ECB), a new academic paper titled “Challenging Bias in the ECB’s Bitcoin Analysis” has been published. Authored by Murray A. Rudd, along with co-authors Allen Farrington, Freddie New, and Dennis Porter, the paper offers a comprehensive critique of a recent working paper by ECB officials Ulrich Bindseil and Jürgen Schaaf.
 
Dennis Porter, CEO and founder of Satoshi Action Fund, who initiated the paper with a few days announced the publication on X, stating, “₿REAKING: Full Academic Rebuttal to the anti-Bitcoin ECB paper officially published.”
 
The original ECB paper by Bindseil and Schaaf portrays BTC as a speculative asset with limited intrinsic value and significant risks. It criticized BTC’s volatility, lack of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Citibank Debanked Ripple's Brad Garlinghouse Due to Crypto, Exec Says]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77bbfd1d17</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/10/23/citibank-debanked-ripples-brad-garlinghouse-due-to-crypto-exec-says/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T21:51:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The chief of Ripple, Brad Garlinghouse, recounted his own brush with the U.S. government's pressure on banks to be wary of digital assets, saying Citi dumped him.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Self-Custody vs. Custodial Bitcoin: A Lesson From FDR ‘Forbidding the Hoarding of Gold’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77bbfdf235</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/self-custody-vs-custodial-bitcoin-a-lesson-from-fdr-forbidding-the-hoarding-of-gold/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T21:44:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Saylor, the founder of Microstrategy, recently downplayed concerns about bitcoin confiscations, calling them a “myth.” He referenced Executive Order 6102, which compelled U.S. citizens to surrender their gold, to support his stance. However, historical evidence paints a different picture, especially regarding voluntary compliance. The gold confiscations of 1933 highlight why self-custody of bitcoin, rather […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GOAT Bot's Chat With Coinbase's Brian Armstrong Triggers Price Explosion in 'Russell' Meme coin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287950</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287950/goat-bots-chat-coinbase-ceo-triggers-price-explosion-russell-memecoin"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T21:42:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A seemingly casual exchange between Coinbase's Brian Armstrong and an online Twitter bot has sent one meme coin soaring.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ledn’s Lending Leap: Record $1.67 Billion in Loans Signals Institutional Confidence in Digital Assets]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77bbf964fc</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ledns-lending-leap-record-1-67-billion-in-loans-signals-institutional-confidence-in-digital-assets/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T21:12:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ledn, a crypto lending platform, has announced $1.67 billion in loans processed year-to-date (YTD) as of Q3 2024, marking a milestone since its inception in 2018. This total includes $258.7 million in retail loans and $1.41 billion in institutional loans, with Q3 alone accounting for over $506 million in digital asset loans. The retail sector […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP ETFs 'Inevitable' After Bitcoin and Ethereum Approvals: Ripple CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287921</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287921/xrp-etfs-inevitable-bitcoin-ethereum-ripple-ceo"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T20:54:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse believes that an XRP exchange-traded fund will get approved by the SEC following recent filings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Say Goodbye to External Bridges: Uniswap’s Newest Feature Is Here]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77bbe60c07</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/say-goodbye-to-external-bridges-uniswaps-newest-feature-is-here/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T20:31:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Uniswap Labs has rolled out permissionless bridging, giving users the ability to transfer assets across nine blockchain networks directly through the Uniswap interface and wallet. This new feature aims to streamline cross-chain transfers, removing the need for third-party bridges. Uniswap Introduces Permissionless Bridging for Multi-Network Asset Transfers Uniswap users now have the option to bridge […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Character AI Imposes New Safety Rules After Teen User Commits Suicide]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287925</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287925/character-ai-safety-rules-teen-user-commits-suicide"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T20:26:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A 14 year old fell in love with a Game of Thrones-themed chatbot, then shot himself, in the latest incident to plague Character AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Saalfield</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kamala Harris Whale Shakes Up Polymarket Election Odds With $2 Million Position]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287926</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287926/kamala-harris-whale-shakes-up-polymarket-election-odds-with-2-million-position"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T20:26:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A newly registered Polymarket user backed Vice President Kamala Harris with $2 million, boosting her odds in the U.S. election showdown.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Russia With Fraud: ‘Crypto Queen’ Diverts Funds To Ukrainian Army]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77bbe6e37b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/from-russia-with-fraud-crypto-queen-diverts-funds-to-ukrainian-army/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T20:24:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A detained social media influencer could be heading to a Russian penitentiary and staying there for about 10 years to live out her sentence for committing crypto fraud. Valeria Fedyakina, dubbed the “Crypto Queen,” is at the center of multiple charges of large-scale swindling activities that reportedly included funding the Ukrainian military amid the ongoing war between Ukraine and Russia.
 

 
 
 
‘Crypto Queen’ Denies The Allegations
 
Fedyakina refuted the swindling allegations being thrown against her by RIC, claiming she did not commit any fraud, but she told Russian media she supports the invasion of Ukraine by her nation.
 
Her defense attorneys added that Fedyakina has no history of conviction for any crime, arguing that her client might be a victim of conspiracy.
 
In September 20…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Altcoin Will Crush the Cardano and XRP Price Performance in 2025, Says Top Altcoin Trader]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77bbe6e379</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/this-altcoin-will-crush-the-cardano-and-xrp-price-performance-in-2025-says-top-altcoin-trader/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T20:24:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a bold forecast for 2025, a top altcoin trader predicts that RCO Finance will outshine Cardano and XRP in price performance. Rooted in the growing demand for its advanced features and highly successful presale, RCOF emerges as the next big crypto sensation.
 
This analysis provides insights into its potential to disrupt the market and paints a picture of a rising altcoin primed to challenge the status quo.
 
Why RCOF May Outperform Both the Cardano and XRP Price Projections 
As RCO Finance (RCOF) grows in popularity, it is attracting not only seasoned trading professionals but also those who have yet to encounter cryptocurrencies. For this reason, analysts believe RCOF will surpass the estimated predictions for Cardano and the XRP price by 2025.
 
Fueled by the growing adoption of its f…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Meme Coin Factory Releases Video Feature, Immediately Goes Horribly Wrong]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287919</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287919/solana-pump-fun-video-feature-goes-wrong"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T20:08:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pump.fun's new tokenized video feature was almost immediately misused to share child sexual abuse material, which has been removed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Tomarket' Reveals Airdrop Details as Telegram Game Tops 40 Million Players]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287912</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287912/tomarket-airdrop-details-telegram-game"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T18:07:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram game Tomarket has shared more airdrop criteria ahead of next week’s TOMA token launch on The Open Network (TON).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Hitting $200,000 in 2025 Is a 'Conservative' Bet: Bernstein]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287901</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287901/bitcoin-200k-next-year-conservative-bet-bernstein"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T17:13:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bullish Bernstein analysts now think Bitcoin will hit $200,000 per coin by the end of 2025—and say that's a "conservative" projection.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Is Today’s 'Major' Telegram Game Puzzle Durov Combo]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286896</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/here-is-todays-major-telegram-puzzle-durov-combo"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T15:15:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking to complete Major’s daily Pavel Durov puzzle on Telegram? Here’s the solution updated on Tuesday, October 22.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Is Today’s 'Tomarket' Telegram Game Daily Combo]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286780</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/here-is-todays-tomarket-telegram-game-daily-combo"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T15:10:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram game Tomarket is handing out free tomatoes and bonus items ahead of the airdrop. Here’s the combo for Wednesday, October 23.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Is Today’s 'Captain Tsubasa: Rivals' Telegram Game Daily Combo]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=250928</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/captain-tsubasa-rivals-telegram-game-daily-combo"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T15:06:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anime soccer game Captain Tsubasa: Rivals gives out 5 million free daily balls ahead of the TON token airdrop. Here’s the combo for Wednesday, October 23.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Assassin’s Creed’ Maker Ubisoft Releases First Original NFT Game ‘Champions Tactics’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287890</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287890/ubisoft-releases-champions-tactics-nft-game"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T14:54:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ubisoft’s Champions Tactics: Grimoria Chronicles, built around NFTs on the Oasys network, is now available to play on PC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin: Michael Saylor's Bitcoin Self-Custody Comments Are 'Batshit Insane']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287881</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287881/vitalik-buterin-michael-saylors-bitcoin-self-custody-comments-are-batshit-insane"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T14:01:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum co-founder Vitalik Buterin has criticized the MicroStrategy co-founder’s recent remarks on crypto self-custody.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Stabilizes as Analysts Flag an Accumulation Period]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287869</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287869/bitcoin-price-stabilize-accumulation-period"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T13:02:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The market needs time to digest higher bond yields, "before Bitcoin can resume its upward movement," 10x Research wrote in a note.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain.com Execs Face Scrutiny for Not Filing Accounts in UK]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287861</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287861/blockchain-com-execs-face-scrutiny-for-not-filing-accounts-in-uk"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T12:35:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["We have sorted all necessary documents related to this entirely administrative matter," a Blockchain.com spokesperson said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nigeria Releases Detained Binance Exec, Drops Charges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287862</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287862/nigeria-releases-detained-binance-exec"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T11:12:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nigeria has withdrawn its charges against Tigran Gambaryan and will release him, citing his poor health.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott,Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stable Diffusion 3.5: Stability AI Redeems Itself With New Models and Expanded Features]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287807</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287807/stable-diffusion-3-5-stability-ai-redeems-itself-with-new-models-and-expanded-features"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T00:07:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After its stumble with Stable Diffusion 3 Medium, Stability AI is back on track with Stable Diffusion 3.5, offering customizable models that are uncensored, fast, and accessible for everyone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scroll Airdrop Farmers Gripe Over Ethereum Layer-2 Token Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287793</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287793/scroll-airdrop-farmers-gripe-ethereum-token-launch"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T22:29:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum layer-2 network Scroll just launched its token—but like the recent Hamster Kombat airdrop, some recipients aren't happy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk's Tesla Moved $776 Million in Bitcoin, But Is Still in Control of Wallets: Arkham]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287790</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287790/elon-musk-tesla-moved-bitcoin-still-control"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T21:52:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Electric car company Tesla moved its stash of Bitcoin last week, but data firm Arkham believes that Elon Musk's company is still holding.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic Unleashes New Claude 3.5 Sonnet: A Model Smart Enough to Take Over Your Computer]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287767</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287767/anthropic-unleashes-claude-3-5-sonnet-smart-enough-take-over-computer"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T21:20:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AI powerhouse just dropped major updates to its models, including a feature that lets its AI physically control computers, marking a shift from chat-only interactions to hands-on automation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bipartisan Hope Grows That Crypto Laws Will Pass Before Year's End]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287785</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287785/bipartisan-hope-grows-crypto-laws-pass"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T21:19:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Republicans and Democrats across the House and Senate are increasingly convinced that key pieces of crypto legislation could soon become law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop Meme Stock Craze Prompted Market 'Plumbing' Changes, Says SEC Chair Gensler]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287764</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287764/gamestop-meme-stock-market-plumbing-changes"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T20:33:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC embraced shorter settlement times after the GameStop short squeeze—but crypto already does 24/7 markets and quick trade completions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A $20 Alternative to Expensive Hearing Aids]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287714</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287714/cheap-alternative-expensive-hearing-aids"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T19:43:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quantum Senses aims to offer an affordable and durable alternative to expensive hearing aids that's made from fully recycled materials.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything You Need to Know Ahead of the 'X Empire' Telegram Game Airdrop]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287756</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287756/x-empire-telegram-game-airdrop-explainer"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T18:47:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk-themed game X Empire is launching its token on The Open Network this week. Here's what you need to know about the airdrop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SOL Outperforms, 10y Rises above 4.2%, AI Tokens Dominate flows]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zu7HXBIc/sol-outperforms-10y-rises-above-42-ai-tokens-dominate-flows</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zu7HXBIc/sol-outperforms-10y-rises-above-42-ai-tokens-dominate-flows"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T17:41:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC: 67k (-2%), ETH: 2620 (-4%), SOL: 166 (0%). Top Gainers: APT, UNI, HNT, POPCAT, RUNE, KAS. BTC drops, SOL continues to outperform. PumpFun has sold $78m of SOL fees so far. Raydium flips ETH for 24hr fees. Scroll launches at $1.2bn FDV, disappoints. Crypto only really used for drug deals: Fed’s Kashkari. VanEck adds staking to SOL ETPs in Europe. LINK announces successful results from SWIFT trial. Brevan Howard trades most crypto from UAE. Japanese parties court crypto tax cuts. XRP co-founder donates $10m to Kamala. CFTC chair says agency is ‘handcuffed’ on crypto. Transak exposes 92k customers’ data. Sky may rebrand back to MakerDAO.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SOL Breaks out, Stripe Acquires Bridge, GIGA hits $600M]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/35JgCoNO/sol-breaks-out-stripe-acquires-bridge-giga-hits-600m</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/35JgCoNO/sol-breaks-out-stripe-acquires-bridge-giga-hits-600m"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T17:30:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC briefly tops $70k as OI tops $40bn. SOL outperforms, DEX volume eclipses ETH + L2s. SOLETH has highest weekly close ever. Pension giant L&G look to test tokenisation. BTC hash rate hits ATH. Stripe acquires stablecoin company Bridge for $1.1bn. PumpFun hints at upcoming token. GOAT drops then rebounds as authenticity questioned. GIGA hits new ATH of $600m, FROG hits $250m. MEW up 15% after Upbit listing. Jaypeg called out for misleading promotions. ACK editions sell for $290k.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['All Roads Lead to Inflation' Says Billionaire Bitcoin Bull Paul Tudor Jones]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287751</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287751/billionaire-bitcoin-bull-paul-tudor-jones-inflation"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T17:29:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Billionaire investor Paul Tudor Jones is worried about U.S. federal debt—and sees inflation coming as a result. He's betting on Bitcoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Should You Play 'Dookey Dash: Unclogged'? The Bored Ape Endless Runner With Big Prizes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287740</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287740/dookey-dash-unclogged-game-review"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T16:50:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[REVIEW: Dookey Dash: Unclogged drops Bored Apes into the sewers for an endless runner with $1 million up for grabs. Here's our take.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Stubbs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stripe $1.1 Billion Bridge Deal Validates Stablecoin Growth, Says Bernstein]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287730</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287730/stripe-bridge-deal-validates-stablecoins-bernstein"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T16:32:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Stripe acquisition of Bridge for a staggering $1.1 billion has underscored the growth of stablecoins as a payment method, says Bernstein.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto CEO Loses $450K to 'Best Friend' After Connecting to His WiFi]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287425</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287425/crypto-ceo-loses-450k-wifi"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T15:37:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A ‘proximity breach’ is a rising trend, when someone exploits someone close to them to steal money—this time through a WiFi network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet HuggingChat: The Free Open-Source Chatbot That's Ready to Rival ChatGPT]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287571</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287571/meet-huggingchat-free-open-source-chatbot"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T15:21:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HuggingChat offers fully open-source alternatives to everything the best chatbots have to offer, including custom assistants, model versatility, internet connection, and multimodality.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentraland Launches Revamped Virtual World with Enhanced Performance, Engaging Features, and Future-Ready Architecture]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287706</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287706/decentraland-launches-revamped-virtual-world-with-enhanced-performance-engaging-features-and-future-ready-architecture"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T15:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Los Angeles, USA, 22nd October 2024, GamingWire]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GamingWire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Protocol Elmnts Launches Tokenized Mineral Rights Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287677</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287677/solana-elmnts-tokenized-mineral-rights-platform"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T13:08:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Energy market analytics company RBN Energy estimates that mineral and royalty interests amount to $700 billion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Napolitano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mark Cuban Dismisses Polymarket Election Odds as Result of 'Foreign Money']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287676</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287676/mark-cuban-dismisses-polymarket-election-odds-as-result-of-foreign-money"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T12:57:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The billionaire isn’t the only one who has questioned the reliability of the crypto betting platform’s predictions in recent weeks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will McCurdy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Saylor Says He'll Give Away His Bitcoin—Like Satoshi Nakamoto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287667</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287667/bitcoin-billionaire-michael-saylor-satoshi-nakamoto"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T12:38:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Just like Satoshi left a million Bitcoin to the universe, so I’m leaving whatever I’ve got to the civilization,” the MicroStrategy co-founder said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vismaya V</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Faces Resistance as Analysts Now Weigh Pre-Election Consolidation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287647</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287647/bitcoin-price-resistance-analysts-now-predict-pre-election-consolidation"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T11:50:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One U.S.-based market research firm still has a cautious outlook, maintaining a "neutral" rating on both Bitcoin and Ethereum.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Huge week for BTC ETFs, Crypto now through Venmo, Memes Dominate Gainers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rLpBnnaQ/huge-week-for-btc-etfs-crypto-now-through-venmo-memes-dominate-gainers</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rLpBnnaQ/huge-week-for-btc-etfs-crypto-now-through-venmo-memes-dominate-gainers"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T19:24:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETFs see biggest inflow week since July. BlackRock ETF sees $1bn inflows in a week. Venmo can now be used to buy crypto on Moonpay. SEC’s XRP appeal doesn’t challenge security status. Worldcoin rebrands to World with new orb. EigenLayer X account compromised. FBI arrests hacker of SEC X account. SCB in Thailand adopts stablecoins for transfers. DBS in Singapore adopts ‘token services’. Trump family to get 75% of WLFL revenue. Scroll team accused of owning sybil addresses. STX Nakamoto upgrade to happen next week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Majors Fall 1 to 2%, A New Tiger takes to the Charts, Van Eck teases Big Web3 Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/a6Tm7OGW/majors-fall-1-to-2-a-new-tiger-takes-to-the-charts-van-eck-teases-big-web3-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/a6Tm7OGW/majors-fall-1-to-2-a-new-tiger-takes-to-the-charts-van-eck-teases-big-web3-gaming"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T17:42:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lucky GOAT memecoin trader turned $5,000 into $1.5M during GOAT's run to $300M. A new memecoin based on Disney Park's new baby tiger "Bakso" was a top mover on Wednesday, running to $10M (now $6M). Crypto majors fall 1-2%, memes red across board. a16z calls 2024 crypto's biggest year yet in "State of Crypto" report. Vitalik publishes part 2 of blog outlining ETH's future. Van Eck teases big bet on Parallel and web3 gaming. Huge day for digital art with 4 marquee mints seeing success.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hamster Kombat Season 2 Teaser]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/qcvjjJxN/hamster-kombat-season-2-teaser</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/qcvjjJxN/hamster-kombat-season-2-teaser"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T12:03:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here's a first look at Season 2 of Telegram tap-to-earn game Hamster Kombat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BTC hits $68K, Trump odds Continue to Rise, GOAT nears $300M]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/c88qN8eB/btc-hits-68k-trump-odds-continue-to-rise-goat-nears-300m</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/c88qN8eB/btc-hits-68k-trump-odds-continue-to-rise-goat-nears-300m"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T18:31:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC hits $68k as ETF inflows continue to soar. Open Interest at CME hits ATH, funding still low. Tesla moves $750m BTC to new wallet. Canary applies for Litcoin ETF, LTC up 8%. Grayscale asks SEC to convert altcoin fund to ETF. Kraken integrates with EigenLayer for restaking. ‘Network state’ Praxis raises $525m for new city. Trump project raises only $11m so far. a16z founders donate $2.5m to Trump PAC. TikTok accused of being crypto exchange in UK. Gotbit CEO arrested in Portugal. Perplexity AI launches finance platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ETF Inflows Soar, Kamala Courts Crypto, TURBO Nears $1BN!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zn2lboMV/etf-inflows-soar-kamala-courts-crypto-turbo-nears-1bn</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zn2lboMV/etf-inflows-soar-kamala-courts-crypto-turbo-nears-1bn"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T18:22:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETFs see $800m inflows in 2-days, huge volume. ETF inflows may be linked to Trump odds: CoinShares. Bitcoin will rival housing market as asset class: Fink. Vitalik proposes drop to 1ETH to become validator. Kamala reveals pro-crypto policies. Kamala mocked for linking crypto to race. Hyperliquid announces HYPE token coming. PUFFER airdrop claim goes live. Tether considering lending to commodities trader. Man takes $500m lost Bitcoin case to court. Google removes crypto prices from search. SUI Foundation denies $400m insider selling. UAE approves $AED stablecoin. Bitget wallet now only behind Binance for downloads.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BTC hits 2-week High, China Stocks Rally again, GOAT hits $120M]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/0V0rYhMX/btc-hits-2-week-high-china-stocks-rally-again-goat-hits-120m</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/0V0rYhMX/btc-hits-2-week-high-china-stocks-rally-again-goat-hits-120m"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T14:09:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC hits 2-week high as China stocks rise. SUI breaks into the top 15 coins. $1.3bn ETH might be sold from PlusToken scam. S. Korea may approve BTC & ETH ETFs this month. Australia launches first ETH ETF. Samara to buy BTC with $33m bond. Altcoins to see $500m unlocks this week. Vitalik writes blog on the future of ETH. Grayscale reveals 35 altcoins considered for funds. Ethena proposes SOL for USDe collateral. Only one Binance launchpad coin up this year. AVAX summit begins this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Falls Ahead of CPI, Stripe Reinstates Crypto, Fed Charges Market-makers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/aYgFvZqj/crypto-falls-ahead-of-cpi-stripe-reinstates-crypto-fed-charges-market-makers</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/aYgFvZqj/crypto-falls-ahead-of-cpi-stripe-reinstates-crypto-fed-charges-market-makers"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T07:29:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Majors drop despite stocks hitting ATHs. Stripe reinstates crypto payments. Crypto settlements near $20bn in 2024. S. Korea to review ban on BTC ETFs. US charges market makers for market manipulation. FBI created their own coin to ensnare targets. Vitalik ‘outside pick’ for Nobel Prize. Trump family token to built on Aave stack. $16m OP tokens allocated to superchain users. Wisdomtree debuts debit card for on-chain fund. 47% of hedge funds have crypto exposure. Argentina overtakes Brazil for crypto inflows. Tucker interviews Ryan Salame over FTX.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Todd ‘revealed’ as Satoshi, Google may be Broken-up, Murad’s Wallets Doxxed]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pLw8b2d2/todd-revealed-as-satoshi-google-may-be-broken-up-murads-wallets-doxxed</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pLw8b2d2/todd-revealed-as-satoshi-google-may-be-broken-up-murads-wallets-doxxed"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T07:29:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC will be range bound until election: Bernstein. TAO & memecoins dominate mindshare. Peter Todd ‘revealed’ as Satoshi by HBO. US government able to sell $4.4bn Silk Road BTC. Ireland unable to access $378m seized BTC. SOL could do 5x if Trump wins: StanChart. Coinbase integrates Taproot addresses for BTC. Canary Capital applies for XRP ETF. S. Korea to regulate stablecoin transfers. CryptoCom files countersuit against SEC. Babylon fills cap with 22k BTC. Scroll airdrop coming Oct 22nd. USDC goes live on SUI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bounces from $59K, Tesla unveils Robotaxis, Memecoins Outperform]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cyJj6tWj/bitcoin-bounces-from-59k-tesla-unveils-robotaxis-memecoins-outperform</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cyJj6tWj/bitcoin-bounces-from-59k-tesla-unveils-robotaxis-memecoins-outperform"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T07:29:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC briefly dips under $59k, $160m liquidations. Mt Gox extends repayment plan by 1 year. Uniswap plans L2 for DeFi. SEC sues crypto trading firm Cumberland. Binomial sues SEC over futures trading. SEC’s Uyeda criticises agency’s policy. Justin Sun named prime minister of Liberland. MicroStrategy wants to become BTC bank. Binance pre-market trading goes live. Nearly 50% of US investors want crypto ETFs. Whale phished for $35m crypto. Ethena invests $46m in RWA funds. Trump’s crypto project aims to raise $300m.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentraland Desktop Client Preview]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qqzvDcTC/decentraland-desktop-client-preview</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qqzvDcTC/decentraland-desktop-client-preview"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T15:53:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum metaverse game Decentraland has shared an exclusive look at the visual and performance upgrades coming via its new desktop client.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Trader Murad Mahmudov talks about the Supercycle and how he chooses Meme Coins.]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Hj3nDp7G/crypto-trader-murad-mahmudov-talks-about-the-supercycle-and-how-he-chooses-meme-coins</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Hj3nDp7G/crypto-trader-murad-mahmudov-talks-about-the-supercycle-and-how-he-chooses-meme-coins"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T21:47:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Trader Murad Mahmudov talks about the Supercycle and how he chooses Meme Coins. Crypto stable, had sold off after China stocks fall. Crypto adopted faster than other tech: BlackRock. Crypto adoption to hit 8% of world population. CryptoCom recieves Wells notice from SEC. HBO documentary on Satoshi airs tonight. FTX bankruptcy plan approved by judge. Scroll airdrop may be imminent. Jupiter goes live on mobile iOS. Phantom rolls out support for Base. AAVE launches GHO on Base. Gensler may be replaced by Robinhood CLO. 87% of new token launches on SOL. National Bank of Bahrain creates BTC fund. BedRock DeFi allows BTC staking on ARB.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Memecoins take off, funding stays low, China stocks keep on rising!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/703mAYhV/memecoins-take-off-funding-stays-low-china-stocks-keep-on-rising</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/703mAYhV/memecoins-take-off-funding-stays-low-china-stocks-keep-on-rising"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T08:27:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR EP213. Memecoins take off, funding stays low, China stocks keep on rising!
Many altcoins & memecoins soar despite stable BTC. Funding rates continue to be low or negative. Crypto funds saw $147m of outflows last week. BTC remains best performing major assets this year. SUI breaks into the top 20 coins again. TAO leads top 100 away from memes, sifu shorts. $100m bridge to SOL over the last 7 days. Metaplanet buys $6.7m more BTC. ETH proposal aims to improve throughput 50%. EIGEN, OP, APT lead token unlocks this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Walrus Protocol Unlocks New Applications for Decentralized Data Storage]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kwEYLYWj/how-walrus-protocol-unlocks-new-applications-for-decentralized-data-storage</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kwEYLYWj/how-walrus-protocol-unlocks-new-applications-for-decentralized-data-storage"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T11:19:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mysten Labs Chief Scientist George Danezis joined Decrypt to talk about its new decentralized storage protocol Walrus, which promises to unlock new applications such as AI and social media, thanks to its novel Red Stuff data encoding algorithm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Coinbase Sees Crypto as a Bipartisan, 'Purple' Political Issue]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/YR2YmmwR/why-coinbase-sees-crypto-as-a-bipartisan-purple-political-issue</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/YR2YmmwR/why-coinbase-sees-crypto-as-a-bipartisan-purple-political-issue"/>
        <updated>2024-10-05T22:18:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase VP of Corporate and Business Development, Shan Aggarwal, joined Decrypt's Sander Lutz and Liz Napolitano at Messari Mainnet 2024 to discuss the exchange's efforts to grow mainstream crypto adoption—and how the changing political conversation around digital assets is rapidly playing a major role in that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Is Playing Offense—Not Just Defense—Against Crypto Crime, Says Head of Financial Investigations]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DiJ8D2Qc/binance-is-playing-offensenot-just-defenseagainst-crypto-crime-says-head-of-financial-investigations</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DiJ8D2Qc/binance-is-playing-offensenot-just-defenseagainst-crypto-crime-says-head-of-financial-investigations"/>
        <updated>2024-10-05T01:58:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nils Anderson Röed, the exchange’s global head of financial investigations, sat down with Decrypt’s Sander Lutz at Messari Mainnet 2024 to discuss how Binance is proactively dismantling criminal networks around the world, the strategy with which the crypto exchange is approaching sensitive conflicts in the Middle East, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 212 - SEEDPHRASE TALKS ART!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PJfaJNkZ/fomo-hour-212-seedphrase-talks-art</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PJfaJNkZ/fomo-hour-212-seedphrase-talks-art"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T19:29:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Payrolls Higher than expected, Bitcoin reacts hard. Crypto sank early in the week as Middle East tensions spooked markets. Powell signals two more rate cuts this year. SUI leads L1s again, nears YTD high despite large unlock. Majority of FTX repayments still months away. EIGEN becomes non-transferable, hits $6bn FDV. SEC to appeal Ripple securities law ruling. Visa launches tokenization platform for banks. SWIFT plans digital asset trial in 2025. ByBit launched trading of global stock indices. SPX, GIGA & FWOG hit ATHs, most memes fall. XCOPY to release 250 piece collection on Shape. HBO documentary claims to have identified Satoshi.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Altcoins bleed, ByBit launches stock index trading, POCHITA soars]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kYjAt3nt/altcoins-bleed-bybit-launches-stock-index-trading-pochita-soars</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kYjAt3nt/altcoins-bleed-bybit-launches-stock-index-trading-pochita-soars"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T21:11:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Altcoins sink, BTC dominance nears cycle high. BTC in ‘three blind mice’ downtrend. Tron revenue hits record $577m in Q3. ByBit to launch trading of major stock indices. Franklin Templeton launch fund on APT. SWIFT banks to trial digital assets in 2025. Aerodrome hits $1bn TVL on Base. Cronje calls out Aerodrome for copyright. ETH ICO wallet sells $47m. SEC files appeal against Ripple ruling. EIGEN falls 20% on staking rewards FUD. FTX to auction off WLD position. Half of US voters think crypto ‘important’. North Korea ‘infiltrating’ crypto industry. Snowden challenged over SOL centralisation view. Top SEC official on crypto set to depart.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>