<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-10-23T01:23:14.330Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-10-23T01:23:14.330Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano Holders Can Now Earn Passive Income: Here’s How]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77bb5a4e4c</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/cardano-holders-passive-income/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T00:45:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yoroi Wallet, a leading light wallet for Cardano, has partnered with Bring, a white-label crypto cashback platform. This collaboration aims to bridge the gap between the Cardano community and global retail, allowing users to earn ADA as cashback rewards when shopping with over 775 international retailers.
 
Passive Income For Cardano Holders
 
The upcoming integration will enable Yoroi Wallet users to receive up to 10% cashback in ADA when they shop with renowned brands such as Vaio, JBL, StockX, Samsonite, and Nubul. Users can make purchases using their credit cards or other preferred payment methods. The process is designed to be user-friendly: with a simple click on the wallet popup during checkout, users can activate the cashback feature and start accumulating ADA passively.
 
 
Exciti…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) Outshines Layer 1 Rivals In This Major Metric]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20071898/Ethereum-ETH-Outshines-Layer-1-Rivals-In-This-Major-Metric</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20071898/Ethereum-ETH-Outshines-Layer-1-Rivals-In-This-Major-Metric"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T00:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH), the second-biggest cryptocurrency, is leading other Layer-1 blockchains in a key metric. Data show soaring active addresses on the Ethereum mainnet and leading Layer-2 networks. The surge in active addresses comes despite ETH registering declining prices on the daily chart. The...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Accumulation Addresses Now Hold $194 Billion in BTC as Long-Term Investors Stack Sats at Unprecedented Pace]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20071894/Bitcoin-Accumulation-Addresses-Now-Hold-194-Billion-in-BTC-as-Long-Term-Investors-Stack-Sats-at-Unprecedented-Pace</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20071894/Bitcoin-Accumulation-Addresses-Now-Hold-194-Billion-in-BTC-as-Long-Term-Investors-Stack-Sats-at-Unprecedented-Pace"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T00:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A number of Bitcoin addresses that have “never had a Bitcoin outflow” are currently accumulating the flagship cryptocurrency at an unprecedented pace, to the point they are now holding 2.9 million BTC, worth around $194 billion at the time of writing. In a newly published report, CryptoQuant...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase CEO, Elon Musk Back Pro-Crypto Senate Challenger Against Elizabeth Warren]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77bb5b3dbf</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/coinbase-ceo-elon-musk-back-pro-crypto-senate-challenger-against-elizabeth-warren/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T00:34:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong and Tesla CEO Elon Musk have voiced their support for pro-crypto Senate candidate John Deaton in his race against Elizabeth Warren. Armstrong warned that Warren, a vocal crypto critic, has pushed harmful regulations and backed U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Chair Gary Gensler’s efforts to curb the industry. Musk signaled […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla likely still owns $780M in Bitcoin despite recent shuffle: Arkham]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20071868/Tesla-likely-still-owns-780M-in-Bitcoin-despite-recent-shuffle-Arkham</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20071868/Tesla-likely-still-owns-780M-in-Bitcoin-despite-recent-shuffle-Arkham"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T00:23:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla’s massive Bitcoin transfers initially sparked fears of a market dump, but Arkham's data suggests the assets are still under the firm's control.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elmnts Launches Tokenized Investment Platform on Solana, Backed by Oil and Gas Royalties]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20070396/Elmnts-Launches-Tokenized-Investment-Platform-on-Solana-Backed-by-Oil-and-Gas-Royalties</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20070396/Elmnts-Launches-Tokenized-Investment-Platform-on-Solana-Backed-by-Oil-and-Gas-Royalties"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T00:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elmnts' public beta introduces a compliant platform for tokenizing real-world assets, allowing investors to access oil and gas royalties through blockchain technology. Expansion into retail offerings planned for the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stable Diffusion 3.5: Stability AI Redeems Itself With New Models and Expanded Features]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287807</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287807/stable-diffusion-3-5-stability-ai-redeems-itself-with-new-models-and-expanded-features"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T00:07:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After its stumble with Stable Diffusion 3 Medium, Stability AI is back on track with Stable Diffusion 3.5, offering customizable models that are uncensored, fast, and accessible for everyone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stable Diffusion 3.5: Stability AI Redeems Itself With New Models and Expanded Features]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20071842/Stable-Diffusion-35-Stability-AI-Redeems-Itself-With-New-Models-and-Expanded-Features</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20071842/Stable-Diffusion-35-Stability-AI-Redeems-Itself-With-New-Models-and-Expanded-Features"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T00:07:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After its stumble with Stable Diffusion 3 Medium, Stability AI is back on track with Stable Diffusion 3.5, offering customizable models that are uncensored, fast, and accessible for everyone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) $3,000 Comeback Is Over, Dogecoin (DOGE) 7.7 Billion Price Peaks, Will Shiba Inu (SHIB) 40% Price Growth Continue?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20071844/Ethereum-ETH-3000-Comeback-Is-Over-Dogecoin-DOGE-77-Billion-Price-Peaks-Will-Shiba-Inu-SHIB-40-Price-Growth-Continue</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20071844/Ethereum-ETH-3000-Comeback-Is-Over-Dogecoin-DOGE-77-Billion-Price-Peaks-Will-Shiba-Inu-SHIB-40-Price-Growth-Continue"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T00:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The market is calming down after the most recent retrace]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Institutional investors now hold 20% of US-traded spot Bitcoin ETFs]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20071738/Institutional-investors-now-hold-20-of-US-traded-spot-Bitcoin-ETFs</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20071738/Institutional-investors-now-hold-20-of-US-traded-spot-Bitcoin-ETFs"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T00:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Institutional investors now hold approximately 20% of all US-traded spot Bitcoin (BTC) exchange-traded funds (ETFs), according to recent data. CryptoQuant CEO and founder Ki Young Ju revealed that the latest 13F Form filings show that institutional investors hold over 193,000 BTC via Bitcoin...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Price Breaks Out Of Symmetrical Triangle, Next Stop $3,400?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20071740/Ethereum-Price-Breaks-Out-Of-Symmetrical-Triangle-Next-Stop-3400</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20071740/Ethereum-Price-Breaks-Out-Of-Symmetrical-Triangle-Next-Stop-3400"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T00:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ethereum price has just broken out of a key symmetrical triangle pattern, signaling a potential surge to new levels above $3,000. The recent breakout is seen as a bullish indicator for the top altcoin by analysts who have closely watched the Ethereum price action for the past few months....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can Injective [INJ] reclaim the $35 level, trigger a rally?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20071734/Can-Injective-INJ-reclaim-the-35-level-trigger-a-rally</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20071734/Can-Injective-INJ-reclaim-the-35-level-trigger-a-rally"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T00:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Injective consolidates above 2021 high, aiming for bullish breakout and higher gains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analyst Predicts 75% Upside Burst for Ethereum, Sees Solana Repeating Massive 2021 Surge]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20071679/Analyst-Predicts-75-Upside-Burst-for-Ethereum-Sees-Solana-Repeating-Massive-2021-Surge</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20071679/Analyst-Predicts-75-Upside-Burst-for-Ethereum-Sees-Solana-Repeating-Massive-2021-Surge"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T00:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A closely followed crypto strategist and trader thinks Ethereum (ETH) is gearing up to ignite big breakout rallies. Pseudonymous analyst Inmortal shares a chart with his 217,500 followers on the social media platform X suggesting that Ethereum will see one final dip before sparking a 75% surge...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETFs thrive with institutional exposure at 20%]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20071677/Bitcoin-ETFs-thrive-with-institutional-exposure-at-20</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20071677/Bitcoin-ETFs-thrive-with-institutional-exposure-at-20"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T23:59:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CryptoQuant founder Ki Young Ju has disclosed that institutional investors own only 20% of all spot Bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs). The data, based on the firms’ form 13F filings, shows that they hold just over 193,000 BTC of the total 961,645 BTC held by all the spot Bitcoin ETFs as of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UAE launches DAO’s legal framework]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20071675/UAE-launches-DAOs-legal-framework</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20071675/UAE-launches-DAOs-legal-framework"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T23:50:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ras Al-Khaimah (RAK), one of the emirates in the United Arab Emirates, has introduced a new legal framework tailored for decentralized autonomous organizations (DAOs) within its free zone designated for digital assets. The DAO Association Regime (DARe) seeks to create a legal framework that is...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Whales Offloading as SOL Price Struggles]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20071662/Solana-Whales-Offloading-as-SOL-Price-Struggles</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20071662/Solana-Whales-Offloading-as-SOL-Price-Struggles"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T23:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the past 24 hours, Solana (SOL) price has been going in the red. This occurred in unison with a significant sell-off by a whale in the crypto market. Most recently, Solana has also seen the Pump.fun Fee Account sells 40,000 SOL, or about $6,680,000. This transaction is not the first one in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Billionaire Paul Tudor Jones is Long on Gold, Bitcoin: Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20071651/Billionaire-Paul-Tudor-Jones-is-Long-on-Gold-Bitcoin-Heres-Why</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20071651/Billionaire-Paul-Tudor-Jones-is-Long-on-Gold-Bitcoin-Heres-Why"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T23:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Billionaire investor Paul Tudor Jones warns of inflation due to rising U.S. debt, saying Bitcoin and gold are the solution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC’s Crypto Crackdown Questioned — Will Clear Guidance Finally Emerge?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77bb409986</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/secs-crypto-crackdown-questioned-will-clear-guidance-finally-emerge/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T23:33:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The enforcement-heavy approach of the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to crypto regulation is stifling innovation and leaving the market without clear standards, an SEC commissioner has warned. Criticizing the reliance on litigation, he argued that case-by-case enforcement delays the creation of a consistent regulatory framework, depriving investors and innovators of necessary guidance. He […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russian Crypto Exchange Regulations ‘Will Be FATF-Compliant’]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20071909/Russian-Crypto-Exchange-Regulations-Will-Be-FATF-Compliant</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20071909/Russian-Crypto-Exchange-Regulations-Will-Be-FATF-Compliant"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T23:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Moscow is set to start policing Russian crypto exchanges, and will likely look to ensure its regulations are Financial Action Task Force (FATF)-compliant.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TSMC alerts U.S. officials over Huawei’s AI chip orders]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20071637/TSMC-alerts-US-officials-over-Huaweis-AI-chip-orders</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20071637/TSMC-alerts-US-officials-over-Huaweis-AI-chip-orders"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T23:24:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Company (TSMC) has informed the U.S. government about a potential attempt to manufacture artificial intelligence (AI) chips for Huawei, a Chinese technology group, in violation of export controls. The US Department of Commerce is currently investigating whether...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analyst Now Predicts A Massive Solana Rally To $4,500]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20071671/Analyst-Now-Predicts-A-Massive-Solana-Rally-To-4500</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20071671/Analyst-Now-Predicts-A-Massive-Solana-Rally-To-4500"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T23:14:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An analyst now predicts a massive Solana rally to $4,500, a 2,500% gain as it begins to form a bullish pattern at current levels.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[India Cracks Down On Crypto: Regulators Favor CBDC In Push Vs. Bitcoin & Co.]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77bb4273d6</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/india-cracks-down-on-crypto-regulators-favor-cbdc-in-push-vs-bitcoin-co/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T23:14:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[India is leaning toward the total prohibition of private cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin and Ethereum in an attempt to regulate risk in its current volatile market.
 
The government said they will have a preference for Central Bank Digital Currencies (CBDC), as they provide all the benefits of private cryptocurrencies, without having the potential for instability or potential for misuse.
 
 
Regulators added that CBDCs don’t necessarily need to meet the goals of financial inclusion often associated with cryptocurrencies. The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) supports CBDCs as this can achieve a safer alternative that can still attain financial inclusion goals usually tied to cryptocurrency.
 
The Growing Adoption Of CBDC In India
 
In 2022, India launched its digital rupee, e₹. Introduced with ove…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Crypto Gainers Today on DEXScreener – CRAZY, FUN, FIJI]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20071636/Top-Crypto-Gainers-Today-on-DEXScreener-CRAZY-FUN-FIJI</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20071636/Top-Crypto-Gainers-Today-on-DEXScreener-CRAZY-FUN-FIJI"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T23:01:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana (SOL) meme season is returning, as meme coin trading fervour picks up once again and traders hunt for top crypto gainers today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pump Fun sells another 40,000 Solana tokens: Impact on SOL?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20071462/Pump-Fun-sells-another-40000-Solana-tokens-Impact-on-SOL</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20071462/Pump-Fun-sells-another-40000-Solana-tokens-Impact-on-SOL"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T23:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana based memecoin launchpad Pump Fun continues with its selling spree, dumping 40000 SOL tokens worth $6.68 million.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Rogan: Embracing Bitcoin Life]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20071594/Joe-Rogan-Embracing-Bitcoin-Life</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20071594/Joe-Rogan-Embracing-Bitcoin-Life"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T23:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even Joe Rogan knows Bitcoin is the only cryptoBrought to you by Bitcoinwell.com a bitcoin-only platform on a mission to enable independence.#bitcoin #bitcoinnews #shortsopen]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinshares Opens New York Office Amid Ambitious US Expansion Plans]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77bb4e8be7</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/coinshares-opens-new-york-office-amid-ambitious-us-expansion-plans/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T22:32:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinshares International has opened an office in New York City, marking a key step in its strategy to expand in the United States. The company aims to bolster its presence in the U.S. financial market through this move and recent acquisitions. Coinshares’ New Office Signals Major U.S. Push According to the announcement, the New York […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scroll Airdrop Farmers Gripe Over Ethereum Layer-2 Token Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287793</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287793/scroll-airdrop-farmers-gripe-ethereum-token-launch"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T22:29:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum layer-2 network Scroll just launched its token—but like the recent Hamster Kombat airdrop, some recipients aren't happy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk's Tesla Moved $776 Million in Bitcoin, But Is Still in Control of Wallets: Arkham]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287790</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287790/elon-musk-tesla-moved-bitcoin-still-control"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T21:52:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Electric car company Tesla moved its stash of Bitcoin last week, but data firm Arkham believes that Elon Musk's company is still holding.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘All Roads Lead to Inflation’ — Why Legendary Investor Paul Tudor Jones Is Betting on Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77bb4bfe43</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/all-roads-lead-to-inflation-why-legendary-investor-paul-tudor-jones-is-betting-on-bitcoin/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T21:42:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Veteran investor Paul Tudor Jones shared his thoughts on CNBC this past Tuesday, confidently stating that he’s sticking with hard money like gold and bitcoin. In his view, any other option leads straight to inflation. What’s Driving Paul Tudor Jones’ Latest Push for Bitcoin, Gold and Commodities? Jones is optimistic about both gold and bitcoin, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Price Replicates ‘Reversal Box’ Move From 2020, What Happens Next?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77bb3421b9</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-price-replicates-2020/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T21:41:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto analyst Trader Tardigrade has drawn the crypto community’s attention to a historical pattern in which the Dogecoin price has replicated this cycle. The analyst indicated this is bullish for the foremost meme coin as he revealed what will likely happen next. 
 
Dogecoin Price Replicates Reversal Box Move From 2020
 
Trader Tardigrade mentioned in an X post that the Dogecoin price has repeated the move in a ‘Reversal Box’ from 2020. He added that the price action is almost the same, as DOGE has again formed three higher lows and is now breaking the resistance before the “hard pump.” In 2020, the meme coin formed these three higher lows before it broke out and rose to its current all-time high (ATH) of $0.73. 
 
 
 
The analyst’s accompanying chart showed that he once again envisages t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic Unleashes New Claude 3.5 Sonnet: A Model Smart Enough to Take Over Your Computer]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287767</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287767/anthropic-unleashes-claude-3-5-sonnet-smart-enough-take-over-computer"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T21:20:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AI powerhouse just dropped major updates to its models, including a feature that lets its AI physically control computers, marking a shift from chat-only interactions to hands-on automation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bipartisan Hope Grows That Crypto Laws Will Pass Before Year's End]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287785</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287785/bipartisan-hope-grows-crypto-laws-pass"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T21:19:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Republicans and Democrats across the House and Senate are increasingly convinced that key pieces of crypto legislation could soon become law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin, the XRP Price, and the RCO Finance Presale Token Could See Bigger Gains in Q4 2024, Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77bb37a7ac</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-the-xrp-price-and-the-rco-finance-presale-token-could-see-bigger-gains-in-q4-2024-heres-why/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T21:10:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto market is pumping again, with the XRP price gaining traction. Meanwhile, Dogecoin (DOGE) has performed exceptionally, jumping by double digits over the past week. Despite these gains, investors increasingly flock to RCO Finance (RCOF), an upcoming presale token. 
 
Why are XRP and Dogecoin investors rushing to buy RCO Finance (RCOF)? Let’s find out!
 
XRP Price Climbs 3% in a Week: More Gains Coming? 
XRP has performed decently over the past week, maintaining a green chart. On October 14, the XRP price was hovering around $0.5294. The XRP price began pumping the same day after Bitcoin (BTC) jumped past $66,000, triggering an altcoin rally. 
 
Also, on October 15, Ripple announced the partners of its Ripple USD (RLUSD) stablecoin. This generated massive hype, which saw the XRP pr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop Meme Stock Craze Prompted Market 'Plumbing' Changes, Says SEC Chair Gensler]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287764</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287764/gamestop-meme-stock-market-plumbing-changes"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T20:33:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC embraced shorter settlement times after the GameStop short squeeze—but crypto already does 24/7 markets and quick trade completions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside DMG Blockchain’s Plan for Canada’s First Indigenous-Led AI Data Centers]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77bb33c846</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/inside-dmg-blockchains-plan-for-canadas-first-indigenous-led-ai-data-centers/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T20:33:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bitcoin mining company and vertically integrated blockchain firm DMG Blockchain Solutions has announced a partnership with Malahat Nation to develop Canada’s first Indigenous-led artificial intelligence (AI) data centers. The project, designed to utilize clean energy, is expected to expand technology infrastructure while promoting economic growth in Indigenous communities. DMG Blockchain and Malahat Nation Join […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s Uptober Breakout In Sight: Here Are The Next Potential Critical Levels]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77bb3eeda5</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoins-uptober-breakout-in-sight/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T20:07:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October has historically been one of Bitcoin‘s best-performing months, triggering notable price increases over the years. Considering the price of BTC this month, several crypto analysts believe that the digital asset could be gearing up for a breakout that might catalyze a move to new all-time highs.
 
Is A Major Move For Bitcoin Around The Corner?
 
As the month of October gradually approaches its end, Titan of Crypto, a market expert and trader has predicted a notable breakout for Bitcoin in the month usually termed “Uptober,” reflecting the much-anticipated bullish momentum. 
 
 
The expert’s forecast suggests the present lengthy consolidation phase is about to come to an end as the crypto asset prepares for the impending surge. Additionally, his bullish perspective stems from BTC’s mo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Godspower Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Major Improvement to Bitcoin Cash Will Smash Developer Bottlenecks]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77bb38c86a</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/a-major-improvement-to-bitcoin-cash-will-smash-developer-bottlenecks/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T19:51:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Andrei Terentiev, CTO of Bitcoin.com, explains why Bitcoin.com has thrown its full support behind Bitcoin Cash Improvement Proposal 2021-05. CHIP-2021-05 Gains Bitcoin.com’s Support With Promise Of A New Era for Bitcoin Cash Smart Contracts Bitcoin.com endorses Bitcoin Cash Improvement Proposal (CHIP) 2021-05 VM Limits: Targeted Virtual Machine Limits. The current VM limits, while necessary for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrei Terentiev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Andy Barr's 'Vision' for House Financial Services]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77bb3984a3</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/opinion/2024/10/22/andy-barrs-vision-for-house-financial-services/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T19:44:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Congressman Andy Barr (R-Ky.) is one of the lawmakers running to succeed U.S. House Financial Services Committee Chair Patrick McHenry (R-N.C.) as the head of the Republican wing of the committee, which oversees regulators like the Securities and Exchange Commission and is responsible for shepherding legislation that might affect the U.S. capital markets and banking sectors, among others. He shared some of his thoughts on what his crypto priorities might be during an aside at the Flyover Fintech conference on Monday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A $20 Alternative to Expensive Hearing Aids]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287714</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287714/cheap-alternative-expensive-hearing-aids"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T19:43:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quantum Senses aims to offer an affordable and durable alternative to expensive hearing aids that's made from fully recycled materials.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything You Need to Know Ahead of the 'X Empire' Telegram Game Airdrop]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287756</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287756/x-empire-telegram-game-airdrop-explainer"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T18:47:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk-themed game X Empire is launching its token on The Open Network this week. Here's what you need to know about the airdrop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sky’s Rune Christensen Reveals Star Allocation Proposal—and Possibly a Return to the Old Maker Name]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77bb212187</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/skys-rune-christensen-reveals-star-allocation-proposal-and-possibly-a-return-to-the-old-maker-name/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T18:42:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rune Christensen, founder of Makerdao, has outlined a comprehensive plan for the future of the decentralized finance (defi) ecosystem, highlighting the success of the USDS stablecoin and introducing the Star Allocation System Framework. A key aspect of the plan includes a possible transition back to the Maker brand, following community feedback on recent changes. Makerdao […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether CEO Ardoino Says He Expects U.S. Will Catch Up in Crypto Regulation]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77bb2353ee</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/10/22/tether-ceo-ardoino-says-he-expects-us-will-catch-up-in-crypto-regulation/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T18:25:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tether CEO Paolo Ardoino told a U.S. crowd on Tuesday that he's counting on sensible crypto regulations coming soon from the U.S. "There is no place like the U.S.," he said via video link at DC Fintech Week in Washington.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aurum Launches $1B Tokenized Fund for Data Center Investments on XRP Ledger With Zoniqx]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77bb2c6f11</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2024/10/22/aurum-launches-1b-tokenized-fund-for-data-center-investments-on-xrp-ledger-with-zoniqx/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T18:17:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The vehicle will focus on data center investments across the U.S, United Arab Emirates, Saudi Arabia, India, and Europe, claiming to be the "world’s first combined equity and debt tokenized fund."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paul Tudor Jones Points To Bitcoin And Gold As Shields Against US Inflation Threats]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77bb2e1fe6</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/paul-tudor-jones-points-to-bitcoin-and-gold-shields/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T18:04:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Billionaire hedge fund manager Paul Tudor Jones, CEO of Tudor Investment Corporation, highlighted the growing threat of inflation in a recent interview with CNBC, describing Bitcoin and gold as essential assets amid rising recession fears in the United States.
 
During the interview, Jones revealed his investment strategy, stating that he is actively purchasing both Bitcoin and gold, positioning himself long in these assets, further reflecting a broader concern about the current economic landscape and the potential consequences of “unchecked government spending.”
 
Jones Urges Investment In Bitcoin And Gold
 
Jones articulated his worries about the US fiscal situation, saying, “We are going to be broke really quickly unless we get serious about dealing with our spending issues.” 
 
Jones w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stripe to Acquire Stablecoin Startup for Over $1Billion: Report]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77bb2eb82f</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com/cryptocurrency/stripe-to-acquire-stablecoin-startup-for-over-1billion-report/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T18:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stripe plans to acquire the stablecoin infrastructure 
provider Bridge to strengthen its position in the fintech and crypto markets. 
This acquisition is estimated to be valued at $1.1 billion, Forbes reported. According to sources familiar with the matter, 
Stripe's purchase aims to enhance international money transfers and bolster its 
payment solutions for businesses globally. 
The company was founded by John and Patrick Collison 
in 2010 and has established itself in the payment processing sector, with a 
valuation of 65 billion earlier this year.
Expanding Stablecoin Services
Stripe reportedly confirmed the acquisition of Bridge, 
which specializes in enabling businesses to use stablecoins, cryptocurrencies pegged to traditional currencies like the US dollar, for 
transactions.
Bridge has experienced remarkable growth, reporting a 
tenfold increase in business this year alone. CEO Zach Abrams noted the 
company's rapid expansion and its existing clientele, which includes notable 
firms like Coinbase and SpaceX. 
Bridge will reportedly serve as a Web3 version of 
Stripe, enabling seamless payment solutions for digital transactions worldwide. The acquisition comes at a time when digital currencies are gaining 
traction, largely due to recent decisions by the US Securities and Exchange 
Commission (SEC) that have eased regulations surrounding cryptocurrencies. 
This shift has encouraged major companies, including 
PayPal, to embrace digital currencies. PayPal launched its own US dollar 
stablecoin last year.
International Transactions
Although the details about the timeline for the 
acquisition were not disclosed, the move could position Stripe to compete effectively in the digital finance space. By integrating Bridge's capabilities, 
Stripe aims to enhance its offerings and provide businesses with better 
solutions for international transactions.
Expect ongoing updates as this story evolves. 
 

 
This article was written by Jared Kirui at www.financemagnates.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BTC Miner Core Scientific Expands Contract With Coreweave, Eyes $8.7B in HPC Revenue]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77bb2fea97</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/btc-miner-core-scientific-expands-contract-with-coreweave-eyes-8-7b-in-hpc-revenue/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T17:51:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Core Scientific has revealed that Coreweave has chosen to expand its high-performance computing (HPC) infrastructure by another 120 megawatts (MW), pushing the total contracted capacity to around 500 MW. Core Scientific and Coreweave Extend Partnership This contract extension could bring Core Scientific’s (Nasdaq: CORZ) total revenue up to $8.7 billion over the next 12 years. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SOL Outperforms, 10y Rises above 4.2%, AI Tokens Dominate flows]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zu7HXBIc/sol-outperforms-10y-rises-above-42-ai-tokens-dominate-flows</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zu7HXBIc/sol-outperforms-10y-rises-above-42-ai-tokens-dominate-flows"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T17:41:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC: 67k (-2%), ETH: 2620 (-4%), SOL: 166 (0%). Top Gainers: APT, UNI, HNT, POPCAT, RUNE, KAS. BTC drops, SOL continues to outperform. PumpFun has sold $78m of SOL fees so far. Raydium flips ETH for 24hr fees. Scroll launches at $1.2bn FDV, disappoints. Crypto only really used for drug deals: Fed’s Kashkari. VanEck adds staking to SOL ETPs in Europe. LINK announces successful results from SWIFT trial. Brevan Howard trades most crypto from UAE. Japanese parties court crypto tax cuts. XRP co-founder donates $10m to Kamala. CFTC chair says agency is ‘handcuffed’ on crypto. Transak exposes 92k customers’ data. Sky may rebrand back to MakerDAO.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SOL Breaks out, Stripe Acquires Bridge, GIGA hits $600M]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/35JgCoNO/sol-breaks-out-stripe-acquires-bridge-giga-hits-600m</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/35JgCoNO/sol-breaks-out-stripe-acquires-bridge-giga-hits-600m"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T17:30:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC briefly tops $70k as OI tops $40bn. SOL outperforms, DEX volume eclipses ETH + L2s. SOLETH has highest weekly close ever. Pension giant L&G look to test tokenisation. BTC hash rate hits ATH. Stripe acquires stablecoin company Bridge for $1.1bn. PumpFun hints at upcoming token. GOAT drops then rebounds as authenticity questioned. GIGA hits new ATH of $600m, FROG hits $250m. MEW up 15% after Upbit listing. Jaypeg called out for misleading promotions. ACK editions sell for $290k.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['All Roads Lead to Inflation' Says Billionaire Bitcoin Bull Paul Tudor Jones]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287751</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287751/billionaire-bitcoin-bull-paul-tudor-jones-inflation"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T17:29:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Billionaire investor Paul Tudor Jones is worried about U.S. federal debt—and sees inflation coming as a result. He's betting on Bitcoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitget Partners With Solayer to Launch CEX-based Solana (SOL) Liquid Staking Services]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77bb15c683</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitget-partners-with-solayer-to-launch-cex-based-solana-sol-liquid-staking-services/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T17:10:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Victoria, Seychelles, 22nd October 2024 – Bitget, the leading cryptocurrency exchange and Web3 company, has announced the launch of its Solana (SOL) liquid staking service, in partnership with Solayer, a leading restaking network on Solana. This service introduces BGSOL, a token that users receive in exchange for staking their SOL assets, providing them with increased […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Price Could Resume Uptrend To $0.00002 As Whale Transactions Jump 240% To 3.42 Trillion SHIB]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77bb16f6d4</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-price-0-00002/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T17:02:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu whale transactions have skyrocketed by a whopping 240%, as large-scale investors have been seen moving trillions of SHIB tokens this week. Considering the significant increase in SHIB whale movements, the price of Shiba Inu could continue its previously halted uptrend to $0.00002.
 
SHIB Whale Activity Spikes
 
New data from IntoTheBlock has shown a massive 269% increase in the Shiba Inu whale transactions. On October 20, the total volume of large-scale transactions by SHIB whales was estimated at 925.79 billion. However, in just one day, whale transaction volume skyrocketed to 3.42 trillion, basically tripling the volume from the previous day. 
 
 
With an average Shiba Inu price of $0.000018, this means that whales have moved over $61.5 million worth of SHIB tokens in just one …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Should You Play 'Dookey Dash: Unclogged'? The Bored Ape Endless Runner With Big Prizes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287740</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287740/dookey-dash-unclogged-game-review"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T16:50:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[REVIEW: Dookey Dash: Unclogged drops Bored Apes into the sewers for an endless runner with $1 million up for grabs. Here's our take.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Stubbs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stripe $1.1 Billion Bridge Deal Validates Stablecoin Growth, Says Bernstein]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287730</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287730/stripe-bridge-deal-validates-stablecoins-bernstein"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T16:32:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Stripe acquisition of Bridge for a staggering $1.1 billion has underscored the growth of stablecoins as a payment method, says Bernstein.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto CEO Loses $450K to 'Best Friend' After Connecting to His WiFi]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287425</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287425/crypto-ceo-loses-450k-wifi"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T15:37:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A ‘proximity breach’ is a rising trend, when someone exploits someone close to them to steal money—this time through a WiFi network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet HuggingChat: The Free Open-Source Chatbot That's Ready to Rival ChatGPT]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287571</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287571/meet-huggingchat-free-open-source-chatbot"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T15:21:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HuggingChat offers fully open-source alternatives to everything the best chatbots have to offer, including custom assistants, model versatility, internet connection, and multimodality.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentraland Launches Revamped Virtual World with Enhanced Performance, Engaging Features, and Future-Ready Architecture]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287706</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287706/decentraland-launches-revamped-virtual-world-with-enhanced-performance-engaging-features-and-future-ready-architecture"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T15:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Los Angeles, USA, 22nd October 2024, GamingWire]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GamingWire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Is Today’s 'Captain Tsubasa: Rivals' Telegram Game Daily Combo]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=250928</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/captain-tsubasa-rivals-telegram-game-daily-combo"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T14:51:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anime soccer game Captain Tsubasa: Rivals gives out 5 million free daily balls ahead of the TON token airdrop. Here’s the combo for Tuesday, October 22.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Protocol Elmnts Launches Tokenized Mineral Rights Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287677</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287677/solana-elmnts-tokenized-mineral-rights-platform"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T13:08:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Energy market analytics company RBN Energy estimates that mineral and royalty interests amount to $700 billion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Napolitano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mark Cuban Dismisses Polymarket Election Odds as Result of 'Foreign Money']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287676</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287676/mark-cuban-dismisses-polymarket-election-odds-as-result-of-foreign-money"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T12:57:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The billionaire isn’t the only one who has questioned the reliability of the crypto betting platform’s predictions in recent weeks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will McCurdy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Is Today’s 'Tomarket' Telegram Game Daily Combo]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286780</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/here-is-todays-tomarket-telegram-game-daily-combo"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T12:50:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram game Tomarket is handing out free tomatoes and bonus items ahead of the airdrop. Here’s the combo for Tuesday, October 22.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Saylor Says He'll Give Away His Bitcoin—Like Satoshi Nakamoto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287667</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287667/bitcoin-billionaire-michael-saylor-satoshi-nakamoto"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T12:38:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Just like Satoshi left a million Bitcoin to the universe, so I’m leaving whatever I’ve got to the civilization,” the MicroStrategy co-founder said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vismaya V</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Faces Resistance as Analysts Now Weigh Pre-Election Consolidation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287647</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287647/bitcoin-price-resistance-analysts-now-predict-pre-election-consolidation"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T11:50:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One U.S.-based market research firm still has a cautious outlook, maintaining a "neutral" rating on both Bitcoin and Ethereum.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Is Today’s 'Major' Telegram Game Puzzle Durov Combo]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286896</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/here-is-todays-major-telegram-puzzle-durov-combo"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T01:08:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking to complete Major’s daily Pavel Durov puzzle on Telegram? Here’s the solution updated on Monday, October 21.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Labs Founder Donates Another $10 Million in XRP to Support Kamala Harris]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287549</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287549/ripple-founder-10-million-xrp-kamala-harris"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T22:56:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple co-founder Chris Larsen said that he has donated another $10 million in XRP to help boost Kamala Harris in the U.S. election.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Will 'Not Relent' in Push to Uncover Motives Behind US Crypto Crackdown]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287546</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287546/coinbase-not-relent-motives-us-crypto-crackdown"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T22:41:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto exchange Coinbase is seeking documents from the FDIC over whether the bank regulator privately prohibited depository institutions from holding digital assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF Options Could Boost Action on Wall Street—And Volatility, Say Analysts]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287543</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287543/bitcoin-etf-options-boost-action-volatility"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T22:24:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the SEC's approval of options for spot Bitcoin ETFs, analysts expect another wave of institutional adoption and associated volatility.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Blade Runner 2049' Studio Sues Elon Musk for Copyright Infringement Over AI Images]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287518</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287518/blade-runner-2049-studio-elon-musk-copyright-ai-images"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T21:57:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Attorneys for Alcon Entertainment said the company did not want to be associated with Musk’s capricious behavior, “which veers into hate speech.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fed President Says Crypto 'Almost Never' Used Outside of Drug Deals, Illegal Activities]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287542</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287542/fed-president-crypto-drug-deals-illegal-activities"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T21:44:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Minneapolis Federal Reserve President Neel Kashkari said “very few transactions are actually happening” in crypto at a town hall in Wisconsin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Napolitano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘America Loves Crypto’? The Black Keys Will Play Ohio Concert Amid Contentious Senate Race]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287491</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287491/america-loves-crypto-black-keys-concert"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T20:48:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Pretty liberal” rock duo The Black Keys will play a Coinbase-backed event in Ohio, as a PAC backed by the exchange aims to elect a hardline conservative to Senate in the battleground state.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['I Just Like Dogecoin': Elon Musk Pumps Meme Coin to 4-Month High]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287505</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287505/elon-musk-likes-dogecoin-4-month-high"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T20:27:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk insists that he's not "actively involved" in crypto, but his recent Dogecoin mentions appear to be pumping the meme coin's price.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New AI Model Developed by Harvard Detects Cancer With 96% Accuracy]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287471</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287471/ai-model-harvard-detects-cancer"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T19:53:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developed by Harvard Medical School, CHIEF was trained on 44 terabytes of data, to make it extremely good at detecting tumors and providing insights for healthcare professionals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETFs Add Billions of Dollars Amid Rising Trump Optimism: CoinShares]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287427</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287427/bitcoin-etfs-add-billions-trump-optimism"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T18:52:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Investors are feeling bullish about Bitcoin again, with over $2 billion flowing into ETFs last week as BTC flirted with $70,000.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pump.fun Teases Token and 'Lucrative' Solana Airdrop Amid Record Week]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287465</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287465/pump-fun-token-solana-airdrop-record-week"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T18:30:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana meme coin factory Pump.fun launched a new trading bot—and revealed that it will launch a token with a likely airdrop attached.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Dips After Failing to Hit $70,000, Leaving Longs Rekt]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287459</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287459/bitcoin-misses-70000-leaving-longs-rekt"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T18:13:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin's close call with $70,000 may have boosted trader optimism, leaving a trail of liquidations as the price fell below $67,000 Monday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VanEck Adds Staking Rewards to Solana Investment Product in Europe]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287431</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287431/vaneck-solana-staking-rewards-europe"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T17:35:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As VanEck’s Solana ETN begins offering investors passive income in the EU, the asset manager awaits input on an application in the U.S.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether-Owned Northern Data Considering Sale of Bitcoin Mining Firm Peak]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287456</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287456/northern-data-bitcoin-mining-sale-ai"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T17:05:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Northern Data Group has plans to acquire data centers and AI-centric GPUs with funds raised from the potential sale of its Bitcoin mining business.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Napolitano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Bitcoin ETF Options Will Supercharge the Trump Trade, According to QCP]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287430</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287430/bitcoin-etf-options-supercharge-trump-trade"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T16:15:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF options will give Bitcoin ETFs "the needed liquidity to attract sustainable inflows,” QCP Capital wrote.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Huge week for BTC ETFs, Crypto now through Venmo, Memes Dominate Gainers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rLpBnnaQ/huge-week-for-btc-etfs-crypto-now-through-venmo-memes-dominate-gainers</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rLpBnnaQ/huge-week-for-btc-etfs-crypto-now-through-venmo-memes-dominate-gainers"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T19:24:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETFs see biggest inflow week since July. BlackRock ETF sees $1bn inflows in a week. Venmo can now be used to buy crypto on Moonpay. SEC’s XRP appeal doesn’t challenge security status. Worldcoin rebrands to World with new orb. EigenLayer X account compromised. FBI arrests hacker of SEC X account. SCB in Thailand adopts stablecoins for transfers. DBS in Singapore adopts ‘token services’. Trump family to get 75% of WLFL revenue. Scroll team accused of owning sybil addresses. STX Nakamoto upgrade to happen next week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Majors Fall 1 to 2%, A New Tiger takes to the Charts, Van Eck teases Big Web3 Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/a6Tm7OGW/majors-fall-1-to-2-a-new-tiger-takes-to-the-charts-van-eck-teases-big-web3-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/a6Tm7OGW/majors-fall-1-to-2-a-new-tiger-takes-to-the-charts-van-eck-teases-big-web3-gaming"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T17:42:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lucky GOAT memecoin trader turned $5,000 into $1.5M during GOAT's run to $300M. A new memecoin based on Disney Park's new baby tiger "Bakso" was a top mover on Wednesday, running to $10M (now $6M). Crypto majors fall 1-2%, memes red across board. a16z calls 2024 crypto's biggest year yet in "State of Crypto" report. Vitalik publishes part 2 of blog outlining ETH's future. Van Eck teases big bet on Parallel and web3 gaming. Huge day for digital art with 4 marquee mints seeing success.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hamster Kombat Season 2 Teaser]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/qcvjjJxN/hamster-kombat-season-2-teaser</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/qcvjjJxN/hamster-kombat-season-2-teaser"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T12:03:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here's a first look at Season 2 of Telegram tap-to-earn game Hamster Kombat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BTC hits $68K, Trump odds Continue to Rise, GOAT nears $300M]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/c88qN8eB/btc-hits-68k-trump-odds-continue-to-rise-goat-nears-300m</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/c88qN8eB/btc-hits-68k-trump-odds-continue-to-rise-goat-nears-300m"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T18:31:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC hits $68k as ETF inflows continue to soar. Open Interest at CME hits ATH, funding still low. Tesla moves $750m BTC to new wallet. Canary applies for Litcoin ETF, LTC up 8%. Grayscale asks SEC to convert altcoin fund to ETF. Kraken integrates with EigenLayer for restaking. ‘Network state’ Praxis raises $525m for new city. Trump project raises only $11m so far. a16z founders donate $2.5m to Trump PAC. TikTok accused of being crypto exchange in UK. Gotbit CEO arrested in Portugal. Perplexity AI launches finance platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ETF Inflows Soar, Kamala Courts Crypto, TURBO Nears $1BN!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zn2lboMV/etf-inflows-soar-kamala-courts-crypto-turbo-nears-1bn</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zn2lboMV/etf-inflows-soar-kamala-courts-crypto-turbo-nears-1bn"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T18:22:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETFs see $800m inflows in 2-days, huge volume. ETF inflows may be linked to Trump odds: CoinShares. Bitcoin will rival housing market as asset class: Fink. Vitalik proposes drop to 1ETH to become validator. Kamala reveals pro-crypto policies. Kamala mocked for linking crypto to race. Hyperliquid announces HYPE token coming. PUFFER airdrop claim goes live. Tether considering lending to commodities trader. Man takes $500m lost Bitcoin case to court. Google removes crypto prices from search. SUI Foundation denies $400m insider selling. UAE approves $AED stablecoin. Bitget wallet now only behind Binance for downloads.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BTC hits 2-week High, China Stocks Rally again, GOAT hits $120M]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/0V0rYhMX/btc-hits-2-week-high-china-stocks-rally-again-goat-hits-120m</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/0V0rYhMX/btc-hits-2-week-high-china-stocks-rally-again-goat-hits-120m"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T14:09:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC hits 2-week high as China stocks rise. SUI breaks into the top 15 coins. $1.3bn ETH might be sold from PlusToken scam. S. Korea may approve BTC & ETH ETFs this month. Australia launches first ETH ETF. Samara to buy BTC with $33m bond. Altcoins to see $500m unlocks this week. Vitalik writes blog on the future of ETH. Grayscale reveals 35 altcoins considered for funds. Ethena proposes SOL for USDe collateral. Only one Binance launchpad coin up this year. AVAX summit begins this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Todd ‘revealed’ as Satoshi, Google may be Broken-up, Murad’s Wallets Doxxed]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pLw8b2d2/todd-revealed-as-satoshi-google-may-be-broken-up-murads-wallets-doxxed</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pLw8b2d2/todd-revealed-as-satoshi-google-may-be-broken-up-murads-wallets-doxxed"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T07:29:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC will be range bound until election: Bernstein. TAO & memecoins dominate mindshare. Peter Todd ‘revealed’ as Satoshi by HBO. US government able to sell $4.4bn Silk Road BTC. Ireland unable to access $378m seized BTC. SOL could do 5x if Trump wins: StanChart. Coinbase integrates Taproot addresses for BTC. Canary Capital applies for XRP ETF. S. Korea to regulate stablecoin transfers. CryptoCom files countersuit against SEC. Babylon fills cap with 22k BTC. Scroll airdrop coming Oct 22nd. USDC goes live on SUI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Falls Ahead of CPI, Stripe Reinstates Crypto, Fed Charges Market-makers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/aYgFvZqj/crypto-falls-ahead-of-cpi-stripe-reinstates-crypto-fed-charges-market-makers</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/aYgFvZqj/crypto-falls-ahead-of-cpi-stripe-reinstates-crypto-fed-charges-market-makers"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T07:29:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Majors drop despite stocks hitting ATHs. Stripe reinstates crypto payments. Crypto settlements near $20bn in 2024. S. Korea to review ban on BTC ETFs. US charges market makers for market manipulation. FBI created their own coin to ensnare targets. Vitalik ‘outside pick’ for Nobel Prize. Trump family token to built on Aave stack. $16m OP tokens allocated to superchain users. Wisdomtree debuts debit card for on-chain fund. 47% of hedge funds have crypto exposure. Argentina overtakes Brazil for crypto inflows. Tucker interviews Ryan Salame over FTX.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bounces from $59K, Tesla unveils Robotaxis, Memecoins Outperform]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cyJj6tWj/bitcoin-bounces-from-59k-tesla-unveils-robotaxis-memecoins-outperform</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cyJj6tWj/bitcoin-bounces-from-59k-tesla-unveils-robotaxis-memecoins-outperform"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T07:29:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC briefly dips under $59k, $160m liquidations. Mt Gox extends repayment plan by 1 year. Uniswap plans L2 for DeFi. SEC sues crypto trading firm Cumberland. Binomial sues SEC over futures trading. SEC’s Uyeda criticises agency’s policy. Justin Sun named prime minister of Liberland. MicroStrategy wants to become BTC bank. Binance pre-market trading goes live. Nearly 50% of US investors want crypto ETFs. Whale phished for $35m crypto. Ethena invests $46m in RWA funds. Trump’s crypto project aims to raise $300m.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentraland Desktop Client Preview]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qqzvDcTC/decentraland-desktop-client-preview</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qqzvDcTC/decentraland-desktop-client-preview"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T15:53:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum metaverse game Decentraland has shared an exclusive look at the visual and performance upgrades coming via its new desktop client.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Trader Murad Mahmudov talks about the Supercycle and how he chooses Meme Coins.]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Hj3nDp7G/crypto-trader-murad-mahmudov-talks-about-the-supercycle-and-how-he-chooses-meme-coins</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Hj3nDp7G/crypto-trader-murad-mahmudov-talks-about-the-supercycle-and-how-he-chooses-meme-coins"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T21:47:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Trader Murad Mahmudov talks about the Supercycle and how he chooses Meme Coins. Crypto stable, had sold off after China stocks fall. Crypto adopted faster than other tech: BlackRock. Crypto adoption to hit 8% of world population. CryptoCom recieves Wells notice from SEC. HBO documentary on Satoshi airs tonight. FTX bankruptcy plan approved by judge. Scroll airdrop may be imminent. Jupiter goes live on mobile iOS. Phantom rolls out support for Base. AAVE launches GHO on Base. Gensler may be replaced by Robinhood CLO. 87% of new token launches on SOL. National Bank of Bahrain creates BTC fund. BedRock DeFi allows BTC staking on ARB.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Memecoins take off, funding stays low, China stocks keep on rising!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/703mAYhV/memecoins-take-off-funding-stays-low-china-stocks-keep-on-rising</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/703mAYhV/memecoins-take-off-funding-stays-low-china-stocks-keep-on-rising"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T08:27:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR EP213. Memecoins take off, funding stays low, China stocks keep on rising!
Many altcoins & memecoins soar despite stable BTC. Funding rates continue to be low or negative. Crypto funds saw $147m of outflows last week. BTC remains best performing major assets this year. SUI breaks into the top 20 coins again. TAO leads top 100 away from memes, sifu shorts. $100m bridge to SOL over the last 7 days. Metaplanet buys $6.7m more BTC. ETH proposal aims to improve throughput 50%. EIGEN, OP, APT lead token unlocks this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Walrus Protocol Unlocks New Applications for Decentralized Data Storage]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kwEYLYWj/how-walrus-protocol-unlocks-new-applications-for-decentralized-data-storage</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kwEYLYWj/how-walrus-protocol-unlocks-new-applications-for-decentralized-data-storage"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T11:19:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mysten Labs Chief Scientist George Danezis joined Decrypt to talk about its new decentralized storage protocol Walrus, which promises to unlock new applications such as AI and social media, thanks to its novel Red Stuff data encoding algorithm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Coinbase Sees Crypto as a Bipartisan, 'Purple' Political Issue]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/YR2YmmwR/why-coinbase-sees-crypto-as-a-bipartisan-purple-political-issue</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/YR2YmmwR/why-coinbase-sees-crypto-as-a-bipartisan-purple-political-issue"/>
        <updated>2024-10-05T22:18:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase VP of Corporate and Business Development, Shan Aggarwal, joined Decrypt's Sander Lutz and Liz Napolitano at Messari Mainnet 2024 to discuss the exchange's efforts to grow mainstream crypto adoption—and how the changing political conversation around digital assets is rapidly playing a major role in that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Is Playing Offense—Not Just Defense—Against Crypto Crime, Says Head of Financial Investigations]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DiJ8D2Qc/binance-is-playing-offensenot-just-defenseagainst-crypto-crime-says-head-of-financial-investigations</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DiJ8D2Qc/binance-is-playing-offensenot-just-defenseagainst-crypto-crime-says-head-of-financial-investigations"/>
        <updated>2024-10-05T01:58:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nils Anderson Röed, the exchange’s global head of financial investigations, sat down with Decrypt’s Sander Lutz at Messari Mainnet 2024 to discuss how Binance is proactively dismantling criminal networks around the world, the strategy with which the crypto exchange is approaching sensitive conflicts in the Middle East, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 212 - SEEDPHRASE TALKS ART!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PJfaJNkZ/fomo-hour-212-seedphrase-talks-art</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PJfaJNkZ/fomo-hour-212-seedphrase-talks-art"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T19:29:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Payrolls Higher than expected, Bitcoin reacts hard. Crypto sank early in the week as Middle East tensions spooked markets. Powell signals two more rate cuts this year. SUI leads L1s again, nears YTD high despite large unlock. Majority of FTX repayments still months away. EIGEN becomes non-transferable, hits $6bn FDV. SEC to appeal Ripple securities law ruling. Visa launches tokenization platform for banks. SWIFT plans digital asset trial in 2025. ByBit launched trading of global stock indices. SPX, GIGA & FWOG hit ATHs, most memes fall. XCOPY to release 250 piece collection on Shape. HBO documentary claims to have identified Satoshi.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Altcoins bleed, ByBit launches stock index trading, POCHITA soars]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kYjAt3nt/altcoins-bleed-bybit-launches-stock-index-trading-pochita-soars</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kYjAt3nt/altcoins-bleed-bybit-launches-stock-index-trading-pochita-soars"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T21:11:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Altcoins sink, BTC dominance nears cycle high. BTC in ‘three blind mice’ downtrend. Tron revenue hits record $577m in Q3. ByBit to launch trading of major stock indices. Franklin Templeton launch fund on APT. SWIFT banks to trial digital assets in 2025. Aerodrome hits $1bn TVL on Base. Cronje calls out Aerodrome for copyright. ETH ICO wallet sells $47m. SEC files appeal against Ripple ruling. EIGEN falls 20% on staking rewards FUD. FTX to auction off WLD position. Half of US voters think crypto ‘important’. North Korea ‘infiltrating’ crypto industry. Snowden challenged over SOL centralisation view. Top SEC official on crypto set to depart.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DACOM Summit: Fastex CLO Vardan Khachatryan on Crypto Compliance]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LGGnxkb6/dacom-summit-fastex-clo-vardan-khachatryan-on-crypto-compliance</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LGGnxkb6/dacom-summit-fastex-clo-vardan-khachatryan-on-crypto-compliance"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T14:32:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fastex Chief Legal Officer Vardan Khachatryan joined Rug Radio creator Mlow at DACOM Summit to discuss how the crypto exchange is advancing compliance, and the regulatory challenges that lie ahead for the sector.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>