<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-01-08T19:12:44.123Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-01-08T19:12:44.123Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock’s Strategic Play: Undercutting Rivals With Lower Spot Bitcoin ETF Fees]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74faee7c60</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/blackrock-undercut-lower-spot-bitcoin-etf-fees/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T19:07:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the potential approval of several spot Bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETF) by the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) approaches, BlackRock has made a significant move by announcing a comparatively low fee for its upcoming spot Bitcoin ETF earlier today.
 
BlackRock Takes Competitive Edge In Spot Bitcoin ETF Race
 
In a report published by Reuters in the early hours of Monday, the asset management giant announced that it has now set the fee at 0.20 percent for its iShares Bitcoin Trust, then increasing its fees to 0.30 positioning itself competitively against its rivals.
 
 
 
This strategic pricing undercuts the fees of Valkyrie Investments and Fidelity, which stand at 0.80 percent and 0.39 percent, respectively, for their spot BTC ETF offerings.
 
This latest report…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bullish Beginning? $151 Million Poured Into Crypto Funds In 2024’s First Week]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19159264/A-Bullish-Beginning-151-Million-Poured-Into-Crypto-Funds-In-2024s-First-Week</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19159264/A-Bullish-Beginning-151-Million-Poured-Into-Crypto-Funds-In-2024s-First-Week"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T19:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first week of 2024 marked a notable milestone in crypto asset investments. Investment products in this particular sector witnessed inflows amounting to $151 million, according to a recent report from CoinShares. Crypto Asset Funds Sees Surge In Inflows This $151 million surge in inflow, as...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock’s Strategic Play: Undercutting Rivals With Lower Spot Bitcoin ETF Fees]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19159286/BlackRocks-Strategic-Play-Undercutting-Rivals-With-Lower-Spot-Bitcoin-ETF-Fees</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19159286/BlackRocks-Strategic-Play-Undercutting-Rivals-With-Lower-Spot-Bitcoin-ETF-Fees"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T19:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the potential approval of several spot Bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETF) by the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) approaches, BlackRock has made a significant move by announcing a comparatively low fee for its upcoming spot Bitcoin ETF earlier today. BlackRock Takes...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CNBC Reporter Reveals the Date She Expects Approval for Bitcoin Spot ETF, According to News Based on Two Sources]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19159278/CNBC-Reporter-Reveals-the-Date-She-Expects-Approval-for-Bitcoin-Spot-ETF-According-to-News-Based-on-Two-Sources</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19159278/CNBC-Reporter-Reveals-the-Date-She-Expects-Approval-for-Bitcoin-Spot-ETF-According-to-News-Based-on-Two-Sources"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T18:54:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CNBC reporter Kate Rooney shared her prediction for the date of Bitcoin Spot ETF approvals in her statement. Continue Reading: CNBC Reporter Reveals the Date She Expects Approval for Bitcoin Spot ETF, According to News Based on Two Sources]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF Deadline Week: SEC Chief Warns on Crypto Investments]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fae8327c</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/bitcoin-etf-deadline-week-sec-chief-warns-on-crypto-investments/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T18:53:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amid anticipations surrounding the potential  
approval of a spot Bitcoin exchange-traded product by the Securities and  
Exchange Commission (SEC), Chair Gary Gensler's recent cautionary statements  
have cast a spotlight on the inherent risks within the crypto landscape. 
Gensler's thread on social media, although not  
explicitly addressing the pending spot Bitcoin ETF decision, underscores the  
significant concerns around crypto investments, emphasizing their volatility  
and susceptibility to fraudulent schemes.
Gensler has warned against the risks inherent in  
cryptocurrency investments. His social media thread, albeit not explicitly tied  
to the awaited ETF approval, sheds light on the broader concerns surrounding  
crypto investments.

2⃣ Investments in crypto assets also can be exceptionally risky & are often volatile. A number of major platforms & crypto assets have become insolvent and/or lost value. Investments in crypto assets continue to be subject to significant risk.
— Gary Gensler (@GaryGensler) January 8, 2024
Highlighting Risks and Volatility
Gensler's cautionary tone concerns asset managers  
potentially bypassing federal securities laws with their crypto investment  
offerings. The SEC Chair's commentary alludes to the possibility that certain  
investment assets may not align with established regulatory frameworks,  
prompting a call for investors' vigilance and due diligence.
Expect ongoing updates as this story evolves. 
 
  
 
  
This article was written by Jared Kirui at www.financemagnates.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wen SHIB Moon? Shiba Inu Whales Go Haywire On SHIB Buys As Transaction Volume Hits Trillions]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19159244/Wen-SHIB-Moon-Shiba-Inu-Whales-Go-Haywire-On-SHIB-Buys-As-Transaction-Volume-Hits-Trillions</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19159244/Wen-SHIB-Moon-Shiba-Inu-Whales-Go-Haywire-On-SHIB-Buys-As-Transaction-Volume-Hits-Trillions"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T18:49:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In tandem with this tug-of-war price, SHIB has witnessed a surge in transaction volume, notably hitting trillions, according to IntoTheBlock data.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spot Bitcoin ETFs Could Trade Live on Thursday or Friday: CNBC]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fae93f6c</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/markets/spot-bitcoin-etfs-could-trade-live-on-thursday-or-friday-cnbc"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T18:45:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spot Bitcoin Exchange-Traded Funds (ETFs) could potentially commence live trading as early as Thursday or Friday, with approval happening this Wednesday, sources close to the matter told CNBC. 



This news comes amid intense anticipation for the launch of Spot Bitcoin ETFs, a significant milestone anticipated to provide mainstream investors with a regulated avenue to gain direct exposure to Bitcoin.
"Two sources close to the process now telling me it's looking like Wednesday, which is also the deadline for Cathie Wood's ARK and 21Shares bid," said CNBC anchor Kate Rooney. "Then I'm told trading would happen Thursday or Friday, but it has been a moving target here on dates."
The imminent possibility of live trading for these ETFs signals a significant leap forward in the integration of Bitcoin into traditional financial markets. CNBC's report adds to the growing speculation surrounding the imminent introduction of these ETFs, which have been eagerly awaited by both institutional and retail investors.
Should the live trading commence as projected, it would mark a historic moment for the Bitcoin industry, reflecting a seismic shift in the perception and adoption of BTC among traditional investors.
While the specific details and exact launch time remain speculative, the potential realization of Spot Bitcoin ETFs trading live signifies a culmination of rigorous regulatory evaluations and market readiness, bringing Bitcoin one step closer to wider acceptance and legitimacy within the financial landscape.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nik Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BREAKING: 95% Chance Bitcoin ETF Approval this Week | EP 899]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19158801/BREAKING-95-Chance-Bitcoin-ETF-Approval-this-Week-EP-899</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19158801/BREAKING-95-Chance-Bitcoin-ETF-Approval-this-Week-EP-899"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T18:44:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF Approval Odds Raised to Over 90% by Bloomberg Analysts - CoinDesk✓ SUBSCRIBE - https://bit.ly/3QbgqTQ✓ LEAVE A LIKE & COMMENT LIMITED MERCH DROP► https://simplybitcoin.com/collections/allSPONSORS► Foundation's Bitcoin Hardware Wallet Passport: https://foundationdevices.com/simply►...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Investors are ‘the clear winners’ as bitcoin ETF fee battle comes into focus]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19159250/Investors-are-the-clear-winners-as-bitcoin-ETF-fee-battle-comes-into-focus</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19159250/Investors-are-the-clear-winners-as-bitcoin-ETF-fee-battle-comes-into-focus"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T18:41:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Planned spot bitcoin funds sporting fees competitive to physical gold offerings “a rather mind-boggling development,” ETF executive says]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morgan Stanley’s Chief Economist Predicts Rate Cuts ‘This Year’ as Market Eyes Federal Reserve’s Next Move]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74faea5764</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/morgan-stanleys-chief-economist-predicts-rate-cuts-this-year-as-market-eyes-federal-reserves-next-move/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T18:37:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This year, mirroring last year’s speculation, market observers are keenly awaiting decisions from the U.S. Federal Reserve concerning the federal funds rate, with a particular focus on potential rate cuts this year. Ellen Zentner, Morgan Stanley’s lead economist in the U.S., predicts rate reductions in the coming months. However, she cautions that the central bank has the luxury of patience, suggesting they are in no rush to make these changes.
 
Market Awaits Federal Reserve’s Target Rate Decisions
 
All eyes are on the Federal Reserve’s next moves and currently, according to the CME Fedwatch tool, the market anticipates a projected 25 basis points increase at the upcoming Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC) session. A commanding 95.3% of market predicts an increase, whereas a mere 4.7% …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Makes Play for EU Crypto Derivatives Market]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19159224/Coinbase-Makes-Play-for-EU-Crypto-Derivatives-Market</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19159224/Coinbase-Makes-Play-for-EU-Crypto-Derivatives-Market"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T18:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin and Ethereum ETFs To Push the Markets Higher: Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19159227/Bitcoin-and-Ethereum-ETFs-To-Push-the-Markets-Higher-Analyst</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19159227/Bitcoin-and-Ethereum-ETFs-To-Push-the-Markets-Higher-Analyst"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T18:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mysterious $1.2M Bitcoin Transaction to Satoshi Nakamoto Sparks Speculations]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74faead036</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/01/08/mysterious-12m-bitcoin-transaction-to-satoshi-nakamoto-sparks-speculations/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T18:33:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The wallet receiving the hefty payout is the address that mined the Bitcoin network's first-ever block reward some 15 years ago, commencing the start of the blockchain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Price analysis 1/8: SPX, DXY, BTC, ETH, BNB, SOL, XRP, ADA, AVAX, DOGE]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19159220/Price-analysis-18-SPX-DXY-BTC-ETH-BNB-SOL-XRP-ADA-AVAX-DOGE</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19159220/Price-analysis-18-SPX-DXY-BTC-ETH-BNB-SOL-XRP-ADA-AVAX-DOGE"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T18:33:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin and select altcoins are trading above their respective support levels as traders await the SEC’s decision on each spot Bitcoin ETF application.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean Lazarus Group moves BTC around after weeks of inactivity]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19159221/North-Korean-Lazarus-Group-moves-BTC-around-after-weeks-of-inactivity</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19159221/North-Korean-Lazarus-Group-moves-BTC-around-after-weeks-of-inactivity"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T18:32:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The state-sponsored hackers reportedly pulled over $1 million in BTC from a mixer and sent some to an inactive wallet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Injective (INJ) eyes new all-time high as Bitcoin surges to $46k]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19159190/Injective-INJ-eyes-new-all-time-high-as-Bitcoin-surges-to-46k</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19159190/Injective-INJ-eyes-new-all-time-high-as-Bitcoin-surges-to-46k"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T18:29:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Injective (INJ) price has surged 14% in the past 24 hours as bulls crossed above $40. INJ is targeting a new all-time high above $44, with the gains coming amid a new upside for Bitcoin that saw BTC soar to $46k. An infusion of fresh impetus has seen the price of Injective (INJ) rise sharply. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spot bitcoin ETFs may bring $50-100 billion of inflows in 2024, says Standard Chartered Bank]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19159205/Spot-bitcoin-ETFs-may-bring-50-100-billion-of-inflows-in-2024-says-Standard-Chartered-Bank</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19159205/Spot-bitcoin-ETFs-may-bring-50-100-billion-of-inflows-in-2024-says-Standard-Chartered-Bank"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T18:26:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spot Bitcoin ETFs are expected to attract inflows of $50-100 billion in 2024, according to Standard Chartered Bank.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why NOBODY Is Saying This About The ETF]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19159223/Why-NOBODY-Is-Saying-This-About-The-ETF</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19159223/Why-NOBODY-Is-Saying-This-About-The-ETF"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T18:24:51.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETFs: The Bull Case]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fad4f1df</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2024/01/08/bitcoin-etfs-the-bull-case/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T18:18:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One train of thought says that SEC approval of spot bitcoin ETF will send the market flying. Here’s how that could play out. In a separate post, we review the bear case, where the market may not react with such optimism.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Kuhn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mysterious $1.2M Bitcoin Transaction to Satoshi Nakamoto Sparks Speculations]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19159191/Mysterious-12M-Bitcoin-Transaction-to-Satoshi-Nakamoto-Sparks-Speculations</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19159191/Mysterious-12M-Bitcoin-Transaction-to-Satoshi-Nakamoto-Sparks-Speculations"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T18:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The wallet receiving the hefty payout is the address that mined the Bitcoin network's first-ever block reward some 15 years ago, commencing the start of the blockchain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jane Street named as authorized participant by all 11 bitcoin ETF hopefuls]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19159188/Jane-Street-named-as-authorized-participant-by-all-11-bitcoin-ETF-hopefuls</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19159188/Jane-Street-named-as-authorized-participant-by-all-11-bitcoin-ETF-hopefuls"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T18:16:09.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Stocks Rebound, Semiconductors Shine, Boeing's Struggles Weigh On Dow: What's Driving Markets Monday?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19159219/US-Stocks-Rebound-Semiconductors-Shine-Boeings-Struggles-Weigh-On-Dow-Whats-Driving-Markets-Monday</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19159219/US-Stocks-Rebound-Semiconductors-Shine-Boeings-Struggles-Weigh-On-Dow-Whats-Driving-Markets-Monday"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T18:15:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wall Street kicked off the week on a positive note, marking a turnaround from the challenging start to the year. All major stock indices showed gains, except for the Dow Jones, as financial conditions showed signs of improvement. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[X offers 80% price cut for gold check accounts amid surge in crypto scams]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19159173/X-offers-80-price-cut-for-gold-check-accounts-amid-surge-in-crypto-scams</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19159173/X-offers-80-price-cut-for-gold-check-accounts-amid-surge-in-crypto-scams"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T18:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don't Underestimate Mobile Gaming: Qualcomm's Matthew Grossman]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/34Oil4Qu/dont-underestimate-mobile-gaming-qualcomms-matthew-grossman</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/34Oil4Qu/dont-underestimate-mobile-gaming-qualcomms-matthew-grossman"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Qualcomm product marketing manager Matthew Grossman tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin why mobile esports is exploding in popularity around the world—and dispels some of the misconceptions around mobile gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don't Underestimate Mobile Gaming: Qualcomm's Matthew Grossman]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19159196/Dont-Underestimate-Mobile-Gaming-Qualcomms-Matthew-Grossman</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19159196/Dont-Underestimate-Mobile-Gaming-Qualcomms-Matthew-Grossman"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Qualcomm product marketing manager Matthew Grossman tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin why mobile esports is exploding in popularity around the world—and dispels some of the misconceptions around mobile gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Drops 9.9%, Solana Memecoins Tank Over 20%: Is This The End Of The Dogecoin Killers?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19159187/Solana-Drops-99-Solana-Memecoins-Tank-Over-20-Is-This-The-End-Of-The-Dogecoin-Killers</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19159187/Solana-Drops-99-Solana-Memecoins-Tank-Over-20-Is-This-The-End-Of-The-Dogecoin-Killers"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T18:07:34.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Layer 1 Areon to Launch Mainnet on January 12]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fad6ade7</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/layer-1-areon-to-launch-mainnet-on-january-12/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T18:06:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. A highly anticipated layer 1 project, Areon Network, is launching their mainnet on January 12, remarking the start of the Areon ecosystem.
 
The date also coincides with Areon’s self-designated birthday: the day when their token AREA was first listed in 2023 on BSC.
 
What is Areon Network?
 
Areon stands out as a user-oriented, convenient infrastructure with a comprehensive network. Guided and backed by a foundation, this layer 1 project has a long-term plan for expansion.
 
The main currency, AREA, is used for all transaction fees as well as dApp usage. It has three main utilities within the network: staking, security and governance.Their website is a good place to learn more about the project.
 
What is the technical infrastructure? 
 
The Areon Chain is scalable and inte…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF Deadline Day: SEC Receives Updated S-1’s From All Crypto Issuers Except Hashdex]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fad6bc83</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-etf-deadline-sec-receives-updated-s-1s/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T18:06:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a highly anticipated week for the crypto industry, the approval or rejection of Bitcoin ETF applications hangs in the balance. As the largest asset managers in the world vie for SEC approval, recent updates in their filings have sparked optimism within the crypto community. 
 
Bitwise And VanEck Lead The Pack
 
According to FOX Journalist Eleanor Terret, all issuers, except Hashdex, a global crypto asset manager, have successfully submitted their updated S-1s (S-3 in Grayscale’s case) to the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) by the official deadline of 8 AM. 
 
Terret suggests that unless there is a last-minute filing from Hashdex, these issuers have completed their preparations and are theoretically ready to launch their Bitcoin ETF this week.
 
 
The filings submitted by cry…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OKX Lists BONK, JTO as Solana Tokens Plummet to Monthly Lows]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19159154/OKX-Lists-BONK-JTO-as-Solana-Tokens-Plummet-to-Monthly-Lows</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19159154/OKX-Lists-BONK-JTO-as-Solana-Tokens-Plummet-to-Monthly-Lows"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T18:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Devs Preserve Classic Nintendo Games With Ordinals]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212006</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212006/bitcoin-nintendo-ordinals-inscriptions-blockchain-games"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T18:04:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leaping well beyond monkey JPEGs, Ninjalerts has inscribed a Super Nintendo Entertainment System emulator on a satoshi.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gary Gensler Again Warns Against Investing in Crypto as Market Awaits Bitcoin ETF]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=212012</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/212012/gary-gensler-warns-against-investing-in-crypto-market-awaits-bitcoin-etf"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T17:56:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC chair warned of risks in crypto investments, highlighting compliance issues and volatility as several Bitcoin ETFs await SEC approval.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Chair Gensler Cautions Investors As Bitcoin ETF Launch Looms: Key Details Revealed]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fad1e1fc</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/gensler-cautions-investors-bitcoin-etf-launch-looms/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T17:46:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the crypto community eagerly awaits the SEC’s decision on Bitcoin ETF applications, SEC Chair Gary Gensler has issued a list of considerations for potential investors in the crypto market. 
 
Gensler, known for its skeptical stance on cryptocurrencies, aims to remind investors of the risks associated with the industry. The advisory serves as a timely reminder of the potential approval of Bitcoin ETF applications, which could provide a regulated entry point for retail and institutional investors.
 
SEC Chair Gensler Raises Alarm Ahead Of Bitcoin ETF Approval
 
In a recent communication on X (formerly Twitter), Gensler highlighted several key points for individuals contemplating investments in crypto assets. 
 
The SEC’s chair message emphasized the need for caution, as some entities offe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitwise Tops Bitcoin ETF Low-Fee Table, While Grayscale Bets on Size]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fadc5c63</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2024/01/08/bitwise-tops-bitcoin-etf-low-fee-table-while-grayscale-bets-on-size/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T17:29:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just one potential spot bitcoin ETF issuer has set a management fee above 1%, and many of the others are asking for less than 0.5%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former SEC Chair: Spot Bitcoin ETF Approval Is Inevitable, "There's Nothing Left to Decide"]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fade7097</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/markets/former-sec-chair-spot-bitcoin-etf-approval-is-inevitable-theres-nothing-left-to-decide"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T17:15:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A bold statement has emerged from a former U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Chair Jay Clayton, suggesting that the approval of a Spot Bitcoin Exchange-Traded Fund (ETF) is inevitable, stating that "there's nothing left to decide," in an interview with CNBC today.



The former SEC Chair's confident proclamation hints at an imminent breakthrough in the regulatory landscape for Bitcoin-related financial products. This assertion aligns with the growing sentiment within the Bitcoin community, eagerly anticipating the approval of a Spot Bitcoin ETF.
"I think approval is inevitable, there's nothing left to decide," Clayton said. "Is the Bitcoin underlying trading market something that is robust enough, efficacious enough, where you can rely on it? It is much better today than it was five years ago."
These statements imply that key concerns or considerations previously hindering the approval process have been sufficiently addressed, paving the way for an inevitable green light from the SEC.
This bold declaration underscores the evolving sentiment within regulatory circles, reflecting a growing acceptance and understanding of Bitcoin. The potential approval of a spot Bitcoin ETF is anticipated to mark a watershed moment in the financial sphere, enabling broader access for traditional investors seeking exposure to BTC through regulated investment vehicles.
"The last thing, and I think this is missed, is the technology to actually provide the product," the former SEC Chair continued. "The custodying, the create, the redeem. This is a big step, not just for Bitcoin but for finance generally."
The SEC is expected to approve spot Bitcoin ETFs by the end of day Wednesday. Bloomberg reported yesterday that if approved, the ETFs could be listed and starting to trade as soon as the next business day.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nik Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin, Cardano Kick 2024 Off Continuing 2023 Adoption Trend]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fadfb61e</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-cardano-kick-2024-off-2023-adoption-trend/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T17:07:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data shows Dogecoin and Cardano are among some of the assets that have continued to show the same adoption trend this year so far as in 2023.
 
Dogecoin & Cardano Have Observed Wallet Growth In The First Week Of 2024
 
In a new post on X, the on-chain analytics firm Santiment has talked about what the address growth of various cryptocurrencies in the sector has been like over the past year.
 
The relevant indicator here is the “total amount of holders,” which keeps track of the number of wallets of any asset that carries some non-zero balance on the blockchain.
 
 
When the value of this metric goes up, it can mean that investors are opening new addresses on the network currently, or old holders are investing again in the asset after having emptied out their addresses earlier. As such, thi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Spot Bitcoin ETF Applicants Submit Final Amendments With SEC]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fad9142f</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/10-spot-bitcoin-etf-applicants-submit-final-amendments-with-sec/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T16:58:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ten spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) applicants have filed their final amended registration statements with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). The amended filings reveal a fierce fee war among spot bitcoin ETF issuers. Grayscale charges the highest fee of 1.5% while Bitwise undercuts rivals with the lowest fee of 0.24%, applicable after a six-month fee waiver. Blackrock, the world’s largest asset manager, will charge 0.20% for the first 12 months and $5 billion, rising to 0.30% thereafter.
 
Spot Bitcoin ETFs Get Closer to Approval
 
Ten final amended registration statements for spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) flooded the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) by Monday’s 8 a.m. deadline. Bloomberg analyst James Seyffart shared on social media platfo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[As Crypto World Watches SEC, Chair Gensler Says (Again) That Sector is Dangerous]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fadae03e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/01/08/as-crypto-world-watches-sec-chair-gensler-says-again-that-sector-is-dangerous/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T16:46:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The entire crypto world and much of the U.S. financial sector is anxiously awaiting word from the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) on whether it will approve a spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF). SEC Chair Gary Gensler has chosen this moment to issue a broad warning about the hazards to investors of getting into digital assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Exchange Upbit Gets Full Licensing in Singapore]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fac40f14</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/01/08/crypto-exchange-upbit-gets-full-licensing-in-singapore/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T16:38:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Upbit said it is "poised to expand [its] range of offerings," having acquired a MPI license.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[L2 Crypto Token Stacks Leads With 29% Gain in Varied Week for Cryptocurrencies]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fac0ff14</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/l2-crypto-token-stacks-leads-with-29-gain-in-varied-week-for-cryptocurrencies/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T16:06:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week witnessed a 5% uptick in bitcoin’s value, while ethereum experienced a 1.6% dip over the same period. Leading the charge among the top 100 cryptocurrencies, stacks (STX) soared 29.2%, with osmosis (OSMOS) closely trailing with a 17% increase against the U.S. dollar. 
 
Mixed Week for Crypto: Stacks Witnesses 29% Surge, Heavy Losses for Many
 
Among the top 100 cryptocurrencies by market cap, eight have posted double-digit growth. These include STX, OSMOS, AKT, INJ, ARB, TIA, CORGIAI, and GMT. Specifically, STX surged over 29% this week, OSMOS climbed by 17%, and AKT ascended 16.4%.
 
Currently, STX boasts a market valuation of $2.78 billion and has seen $646 million in global trade volume in the past day. Other cryptos showing notable increases this week were SEI, BGB, BEAM, and …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Insider Claps Back: Threatens To Expose Criminals Of An Unprecedented Magnitude]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fac1195a</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-insider-expose-criminals/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T16:06:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Insider Steven Nerayoff has threatened to release more evidence on the alleged irregularities involving the network. His comment suggests that this evidence could have far-reaching consequences as it will expose “criminals on a magnitude that is unprecedented.”
 
Nerayoff Promises To Expose Criminals Posed As Altruists
 
Nerayoff stated in an X (formerly Twitter) post that he was soon going to unveil “data” that unmasks certain criminals that are currently posing as “altruists.” He noted that he had made good on his earlier promise of the recording. As such, the crypto community can also be certain that he will make good on this one, too. 
 
 
It is uncertain who these “altruists” might be. However, Nerayoff could be alluding to Ethereum founders Vitalik Buterin and Joe Lubin, as …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Bitcoin ETF Battle, Grayscale Is Bringing 'A Gun to a Knife Fight']]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fac1aa00</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2024/01/08/in-bitcoin-etf-battle-grayscale-is-bringing-a-gun-to-a-knife-fight/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T16:02:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Grayscale Bitcoin Trust's (GBTC) $27 billion of bitcoin and $350 million of daily volume gives Grayscale an advantage versus BlackRock and other wannabe rivals, according to Bloomberg's Eric Balchunas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Upbit Singapore Granted MPI License for Institutional Crypto Services]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74face89ee</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/upbit-singapore-granted-mpi-license-for-institutional-crypto-services/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T15:31:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS) has  
officially granted Upbit Singapore a Major Payment Institution (MPI) license,  
marking a pivotal advancement in its commitment to complying with the Payment  
Services Act 2019. 
Alex Kim, the Founder and CEO of Upbit Singapore,  
mentioned: "Singapore has emerged as a global hub for digital asset  
innovation, and its significance for institutional business cannot be overstated.  
Upbit Singapore is poised to be the nexus of institutional activities,  
capitalizing on Singapore's robust regulatory framework and its reputation as a  
leading financial center in Asia. 
"This license marks an important step for us to  
serve institutional and retail clients with cutting-edge digital asset  
solutions contributing to Singapore's thriving digita…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Key to Building Sustainable DePIN]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74facf47ec</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2024/01/08/the-key-to-building-sustainable-depin/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T15:26:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized Physical Infrastructure Networks (DePIN) are powerful uses of blockchain technology. But success depends on tokenomics built for the long-term, says the co-founder of Hivemapper.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ariel Seidman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Reclaims $45,000 As ETF Hopefuls Make Final Filings]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211993</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211993/bitcoin-reclaims-45000-as-etf-hopefuls-make-final-filings"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T13:35:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin has recovered the losses from last week's flash crash, as firms made their final amendments to their spot Bitcoin ETF applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock, VanEck, WisdomTree Reveal Bitcoin ETF Fees in Amended S-1 Filings]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211987</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211987/blackrock-vaneck-wisdomtree-reveal-bitcoin-etf-fees-in-amended-s-1-filings"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T12:50:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF hopefuls have filed a rush of amended S-1 forms as they race to meet the SEC's final deadline Monday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF Approval Odds Raised to 95%: Bloomberg Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211935</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211935/bitcoin-etf-approval-odds-raised-to-95-bloomberg-analyst"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T11:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Bloomberg Intelligence analyst puts the odds of a Bitcoin ETF being approved in January at 95%, as crunch time looms for the SEC's decision.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Transformed, Not Terminated: AI Researchers Weigh In on the Future]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211923</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211923/transformed-not-terminated-ai-researchers-weigh-in-on-the-future"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T10:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A large-scale survey of artificial intelligence researchers found few worried about extinction, but many sounding the alarm over employment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week on Crypto Twitter: ETF Fever Won’t Break]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211905</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211905/this-week-on-crypto-twitter-etf-fever-wont-break"/>
        <updated>2024-01-07T12:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rumors and predictions about a looming spot Bitcoin ETF approval ran rampant this week, spiking nerves and crypto prices alike.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETFs Take a Big Step Toward Approval, Analysts Say]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211876</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211876/bitcoin-spot-etf-applications-sec"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T23:02:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock's application led the way on Friday, as an ETF analyst predicted that we could see a $100 billion Bitcoin ETF in as little as five years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report Crypto Trades Over $10K to IRS or Face Jail? It’s Complicated]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211843</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211843/crypto-trades-10k-irs-jail-complicated"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T21:11:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new tax law appears to have massive implications for crypto users. But who it might affect, and when, is not so straightforward.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF: This Is the 'Calm Before the Storm', Says ETF Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/VOX04ytt/bitcoin-etf-this-is-the-calm-before-the-storm-says-etf-analyst</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/VOX04ytt/bitcoin-etf-this-is-the-calm-before-the-storm-says-etf-analyst"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T20:20:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bloomberg Senior ETF Analyst Eric Balchunas joins Farokh Sarmad, Michael Anderson, and Ovie Faruq on the FOMO Hour to share the latest intel on the looming approval for a spot Bitcoin ETF, what might happen when the very different worlds of TradFi and crypto collide, and his insights on “Genslish,” the unique and strategic language of SEC chair Gary Gensler.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pixels Game Airdrop Announced—Here’s How to Get Pixel Tokens]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211855</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211855/pixels-game-airdrop-announced-heres-how-to-get-pixel-tokens"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T18:52:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Airdrops continue to keep crypto believers enthralled, further fueled by Pixels’ latest announcement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic Says It Won’t Use Your Private Data to Train Its AI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211846</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211846/anthropic-says-it-wont-use-your-private-data-to-train-its-ai"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T18:44:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As AI companies hungrily consume every trove of data they can find, the makers of Claude.AI say they won’t their its own customers' work to improve its chatbot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Bitcoin's Time Has Arrived': ETF Hopefuls Eagerly Await SEC Decision]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211839</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211839/whats-happening-with-the-bitcoin-etf-today"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T16:54:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETF hopeful Hashdex releases a Bitcoin advert as analysts speculate that the SEC’s decision on Bitcoin ETFs may be imminent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celsius to Unstake $466 Million Ethereum Holdings, 'Ensure Ample Liquidity' for Creditors]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211799</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211799/celsius-to-unstake-466-million-ethereum-holdings-ensure-ample-liquidity-for-creditors"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T10:39:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celsius accounts for almost a third of ETH awaiting withdrawal, as it begins "recalling and rebalancing assets" ahead of asset distributions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saga Airdrop Coming Ahead of Blockchain Launch—Here’s Who Is Eligible]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211794</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211794/who-is-eligible-for-the-saga-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T00:29:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some Polygon, Avalanche, Cosmos, and Celestia users will be included in Saga’s community token airdrop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘We’re Not Here to Sell You Another ChatGPT’: Perplexity AI CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211784</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211784/perplexity-ai-answer-engine-not-another-chatbot"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T00:15:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Co-founder Aravind Srinivas wants to change the perception of generative AI through a trustworthy "answer engine."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana’s LFG Token Lures Ethereum Users, Plans Second Airdrop and Grants Program]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211778</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211778/solana-lfg-ethereum-users-second-airdrop-grants-program"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T22:54:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana's “Less Fn Gas” airdropped LFG tokens to Ethereum users who spent over $4,269 in gas over the last year. It doesn't want to stop there.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Logan Paul Launches CryptoZoo NFT ‘Buyback,’ Files Countersuit As Legal Battles Rage On]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211776</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211776/logan-paul-launches-cryptozoo-nft-buyback-files-countersuit-as-legal-battles-rage-on"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T22:06:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The famous YouTuber and influencer alleges two of his CryptoZoo co-creators engaged in “nefarious trading activity.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blame Human Lawyers, Not Tech, for Courtroom Blunders: Robin AI Cofounder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211764</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211764/uk-startup-raises-26-million-to-build-law-ai"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T21:42:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robin AI is taking on hallucinations and other thorny issues to ensure tech is an effective courtroom partner.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Financial Advisors Are Still Skeptical SEC Approves Bitcoin ETF, Bitwise Says]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211770</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211770/financial-advisors-are-still-skeptical-sec-approves-bitcoin-etf-bitwise-says"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T21:01:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Only 39% of 437 financial advisors polled said they think we'll see a Bitcoin ETF available to U.S. investors in 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beam Token Up 36% as Merit Circle Network Transactions Hit All-Time High]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211737</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211737/beam-token-up-merit-circle-transactions-hit-all-time-high"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T20:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Avalanche subnet token is climbing back toward its highest price ever.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Adds Dedicated AI Key to Windows 11 Keyboard]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211739</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211739/microsoft-copilot-keyboard-dedicated-key"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T19:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cortana didn’t fare much better than Clippy, but the Redmond-based tech giant is betting that Copilot will finally earn its spot at our fingertips.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nikon, Sony, and Canon Pitch a New Way to Fight Deepfakes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211744</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211744/nikon-sony-and-canon-pitch-a-new-way-to-fight-deepfakes"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T19:08:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Instead of watermarking AI images, top cameramakers propose encoding signatures into real photos instead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale, VanEck and ARK Bitcoin ETFs Register to Trade on Exchanges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211735</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211735/grayscale-and-vaneck-bitcoin-etfs-register-to-trade-on-exchanges"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T18:46:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two more Bitcoin ETF applicants have gotten the green light to have their funds listed on exchanges—but it's all pending SEC approval.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Rebounds From Flash Crash as Market Fixates on ETF]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211732</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211732/bitcoin-rebounds-flash-crash-btc-etf-price"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T17:37:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC has recovered losses after slipping briefly yesterday on fears that Bitcoin ETFs might again be denied or delayed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Privacy Coins Monero, Zcash, Horizen 'At Risk' of Delisting by Binance]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211717</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211717/privacy-coins-monero-zcash-horizen-at-risk-of-delisting-by-binance"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T11:16:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance has flagged several privacy coins with a "monitoring tag" indicating that they are at risk of being delisted from its platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here's What's Coming to Xbox Game Pass]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208162</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208162/heres-whats-coming-xbox-game-pass"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T00:34:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft's Xbox Game Pass is adding more indie games to its subscription service, as well as a few big names. Here's a look at the lineup.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF: Is It Priced In?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211708</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211708/bitcoin-etf-priced-in"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T22:34:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Analysts are split on whether the long-awaited approval of a Bitcoin ETF will halt BTC’s momentum, or pump the cryptocurrency even higher.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fidelity Bitcoin ETF Set to Trade on CBOE—But No Word From SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211702</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211702/fidelity-bitcoin-etf-set-to-trade-on-cboe-but-no-word-from-sec"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T20:47:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Fidelity Wise Origin Bitcoin Trust got the ok to trade on the CBOE under the FBTC ticker, but there's still no word from the SEC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Supreme Court Justice Ponders Impact of AI on Law]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211696</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211696/supreme-court-justice-warns-of-ais-impact-on-legal-system"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T20:29:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Justice Roberts emphasized AI's ability to aid people, but also 'dehumanize' the legal processes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Before AI Puts Us Out of Work, AI Jobs Could Pay Well]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211675</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211675/before-ai-puts-us-out-of-work-ai-jobs-could-pay-well"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T19:36:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI jobs are paying on average 77% more than other jobs, with entry-level positions paying more than twice the average salary.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Possible Scenarios for Bitcoin ETFs in 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211560</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211560/three-possible-scenarios-bitcoin-etf-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T19:19:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Will they or won’t they? The SEC is on the clock and crypto markets eagerly await its decision on a Bitcoin ETF. Here’s what could happen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Losing 1500 BTC on Mt Gox and the Problem with Women in Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/EfNuNu8a/losing-1500-btc-on-mt-gox-and-the-problem-with-women-in-web3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/EfNuNu8a/losing-1500-btc-on-mt-gox-and-the-problem-with-women-in-web3"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T19:02:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week our host is joined by Brooke Lacey! 

They discuss:  
- Making and losing generational wealth
- Trauma Bond
- Women in Web3
- The Problem with WAGMI]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gaming Tokens IMX, SAND and AXS Plunge Following Bitcoin Flash Crash]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211671</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211671/gaming-tokens-imx-sand-and-axs-plunge-following-bitcoin-flash-crash"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T18:33:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Immutable, The Sandbox, Axie Infinity, and Gala tokens dropped 8-15%, facing deeper losses after Bitcoin’s dip.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Ordinals Upgrade Could Create a Centralized Fork, Says BRC-20 Creator]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211665</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211665/bitcoin-ordinals-upgrade-could-be-unsafe-create-centralized-fork"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T18:14:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest drama in Bitcoin inscriptions swirls around the BRC-20 protocol, which allows the creation of meme coins.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bearish Bitcoin ETF Report Spooks Market—But Analysts Say Denial Is Unlikely]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211658</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211658/bearish-bitcoin-etf-report-spooks-market-analysts-say-denial-unlikely"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T17:09:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A line about approval by Q2 2024 didn’t calm fears. The suggestion that none of the ETF applications will be approved in January panicked the market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana's MixMob Launches 'Race-to-Earn' Game Ahead of Airdrop, Saga Phone Perks]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211637</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211637/solanas-mixmob-launches-race-earn-game-ahead-airdrop-saga-phone-perks"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T15:01:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MixMob's Racer 1 lets players gamble on races or earn crypto for wins. An airdrop is coming, along with benefits for Solana Saga owners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Plunges 7% to $42,000 in Flash Crash as Bull Run Falters]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211634</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211634/bitcoin-plunges-7-to-42000-in-flash-crash-as-bull-run-falters"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T12:33:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price of Bitcoin plunged by over 7% in the past 24 hours, erasing the past week's gains in a matter of minutes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Saylor to Sell $216 Million in MicroStrategy Stock Options, Buy More Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211626</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211626/michael-saylor-to-sell-216-million-in-microstrategy-stock-options-buy-more-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T11:15:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy co-founder Michael Saylor plans to "acquire additional Bitcoin" for his personal holdings with some of the proceeds of the sale.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Powered Cybercrime Will Explode in 2024: CrowdStrike Executive]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211596</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211596/ai-powered-cybercrime-will-explode-in-2024-crowdstrike-executive"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T02:08:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security exec Shawn Henry says the capability of AI to deceive and misinform is coming of age just in time for the 2024 elections.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Midjourney Leaps into AI Video Creation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211583</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211583/midjourney-leaps-into-ai-video-creation"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T01:16:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AI image generator MidJourney will begin training its video model in the upcoming days and they expect to release a final product "in a few months"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s When to Expect the Jupiter JUP Airdrop for Solana DeFi Users]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211576</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211576/heres-when-expect-jupiter-jup-airdrop-solana-defi-users"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T00:56:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jupiter’s airdrop draws nearer and nearer. Here’s when the Solana DEX aggregator plans to launch JUP to the community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ESL Faceit Group Exploring Blockchain 'Opportunistically,' Says Exec]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/yvrs4lBx/esl-faceit-group-exploring-blockchain-opportunistically-says-exec</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/yvrs4lBx/esl-faceit-group-exploring-blockchain-opportunistically-says-exec"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T02:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Braithwaite—ESL Faceit Group's VP of Game Ecosystems, Mobile, and Snapdragon Pro Series—shares the esports firm's approach to blockchain technology with GG's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bryan Johnson Explains His Quest for Immortality and Why He Started with the Penis]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tAwP55g9/bryan-johnson-explains-his-quest-for-immortality-and-why-he-started-with-the-penis</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tAwP55g9/bryan-johnson-explains-his-quest-for-immortality-and-why-he-started-with-the-penis"/>
        <updated>2023-12-24T19:38:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Billionaire biohacker Bryan Johnson shared with Decrypt's Jason Nelson why he began his longevity quest and how technology has shaped the endeavor. Johnson also discusses some of his controversial experiments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wildcard's Plans for 2024 with Founders Paul and Katy Bettner]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/TI3aFBhO/wildcards-plans-for-2024-with-founders-paul-and-katy-bettner</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/TI3aFBhO/wildcards-plans-for-2024-with-founders-paul-and-katy-bettner"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T21:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wildcard developers Paul and Katy Bettner tell Decrypt's Kate Irwin about why they see their game as a "Web3 game," not a crypto game, and share why they've stuck with their initial vision despite the challenging broader market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt and Rug Radio Merge to Create Global Web3 Publishing Company]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/VTEBYFD8/decrypt-and-rug-radio-merge-to-create-global-web3-publishing-company</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/VTEBYFD8/decrypt-and-rug-radio-merge-to-create-global-web3-publishing-company"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T17:04:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt and Rug Radio have announced their intent to merge, creating the world’s biggest decentralized publishing company. Codenamed [REDACTED], the alliance is aimed at revolutionizing tech-media, bringing together the forces of content creation and consumption.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['If You Play Well, You're Gonna be Rewarded': How FPS Web3War is Bringing 'Skill-to-Earn' to Crypto Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Jl5AEFuD/if-you-play-well-youre-gonna-be-rewarded-how-fps-web3war-is-bringing-skill-to-earn-to-crypto-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Jl5AEFuD/if-you-play-well-youre-gonna-be-rewarded-how-fps-web3war-is-bringing-skill-to-earn-to-crypto-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T10:20:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roll1ng Thund3rz co-founder Valentin Cobelea and Zilliqa CEO Matt Dyer joined Decrypt to discuss how the new FPS game Web3War is shaking up the crypto gaming space with a novel "skill to earn" mechanic that rewards players for high-quality gameplay.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating peaceful money & taking over your local government w/ Joseph Schiarizzi]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zb0VG27G/creating-peaceful-money-taking-over-your-local-government-w-joseph-schiarizzi</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zb0VG27G/creating-peaceful-money-taking-over-your-local-government-w-joseph-schiarizzi"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T23:23:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week our host Reza Jafery is joined by Joseph Schiarizzi, founder of OpenDollar and prolific solidity developer. 


We discuss: 
- Onchain beer
- Taking over your local government
- His Emmy and 3 patents?!?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>