<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-10-13T03:26:01.376Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-10-13T03:26:01.376Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can Solana’s $5B DeFi milestone help rescue SOL’s price action?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19998082/Can-Solanas-5B-DeFi-milestone-help-rescue-SOLs-price-action</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19998082/Can-Solanas-5B-DeFi-milestone-help-rescue-SOLs-price-action"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T03:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana has hit several new milestones in the recent past, but the token might face trouble ahead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Singaporean Exchange Fairdesk Announces Plan To Shut Down – Details]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e744111d088</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/singaporean-exchange-fairdesk-to-shut-down/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T02:51:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Singaporean cryptocurrency exchange Fairdesk has unveiled plans to wind down its operations in the coming month. This move comes as a surprise, as there had been no prior indications of difficulties facing the platform. However, it aligns with a broader trend of exchanges shutting down amid increasingly strict crypto regulations imposed by national authorities. 
 
 
Fairdesk To Cease Operations By November 30
 
Fairdesk was launched in 2021 by former Binance and Morgan Stanley executives and has since gained a reputation for offering advanced trading features that cater to both new and veteran traders. In a recent X post, the management of Fairdesk shared the exchange would be discontinuing its operations effective November 30. 
 
This has come as an unexpected development for the crypto e…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Semilore Faleti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JPMorgan CEO Jamie Dimon Warns of ‘Treacherous’ Global Tensions — and It’s Getting Worse]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74411343ec</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/jpmorgan-ceo-jamie-dimon-warns-of-treacherous-global-tensions-and-its-getting-worse/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T02:27:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JPMorgan Chase CEO Jamie Dimon sounded the alarm on mounting global instability, warning it could spark far-reaching economic disruptions. The executive stressed the toll of geopolitical tensions and the looming risks of fiscal deficits and remilitarization. With uncertainty escalating, Dimon urged vigilance, emphasizing that these crises could reshape both the economy and the course of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Companies paid $19B in Settlements to US Regulators in 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19998046/Crypto-Companies-paid-19B-in-Settlements-to-US-Regulators-in-2024</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19998046/Crypto-Companies-paid-19B-in-Settlements-to-US-Regulators-in-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T02:26:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since 2019, US regulators have collected a total of $31.92 billion in settlements against 25 crypto companies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robert Kiyosaki Predicts ‘Everything Crash’: Bitcoin May Drop to $5,000 Amid Market Collapse]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74411f28b1</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/robert-kiyosaki-predicts-everything-crash-bitcoin-may-drop-to-5000-amid-market-collapse/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T01:26:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rich Dad Poor Dad author Robert Kiyosaki predicts a catastrophic stock market crash and the collapse of “The Everything Bubble,” warning that gold, silver, and bitcoin will nosedive, triggering a global depression. He urges investors to brace for financial turmoil, saying only the prepared will emerge wealthier from the ruins. “Take bitcoin for example… it […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CZ Drops Major AI Warning: What Binance’s Founder Wants You To Know]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74411f5b07</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/cz-drops-major-ai-warning-what-binances-founder-wants-you-to-know/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T01:22:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The co-founder and former CEO of crypto exchange Binance, Changpeng Zhao, has issued a warning to the general public and the cryptocurrency community regarding the emergence of numerous of deepfake videos created by artificial intelligence and their potential to trick gullible and unsuspecting users into making false or fraudulent cryptocurrency investments.
 
 
A Public Warning Against AI Deepfakes
 
Zhao further expounded on the imminent threat from impersonation using AI and fraud in cyberspace. Zhao’s warning comes at the back of increasing AI scams that not only hit the crypto world but also international giants such as Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse and even famous celebrities like Taylor Swift.
 
 
Former Binance CEO warns of deepfake scams on social media
 
Former Binance CEO Changpe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$SOLMER: The Token Powering SolMerch - A New Era for Crypto Fashion and Merch!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19997991/SOLMER-The-Token-Powering-SolMerch-A-New-Era-for-Crypto-Fashion-and-Merch</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19997991/SOLMER-The-Token-Powering-SolMerch-A-New-Era-for-Crypto-Fashion-and-Merch"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T01:16:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey Redditors and crypto enthusiasts! 🚀 Introducing $SOLMER, the utility token that is set to revolutionize the world of decentralized fashion and merchandise. Whether you're a collector, crypto lover, or fashion-forward, this token and its associated marketplace offer something unique and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Whales Hoard $90 Million In Bitcoin: A Sign Of What’s To Come?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19997988/Whales-Hoard-90-Million-In-Bitcoin-A-Sign-Of-Whats-To-Come</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19997988/Whales-Hoard-90-Million-In-Bitcoin-A-Sign-Of-Whats-To-Come"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T01:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin whales have stockpiled $90 billion in BTC since May, a period marked by range-bound market conditions. According to an open disclosure by Axel Adler Jr. of CryptoQuant, investors holding over 1,000 BTC have seen rapid growth in their balances. Related Reading: Helium (HNT) Falters 15% As...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Fires Back at SEC: Cross-Appeal Seeks to Overturn Unresolved XRP Issues]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74411ab877</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ripple-fires-back-at-sec-cross-appeal-seeks-to-overturn-unresolved-xrp-issues/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T00:26:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple has escalated its legal battle with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), filing a cross-appeal to challenge unresolved issues around XRP sales. This comes after the SEC sought to overturn parts of the rulings that cleared Ripple’s retail XRP transactions from securities violations. Ripple’s latest move aims to ensure the SEC’s arguments on […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock AUM Hits $11.48T Amid Market Rally, Private Expansion]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19997958/BlackRock-AUM-Hits-1148T-Amid-Market-Rally-Private-Expansion</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19997958/BlackRock-AUM-Hits-1148T-Amid-Market-Rally-Private-Expansion"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T00:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock’s assets under management soared to a record $11.48 trillion in the third quarter, helped by robust market inflows. It’s the third consecutive quarter of record growth, driven by the U.S. stock market rally and rising client demand for private market investments. BlackRock continues to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why The Dogecoin Price Will Never Touch $100, But Shiba Inu Can Reach $0.001, And ETFSwap Will Jump 30000X To $4]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74411ae85c</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/why-the-dogecoin-price-will-never-touch-100-but-shiba-inu-can-reach-0-001-and-etfswap-will-jump-30000x-to-4/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T00:23:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the crypto market, market sentiments have often dictated the price movement of any digital asset. Presently, the narrative surrounding Dogecoin has shattered dreams as analysts predict it will never touch the $100 mark. On the other hand, Shiba Inu’s potential to reach $0.001 is acknowledged, and ETFSwap (ETFS) is expected to bring the most value as ETFS is expected to jump 30,000x to $4 in weeks.
 
ETFSwap (ETFS): A Promising Platform With 30,000x Potential 
ETFSwap (ETFS) is a highly liquid asset platform that offers tokenized exchange-traded funds to investors seeking to make more gains by spreading their assets across multiple industries through crypto. These ETFs range from real estate, agriculture, equity, fixed-income, commodities, and other ETF currencies.
 
Many factors that co…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum-Based Virtual Reality Platform Decentraland Tops Santiment’s Rankings of NFT Projects by Development]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19997930/Ethereum-Based-Virtual-Reality-Platform-Decentraland-Tops-Santiments-Rankings-of-NFT-Projects-by-Development</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19997930/Ethereum-Based-Virtual-Reality-Platform-Decentraland-Tops-Santiments-Rankings-of-NFT-Projects-by-Development"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T00:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ethereum (ETH)-based virtual reality platform Decentraland (MANA) clocked more notable development activity than any other non-fungible token (NFT) project in the past month, according to the crypto analytics firm Santiment. Santiment notes on the social media platform X that Decentraland...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PEPE’s selling pressure hike can push memecoin’s price to…]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19997928/PEPEs-selling-pressure-hike-can-push-memecoins-price-to</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19997928/PEPEs-selling-pressure-hike-can-push-memecoins-price-to"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T00:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Selling pressure on PEPE increased. Can this result in a price correction?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Bitcoin Miners Are Tapping Into the AI Gold Rush – Part 1]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e744106659d</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/how-bitcoin-miners-are-tapping-into-the-ai-gold-rush-part-1/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T23:26:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The following guest post comes from Bitcoinminingstock.io, the one-stop hub for all things bitcoin mining stocks, educational tools, and industry insights. Originally published on Aug. 29, 2024, it was penned by Bitcoinminingstock.io author Cindy Feng. In the piece, Feng explores how bitcoin miners are branching out into high-performance computing (HPC) and artificial intelligence (AI) cloud […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Guest Author</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$KEYCAT on BASE to multiple billions]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19997844/KEYCAT-on-BASE-to-multiple-billions</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19997844/KEYCAT-on-BASE-to-multiple-billions"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T22:29:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by   /u/Zilivanili [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elizabeth Warren vs. Innovation: It’s Time for Massachusetts to Choose]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7441028ecf</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/elizabeth-warren-vs-innovation-its-time-for-massachusetts-to-choose/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T22:24:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elizabeth Warren has been a major political figure in Massachusetts for over a decade. While she’s known for championing consumer protection and taking on big banks, her stance on modern financial innovation—particularly her aggressive opposition to cryptocurrency—shows that her leadership is increasingly out of touch with today’s fast-changing economy. Massachusetts needs fresh leadership that embraces […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Friedman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Latam Insights: Venezuela Reaches Crypto Milestone, Consortium Announces Real Stablecoin]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7441028ecd</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/latam-insights-venezuela-reaches-crypto-milestone-consortium-announces-real-stablecoin/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T22:24:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Latam Insights, a compendium of Latin America’s most relevant crypto and economic news from the past week. In this issue, Chainalysis states Venezuela was the country where cryptocurrency markets grew most last year, Brazilian giants team to launch a real-pegged stablecoin, and Littio leveraged Avalanche to offer yield-bearing dollar-based savings accounts. Chainalysis Latam […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Influencer Says You’ll Wish You Bought More XRP In 5 Years, Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e744102a3b3</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/youll-wish-you-bought-xrp/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T22:23:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ben Armstrong, widely recognized as BitBoy across social media platforms, has once again attracted attention from members of the crypto community with his firm endorsement of XRP. In a recent post on X, the influential crypto commentator emphasized the significance of investing in XRP at its current price level. 
 
BitBoy underscored his belief that potential investors who overlook the current opportunity to acquire XRP may regret their decision after the next five years. His remarks seem to be anchored in anticipation of a substantial surge in the price of XRP in the next five years.
 
BitBoy Remains Bullish On XRP
 
BitBoy is one of the most popular names among crypto traders and investors. The crypto influencer is particularly known for his bullish stance on the industry, with XRP havin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK man takes Newport City Council to court for $647M over Bitcoin buried in landfill]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19997837/UK-man-takes-Newport-City-Council-to-court-for-647M-over-Bitcoin-buried-in-landfill</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19997837/UK-man-takes-Newport-City-Council-to-court-for-647M-over-Bitcoin-buried-in-landfill"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T22:15:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[James Howells is taking Newport City Council to court, demanding $647 million (£495 million) for 8,000 Bitcoins that he lost after a hard drive was mistakenly dumped in a landfill in 2013. The 39-year-old IT engineer says this is his “last resort” after years of being ignored by the council....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Memecoins to the moon in Q4? Here’s why FLOKI could lead the charge]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19997826/Memecoins-to-the-moon-in-Q4-Heres-why-FLOKI-could-lead-the-charge</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19997826/Memecoins-to-the-moon-in-Q4-Heres-why-FLOKI-could-lead-the-charge"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T22:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FLOKI is leading the memecoin rally, with the larger memecoin market seeing some momentum too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former President Trump leads Harris by 10 points — Polymarket]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19997797/Former-President-Trump-leads-Harris-by-10-points-Polymarket</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19997797/Former-President-Trump-leads-Harris-by-10-points-Polymarket"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T21:42:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to Polymarket users, Vice President Kamala Harris is currently favored to win the popular vote by a staggering 72% margin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETFs Climb With $253M Inflows as Ethereum Funds Show Weakness]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74410e9816</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-etfs-climb-with-253m-inflows-as-ethereum-funds-show-weakness/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T21:24:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Friday, the 12 U.S. spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) shook things up, recording net inflows of $253.54 million. Meanwhile, the nine spot ethereum ETFs had a rougher day, with modest outflows totaling around $97,110. Friday’s Crypto ETF Action The spot bitcoin ETFs saw gains, pulling in $253.54 million in total on Oct. 11. Fidelity’s […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arbitrum DAO member proposes $120 million recall from gaming fund that missed deadlines]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19997763/Arbitrum-DAO-member-proposes-120-million-recall-from-gaming-fund-that-missed-deadlines</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19997763/Arbitrum-DAO-member-proposes-120-million-recall-from-gaming-fund-that-missed-deadlines"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T21:12:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CEO and an employee of Offchain Labs, which develops Arbitrum, have countered that complex logistics have led to the program's apparent delays.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What chances of an Uptober are there left for Bitcoin now?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19997729/What-chances-of-an-Uptober-are-there-left-for-Bitcoin-now</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19997729/What-chances-of-an-Uptober-are-there-left-for-Bitcoin-now"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T20:35:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin is not having the Uptober many were hoping for. Historically, October has been a good month for the apex crypto. The term “Uptober” comes from past performances, with Bitcoin averaging 22.9% gains in this month since 2013. Some years, like 2021, saw even bigger gains, like the 40% jump....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thousands Drained From Elderly Man’s Bank Account in Sophisticated ‘Hi Dad’ Email Scheme As Lender Remains Silent: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19997728/Thousands-Drained-From-Elderly-Mans-Bank-Account-in-Sophisticated-Hi-Dad-Email-Scheme-As-Lender-Remains-Silent-Report</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19997728/Thousands-Drained-From-Elderly-Mans-Bank-Account-in-Sophisticated-Hi-Dad-Email-Scheme-As-Lender-Remains-Silent-Report"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T20:34:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An elderly parent is reportedly devastated after scammers contacted him via email masquerading as his own daughter. Françoise Schorosch says the criminals said all the right things to her father online, perfectly mimicking the way she writes partially in German and partially in English, The...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Is Why Altcoin Season May Be Closer Than You Think]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19997743/Here-Is-Why-Altcoin-Season-May-Be-Closer-Than-You-Think</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19997743/Here-Is-Why-Altcoin-Season-May-Be-Closer-Than-You-Think"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October has so far been marked by a decline in the value of many altcoins. Due to political tensions in the Middle East, global cryptocurrency market capitalization has plummeted by 6% over the past ten days. However, as market sentiment begins to recover and fear subsides, analysts point to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TRAC and TAP Protocol: An Innovative Bitcoin Layer One Solution]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74410aedcd</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/trac-and-tap-protocol-an-innovative-bitcoin-layer-one-solution/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T20:22:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Until recently, the Bitcoin ecosystem hasn’t seen much development. Now it is rapidly evolving, with numerous projects aiming to enhance Bitcoin’s scalability and functionality. In this early stage, there are many methods being tried out to expand Bitcoin’s rather limited capabilities from sidechains to layer twos (L2). One of the more novel approaches is TRAC […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Sencil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is ‘Off the Grid’? The Buzzy Battle Royale Shooter Built on Avalanche]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285941</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-off-the-grid-battle-royale-shooter-avalanche"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T20:10:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Off the Grid just launched on PS5, Xbox, and PC in early access, and it's already a hit with players—oh, and it's a blockchain game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Stubbs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is ‘Off the Grid’? The Buzzy Battle Royale Shooter Built on Avalanche]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19997699/What-Is-Off-the-Grid-The-Buzzy-Battle-Royale-Shooter-Built-on-Avalanche</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19997699/What-Is-Off-the-Grid-The-Buzzy-Battle-Royale-Shooter-Built-on-Avalanche"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T20:10:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Off the Grid just launched on PS5, Xbox, and PC in early access, and it's already a hit with players—oh, and it's a blockchain game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[#Bitcoin's best quarters historically, are Q1 &amp; Q4.

We're just into the new quarter which has started off choppy.

Where do you think it ends by the end of the year?

The average return in Q4 is +81.11% which is largely due to 3 good years (2013, 2017 &amp; 2020).]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19997705/Bitcoins-best-quarters-historically-are-Q1-amp-Q4-Were-just-into-the-new-quarter-which-has-started-off-choppy-Where-do-you-think-it-ends-by-the-end-of-the-year-The-average-return-in-Q4-is-8111-which-is-largely-due-to-3-good-years-2013-2017-amp-2020</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19997705/Bitcoins-best-quarters-historically-are-Q1-amp-Q4-Were-just-into-the-new-quarter-which-has-started-off-choppy-Where-do-you-think-it-ends-by-the-end-of-the-year-The-average-return-in-Q4-is-8111-which-is-largely-due-to-3-good-years-2013-2017-amp-2020"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T20:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Ticks Up in Price As Bankrupt Crypto Exchange Mt. Gox Delays Deadline for Long-Awaited BTC Repayments]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19997687/Bitcoin-Ticks-Up-in-Price-As-Bankrupt-Crypto-Exchange-Mt-Gox-Delays-Deadline-for-Long-Awaited-BTC-Repayments</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19997687/Bitcoin-Ticks-Up-in-Price-As-Bankrupt-Crypto-Exchange-Mt-Gox-Delays-Deadline-for-Long-Awaited-BTC-Repayments"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T20:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) surged by more than 6% on Friday amid news that the bankrupt crypto exchange Mt. Gox will extend the deadline on its remaining creditor repayments. Mt. Gox started paying back its creditors in July and has “largely completed the Base Repayment, Early Lump-Sum Repayment, and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Todd named Satoshi on HBO, Mt. Gox repayment plan deadline postponed, and more: Hodler’s Digest, Oct. 6 – 12]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19997702/Peter-Todd-named-Satoshi-on-HBO-Mt-Gox-repayment-plan-deadline-postponed-and-more-Hodlers-Digest-Oct-6-12</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19997702/Peter-Todd-named-Satoshi-on-HBO-Mt-Gox-repayment-plan-deadline-postponed-and-more-Hodlers-Digest-Oct-6-12"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T20:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mt. Gox postponed the deadline to repay creditors, Canadian Bitcoin core developer Peter Todd was named Satoshi in HBO doco: Hodlers Digest]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xi and Putin might be way in over their heads with de-dollarization]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19997695/Xi-and-Putin-might-be-way-in-over-their-heads-with-de-dollarization</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19997695/Xi-and-Putin-might-be-way-in-over-their-heads-with-de-dollarization"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T20:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Xi Jinping and Vladimir Putin are leading efforts to knock the U.S. dollar down a peg. With Russia as the current chair of BRICS, and the Kazan summit set for October 22, both leaders are pushing to replace the dollar in global trade. The group (originally Brazil, Russia, India, China, and South...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analysts Consider These 2 Chains Might Become Ethereum Killers]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7442f7ca1c</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/analysts-consider-these-2-chains-might-become-ethereum-killers/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T19:20:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETC Group, a Bitwise-owned London-based fund issuer, examined the possibility of Solana and Aptos becoming the next Ethereum in its latest newsletter. Their analysts revealed that while these two chains have grown and enjoyed momentum, Ethereum is still the overall leader according to ETC Group’s Network Dominance Index. ETC Group Analysts Reinforce Ethereum Market Dominance […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Phaver Is a Web3 Socialfi Super App]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7442fcbafa</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/phaver-is-a-web3-socialfi-super-app/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T18:19:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an interview with Phaver’s CEO Joonatan Lintala and Ecosystem CFO Tomi Fyrqvist, we explore how this Web3-powered social platform aims to revolutionize social media by integrating blockchain technology and token-based incentives. Phaver’s Decentralized Social Media Puts Users in Control Phaver is a decentralized social media platform that integrates Web3 technologies, allowing users to take […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Sencil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock Is Selling Bitcoin To Buy Ethereum, Will This Bullishness Trigger Another Altcoin Season?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7442feb0a9</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/blackrock-bitcoin-buy-ethereum/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T17:56:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New reports have revealed that BlackRock, the world’s largest asset manager and American multinational investment company, is now selling Bitcoin (BTC) to buy Ethereum (ETH). Many market watchers propose that this unexpected investment change could trigger a bullish rally for Ethereum, potentially catalyzing another altcoin season. 
 
BlackRock Dumps Bitcoin For Ethereum
 
Lookonchain, a blockchain analytics tool has uncovered a shocking new transaction executed by asset manager, BlackRock. In its official X (formerly Twitter) account, Lookonchain disclosed that BlackRock has recently sold off 182 BTC, valued at $11.34 million. 
 
 
Around the same period, the blockchain analytics tool recorded BlackRock purchasing 7,574 ETH tokens, worth approximately $18.52 million. This surprising devel…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jailed Binance Employee’s Bail Application Denied Despite Medical Needs]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7442fa1a06</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/jailed-binance-employees-bail-application-denied-despite-medical-needs/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T17:17:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The judge in Abuja denied bail to Tigran Gambaryan, the jailed Binance employee and a U.S. citizen unlawfully detained in Nigeria. Despite meeting all the medical requirements for bail, the judge’s decision contradicts established Nigerian legal precedents. Gambaryan’s health has deteriorated significantly in prison, and he requires medical treatment that the prison cannot provide. His […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[POPCAT Bullish Revival Gathers Pace, Targeting Major $1.5 Resistance]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7442e754df</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/popcat-bullish-revival-gathers-pace/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T16:25:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[POPCAT is making waves in the crypto market with a powerful bullish revival, setting its sights on the formidable $1.5 all-time high. After a period of consolidation, the cryptocurrency has shifted gears, with momentum building as it approaches the significant milestone of $1.5.
 
As POPCAT approaches this key resistance level, this analysis aims to explore its recent price movements. By examining technical indicators, market sentiment, and crucial resistance levels, we seek to assess the potential for the meme coin to break through the $1.5 barrier. This evaluation will offer insights into the strength of the current rally and the likelihood of achieving new all-time highs.
 
What The Charts Reveal About POPCAT’s Rally
 
On the 4-hour chart, despite experiencing a pullback, POPCAT has sho…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Godspower Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accused $150M Crypto Fraudster Turns Fugitive After Disabling Ankle Monitor]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285882</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285882/accused-150m-crypto-fraudster-fugitive"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T15:57:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Horst Jicha is being treated as a fugitive after the accused crypto scammer's ankle monitor went dark and he skipped a pre-trial meeting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Takes Another Shot at $63.5K as China's Vague Fiscal Stimulus Deters Capital Shift]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7442e24d3f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/10/12/bitcoin-takes-another-shot-at-635k-as-chinas-vague-fiscal-stimulus-deters-capital-shift/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T15:56:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[China's highly-anticipated fiscal stimulus announcement fell short of expectations, reducing the likelihood of capital flows into Chinese equities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Is Today’s 'Captain Tsubasa: Rivals' Telegram Game Daily Combo]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=250928</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/captain-tsubasa-rivals-telegram-game-daily-combo"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T15:36:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anime soccer game Captain Tsubasa: Rivals gives out 5 million free daily balls ahead of the TON token airdrop. Here’s the combo for Saturday, October 12.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Are Today’s ‘X Empire’ Elon Musk Game Daily Combo, Riddle, and Rebus Solutions]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241078</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/todays-musk-empire-stock-exchange-daily-combo"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T15:35:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking for the X Empire daily combo and rebus solution for Saturday, October 12? Here are the latest boosts for the Telegram game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Crypto Trader Backs Pepe Unchained to Outperform NEIRO, Forecasts 100x Gains]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7442ee687f</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/top-crypto-trader-backs-pepe-unchained-to-outperform-neiro-forecasts-100x-gains/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T15:16:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new meme coin is going viral – and has raised $18.6 million before officially launching. Pepe Unchained (PEPU) is turning heads across the crypto space, with one top trader backing it to outperform NEIRO once it goes live. The trader even suggested PEPU holders could be in line for 100x (or more) gains. Popular […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tokenized US Treasuries Climb by $210M Since Crossing the $2 Billion Mark]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7442ee687e</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/tokenized-us-treasuries-climb-by-210m-since-crossing-the-2-billion-mark/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T15:16:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since surpassing the $2 billion milestone in tokenized U.S. Treasuries at the end of August, the sector has added another $210 million. The Blackrock USD Institutional Digital Liquidity Fund (BUIDL) still holds the top spot with a market cap of $531.88 million, reflecting a 3.32% rise over the last 30 days. Meanwhile, the Hashnote Short […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gotbit? Never Heard of It! Meme Coins Try to Distance Themselves]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285890</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285890/gotbit-charges-meme-coins-distance-themselves"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T22:39:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Numerous token projects now claim they have severed ties with market maker Gotbit after it was hit with market manipulation charges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Labs Co-Founder Donates $1 Million in XRP to Pro-Kamala Harris PAC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285904</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285904/ripple-cofounder-1-million-kamala-harris-election"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T22:23:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An FEC filing released this week shows that Chris Larsen donated more than 1,700,000 XRP to the Future Forward USA PAC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Napolitano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche Shooter 'Off the Grid' Becomes Top Free Title on Epic Games Store]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285896</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285896/avalanche-shooter-off-the-grid-becomes-top-free-title-on-epic-games-store"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T20:49:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following its early access release, the Avalanche-based battle royale shooter Off the Grid saw notable traction on the Epic Games Store.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Crypto Project World Liberty Financial Sets Token Sale Date]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285871</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285871/trump-world-liberty-financial-token-sale"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T20:40:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Donald Trump-backed DeFi project World Liberty Financial will launch its token sale for accredited investors next week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wall Street Is on a Bull Run—It’s Nothing Compared to Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285872</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285872/wall-street-bull-run-bitcoin-dominates"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T20:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The S&P 500 is up 60% over the last two years, but Bitcoin's price jump during the same span has crushed that mark.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prediction Markets Invite Insider Trading—And That’s a Good Thing, Experts Say]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285857</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285857/prediction-markets-insider-trading"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T19:36:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Platforms like Polymarket are attracting billions of dollars in bets, but appear to be doing little to prevent insider trading. Is that a flaw, or a feature?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When to Expect Season 2 of Telegram Crypto Game 'Hamster Kombat']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285855</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285855/hamster-kombat-telegram-season-2"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T19:01:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Players who withdrew their HMSTR tokens will have the option to deposit them into Hamster Kombat for benefits, the devs told Decrypt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy Aims to Be ‘Bitcoin Bank’ With Trillion-Dollar Valuation: Michael Saylor]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285838</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285838/microstrategy-bitcoin-bank-trillion-dollar"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T18:20:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With nearly $16 billion worth of Bitcoin in the bank, MicroStrategy's Michael Saylor shares big plans ahead for BTC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeLorean, Christopher Lloyd Reunite for Time Capsule Digital Collectibles]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285836</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285836/delorean-christopher-lloyd-reunite-for-time-capsule-digital-collectibles"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T18:15:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lloyd features in a new promo film for the digital collectibles, which unlock exclusive prizes including a new DeLorean EV.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk-Themed Telegram Game ‘X Empire’ Sets Airdrop Date]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285834</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285834/telegram-game-x-empire-airdrop-date"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T17:40:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The X token launch is less than two weeks away, and will follow X Empire’s brief “chill phase” season after the airdrop was delayed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Exec Ryan Salame Headed to Prison After Tucker Carlson Video Derails 'Dog Bite' Claim]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285811</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285811/ftx-ryan-salame-prison-tucker-carlson"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T16:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ryan Salame's latest request for a prison postponement wasn't granted, due in part to a Tucker Carlson video interview posted this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Christopher Lloyd Reunites With Delorean to Unveil the Time Capsule]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285684</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285684/christopher-lloyd-reunites-with-delorean-to-unveil-the-time-capsule"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T15:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DeLorean Labs will be giving away a brand new electric vehicle.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Press Releases</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Gets a Boost as Mt. Gox Postpones Repayments]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285812</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285812/bitcoin-mt-gox-postpones-repayments"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T15:29:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mt. Gox now has another full year to repay billions of dollars in Bitcoin to users of the hacked exchange. Here's why BTC is now rising.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward,Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Karate Combat Launches Layer-2 Network to License Game Model to Other Sports]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285706</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285706/karate-combat-layer2-license-game-model-up-token"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T14:16:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Karate Combat, a crypto-friendly fighting organization, is set to launch a layer-2 next year in a move to help other sports copy its betting app.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Has Been Stuck Trading Sideways After Halving—What's Different This Time?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285793</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285793/bitcoin-trading-sideways-whats-different"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T14:09:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some "components of this cycle, such as altcoin seasons or bull runs, might have different timelines than we’re used to seeing," an analyst said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Creditor Says Hedge Fund Owes Him for Claim It Bought at '42% Discount']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285785</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285785/ftx-creditor-sues-hedge-fund"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T12:10:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gierczyk sold his $1.59 million claim to the hedge fund last year at what he says was a 42% discount.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Exec Tigran Gambaryan Denied Bail Despite 'Meeting All the Requirements,' Says Family]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285782</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285782/binance-exec-tigran-gambaryan-denied-bail-despite-meeting-all-the-requirements-says-family"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T11:33:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gambaryan has "suffered countless health scares," the family spokesperson said in an emailed statement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla Reveals Autonomous Robotaxi and Robovan, Plans 2025 Self-Driving Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285760</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285760/the-future-should-look-like-the-future-elon-musk-says-at-robotaxi-reveal"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T06:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The late-night presentation showed off Tesla's new line of self-driving vehicles and updates to its Optimus robots.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From LinkedIn to LockedIn: Former FTX Exec Ryan Salame Shares Bizarre Prison Post]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285759</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285759/former-ftx-exec-ryan-salame-shares-bizarre-prison-post"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T05:45:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Salame, who once held a high-flying position at FTX, is now one of several executives to face consequences following the exchange's fall]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vismaya V</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Metaplanet Scoops Another $6.5 Million in Bitcoin, Doubling Down on Its October Spree]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285756</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285756/metaplanet-scoops-6-5-million-bitcoin-doubling-down-october-spree"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T05:08:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Metaplanet's latest purchase brings the company's total Bitcoin holdings to 748.502 BTC, reinforcing its long-term bet on the leading crypto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Holds Steady Despite SEC's Case Against Market Maker Cumberland DRW]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285754</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285754/bitcoin-price-holds-steady-despite-secs-case-against-market-maker-cumberland-drw"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T01:59:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Thursday, the SEC charged Cumberland DRW with various securities allegations, though bellwether Bitcoin has so far shrugged it off.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Sinclair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your Lifelike Zoom Clone May Soon be Taking Meetings For You. Here's How]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285732</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285732/your-lifelike-zoom-clone-may-soon-be-taking-meetings-for-you-heres-how"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T00:22:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Zoom prepares to launch lifelike AI clones in 2025, the company is banking on a rethink to workplace communication—for better or worse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who is Cumberland, the SEC's Latest Big Crypto Target?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285729</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285729/what-is-cumberland-sec-lawsuit-crypto"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T00:09:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC's latest target isn't exactly a household name. Yet, as a critical liquidity provider, Cumberland is one of crypto’s major players.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Napolitano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Justin Sun Is Now Prime Minister of Liberland—What Does That Even Mean?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285717</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285717/justin-sun-prime-minister-liberland"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T23:12:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Liberland is an imagined libertarian utopia on the Danube, where every system lives on-chain and the age of consent is 13.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto ETFs Still Hot, With Nearly 50% of U.S. Investors Planning to Buy: Charles Schwab]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285715</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285715/crypto-etfs-still-hot-nearly-50-u-s-investors-planning-buy"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T22:48:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Charles Schwab survey shows that there’s massive demand for new American Bitcoin and Ethereum exchange-traded funds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Labs Files Cross-Appeal as Battle With SEC Rages On]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285714</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285714/ripple-labs-cross-appeal-sec"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T22:23:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Labs moved to file a cross-appeal in its years-long legal battle with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission over XRP sales.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Falls Under $60,000 as $150 Million in Crypto Longs Get Rekt]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=284560</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/284560/bitcoin-falls-60000-150m-longs-rekt"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T21:55:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin dipped below the $60,000 mark Thursday after three weeks above that line. What's to blame for the latest cooldown?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Settles Charges With Trading Firm It Says Tricked Investors With AI 'Buzzwords']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285680</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285680/sec-trading-firm-tricked-investors-ai"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T20:40:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC has hit trading firm Rimar Capital with civil charges for allegedly lying to investors about its use of AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FBI Made a Profit From Ethereum Token Created to Catch Fraudsters]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285701</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285701/fbi-made-profit-ethereum-token"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T20:21:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An Ethereum token created by the FBI to foil market manipulators netted investigators around $14,500 in profit, on-chain data shows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Sues Crypto Trading Firm Cumberland, Again Alleges Solana and Polygon Are Securities]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285688</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285688/sec-sues-cumberland-solana-polygon"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T17:09:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC continued its crypto crackdown Thursday with charges against Cumberland, again calling Solana and other assets securities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward,Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TON Holders Top 100 Million Following 'Hamster Kombat' Telegram Game Airdrop]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285674</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285674/ton-holders-100-million-hamster-kombat-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T16:27:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More than 100 million wallets now hold TON as the Telegram-linked network has surged via tap-to-earn games like Hamster Kombat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Walrus Protocol is Reinventing Decentralized Storage]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285471</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285471/how-walrus-protocol-is-reinventing-decentralized-storage"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T16:23:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The decentralized storage protocol’s novel data encoding algorithm will unlock applications across AI, websites and social media.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentraland Desktop Client Preview]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qqzvDcTC/decentraland-desktop-client-preview</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qqzvDcTC/decentraland-desktop-client-preview"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T15:53:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum metaverse game Decentraland has shared an exclusive look at the visual and performance upgrades coming via its new desktop client.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Trader Murad Mahmudov talks about the Supercycle and how he chooses Meme Coins.]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Hj3nDp7G/crypto-trader-murad-mahmudov-talks-about-the-supercycle-and-how-he-chooses-meme-coins</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Hj3nDp7G/crypto-trader-murad-mahmudov-talks-about-the-supercycle-and-how-he-chooses-meme-coins"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T21:47:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Trader Murad Mahmudov talks about the Supercycle and how he chooses Meme Coins. Crypto stable, had sold off after China stocks fall. Crypto adopted faster than other tech: BlackRock. Crypto adoption to hit 8% of world population. CryptoCom recieves Wells notice from SEC. HBO documentary on Satoshi airs tonight. FTX bankruptcy plan approved by judge. Scroll airdrop may be imminent. Jupiter goes live on mobile iOS. Phantom rolls out support for Base. AAVE launches GHO on Base. Gensler may be replaced by Robinhood CLO. 87% of new token launches on SOL. National Bank of Bahrain creates BTC fund. BedRock DeFi allows BTC staking on ARB.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Memecoins take off, funding stays low, China stocks keep on rising!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/703mAYhV/memecoins-take-off-funding-stays-low-china-stocks-keep-on-rising</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/703mAYhV/memecoins-take-off-funding-stays-low-china-stocks-keep-on-rising"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T08:27:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR EP213. Memecoins take off, funding stays low, China stocks keep on rising!
Many altcoins & memecoins soar despite stable BTC. Funding rates continue to be low or negative. Crypto funds saw $147m of outflows last week. BTC remains best performing major assets this year. SUI breaks into the top 20 coins again. TAO leads top 100 away from memes, sifu shorts. $100m bridge to SOL over the last 7 days. Metaplanet buys $6.7m more BTC. ETH proposal aims to improve throughput 50%. EIGEN, OP, APT lead token unlocks this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Walrus Protocol Unlocks New Applications for Decentralized Data Storage]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kwEYLYWj/how-walrus-protocol-unlocks-new-applications-for-decentralized-data-storage</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kwEYLYWj/how-walrus-protocol-unlocks-new-applications-for-decentralized-data-storage"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T11:19:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mysten Labs Chief Scientist George Danezis joined Decrypt to talk about its new decentralized storage protocol Walrus, which promises to unlock new applications such as AI and social media, thanks to its novel Red Stuff data encoding algorithm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Coinbase Sees Crypto as a Bipartisan, 'Purple' Political Issue]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/YR2YmmwR/why-coinbase-sees-crypto-as-a-bipartisan-purple-political-issue</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/YR2YmmwR/why-coinbase-sees-crypto-as-a-bipartisan-purple-political-issue"/>
        <updated>2024-10-05T22:18:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase VP of Corporate and Business Development, Shan Aggarwal, joined Decrypt's Sander Lutz and Liz Napolitano at Messari Mainnet 2024 to discuss the exchange's efforts to grow mainstream crypto adoption—and how the changing political conversation around digital assets is rapidly playing a major role in that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Is Playing Offense—Not Just Defense—Against Crypto Crime, Says Head of Financial Investigations]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DiJ8D2Qc/binance-is-playing-offensenot-just-defenseagainst-crypto-crime-says-head-of-financial-investigations</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DiJ8D2Qc/binance-is-playing-offensenot-just-defenseagainst-crypto-crime-says-head-of-financial-investigations"/>
        <updated>2024-10-05T01:58:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nils Anderson Röed, the exchange’s global head of financial investigations, sat down with Decrypt’s Sander Lutz at Messari Mainnet 2024 to discuss how Binance is proactively dismantling criminal networks around the world, the strategy with which the crypto exchange is approaching sensitive conflicts in the Middle East, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 212 - SEEDPHRASE TALKS ART!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PJfaJNkZ/fomo-hour-212-seedphrase-talks-art</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PJfaJNkZ/fomo-hour-212-seedphrase-talks-art"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T19:29:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Payrolls Higher than expected, Bitcoin reacts hard. Crypto sank early in the week as Middle East tensions spooked markets. Powell signals two more rate cuts this year. SUI leads L1s again, nears YTD high despite large unlock. Majority of FTX repayments still months away. EIGEN becomes non-transferable, hits $6bn FDV. SEC to appeal Ripple securities law ruling. Visa launches tokenization platform for banks. SWIFT plans digital asset trial in 2025. ByBit launched trading of global stock indices. SPX, GIGA & FWOG hit ATHs, most memes fall. XCOPY to release 250 piece collection on Shape. HBO documentary claims to have identified Satoshi.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Altcoins bleed, ByBit launches stock index trading, POCHITA soars]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kYjAt3nt/altcoins-bleed-bybit-launches-stock-index-trading-pochita-soars</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kYjAt3nt/altcoins-bleed-bybit-launches-stock-index-trading-pochita-soars"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T21:11:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Altcoins sink, BTC dominance nears cycle high. BTC in ‘three blind mice’ downtrend. Tron revenue hits record $577m in Q3. ByBit to launch trading of major stock indices. Franklin Templeton launch fund on APT. SWIFT banks to trial digital assets in 2025. Aerodrome hits $1bn TVL on Base. Cronje calls out Aerodrome for copyright. ETH ICO wallet sells $47m. SEC files appeal against Ripple ruling. EIGEN falls 20% on staking rewards FUD. FTX to auction off WLD position. Half of US voters think crypto ‘important’. North Korea ‘infiltrating’ crypto industry. Snowden challenged over SOL centralisation view. Top SEC official on crypto set to depart.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DACOM Summit: Fastex CLO Vardan Khachatryan on Crypto Compliance]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LGGnxkb6/dacom-summit-fastex-clo-vardan-khachatryan-on-crypto-compliance</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LGGnxkb6/dacom-summit-fastex-clo-vardan-khachatryan-on-crypto-compliance"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T14:32:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fastex Chief Legal Officer Vardan Khachatryan joined Rug Radio creator Mlow at DACOM Summit to discuss how the crypto exchange is advancing compliance, and the regulatory challenges that lie ahead for the sector.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 210 - MIDDLE EAST TENSIONS RISE]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Bcj37IF2/fomo-hour-210-middle-east-tensions-rise</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Bcj37IF2/fomo-hour-210-middle-east-tensions-rise"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T17:14:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto drops as Middle East tensions flare. $500m liquidations in drop. BTC ETFs see largest outflows in a month. Fidelity ETH ETF sees 2nd highest outflow ever. SUI hits 6-month highs, bridge goes live on mainnet. Hashdex set to launch XRP ETF. Wormhole leads altcoin gains after Upbit lists. BTC miners hit record low profits in September Crypto hackers stole $750m in Q3. Telegram has been disclosing IPs since 2018.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Arbitrum is Simplifying Web3 for Web2 Adopters]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Mm9OGAoG/how-arbitrum-is-simplifying-web3-for-web2-adopters</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Mm9OGAoG/how-arbitrum-is-simplifying-web3-for-web2-adopters"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T14:19:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arbitrum's Head of Korea, John Park, joined Rug Radio creator Pukerainbow at ArbiVerse to talk about the Ethereum layer-2's strategy in Asia, hackathons, and bringing enterprise clients to its ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rep. Tom Emmer Is Confident Crypto Laws Are Coming Soon—No Matter Who Wins the Election]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qWDybFgM/rep-tom-emmer-is-confident-crypto-laws-are-coming-soonno-matter-who-wins-the-election</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qWDybFgM/rep-tom-emmer-is-confident-crypto-laws-are-coming-soonno-matter-who-wins-the-election"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T20:37:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Republican Majority Whip Tom Emmer sat down with Decrypt’s Sander Lutz and Liz Napolitano to discuss the state of crypto legislation, Kamala Harris, Fairshake, and more at Messari Mainnet 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 209 - LET UPTOBER BEGIN!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DdOpex2X/fomo-hour-209-let-uptober-begin</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DdOpex2X/fomo-hour-209-let-uptober-begin"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T19:23:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETFs see inflows for 8 straight days. SUI enters top 20, $110m of unlocks today. SOL weekly DEX volume flips ETH. Firedancer sees very fast TPS on Testnet. ETH gas up 500% in 2 weeks. EIGEN opens at $7bn FDV. FTX creditors vote in favour of restructuring plan. Dell to sell another $1.2bn Dell stock. Metaplanet buys another 107 BTC.Grayscale opens decentralised AI fund to investors. Robinhood allows crypto transfer in EU. Pollak to head Coinbase Wallet & join exec team. Gemini to close in Canada. Japan considers lower cap gains tax on crypto. Ohio bill would make it legal to pay taxes in crypto. Trump project opens whitelist to non-US users. CZ pledges to invest in blockchain companies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance CEO Richard Teng Talks Progress on Exchange's Global Regulatory Goals]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DNhZEWGn/binance-ceo-richard-teng-talks-progress-on-exchanges-global-regulatory-goals</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DNhZEWGn/binance-ceo-richard-teng-talks-progress-on-exchanges-global-regulatory-goals"/>
        <updated>2024-09-28T22:11:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt Reporters Sander Lutz and Liz Napolitano spoke with Binance CEO Richard Teng about the crypto exchange's progress on establishing a global headquarters, improving its relationships with regulators, and expanding its global presence in the wake of founder Changpeng "CZ" Zhao's jailing in the U.S.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 207 - WELCOME BACK TO THE BULL!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/2OVTsv7N/fomo-hour-207-welcome-back-to-the-bull</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/2OVTsv7N/fomo-hour-207-welcome-back-to-the-bull"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T18:14:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kamala signals support for crypto. Top memecoins all soar, add $10bn in value in a week. MOODENG hits $180m, does 11x in a week. SUI & SEI continue to lead L1s for price & TVL growth. Revolut & Robinhood are considering stablecoin. Visa launches new tokenisation platform for banks. PayPal to allow business accounts to hold crypto Hamster kombat's HMSTER disappoints on launch. Biden admin may have forced Silvergate’s closure. Court rules crypto mining boxes ‘are securities’.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 206 - MEMES ARE PUMPING!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Uc5GOy50/fomo-hour-206-memes-are-pumping</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Uc5GOy50/fomo-hour-206-memes-are-pumping"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T15:50:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC nears $65k key resistance level. Kamala makes positive comments about crypto. PayPal allows businesses to hold crypto. Visa allows banks to test RWAs & smart contracts. Cuban wants to be head of SEC. Silvergate claims about ‘Chokepoint 2.0’ grow. Truflation hacked for $5m. Telegram Wallet blocked in UK & US. Court rules crypto mining boxes are securities. Infinex DeFi platform raises $65m. Ethena announces new stablecoin linked to BUIDL.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 205 - ALTCOINS CONTINUE TO RALLY!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mtR8OATG/fomo-hour-205-altcoins-continue-to-rally</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mtR8OATG/fomo-hour-205-altcoins-continue-to-rally"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T15:16:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SUI leads L1 gains as TVL crosses $1bn. Altcoin market cap close to breaking downtrend. SEI becomes top chain for 1 month TVL growth. ETH ETFs sees 3rd largest inflow ever. SEC delays ETH ETF options decision. SOL took most of ETH outflows over last 3 months. SOLETH continues to be trading at resistance. $8.1bn BTC options to expire this week. BTC heading to $500k-$1m in a year: PlanB. Stablecoin supply hits new ATH. Caroline Ellison sentenced to 2 years in jail. SBF & Diddy in the same jail. SEC settles against TUSD for not being collateralised. Gensler gets derided for crypto approach. Hester Pierce admits flaws in SEC crypto policy. Harris against regulation by litigation: Cuban. Golem claims ETH move to CEXs due to staking. Binance refutes data leak claims. Next Y combinator batch has ‘no crypto companies’. Celo overtakes Tron for stablecoin addresses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 204 - MOODENG MOO-NING!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/g2yV7DjU/fomo-hour-204-moodeng-moo-ning</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/g2yV7DjU/fomo-hour-204-moodeng-moo-ning"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T15:53:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC needs to top $65.2k to put in a higher high. ETH ETFs see biggest outflow since July. ETH outperformance could be start of ‘alt season’. BlackRock gets 12hr BTC withdrawal from Coinbase. cbBTC only wrapped BTC to not show reserves. Telegram to share user data upon legal requests. EIGEN non-transferability to be removed Sep 30th. TIA announces $100m funding round. TIA deal was OTC token sale ‘done months ago’. Polymarket considers token, trying $50m raise. Maybe we will pay off debt with crypto: Trump. Harris unlikely to give full crypto policy pre-election. 13m Binance users’ data may have been leaked. Caroline Ellison likely won’t serve time in jail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 203 - KAMALA GOES PRO-CRYPTO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZIgJfh06/fomo-hour-203-kamala-goes-pro-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZIgJfh06/fomo-hour-203-kamala-goes-pro-crypto"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T16:14:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto funds saw $321m inflows last week. Kamala commits to crypto & AI expansion. TAO leads gains in AI hype, does 2x in 2 weeks. SUI TVL breaks $900m. Average Q4 returns for BTC is 88%. BTC Google searches down 75% since 2021. BTC 161 days from halving, when it rallied in 2020. Crypto VCs raised $2.2bn this year, well below 2021.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 202 - SOL STARTS TO SEND IT]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kMr0ptrw/fomo-hour-202-sol-starts-to-send-it</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kMr0ptrw/fomo-hour-202-sol-starts-to-send-it"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T18:42:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SOL leads majors as Breakpoint begins. SOL launches Frankendancer on mainnet. Helio Pay allows Shopify items to sell on X. Franklin Templeton to launch fund on SOL. BTC short term holders fall at fastest rate in 12 years. MicroStrategy upsizes convertible note raise to $1bn. BingX loses $52m in hack. $243m crypto heist exposed by ZachXBT. Supreme Court of India hacked on X, shills scam. SocGen launches Euro stablecoin on SOL. Sky agrees to stop using WBTC. Germany shuts down 47 crypto exchanges. Stablecoin’s now 18th biggest holder of treasuries. Consensys lawsuit against SEC dismissed. Partisanship will stop Trump crypto plans: Hoskinson. Scaramucci working with Kamala on crypto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>