<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-06-11T02:32:41.648Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-06-11T02:32:41.648Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fault Proofs Go Live on OP Mainnet]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19574695/Fault-Proofs-Go-Live-on-OP-Mainnet</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19574695/Fault-Proofs-Go-Live-on-OP-Mainnet"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T02:24:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Optimism achieves 'Stage 1' decentralization in major milestone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Whales Make $28 Million Withdrawal From Binance: Bullish Sign?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74108ad1b3</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/xrp-whales-28-million-withdrawal-binance-bullish/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T02:01:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data shows the XRP whales have made some large outflows from the Binance exchange, a sign that may be positive for the asset’s price.
 
XRP Whales Have Made Some Transactions During The Past 24 Hours
 
According to data from the cryptocurrency transaction tracker service Whale Alert, a few large transactions have been spotted on the XRP network during the past day.
 
All of these transfers have been of a scale generally associated with whale entities. Whales are humongous investors capable of moving large amounts quickly across the market, thus having the potential to move the price of the asset.
 
As such, the moves made by these holders during the last 24 hours can be worth knowing about as, even if they don’t end up having any visible effects on the cryptocurrency, they can at …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Whales Make $28 Million Withdrawal From Binance: Bullish Sign?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19574671/XRP-Whales-Make-28-Million-Withdrawal-From-Binance-Bullish-Sign</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19574671/XRP-Whales-Make-28-Million-Withdrawal-From-Binance-Bullish-Sign"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T02:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data shows the XRP whales have made some large outflows from the Binance exchange, a sign that may be positive for the asset’s price. XRP Whales Have Made Some Transactions During The Past 24 Hours According to data from the cryptocurrency transaction tracker service Whale Alert, a few...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon beats Ethereum in key area – What it means for MATIC]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19574670/Polygon-beats-Ethereum-in-key-area-What-it-means-for-MATIC</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19574670/Polygon-beats-Ethereum-in-key-area-What-it-means-for-MATIC"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T02:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon's gas usage exceeds Ethereum - is this a sign of better things for MATIC?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum, Dogecoin Remain Choppy, Analyst Forecasts 2X-10X Increase For King Crypto This Bull Cycle]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19574687/Bitcoin-Ethereum-Dogecoin-Remain-Choppy-Analyst-Forecasts-2X-10X-Increase-For-King-Crypto-This-Bull-Cycle</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19574687/Bitcoin-Ethereum-Dogecoin-Remain-Choppy-Analyst-Forecasts-2X-10X-Increase-For-King-Crypto-This-Bull-Cycle"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T01:53:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leading cryptocurrencies traded mostly flat on Monday, as efforts by bulls for an upside breakout stalled yet again. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HSBC China Introduces Digital Yuan Services for Corporate Clients]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7410744000</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/hsbc-china-introduces-digital-yuan-services-for-corporate-clients/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T01:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HSBC Bank (China) Ltd. announced on Friday the launch of digital yuan (e-CNY) services for corporate clients, becoming one of the first international banks to provide these services to both corporate and retail customers. The e-CNY, or digital yuan, is China’s central bank digital currency (CBDC) issued by the People’s Bank of China (PBOC). Following […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Questions about Bitcoin and Macro to Start the Week]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19574614/Questions-about-Bitcoin-and-Macro-to-Start-the-Week</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19574614/Questions-about-Bitcoin-and-Macro-to-Start-the-Week"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T01:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NLW looks at the end of last week where we saw a market shift in traditional and crypto markets. Here's what happened, and why. Enjoying this content?SUBSCRIBE to the Podcast: https://pod.link/1438693620Watch on YouTube: https://www.youtube.com/nathanielwhittemorecryptoSubscribe to the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BNB’s Price Surge Propels Binance’s CZ To Richest US Prisoner Status With $38B Net Worth]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7410779771</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bnb-price-makes-binance-cz-richest-us-inmate/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T01:10:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Coin (BNB), the native token of the world’s largest crypto exchange Binance, recently hit an all-time high of $725 on June 6th, the first week of exchange founder Chagpeng Zhao’s (CZ) four-month prison sentence in the US. 
 
According to a Bloomberg report, this price rally for the Binance Coin has made CZ the richest person ever to serve time in a US federal prison. Despite his legal troubles, the token’s market capitalization surpassed $109 billion in the past week, based on data from CoinGecko. 
 
BNB’s Price Surge Mirrors Exchange’s Rise? 
 
Per the report, Binance Coin’s price trajectory mirrors the fortunes of the exchange itself, as the total value of assets on the platform has climbed from approximately $80 billion in early January to $125 billion currently. 
 
This growth …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin flat despite high ETF inflows as hedge funds short BTC at record levels]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19574606/Bitcoin-flat-despite-high-ETF-inflows-as-hedge-funds-short-BTC-at-record-levels</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19574606/Bitcoin-flat-despite-high-ETF-inflows-as-hedge-funds-short-BTC-at-record-levels"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T01:10:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin's spot price remains stable despite substantial inflows into Bitcoin ETFs over the past 19 days, as large hedge funds simultaneously buy ETFs and sell futures contracts, offsetting the potential impact of the inflows on the spot price.Crypto investment firm CMS Holdings recently tweeted...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk to ban Apple devices if OpenAI is integrated in OS]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19574600/Elon-Musk-to-ban-Apple-devices-if-OpenAI-is-integrated-in-OS</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19574600/Elon-Musk-to-ban-Apple-devices-if-OpenAI-is-integrated-in-OS"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T01:01:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Musk called it an “unacceptable security violation” and even said the Apple block could extend to visitors to his company’s headquarters.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Newcomer Base challenges Solana with rapid adoption]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19574602/Newcomer-Base-challenges-Solana-with-rapid-adoption</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19574602/Newcomer-Base-challenges-Solana-with-rapid-adoption"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T01:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When analyzing the DeFi market, Solana is almost exclusively compared to Ethereum. Both are Layer 1 networks, and Solana is often perceived as an alternative to Ethereum, which yields an interesting market perspective. However, comparing Solana to Base makes more sense as the two blockchains are...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Analyst Predicts XRP Price Will Rally 50,000% To $250, Here’s When]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19574584/Crypto-Analyst-Predicts-XRP-Price-Will-Rally-50000-To-250-Heres-When</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19574584/Crypto-Analyst-Predicts-XRP-Price-Will-Rally-50000-To-250-Heres-When"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T01:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto analyst Chad Steingraber has made an ultra-bullish price prediction for the XRP price, stating that the crypto token’s price could rise to three figures. The analyst also outlined when this price target will be attained.  XRP Will Hit $250 In This Market Cycle Steingraber mentioned in an...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BNB’s Price Surge Propels Binance’s CZ To Richest US Prisoner Status With $38B Net Worth]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19574599/BNBs-Price-Surge-Propels-Binances-CZ-To-Richest-US-Prisoner-Status-With-38B-Net-Worth</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19574599/BNBs-Price-Surge-Propels-Binances-CZ-To-Richest-US-Prisoner-Status-With-38B-Net-Worth"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T01:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Coin (BNB), the native token of the world’s largest crypto exchange Binance, recently hit an all-time high of $725 on June 6th, the first week of exchange founder Chagpeng Zhao’s (CZ) four-month prison sentence in the US. According to a Bloomberg report, this price rally for the Binance...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lykke halts trading after losing $22 million in security breach]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19574581/Lykke-halts-trading-after-losing-22-million-in-security-breach</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19574581/Lykke-halts-trading-after-losing-22-million-in-security-breach"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T00:57:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A UK cryptocurrency exchange, Lykke, has suspended operations after losing $22 million in a suspected security incident. The exchange reportedly shut down trades after unauthorized access to its system occurred on June 4. Also read: DeFi protocol founded by ‘Sifu’ hacked for $19.4 million This...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Korean Regulator Excludes Certain NFTs From Crypto Regulations]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7410730655</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/south-korean-regulator-excludes-certain-nfts-from-crypto-regulations/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T00:34:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[South Korea’s top financial regulator has issued guidelines clarifying when non-fungible tokens (NFTs) are considered virtual assets. This distinction aims to minimize the risk of widespread user harm. The guidelines will be part of the Virtual Asset User Protection Act, effective July 19, 2024. FSC Issues New NFT Classification Guidelines On Monday, South Korea’s top […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forget Shiba Inu And Dogecoin, Crypto Whales Are Buying Millions Worth Of This Meme Coin]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74107d60ab</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-whales-meme-coin/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T00:10:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto whales are gearing up for what might be an interesting week for PEPE. On-chain data reveals crypto whales have been busy over the weekend as many look to position themselves before the start of the new week. Amidst this positioning and accumulation, PEPE has shot up as an interesting option for a few whales.
 
Crypto Whales Make Large PEPE Purchases
 
PEPE is coming off of a seven-day period of intense volatility and bearish momentum. Price action indicates the meme coin lost about 20% of its value last week, and it seems some whales are going with a buy-the-dip strategy. Multiple transactions involving billions of PEPE tokens were recorded. According to on-chain data, there were multiple instances of whales buying millions worth of PEPE during the weekend, giving a glimpse of wheth…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forget Shiba Inu And Dogecoin, Crypto Whales Are Buying Millions Worth Of This Meme Coin]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19574509/Forget-Shiba-Inu-And-Dogecoin-Crypto-Whales-Are-Buying-Millions-Worth-Of-This-Meme-Coin</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19574509/Forget-Shiba-Inu-And-Dogecoin-Crypto-Whales-Are-Buying-Millions-Worth-Of-This-Meme-Coin"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T00:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto whales are gearing up for what might be an interesting week for PEPE. On-chain data reveals crypto whales have been busy over the weekend as many look to position themselves before the start of the new week. Amidst this positioning and accumulation, PEPE has shot up as an interesting...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trader Unveils List of Five Strong Altcoins Including Injective Amid Choppy Market Conditions]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19574497/Trader-Unveils-List-of-Five-Strong-Altcoins-Including-Injective-Amid-Choppy-Market-Conditions</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19574497/Trader-Unveils-List-of-Five-Strong-Altcoins-Including-Injective-Amid-Choppy-Market-Conditions"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A closely followed crypto analyst is listing five altcoins he believes are showing strength despite the choppy market conditions. Pseudonymous crypto trader Altcoin Sherpa tells his 217,200 followers on the social media platform X that layer-1 protocol Injective (INJ), cross-chain protocol...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Korean Court Jails Duo for Crypto-powered Drug Trafficking]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19574459/South-Korean-Court-Jails-Duo-for-Crypto-powered-Drug-Trafficking</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19574459/South-Korean-Court-Jails-Duo-for-Crypto-powered-Drug-Trafficking"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T23:30:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A South Korean court has jailed two people for crypto-powered drug trafficking, as the nation’s judiciary continues to crack down on Bitcoin and altcoin-fuelled crime.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sora Who? Kling Is the New AI Video Generator Everyone Is Talking About]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234706</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234706/kling-ai-video-generator-china-beats-pika-runwayml-openai-sora"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T23:30:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hailing from China, the Kling AI video model is a potential game changer, blasting past mainstays like Pika or RunwayML. Here's what you need to know.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sora Who? Kling Is the New AI Video Generator Everyone Is Talking About]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19574460/Sora-Who-Kling-Is-the-New-AI-Video-Generator-Everyone-Is-Talking-About</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19574460/Sora-Who-Kling-Is-the-New-AI-Video-Generator-Everyone-Is-Talking-About"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T23:30:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hailing from China, the Kling AI video model is a potential game changer, blasting past mainstays like Pika or RunwayML. Here's what you need to know.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modi Reappoints Nirmala Sitharaman as India’s Finance Minister — Investors Remain Concerned Over High Crypto Taxes]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74107abbf5</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/modi-reappoints-nirmala-sitharaman-as-indias-finance-minister-investors-remain-concerned-over-high-crypto-taxes/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T23:17:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Indian Prime Minister Narendra Modi has reappointed Nirmala Sitharaman as Finance Minister. She remains instrumental in shaping India’s economic policies, including cryptocurrency regulation and taxation. Nirmala Sitharaman Reappointed as Finance Minister Indian Prime Minister Narendra Modi has reappointed Nirmala Sitharaman as Finance Minister, extending her tenure that began in 2019. Sitharaman, who delivered her sixth […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Whales Open Massive Longs At $69,000: All Ahead From Here?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74107b6bab</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-whales-open-massive-longs-69000-all-ahead/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T23:10:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data shows the Bitcoin whales on cryptocurrency exchanges Bybit and HTX have opened massive long positions at the current price levels.
 
Bitcoin Taker Buy Sell Ratio Has Spiked For Bybit and HTX Recently
 
In a new post on X, CryptoQuant founder and CEO Ki Young Ju has revealed that the whales on the HTX platform have opened large long positions recently. The indicator of relevance here is the “Taker Buy Sell Ratio,” which keeps track of the ratio between the Bitcoin taker buy and taker sell volumes.
 
When the value of this metric is greater than 1, it means the taker buy or long volume is greater than the taker sell or short volume right now. Such a trend implies the derivatives market currently shares a bullish majority sentiment.
 
 
On the other hand, the indicator being less than th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Exchange Swan Sponsors Tucker Carlson’s Live Tour]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19574439/Bitcoin-Exchange-Swan-Sponsors-Tucker-Carlsons-Live-Tour</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19574439/Bitcoin-Exchange-Swan-Sponsors-Tucker-Carlsons-Live-Tour"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T23:10:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin may be in for some mainstream exposure as a leading Bitcoin-only exchange sponsors Tucker Carlson's political tour this fall.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Whales Open Massive Longs At $69,000: All Ahead From Here?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19574432/Bitcoin-Whales-Open-Massive-Longs-At-69000-All-Ahead-From-Here</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19574432/Bitcoin-Whales-Open-Massive-Longs-At-69000-All-Ahead-From-Here"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T23:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data shows the Bitcoin whales on cryptocurrency exchanges Bybit and HTX have opened massive long positions at the current price levels. Bitcoin Taker Buy Sell Ratio Has Spiked For Bybit and HTX Recently In a new post on X, CryptoQuant founder and CEO Ki Young Ju has revealed that the whales on...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Ethereum’s price dip signaling the start of a new rally?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19574430/Is-Ethereums-price-dip-signaling-the-start-of-a-new-rally</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19574430/Is-Ethereums-price-dip-signaling-the-start-of-a-new-rally"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T23:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum whale wallets have continued to accumulate more ETH as its price drops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Call of Duty: Black Ops 6 Preview: Everything You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=214893</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/214893/call-of-duty-2024-preview-leaks-rumors-release-date"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T22:45:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATED: Activision just shared a ton of details about Call of Duty: Black Ops 6—including some big changes from last year's entry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi protocol founded by ‘Sifu’ hacked for $19.4 million]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19574396/DeFi-protocol-founded-by-Sifu-hacked-for-194-million</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19574396/DeFi-protocol-founded-by-Sifu-hacked-for-194-million"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T22:36:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Uwu Lend, a DeFi protocol created by fraudster Michael Patryn, a.k.a “Sifu”, has been hacked for $19.4 million, according to the blockchain security firm Peckshield. Uwu Lend confirmed the exploit on Monday and said it would refund users “up to 80% of their original deposited amount.” Also read:...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Says He Will Ban Apple Devices From His Companies If They Integrate OpenAI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234689</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234689/elon-musk-apple-device-ban-chatgpt-security-privacy"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T22:22:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“That is an unacceptable security violation,” the Tesla CEO declared, asserting that Apple can't guarantee that OpenAI will keep user data secure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Says He Will Ban Apple Devices From His Companies If They Integrate OpenAI]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19574373/Elon-Musk-Says-He-Will-Ban-Apple-Devices-From-His-Companies-If-They-Integrate-OpenAI</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19574373/Elon-Musk-Says-He-Will-Ban-Apple-Devices-From-His-Companies-If-They-Integrate-OpenAI"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T22:22:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“That is an unacceptable security violation,” the Tesla CEO declared, asserting that Apple can't guarantee that OpenAI will keep user data secure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOJ and FBI Unveil Charges Against 3 UK Nationals in NFT Rug Pull Scam]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7410619eb4</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/doj-and-fbi-unveil-charges-against-3-uk-nationals-in-nft-rug-pull-scam/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T22:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Department of Justice (DOJ) and the Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) have unveiled charges against three UK nationals for a fraudulent non-fungible token (NFT) scheme involving “Evolved Apes,” promising a game development. “They allegedly took investor funds, never developed the game, and pocketed the proceeds.” US Charges 3 UK Nationals in NFT Rug […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Hamster Kombat? The Telegram Crypto Game and Airdrop]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233407</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-hamster-kombat-telegram-game-token-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T22:12:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hamster Kombat is the latest Telegram-based crypto game to go viral, just like Notcoin. Here's what you need to know.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana-Based DePIN Project CEO Steps Down Ahead Of Token Launch]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7410635d2d</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/solana-based-depin-project-ceo-steps-down-ahead-of-token-launch/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T21:59:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ahmad Shadid stepped down as CEO of the Solana-based DePIN Protocol io.net on Sunday. The decision came two days before the launch of io.net’s token, IO. As a result, the crypto community was skeptical of the decision and the former CEO’s past.
 
 
Solana-Based DePIN Project Changes Management
 
Two days before the IO token launch, Ahmad Shadid announced he was stepping down “effective immediately” as CEO of io.net. The Solana-based protocol is a decentralized physical infrastructure network (DePIN) designed to “provide unlimited computing power to machine learning applications.”
 
Io.net aggregates GPUs from different storage providers to offer cost-efficient GPU computing power to AI and ML teams. Additionally, it allows users to earn money renting out their spare GPU capacity.
 
Accordi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rubmar Garcia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roaring Kitty Is Down Over $350 Million on GameStop Since Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234687</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234687/roaring-kitty-down-350-million-gamestop"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T21:54:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meme stock influencer Roaring Kitty says he's still in the black on his massive GameStop (GME) options gamble—just barely.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russia Set to Recognize Bitcoin Mining as Economic Activity]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74106d4371</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/russia-set-to-recognize-bitcoin-mining-as-economic-activity/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T21:44:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to Osman Kabaloev, the Deputy Director of the Financial Policy Department at Russia’s Ministry of Finance, the recognition of Bitcoin mining as an official economic activity is set to happen soon. Following the approval of a law regulating cryptocurrency mining, this activity would be assigned an OKVED code, which classifies company activities for licensing […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Surge in Digital Asset Investments Following SEC ETF Approvals, Coinshares Reports]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741068e99e</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/surge-in-digital-asset-investments-following-sec-etf-approvals-coinshares-reports/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T21:14:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Digital asset investment products have witnessed significant inflows totaling $2 billion, marking a strong five-week streak that accumulates to $4.3 billion. As reported by Coinshares, this surge aligns with increased trading volumes and shifting monetary policy expectations. Record-Breaking Week for Digital Assets as U.S. Ethereum ETF Approval Sparks $2 Billion Surge Digital asset investment products, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Community Targeted By Wallet Scam, Don’t Fall Victim]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7410699ec4</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-wallet-scam/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T21:08:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Shiba Inu team has cautioned against a new scam attack targeting community members. These malicious attackers have executed a sophisticated wallet scam that threatens to drain the funds of unsuspecting SHIB investors.   
 
New Scam Attack Targets SHIB Investors
 
Shibarmy Scam Alerts, an X (formerly Twitter) account dedicated to exposing scams within the SHIB community, has issued an urgent warning about a new wallet scam targeting SHIB token holders. On June 8, the scam tracker disclosed that a new wave of fraudulent websites is spreading across the crypto space. Most of these malicious sites are typically distributed within different social media platforms such as X, discord, telegram and more. 
 
 
According to Shibarmy Scam Alerts, these scam sites pose a significant risk to their …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia's Rumored GPU Upgrades Will Fuel More Demanding AI Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234675</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234675/nvidia-rtx50-leak-gpu-vram-upgrades"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T21:06:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An alleged leak suggests the top chipmaker is bolstering its position as the top provider of AI hardware—but prices could also rise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Taps OpenAI to Bring Big AI Updates to iPhones and Macs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234661</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234661/apple-ai-openai-chatgpt-siri-wwdc"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T20:51:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Siri will plug into ChatGPT, but the tech giant emphasized that its AI features will be private and secure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mexican Billionaire Ricardo Salinas Doubles Down on Bitcoin, Advises Using It as Inflation Hedge]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7410549d21</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/mexican-billionaire-ricardo-salinas-doubles-down-on-bitcoin-advises-using-it-as-inflation-hedge/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T20:45:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ricardo Salinas, the third wealthiest man in Mexico, has recently doubled down on his proposal to use Bitcoin as a reserve asset. On social media, Salinas defended the role of Bitcoin as an inflation hedge, commenting on a post that presented inflation as a hidden tax on fiat money and advised his followers to purchase […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI-Linked Crypto Tokens Underperform as Apple's Event Fails to Impress Traders]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741056af28</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/06/10/ai-linked-crypto-tokens-underperform-as-apples-event-fails-to-impress-traders/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T20:29:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tokens of Render, Fetch.ai, SingularityNET and Bittensor slumped 3%-5% despite mostly flat bitcoin and broader crypto prices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimism Finally Gets Its Mission-Critical 'Fault Proofs']]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741057aa08</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2024/06/10/optimism-finally-gets-its-mission-critical-fault-proofs/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T20:22:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For years, Optimism was missing a core feature at the heart of its design: "Fault proofs." On Monday, that tech is finally here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Margaux Nijkerk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana To Flip Ethereum And Become “Altcoin Leader” In Next Bull Cycle: Analyst]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74105146a3</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/solana-ethereum-altcoin-leader-bull-cycle/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T20:09:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana and top cryptocurrencies like Ethereum and Bitcoin are struggling at spot rates. Following the plunge on June 6, prices are under pressure, cementing the position of sellers who have been dominant since late May 2024. 
 
Will The Solana Uptrend Remain?
 
Even so, some analysts are upbeat, expecting not only altcoins to recover in the sessions ahead but specifically for Solana, a top-5 coin, to emerge as a leader in the next cycle. 
 
 
In a post of X, one analyst noted that provided bulls maintain the current uptrend, rejecting any attempt for lower lows, SOL will continue to float higher. 
 
 
Of note, this will continue the trend seen from the better part of H2 2023, when the coin rose from obscurity to become one of the top performers, even outdoing Bitcoin. Looking at the daily …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dalmas Ngetich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Defense of Meme Coins]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7410524851</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/opinion/2024/06/10/in-defense-of-meme-coins/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T20:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The only thing worse than meme coins is complaining about the financialization of memes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Kuhn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Treasury Strategy Boosts Stock Price of Canadian Firm DeFi Technologies]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234642</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234642/bitcoin-treasury-strategy-boosts-stock-price-defi-technologies"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T19:52:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi Technologies, a Canadian firm and parent company of ETF provider Valour, has adopted Bitcoin as a treasury reserve asset.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Over 200 BTC From 2013 and 2012 Wallets Awaken, Now Valued at Over $14M]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74105e13c9</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/over-200-btc-from-2013-and-2012-wallets-awaken-now-valued-at-over-14m/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T19:33:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past weekend, 211.51 dormant bitcoins valued at $14.79 million were reactivated after over a decade of inactivity. More than half of these funds originated from bitcoin wallets that had been inactive since 2012. Vintage Bitcoin Wallets Unleash 211.51 Bitcoin Since June 8, 2024, a series of four transactions brought 211.51 dormant bitcoins back […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Base Meme Coin Normie Removes Video Depicting Suicide, Following Backlash]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234588</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234588/base-meme-coin-normie-removes-suicide-video-backlash"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T19:20:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The creators of Normie, a meme coin minted on Ethereum layer-2 network Base, said they weren't trying to "trivialize a sensitive topic."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Vs. Ethereum Feud Escalates After SOL Foundation Ousts Validators]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741059863b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/solana-vs-ethereum-feud-validator-ouster/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T19:07:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Solana Foundation has expelled a number of validator operators from its influential delegation program. This action is attributed to their involvement in executing “sandwich attacks” against unsuspecting network users, a form of predatory trading that undermines network integrity. The decision adds a new layer to the escalating rivalry between Solana and Ethereum, highlighting broader concerns over network governance and the ethical dimensions of validator operations.
 
Tim Garcia, the Validator Relations Lead, made the announcement via Discord, emphasizing the finality of the Foundation’s decision: “A group of operators in the Solana Foundation Delegation Program have been removed from the program due to violations […] Decisions in this matter are final. Enforcement actions are ongoin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Is The Best Choice For Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741059bfa2</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/trump-is-the-best-choice-for-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T19:05:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One in four Americans own Bitcoin.
That’s more Americans than are over the age of 65, but how often do you hear candidates talk about senior concerns compared to concerns of crypto owners? 
President Donald Trump has been making a concerted effort in the 2024 campaign trail to appeal to Bitcoiners. 
At the recent Libertarian National Convention, President Trump vowed to “stop Joe Biden’s crusade to crush crypto,” and assured Bitcoin holders specifically that he supports the right to self-custody.
“I say this with your vote, I will keep Elizabeth Warren and her goons away from your Bitcoin, and I will never allow the creation of a central bank digital currency,” President Trump said.
It’s clear which candidate this November is the best choice for Bitcoin owners and the entire industry – Pre…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Morgenstern</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop Dumps 15% as Roaring Kitty Jokes About His Plunging Position]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234649</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234649/gamestop-dumps-15-roaring-kitty-jokes-plunging-position"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T18:45:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop's share price continued to fall Monday as the meme stock influencer Kieth Gill made light of his own losses on paper.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Meme Coin Michi Pumps After Ariana Grande Shares the Cat's Photo]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234635</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234635/solana-meme-coin-michi-pumps-ariana-grande"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T17:57:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pop star Ariana Grande reposted a Michi meme ahead of the Monday surge, prompting debate over whether she knows of its crypto connection.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Layer-2 ZkSync Unveils ZK Nation Ahead of Airdrop]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234619</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234619/zksync-unveils-zk-nation-ahead-of-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T17:21:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The community will be responsible for governing the protocol via the upcoming ZKsync token.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarang Khaitan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Stock Nears All-Time High Price Ahead of Expected AI Push]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234620</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234620/apple-stock-nears-all-time-high-price-ahead-of-expected-ai-push"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T16:47:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple's stock price has been on a bullish streak for seven weeks, with its expected focus on AI at WWDC fueling investor optimism.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Hamster Kombat’ Daily Cipher Guide: How to Use Morse Code to Earn a Million Free Coins in the Telegram Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234027</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/hamster-kombat-daily-cipher-guide-morse-codeearn-million-free-coins"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T16:25:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now there’s another way to rack up free coins ahead of the Hamster Kombat airdrop. Here’s how to do it and where to find the latest code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uniswap Labs Acquires 'Crypto: The Game' Ahead of Next Season]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234608</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234608/uniswap-labs-acquires-crypto-game-next-season"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T16:01:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto: The Game, the Survivor-inspired reality game built around on-chain activities, will continue on under the Uniswap Labs umbrella.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 134 - EU SNAP ELECTIONS LAND]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pZksMKIV/fomo-hour-134-eu-snap-elections-land</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pZksMKIV/fomo-hour-134-eu-snap-elections-land"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T15:46:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Volatility remains low, TL continues to be divisive. 2nd highest weekly close ever for BTC. Crypto funds saw $2bn inflows last week. Rumour that BlackRock will apply for SOL ETF. Base TVL hits $8bn, top of L2s for activity. zk Sync hint at TGE this week. PENDLE enters top 5 for DeFi TVL. Berachain v2 testnet goes live.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Funds Added $2 Billion in Biggest Week for Crypto ETFs Since March]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234599</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234599/bitcoin-funds-added-2-billion-biggest-week-crypto-etfs-march"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T15:17:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto funds added more than $2 billion worth of assets last week with the largest combined inflows since March—most of it for Bitcoin ETFs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ali Shutler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roaring Kitty Posts on Twitter Again. Does It Mean He's Buying AMC?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234559</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234559/roaring-kitty-posts-on-twitter-again-does-it-mean-hes-buying-amc"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T12:31:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop legend Roaring Kitty is back to posting movie references on Twitter. Could this mean he owns meme stock AMC?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Makes 'Crypto President' Play at Fundraiser: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234556</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234556/trump-makes-crypto-president-play-at-fundraiser-report"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T12:25:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Republican presidential hopeful doubled down on his pro-crypto stance, according to attendees of the fundraising event.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notcoin Token Pumps 6% as Telegram Game Hits 40 Million Players]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234557</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234557/notcoin-pumps-40-million-players"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T10:54:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Players have earned $1.5 million across 20 campaigns, according to the project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarang Khaitan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friend.tech Token Down 22% After Migration Off Base L2 Gets Panned]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234545</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234545/friend-tech-token-down-22-after-migration-off-base-l2-gets-panned"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T09:34:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[News of Friend.tech's plans to launch a blockchain for decentralized social projects has not been well received.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Has Put a Weird New Face on an Old Amazon Prime Video Problem]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234361</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234361/ai-weird-new-face-old-amazon-prime-video-problem"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T05:57:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The thumbnail for the classic 12 Angry Men has had a terrifying makeover.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ali Shutler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Crypto Games: ‘Hamster Kombat’ Airdrop, GTA 6 Bitcoin Trailer, and McDonald’s Metaverse]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234536</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234536/this-week-crypto-games-hamster-kombat-airdrop-gta-6-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T19:29:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Catch up on this week’s biggest crypto and NFT gaming news and find some weekend reads in our latest roundup.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Next-Gen Xbox Preview: Everything You Need to Know About the Console and Crypto Plans]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=198822</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/198822/next-gen-xbox-everything-need-know-microsoft-leaks-rumors-news"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T18:30:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATE: Microsoft just showcased three revised hardware models releasing later this year. Here's what to expect ahead of the next-gen Xbox.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Create Hyper-Realistic AI Images with Stable Diffusion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233512</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233512/how-to-create-photorealistic-ai-pictures-with-stable-diffusion"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T13:01:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Specialized models can turn Stable Diffusion into a powerful creator of photorealistic art. Here's a tour of our current toolbox.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week on Crypto Twitter: Roaring Kitty Shows His Face, Gets Rekt]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234518</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234518/this-week-on-crypto-twitter-roaring-kitty-shows-his-face-gets-rekt"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T12:01:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop had a surprise of its own on Friday, making the on-camera return of the famed meme stock influencer even more chaotic than even he expected.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Ethereum Layer-2 Network Taiko Is Spending $100K Daily on Blobs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234426</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234426/why-ethereum-l2-taiko-spending-100k-daily-blobs"/>
        <updated>2024-06-08T18:27:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Taiko, an Ethereum layer-2 scaling network, is spending massive amounts of money on blobs compared to its competitors—but that's by design.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is JAM? Polkadot's Biggest Ever Upgrade Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234377</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-jam-polkadots-biggest-ever-upgrade-explained"/>
        <updated>2024-06-08T15:01:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JAM represents the most significant change to Polkadot’s architecture since the blockchain was first fully introduced.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will McCurdy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the Infamous 'Buy Bitcoin' GTA 6 Game Trailer Was Leaked]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234496</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234496/infamous-buy-bitcoin-gta-6-game-trailer-leaked"/>
        <updated>2024-06-08T13:31:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New revelations point to the culprit also being behind several high-profile SIM-swapping attacks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Dumb Money’: Should You Watch the Roaring Kitty Flick as GameStop Fever Returns?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234479</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234479/dumb-money-review-watch-roaring-kitty-flick-gamestop"/>
        <updated>2024-06-08T12:31:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roaring Kitty is back. Is "Dumb Money," last year’s biopic on the GameStop short squeeze saga, still worth watching today?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Bitcoin and Ethereum Pump—Then Dump—Amid Roaring Kitty Rush]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234493</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234493/this-week-in-coins-roaring-kitty-bitcoin-ethereum-etf"/>
        <updated>2024-06-08T11:31:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bullish talk around ETFs helped Bitcoin and Ethereum rise over the past several days—but they tumbled at the finish line.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Qwen2 AI Model from Alibaba to Challenge Meta, OpenAI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234450</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234450/new-qwen2-ai-model-from-alibaba-to-challenge-meta-openai"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T22:16:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest open-source AI model outperforms Meta's LLama3 in key benchmarks, positioning itself as a strong contender in the AI race.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Fees Are Skyrocketing Again—And It's Not Because of Runes or Ordinals]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234446</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234446/bitcoin-fees-skyrocket-okx-exchange-burning-utxo"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T20:52:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A major exchange is trying to declutter its Bitcoin wallet and is burning a lot of money in the process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who Is Roaring Kitty, and What Does His Return Mean for Crypto?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230566</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230566/who-is-roaring-kitty-keith-gill-deepfuckingvalue-back-on-twitter"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T19:53:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATE: Keith Gill staged his return to Twitter, then Reddit, and finally back to YouTube with a livestream that drew 700,000 viewers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bybit Opens Up Crypto Trading to Chinese Users Living Abroad]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234424</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234424/bybit-opens-up-crypto-trading-to-chinese-users-living-abroad"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T19:20:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The second-largest cryptocurrency exchange welcomes Chinese nationals who reside in other countries it serves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Tanks as Nearly $300 Million in Longs Get Rekt]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234422</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234422/bitcoin-price-tanks-nearly-300-million-longs-get-rekt"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T18:35:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto long positions were just zapped en masse, with nearly $300 million worth liquidated in the last hour as Bitcoin quickly dipped.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward,André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It's Time To Go Long On Bitcoin and Shitcoins: Arthur Hayes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234418</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234418/go-long-bitcoin-and-shitcoins-arthur-hayes"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T18:15:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin will moon as central banks pivot to lower interest rates en masse–with the Bank of England soon to follow, Hayes predicts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['We Must Crash Solana': Andrew Tate Embarks on Meme Coin Spending Spree]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234401</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234401/we-must-crash-solana-andrew-tate-meme-coins"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T18:01:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Controversial influencer and former kickboxer Andrew Tate claims that he will spend a million dollars on “junk” tokens today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['I'm Alive': GameStop Legend Roaring Kitty Just Livestreamed—Here's What Happened]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234404</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234404/gamestop-legend-roaring-kitty-just-livestreamed"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T17:32:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meme stock influencer Roaring Kitty drew a crowd of over 700,000 viewers on Friday while speaking carefully about his GameStop positions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 133 - RUGGED BY HOGEN?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MSvAS9qX/fomo-hour-133-rugged-by-hogen</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MSvAS9qX/fomo-hour-133-rugged-by-hogen"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T17:26:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC still just below ATH after $218m ETF inflows. BTC OI hits record $37bn as long-short ratio rises. Amount of ETH on exchanges lowest since 2015. Franklin Templeton explores broader crypto fund. Mining stocks rise on takeover frenzy. Kraken considers $100m funding round. Binance reinstates crypto buys with Mastercard. Phantom & Jito partner for native staking.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 132 - CRYPTO STRENGTH IS GROWING]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/bQBFWC0w/fomo-hour-132-crypto-strength-is-growing</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/bQBFWC0w/fomo-hour-132-crypto-strength-is-growing"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T19:49:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto consolidates near ATH, $488m ETF inflow. BTC correlation to tech stocks highest since 2023. BTC options anticipate $74-80k move. ETH to $22k by 2030: VanEck. Robinhood to acquire Bitstamp.
Coinbase launches Smart Wallet. ByBit opens up explicitly to China users. Global liquidity breaks out to $94T. US President given new powers to block crypto. Cramer & Gensler continue to bash crypto. Gensler hints at prolonged ETH ETF process. Stand with Crypto PAC hits 1m advocates. Turkey denies plans to tax crypto. EigenLayer surpasses $20bn TVL. IONET to launch on Binance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webinar: Unleashing The Power Of Permissionless Markets With Vega Protocol]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OvA845JA/webinar-unleashing-the-power-of-permissionless-markets-with-vega-protocol</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OvA845JA/webinar-unleashing-the-power-of-permissionless-markets-with-vega-protocol"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T08:23:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join our expert panel for an insightful discussion on Vega Protocol's revolutionary approach to decentralized derivatives trading. Discover how Vega's permissionless markets enable anyone to create and trade futures and perpetuals on a fully decentralized network. Explore the potential of Vega's innovative features, such as the ability to add new assets, transfer network assets, and adjust network parameters—as well as the protocol's active markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 131 - BIG BITCOIN INFLOWS!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/a37DNT7n/fomo-hour-131-big-bitcoin-inflows</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/a37DNT7n/fomo-hour-131-big-bitcoin-inflows"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T17:06:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETFs see large $900M inflows, biggest in weeks. $800M of shorts would be liquidated above $72K. BTC to $100K if it breaks $73K in a week: Novogratz. BNB hits new ATH, breaks $100B market cap. FTX reaches $200M tax settlement with IRS. Most investors should hold BTC: Fidelity. Tether CEO criticises EU on stablecoin regulation. Japanese exchange raises $320M to recover funds. ETH ETFs could see $4B inflows in 5 months: K33. Paradigm propose MEV taxes. StarkWare plans ZK scaling for BTC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 130 - $DOG TARGETS 1B MC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ke2mFBwr/fomo-hour-130-dog-targets-1b-mc</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ke2mFBwr/fomo-hour-130-dog-targets-1b-mc"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T22:05:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Runes & Ordinals soar as DOG passes $900M. rekt Brands opens up its shares claim for NFT holders. BTC led NFT trading volume with $6.3M on the day. NodeMonkes +10% 0.289, Puppets +35% at 0.198. Runes up by DOG which soared 23% to $922M mc. BUS won the Blast Jackpot last night for a 3% win. Memecoin majors are mostly red this AM. Trader buys 10k SOL of GME. Base brings back Onchain Summer. Dapper settles massive lawsuit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 129 - ROARING RETURNS, AGAIN!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ABOejLBT/fomo-hour-129-roaring-returns-again</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ABOejLBT/fomo-hour-129-roaring-returns-again"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T21:42:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto bounces, BTC breaks 2-week downtrend. BTC low volatility points to trend continuation. BTC will top at $150k in September 2025: Brandt. $3bn ETH withdrawn from exchanges since ETF. ETH ETF inflows imply ‘base case’ price $5.3k. ETH ETF inflows won’t be like BTC: Fireblocks. BTC logo projected on ECB building. Ethena USDe hits $3bn market cap in 4 months. Maple launches DeFi institutional lending platform. OKX launches in the Netherlands. Matter Labs drops ZK ticker. Linea shuts down chain after hack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 128 - PUMP DOT FUN KEEPS PUMPING!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cziNL3TF/fomo-hour-128-pump-dot-fun-keeps-pumping</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cziNL3TF/fomo-hour-128-pump-dot-fun-keeps-pumping"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T21:41:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto nears break-out then falls on Trump verdict. 13 straight days of BTC ETF inflows, BTC whale accumulation ‘echoes 2020’. Crypto apps next year will onboard millions: Burniske. Elon denies talking crypto policy with Trump. RFK has bought 21 BTC during campaign. TON market cap falls after updating supply data. a16z donates $25m to crypto PAC. Vitalik sends 30ETH to Tornado devs. DBS Bank in Singapore custodies $650m ETH. Backlash grows over zkSync using ZK ticker. Implementing FIT21 a slow process: CFTC. Pierce recommends UK & US cross-border sandbox. Vitalik writes blog on block size wars. Hong Kong government expresses support for web3. Do Kwon & Terraform reach settlement with SEC. Large unlocks for a number of alts next month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 127 - CELEB COINS CRASH!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mGbE2GHV/fomo-hour-127-celeb-coins-crash</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mGbE2GHV/fomo-hour-127-celeb-coins-crash"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T20:28:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NYSE to launch BTC options. CME has ‘no plans’ to offer SOL futures. Stablecoin market cap rises to 2 year high. Inflation below 3.3% ‘means BTC ATH’. Crypto market cap heading to $200T: Yat Siu. Gemini recovers $2.2bn for Earn users. PayPal stablecoin will offer ‘confidential transfers’. Mastercard launches Crypto Credential pilot on BTC. Layer Zero launches on SOL. L2s are cultural extensions of ETH: Vitalik. FTX’s Salame says he will share story. SEI announces 27m SEI airdrop. ASI merger complete, to launch June 13th.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 126 - MEMECOIN MADNESS!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/eA3xqKLr/fomo-hour-126-memecoin-madness</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/eA3xqKLr/fomo-hour-126-memecoin-madness"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T21:30:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock ETF flips Grayscale in size. BTC ETFs see 11 straight days of inflows. ZKasino gives 72hours for ETH withdrawals. ENS to migrate to L2. ADA drops out of top 10 coins. Salame sentenced to 7.5 years in jail. Riot Platforms attempts takeover of Bitfarms. Ripple donates $25m to Fairshake PAC. Pump(.)fun launches live streaming. Iggy Azelea MOTHER coin leads celeb tokens. Beeple Everyday features many coins. Runes bounce, DOG hits $560m. PEPE active wallets double during rally. Cristiano Ronaldo launches 4th NFT. Friend Tech announces club wars.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum DN-404 Tokens Are a Sensation in Asia. Are They the West’s Next Big Trend?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/drcV3Zte/ethereum-dn-404-tokens-are-a-sensation-in-asia-are-they-the-wests-next-big-trend</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/drcV3Zte/ethereum-dn-404-tokens-are-a-sensation-in-asia-are-they-the-wests-next-big-trend"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T19:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz and Rug Radio creator Pukerainbow sat down for a conversation with some of the biggest adopters involved in Ethereum’s newest trend: dividing NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Buying Crypto Simplified with Mika]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/Z9rxTcnJ/buying-crypto-simplified-with-mika</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/Z9rxTcnJ/buying-crypto-simplified-with-mika"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T16:54:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the first part of our series turning crypto beginners into crypto pros, Rug Radio creator Mika guides you through the process of purchasing cryptocurrency using crypto exchange Kraken.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 125 - ETH NEARS 4K]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BrgFfEe8/fomo-hour-125-eth-nears-4k</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BrgFfEe8/fomo-hour-125-eth-nears-4k"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T17:40:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH leads rally on continued bullish ETF sentiment. Previous anti-crypto Trump comments highlighted. Wave of influencers and celebrities hacked, release coins. Phantom becomes no.1 finance app in the US. Argentina & El Salvador hold talks on BTC adoption. LINK to have large announcement on May 30th. PEPE, MOG, TURBO, TRUMP hit ATHs in ETH memes. MOG up 60%, mentioned in Beeple Everyday. Caitlyn Jenner hacker releases JENNER coin. Garga outlines future plans for BAYC. Friend Tech founder offers $200k to migrate off Base.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 124 - THE ETH ETF IS APPROVED!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5ELzjWt4/fomo-hour-124-the-eth-etf-is-approved</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5ELzjWt4/fomo-hour-124-the-eth-etf-is-approved"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T18:43:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH ETFs get approved 19b-4 forms. ETFs won’t trade until July or August: Galaxy. ETF means many coins not securities: Coinbase CLO. Coinbase relists XRP in US. SOL ETF coming: Scaramucci. US House passes vote to ban CBDC. Building a pro-crypto army in congress: Sen. Lummis. Polymarket backlash over if ETH ETF truly approved. Expect ETH ETFs to be 10-15% of BTC: Bloomberg. BTC ETFs see $1.75bn inflows over 9 days. BTC to $150k in 2024 is base case: Tom Lee. ETH co-founder moves $37m ETH to exchanges. Grayscale launches trusts for STX & NEAR. Coinbase loses against SEC on DOGE sweepstakes. ALGO ad attacks BTC, SOL, ETH. Phantom now no.2 finance App on Google Play.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 123 - ETHEREUM KEEPS GOING!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JE3lB00G/fomo-hour-123-ethereum-keeps-going</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JE3lB00G/fomo-hour-123-ethereum-keeps-going"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T15:43:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH soars, ETF S1 approvals expected in hours. US house greenlights FIT21 bill with broad support. Gensler says SEC already has rules for crypto. Hong Kong set to allow ETH staking for ETFs. ETH OI continues to soar. SOL mentioned as next ETF candidate on CNBC. SOL ETF will take years: Bloomberg. MetaMask plans BTC integration. Fed says only 7% of Americans own crypto. SBF heads to a new prison. Hong Kong orders WLD shutdown. TON added to Binance ahead of potential listing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 122 - ETH ETF MOVES CLOSER!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/FlTuDkm9/fomo-hour-122-eth-etf-moves-closer</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/FlTuDkm9/fomo-hour-122-eth-etf-moves-closer"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T16:33:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH ETFs move closer to approval, drop staking. Blackrock ETF see biggest inflow in 6 weeks. Grayscale ETH discount narrows under 10%. BTC & ETH heading for ATH: StanChart. Banana zone squared coming for ETH: Raoul Pal. Trump accepts crypto donations including DOGE. Pelosi mulls support of crypto bill. Farcaster raises $150M, DEGEN up 20%. Coinbase to launch gold & oil futures trading. Uniswap ‘ready to fight’ against SEC. Vitalik proposes solutions to MEV problems. Phantom may soon support email sign-up. Jupiter announces initiative to tokenise RWAs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 121 - ETHEREUM GOD CANDLES!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/EE1S4Hf4/fomo-hour-121-ethereum-god-candles</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/EE1S4Hf4/fomo-hour-121-ethereum-god-candles"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T16:17:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH ETF suddenly seems likely, flurry of amendments. ETH biggest daily gain ever, gains SOL market cap. ETF approval shifted due to political pressure. ETF approval may come as soon as tomorrow. Squeeze liquidates $230M of shorts. ETH OI hits record of $14B on exchanges. BTC nears ATH amid 6th straight day of ETF inflows. SOL flips ETH in Google search trends. House Democrats will not whip against crypto bills. Anti-crypto FDIC chair Gruenberg to step-down. Grayscale CEO steps down, ETHE discount narrows. Genesis settles for $2B with creditors. Binance to focus launchpad on higher float projects. SEI v2 launch coming next week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Do A Little With Chikai]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BGCnTbKb/we-do-a-little-with-chikai</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BGCnTbKb/we-do-a-little-with-chikai"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T18:21:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week’s episode, we sit down with our good friend and one of the biggest supporters of the pod, Chikai Ohazama. Chikai is the co-founder of Keyhole which was acquired by Google and became Google Earth. He is one of the most caring art collectors in our space, as well as an extremely talented AI artist.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 120 - SOLANA LEADS THE CHARGE]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/7jrsiszc/fomo-hour-120-solana-leads-the-charge</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/7jrsiszc/fomo-hour-120-solana-leads-the-charge"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T18:08:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SOL again leads majors, DEX volume dwarfs others. BTC whales buys $106M in 24hrs. ETH ETF decision on Thursday or Friday. 5 of 7 onchain indicators ‘point to bull-run’. ETH ETF may be rejected due to weak link to futures. AI coins in focus ahead of Nvidia earnings. Cobie inks new article on low float, high FDV coins. ETH foundation staff reveal links to EigenLayer. 12 L2 & L3s controlled by single multisig. Layer Zero pauses sybil rewards. Aevo to airdrop pre-launch tokens on platform. FTM to migrate one-to-one to Sonic S coin. UK judge rules Craig Wright is not Satoshi.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 119 - GOOD MORNING BULLS!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ikMRioZH/fomo-hour-119-good-morning-bulls</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ikMRioZH/fomo-hour-119-good-morning-bulls"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T11:02:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SOL leads majors higher again, BTC stable. ETFs see $257M inflow, volumes hit 2 month high. 414 holders of BlackRock ETF ‘blows away record’. SOL continues to be fastest blockage despite usage. Pump. fun exploited for $1.9M by ex-employee. LINK up 20% after partnership with top banks. Senate also repeals SEC crypto rule. US Senator uses laser eyes PFP. Tether mints another $1B USDT. Bitcoin production costs now $45K: JP Morgan. Pink Drainer retires after stealing $85m assets. PancakeSwap to reimburse fees on Uniswap. TON & Tether partnership on payment solution. Trabucco writes character defence of Ryan Salame.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>