<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-08-02T19:11:43.646Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-08-02T19:11:43.646Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[News Impacting Bitcoin Charts]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18813197/News-Impacting-Bitcoin-Charts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18813197/News-Impacting-Bitcoin-Charts"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T18:57:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[🚀 Learn Technical Analysis with our FREE course! https://www.chartguys.com/trading-courses/7/technical-analysis?utm_source=youtube&utm_medium=social&utm_term=&utm_content=&utm_campaign=free-ta-courseOur goal is to review and discuss the most recent price action in the market in a manner that...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Prime Is Giving Out Free NFTs for This Polygon Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151033</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151033/amazon-prime-free-nft-polygon-game-mojo-melee"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T18:48:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prime subscribers can now download a free Polygon NFT and in-game currency for Mojo Melee, with more freebies to come.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Prime Is Giving Out Free NFTs for This Polygon Game]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18813346/Amazon-Prime-Is-Giving-Out-Free-NFTs-for-This-Polygon-Game</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18813346/Amazon-Prime-Is-Giving-Out-Free-NFTs-for-This-Polygon-Game"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T18:48:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prime subscribers can now download a free Polygon NFT and in-game currency for Mojo Melee, with more freebies to come.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC now ready to consider ETH futures ETFs, sources say — but what’s changed?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18813344/SEC-now-ready-to-consider-ETH-futures-ETFs-sources-say-but-whats-changed</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18813344/SEC-now-ready-to-consider-ETH-futures-ETFs-sources-say-but-whats-changed"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T18:46:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SEC policy on crypto ETFs is “completely incoherent,” VanEck’s head of digital assets research tells Blockworks]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IRS Says Staking Rewards Can Now Be Taxed As Income Once Tokens Are Received]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18813349/IRS-Says-Staking-Rewards-Can-Now-Be-Taxed-As-Income-Once-Tokens-Are-Received</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18813349/IRS-Says-Staking-Rewards-Can-Now-Be-Taxed-As-Income-Once-Tokens-Are-Received"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T18:45:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Internal Revenue Service (IRS) says that US crypto traders staking rewards will now have to treat those earnings as part of their taxable income that year. Staking involves investors locking up their crypto assets into the blockchain in order to validate transactions and obtain rewards....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Calls Out SEC for Missing FTX Debacle, Says Regulator Repeatedly Hurting Retail Investors]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18813350/Ripple-Calls-Out-SEC-for-Missing-FTX-Debacle-Says-Regulator-Repeatedly-Hurting-Retail-Investors</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18813350/Ripple-Calls-Out-SEC-for-Missing-FTX-Debacle-Says-Regulator-Repeatedly-Hurting-Retail-Investors"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T18:41:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Labs is addressing the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and calling out the regulatory agency for what the firm says is inconsistent enforcement actions. In its Q2 2023 XRP Markets Reports, Ripple Labs slams the SEC, saying that its policies never actually protect consumers...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Give Projects a Chance,' Says Aurory's Michael Natoli on NFT Game Challenges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/nBNKKZdK/give-projects-a-chance-says-aurorys-michael-natoli-on-nft-game-challenges</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/nBNKKZdK/give-projects-a-chance-says-aurorys-michael-natoli-on-nft-game-challenges"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aurory is an NFT-driven game franchise that started life on Solana and is expanding to other chains. Decrypt's Jason Nelson spoke with Aurory Head of Marketing Michael Natoli at Solana's PlayGG event, where Natoli shared his thoughts on the challenges that blockchain games face in reaching players.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Give Projects a Chance,' Says Aurory's Michael Natoli on NFT Game Challenges]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18813347/Give-Projects-a-Chance-Says-Aurorys-Michael-Natoli-on-NFT-Game-Challenges</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18813347/Give-Projects-a-Chance-Says-Aurorys-Michael-Natoli-on-NFT-Game-Challenges"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aurory is an NFT-driven game franchise that started life on Solana and is expanding to other chains. Decrypt's Jason Nelson spoke with Aurory Head of Marketing Michael Natoli at Solana's PlayGG event, where Natoli shared his thoughts on the challenges that blockchain games face in reaching players.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bull Michael Saylor Speaks Live About BTC: Will He Buy More?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18813337/Bitcoin-Bull-Michael-Saylor-Speaks-Live-About-BTC-Will-He-Buy-More</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18813337/Bitcoin-Bull-Michael-Saylor-Speaks-Live-About-BTC-Will-He-Buy-More"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T18:36:05.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KuCoin To Suspend Mining Pool Services Starting August 15]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18813332/KuCoin-To-Suspend-Mining-Pool-Services-Starting-August-15</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18813332/KuCoin-To-Suspend-Mining-Pool-Services-Starting-August-15"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T18:31:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto exchange KuCoin has announced that it will suspend its mining pool services on August 15, 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Litecoin Completes Third-Ever Block Reward Halving]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18813348/Litecoin-Completes-Third-Ever-Block-Reward-Halving</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18813348/Litecoin-Completes-Third-Ever-Block-Reward-Halving"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T18:26:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Litecoin, the second-oldest blockchain network, completed its third block reward halving on Wednesday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin Crypto Project Temporarily Halted In Kenya – Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755a9a9f72</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/worldcoin-temporarily-halted-in-kenya/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T18:23:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Wednesday, Kenya’s interior ministry made a significant announcement, suspending the cryptocurrency project Worldcoin until further notice. The decision came as a precautionary measure to ensure public safety, and the suspension will remain in effect until relevant agencies can thoroughly assess the project to ensure it is devoid of risk.
 
Prior to the suspension, Kenya boasted a large number of venues, approximately 18, where individuals could visit “Orb” stations to verify their World IDs using the company’s spherical and mirrored iris-scanners.
 
 
However, due to overwhelming demand, the Orb operators moved their stations to the Kenyatta International Convention Centre (KICC) to accommodate the large number of people seeking verification.
 
Worldcoin: Privacy Concerns And Watchdog …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BREAKING: DOJ Investigation Casts Shadow Over Binance, Sparks Fears Of Bank Run]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755a9a9f67</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/doj-casts-shadow-binance-sparks-fears-of-bank-run/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T18:23:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Per a report from Semafor, the U.S. Department of Justice (DOJ) has been weighing on the possibility of filing fraud charges against crypto exchange Binance. The company has been in the eye of all major regulators worldwide in 2023 and might be about to face its biggest legal hurdle to date.
 
 
Binance At Risk Of Bank Run?
 
According to people familiar with the matter quoted by Semafor, the DOJ has been reluctant to file fraud charges for fear that this could trigger a “bank run.” In other words, the authorities are allegedly worried for investors and their funds if the crypto company becomes insolvent following a massive capital exodus.
 
If this happens, Binance will become the second major crypto exchange to face a bank run in over a year. In 2022, bankrupt exchange FTX faced a similar situation when reports about its financial state began circulating, leaving thousands of users with their funds “stuck” on the platform.
 
In that sense, the DOJ authorities are looking to implement other options, such as fines or an agreement with the company, Semafor wrote. As of this writing, there is no official statement from Binance or its top executives.
 
The company is currently facing a legal battle with U.S. regulators. The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) filed a complaint against the crypto platform and its U.S. subsidiary over allegedly violating securities laws.
 
This has negatively impacted Binance.US market share. If the DOJ proceeds with the fraud charges, the international arm could suffer a similar fate, confirming fears of a major bank run on the platform.
 
On this possibility, pseudonym crypto trader “Hsaka” stated: “The same run they’ve been trying to unsuccessfully ignite for the past few months?”
 
 
As of this writing, Bitcoin and the rest of the crypto market are negatively reacting to the news with the price of top coins tumbling into critical support levels.
 
 
Cover image from Unsplash, chart from Tradingview]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reynaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance’s CZ warns crypto community about emerging scam]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18813297/Binances-CZ-warns-crypto-community-about-emerging-scam</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18813297/Binances-CZ-warns-crypto-community-about-emerging-scam"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T18:18:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The scheme consists of mirroring addresses and sending dust transactions to users to trick them into sending funds to the scammer’s wallet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Low cost of Solana DeFi frees developers from constraints: Ellipsis co-founder]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18813296/Low-cost-of-Solana-DeFi-frees-developers-from-constraints-Ellipsis-co-founder</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18813296/Low-cost-of-Solana-DeFi-frees-developers-from-constraints-Ellipsis-co-founder"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T18:18:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ‘De’ in ‘DeFi’ stands for decentralized — but is it a thing of the past?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether Reports $850M Profit In Second Quarter]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18813301/Tether-Reports-850M-Profit-In-Second-Quarter</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18813301/Tether-Reports-850M-Profit-In-Second-Quarter"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T18:14:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Skeptics Continue To Question Quarterly Attestation Reports]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOJ Weighs Fraud Charges against Binance, Worried about Bank Run: Report]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755a9bf5aa</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/doj-weighs-fraud-charges-against-binance-worried-about-bank-run-report/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T18:12:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US  
prosecutors are mulling over whether to initiate criminal charges against  
Binance, thereby turning the heat on 13 civil charges filed by the securities  
watchdog against the top crypto exchange earlier in June, Semafor reported today  
(Wednesday), citing insider sources. However, the Department of Justice (DOJ)  
is worried that such action could lead to a bank run, throwing the exchange  
into a position similar to that of the now-bankrupt crypto exchange, FTX. 
Prosecutors  
Contemplate Criminal Charges
According  
to the report, the DoJ is contemplating opting for other measures such as fines  
and deferred or non-prosecution agreements (NPAs). An NPA means that the federal prosecutor, despite believing that a crime has been committed, will delay prosecution in exchange for the crypto firm's compliance with certain conditions. 
These  
conditions typically range from payment of fines and the institution of corporate reform to full cooperation with a probe. In such cases, the charges are dismissed if the  
defendant complies with the conditions.
 
  
 
  
This article was written by Solomon Oladipupo at www.financemagnates.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Solomon Oladipupo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Price analysis 8/2: BTC, ETH, BNB, XRP, DOGE, ADA, SOL, MATIC, LTC, DOT]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18813271/Price-analysis-82-BTC-ETH-BNB-XRP-DOGE-ADA-SOL-MATIC-LTC-DOT</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18813271/Price-analysis-82-BTC-ETH-BNB-XRP-DOGE-ADA-SOL-MATIC-LTC-DOT"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T18:07:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin is witnessing a strong battle between the bulls and the bears, with the sellers currently holding a slight edge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rich Dad Poor Dad Author Robert Kiyosaki Says US Dollar ‘Toast’ Amid Rise of Gold-Backed BRICS Currency]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18813280/Rich-Dad-Poor-Dad-Author-Robert-Kiyosaki-Says-US-Dollar-Toast-Amid-Rise-of-Gold-Backed-BRICS-Currency</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18813280/Rich-Dad-Poor-Dad-Author-Robert-Kiyosaki-Says-US-Dollar-Toast-Amid-Rise-of-Gold-Backed-BRICS-Currency"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T18:05:27.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consensys sued over MetaMask intellectual property: CoinDesk]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18813279/Consensys-sued-over-MetaMask-intellectual-property-CoinDesk</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18813279/Consensys-sued-over-MetaMask-intellectual-property-CoinDesk"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T18:04:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a lawsuit, entrepreneur Joel Dietz claims to have started working on a browser-based crypto wallet called Vapor.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin And Litecoin Announcement From KuCoin!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18813283/Bitcoin-And-Litecoin-Announcement-From-KuCoin</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18813283/Bitcoin-And-Litecoin-Announcement-From-KuCoin"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T18:02:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leading cryptocurrency exchange KuCoin announced on August 15 that it will suspend Bitcoin (BTC) and Litecoin (LTC) mining pools. Continue Reading: Bitcoin And Litecoin Announcement From KuCoin!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4,884 ETH Worth $8M Was Just Burned]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18813295/4884-ETH-Worth-8M-Was-Just-Burned</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18813295/4884-ETH-Worth-8M-Was-Just-Burned"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T18:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What happened: On Tuesday a total of 4,884.68 Ether (CRYPTO: ETH) worth $8,957,679, based on the current value of Ethereum at time of publication ($1,833.83), was burned from Ethereum transactions. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Sleuths Discover Potential Connections Between Sam Bankman-Fried and BALD Rugpull]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18813274/Crypto-Sleuths-Discover-Potential-Connections-Between-Sam-Bankman-Fried-and-BALD-Rugpull</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18813274/Crypto-Sleuths-Discover-Potential-Connections-Between-Sam-Bankman-Fried-and-BALD-Rugpull"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Connections can be found between Sam Bankman-Fried’s trading firm Alameda Research and the deployer of an alleged crypto scam called BALD. According to members of the crypto community who have analyzed on-chain data, the deployer of the meme coin, which was built on Coinbase’s new layer 2...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fitch Ratings Downgrades US Government Debt To AA+]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18813310/Fitch-Ratings-Downgrades-US-Government-Debt-To-AA</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18813310/Fitch-Ratings-Downgrades-US-Government-Debt-To-AA"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T17:55:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fitch claims there’s been an “erosion of governance” on how to manage U.S. government debt, but the Treasury Department disagrees.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These Are the High-Profile Ethereum Futures ETF Applications Currently in Play]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151012</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151012/these-are-the-high-profile-ethereum-futures-etf-applications-currently-in-play"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T17:52:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first Ethereum futures ETF could be launched as soon as October 2023—that is, if the SEC approves it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Dunworth  | Simply Bitcoin IRL]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18813255/Peter-Dunworth-Simply-Bitcoin-IRL</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18813255/Peter-Dunworth-Simply-Bitcoin-IRL"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T17:51:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nico talks with Peter Dunworth an extraordinarily bullish financial adviser - his predictions might surprise you!!#bitcoin #jeffross #tomerstrolightPowered by : Swan Bitcoin► https://www.swan.com/simply► Swan Bitcoin is the best way to build your Bitcoin stack, with automated Bitcoin savings...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why I Don’t Feel Bad for HEX Founder Richard Heart’s Victims]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755a87208c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/08/02/why-i-dont-feel-bad-for-hex-founder-richard-hearts-victims/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T17:46:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maybe the SEC can finally convince Hex and PulseChain devotees that they’ve been cheated.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Z. Morris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Could Face U.S. Fraud Charges, but Prosecutors Worry About Risk of Bank Run: Semafor]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755a801a4a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/08/02/binance-could-face-us-fraud-charges-but-prosecutors-worry-about-risk-of-bank-run-semafor/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T17:38:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price of bitcoin (BTC) and Binance's BNB token immediately fell following the report.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Napolitano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Litecoin Completes Third Block Reward Halving, Cutting Rewards to 6.25 LTC; Miners Face Revenue Loss as Prices Dip 4%]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755a809bc2</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/litecoin-completes-third-block-reward-halving-cutting-rewards-to-6-25-ltc-miners-face-revenue-loss-as-prices-dip-4/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T17:34:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Litecoin (LTC) network has officially experienced its third block reward halving at block height 2,520,000, with LTC rewards diminishing from 12.5 LTC to 6.25 LTC. Thus far, the halving has not propelled LTC prices upwards as market data reveals LTC has declined over 4% in the past 24 hours.
 
Halving Unshaken: Litecoin Network Sees Third Reduction in Rewards
 
On August 2, 2023, the Litecoin (LTC) blockchain documented its third block reward halving. Litecoin’s first halving transpired on August 25, 2015, at block height 840,000, and the second occurred on August 5, 2019, at block height 1,680,000.
 
The most recent reward halving, happening at block height 2,520,000, has reduced the reward from 12.5 LTC to 6.25 LTC. Prior to this halving event, LTC miners generated 7,200 new LTC unit…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Spot ETF Approval Odds Rise To 65%: Bloomberg Analysts]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755a81d899</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-spot-etf-odds-65-bloomberg-analysts/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T17:24:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bloomberg Intelligence analysts James Seyffart and Eric Balchunas have ramped up their approval odds for a Bitcoin spot Exchange-Traded Fund (ETF) to 65%, based on recent industry developments. This marks a substantial increase from the mere 1% chance they assigned to it a few months ago.
 
“Based on recent events and new information Eric Balchunas and I are officially increasing our spot Bitcoin ETF approval odds to 65%,” Seyffart remarked on Twitter, adding, “that’s from 50% a couple of weeks ago and 1% a few months ago.”
 
Driving this revised prediction are multiple factors, including recent statements from SEC chair Gary Gensler, developments from leading digital asset manager Grayscale, and the SEC’s perceived approval of Coinbase’s Bitcoin exchange.
 
 
“The odds of a Bitcoin spot E…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF Approval Odds Just Got Better: Bloomberg Analysts]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755a8c901b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/08/02/bloomberg-etf-analysts-raise-chance-of-spot-bitcoin-etf-approval-to-65/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T17:03:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“The odds of a spot Bitcoin ETF launching this year are up to 65%, in our eyes, after a flurry of developments,” analysts James Seyffart and Eric Balchunas wrote. They previously assigned a 50% probability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Venture Capital Is Anything but Boring: Crypto Long & Short]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755a8c900b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/08/02/bitcoin-venture-capital-is-anything-but-boring-crypto-long-short/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T17:03:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The purposeful approach to Bitcoin Core development fuels the idea that “nothing is happening on Bitcoin,” but innovation is actually robust.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christopher  Calicott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Hedge Funds Will Shake Up the Industry: Crypto Long & Short]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755a8c8ff8</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/08/02/crypto-hedge-funds-are-going-to-shake-up-the-industry-crypto-long-short/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T17:03:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are hundreds of them already in crypto, and that’s likely to go up and catalyze the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glenn Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance China Dominance Continues: Volume Hits $90-B Despite Crypto Ban – Report]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755a89eec2</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/binance-china-dominance-continues/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T16:24:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance continues to attract a significant portion of its business from China, even in the face of the country’s prohibition on cryptocurrencies. In May, Binance recorded a staggering trading volume exceeding $90 billion, encompassing both spot and futures transactions originating from the country.
 
This data, disclosed by the Wall Street Journal and referencing the exchange’s internal system “Mission Control,” highlights the prevalence of futures trading within this volume.
 
 
What emerges prominently is the company’s unwavering gusto in maintaining a foothold within the Chinese market. This determination becomes all the more significant as the company deftly maneuvers through the intricate web of global regulatory hurdles that cast a shadow of uncertainty over the future of the entire …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gaming Giant Bandai Namco Launches AI Virtual Pet NFT Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151011</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151011/gaming-giant-bandai-namco-launches-ai-virtual-pet-nft-game"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T16:18:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bandai Namco Research and partners have rolled out a virtual pet game, joining other publishers like Ubisoft and Sega on the Oasys blockchain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ali Shutler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Is 'Big Barbie' Energy]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755a754ce7</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/08/02/bitcoin-is-big-barbie-energy/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T16:02:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Director Greta Gerwig's reimagined and self-empowered Barbie would love Bitcoin, author and influencer Aubrey Strobel writes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aubrey Strobel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why You Should Care About Litecoin: It's the Backbone of Dogecoin]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755a76f4c8</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/08/02/why-you-should-care-about-litecoin-its-the-backbone-of-dogecoin/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T15:50:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Litecoin, a blockchain cloned from Bitcoin in 2011 that underwent a key milestone on Wednesday known as a “halving,” provides network security to Dogecoin via a process called “merged mining.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Frederick  Munawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Litecoin Just Had Its Third Halving—Here's What That Means for LTC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151005</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151005/litecoin-third-halving-what-it-means-for-ltc"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T15:44:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So far, it isn’t looking too good for the Bitcoin fork which recently experienced resurgence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beeple Goes Punk With $208K NFT Purchase]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755a70c093</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/web3/2023/08/02/beeple-goes-punk-with-208k-nft-purchase/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T15:38:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The artist behind the most expensive NFT ever sold bought his first-ever PFP, CryptoPunk #4593.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cam Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biggest Movers: MATIC Bounces From 4-Week Low, After Collision With Key Support Point]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755a71c1c4</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/biggest-movers-matic-bounces-from-4-week-low-after-collision-with-key-support-point/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T15:31:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon rebounded from a four-week low on Wednesday, as bulls rejected a breakout below a key support point. The wider market cap was mostly higher in today’s session, led by the optimism surrounding Microstrategy’s latest bitcoin investment. Chainlink also jumped higher after recent losses. 
 
Polygon (MATIC)
 
Polygon (MATIC) bounced back higher during Wednesday’s session, as the token moved away from a recent four-week low.
 
After plunging to a bottom $0.6751 on Tuesday, MATIC/USD rallied to a peak of $0.7022 earlier in the day.
 
The move came as bulls rejected a breakout below a recent price floor of $0.6750, which coincided with the relative strength index (RSI) pushing away from its own support level.
 
 
After racing from the aforementioned point at 43.00, the index made an attempt to reach resistance of 45.00.
 
However, at the time of writing, price strength is now tracking at a reading of 44.06, with MATIC back below $0.7000.
 
Overall, momentum appears to be bearish, with the token falling for five of the last seven sessions.
 
 
Chainlink (LINK)
 
In addition to polygon, chainlink (LINK) rebounded from a recent losing streak which resulted in price hitting a one-week low.
 
LINK/USD leaped to an intraday high of $7.70 during today’s session, following a drop to a low of $7.40 the day prior.
 
Yesterday’s decline pushed chainlink below a support point of $7.50, and to its weakest level since July 26.
 
 
LINK has managed to recover from its earlier drop, as the RSI climbed away from its own floor at the 55.00 zone.
 
Currently, the index is tracking at 56.78, and appears to be making a move towards a ceiling of 60.00.
 
In the event that this level is hit, there is a good chance that LINK moves above $7.80.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
Could chainlink hit $8.00 by this time next week? Let us know your thoughts in the comments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KPMG Deems Bitcoin ‘Misunderstood’: Energy Consumption At Par With Tumble Dryers]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755a72acd3</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/kpmg-bitcoin-misunderstood-tumble-dryers/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T15:24:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prominent accounting and consultancy firm, KPMG, has published a report delving into Bitcoin and its mining implications. The report focuses on investigating Bitcoin’s potential to align with the principles of environmentally friendly investing, commonly known as ESG (Environmental, Social, and Governance).
 
KPMG’s latest report categorizes Bitcoin (BTC) as a mature asset class, though it highlights the persistent misunderstandings despite its continued adoption.
 
The report’s primary objective is to thoroughly assess the technology’s actual environmental, social, and governance impacts and dispel prevailing misconceptions on these fronts.
 
Related Reading: Here’s What KPMG Said About Slowdown In Crypto Investments
 
In particular, they state that there is a variety of high-impact use c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>anushsamal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Litecoin Undergoes Third 'Halving,' in Milestone for 12-Year-Old Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755a72f030</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/08/02/litecoin-undergoes-third-halving-in-milestone-for-12-year-old-blockchain/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T15:22:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The blockchain's "halving," where the pace of new issuance of cryptocurrency gets cut in half every four years, took place Wednesday, when it reached data block 2,520,000.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Frederick  Munawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Juggernaut MetaMask’s Origin Story Challenged in New Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755a7c6f6f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/08/02/ethereum-juggernaut-metamasks-origin-story-challenged-in-new-lawsuit/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T15:11:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joel Dietz is suing ConsenSys and his former business partner over his claims to MetaMask, the most important crypto wallet for the Ethereum blockchain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized Exchange THORSwap Introduces New Feature Aimed at Better Price Execution for Large Trades]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755a7c6f5a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/08/02/decentralized-exchange-thorswap-introduces-new-feature-aimed-at-better-price-execution-for-large-trades/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T15:11:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Called Streaming Swaps, the feature is designed to improve capital efficiency for decentralized finance users who want to execute large trades.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sage D. Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is A Bitcoin ETF?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755a7a0bc6</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/guides/what-is-a-bitcoin-etf"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T14:29:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction
As interest in bitcoin continues to grow, so does the demand for investment products that provide exposure to companies and funds alike. One such product that has gained significant attention is the Bitcoin Exchange-Traded Fund (ETF).
What Is An ETF?
ETFs are designed to track the performance of a particular index, commodity or asset class. This means that when you invest in an ETF, you are essentially buying a basket of securities or commodities that represent the underlying index or asset. For example, if you invest in an ETF that tracks the S&P 500 index, you will own a proportional share of the companies included in that index.
One of the key advantages of ETFs is their ability to be traded on a stock exchange throughout the day, just like individual stocks. This is in con…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Show Your Face to the Orb': Eyes-on With Sam Altman's Worldcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150961</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150961/show-your-face-to-the-orb-eyes-on-with-sam-altmans-worldcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T12:22:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In former East Berlin, Sam Altman’s Worldcoin is scanning irises for tokens—under the watchful eye of European privacy watchdogs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried's Lawyers Say Basis for Revoking Bail Is 'Extremely Thin']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150946</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150946/sam-bankman-frieds-lawyers-say-basis-revoking-bail-is-extremely-thin"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T10:26:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bankman-Fried's defense fights back against the DOJ’s recent motion, saying it's based on “innuendo” and “assumptions.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kenya Suspends Worldcoin Operations Amid Privacy Concerns]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150942</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150942/kenya-suspends-worldcoin-operations-privacy-concerns"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T09:41:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin faces further scrutiny over its iris-scanning project, despite over 2 million sign-ups worldwide.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Mulling Best Ways to Integrate Lightning Network for Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150938</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150938/coinbase-mulling-best-ways-integrate-lightning-network-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T09:05:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong has reiterated the crypto exchange’s intention to add support for Bitcoin’s Layer-2 scaling solution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Room-Temperature Superconductor Claim Sparks Excitement and Skepticism]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150927</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150927/room-temperature-superconductor-lk-99"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T00:38:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From supercomputer simulations to a kitchen recreation, the news has riled up the science community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ApeCoin Price Sinks to All-Time Low as Bored Ape NFTs Dip Again]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150902</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150902/apecoin-price-sinks-all-time-low-bored-ape-nfts-dip-again"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T23:39:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Days after Yuga Labs showcased fresh elements of its Otherside metaverse game, the Bored Ape-themed Ethereum token notched a new low.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Moneyball' Meets Crypto in 'The Boys of Summer' Experimental NFT Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150909</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150909/moneyball-meets-crypto-boys-summer-experimental-nft-game"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T22:47:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artist Mitchell F. Chan's Ethereum NFT game about statistical overload goes well beyond the baseball diamond.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Cohen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy Makes Profit, Reports $24 Million Bitcoin Impairment Charge in Q2]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150903</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150903/microstrategy-profit-impairment-charge-bitcoin-holdings"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T21:22:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company has returned to profitability after a modest rise in the price of Bitcoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Keep Finding New and Sophisticated Ways to Use AI for Crime]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150899</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150899/wormgpt-fraudgpt-ai-hackers-phishing-malware"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T20:02:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity firm SlashNext sounds the alarm as exploits get much more sophisticated.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop Is Killing Its NFT Wallet and Blames ‘Regulatory Uncertainty’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150898</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150898/gamestop-nft-wallet-canceled-killed"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T19:56:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The video game retailer's NFT push continues to crumble after it fired the CEO who oversaw its launch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Arrows Capital Co-Founder Kyle Davies Says He Doesn't Have to Answer to US Courts]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150890</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150890/three-arrows-capital-co-founder-kyle-davies-rejects-us-court-jurisdiction"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T19:15:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The co-founder of the collapsed firm said in documents that he became a permanent resident of Singapore years ago.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Bets Big on AI to Revive Facebook and Instagram]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150882</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150882/meta-ai-instagram-facebook-chatbot-personalities"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T18:57:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With new chatbots and image editing tools, the social giant is gunning to rise again like a phoenix—with AI as the wind beneath its wings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Ordinals Team Launches Nonprofit as Inscriptions Top 21 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150871</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150871/bitcoin-ordinals-team-launches-nonprofit-inscriptions-top-21-million"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T18:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The team behind Ordinals said its Bitcoin-based protocol's development will be supported by a nonprofit structure moving forward.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia AI Image Generator Fits on a Floppy Disk and Takes 4 Minutes to Train]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150861</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150861/nvidia-ai-image-generator-floppy-disk-4-minutes"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T17:44:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia's new Perfusion image generator takes 100KB of space and needs only 4 minutes of training.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Justin Sun, DCF God and Others Line Up to Buy Curve Finance Founder’s CRV Tokens]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150852</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150852/justin-sun-dcf-god-and-others-line-up-buy-curve-finance-founders-crv-tokens"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T14:27:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After selling CRV to a host of eager buyers, the Curve founder has repaid $9.2 million in Aave loans. But risks still abound.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Term Labs Launches Fixed-Rate Lending Protocol on Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150841</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150841/term-labs-launches-fixed-rate-lending-protocol-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T13:01:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Term Labs took inspiration from the U.S. Treasury to build a platform that matches borrowers with lenders according to their preferred rates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Genesis Digital Assets Expands Bitcoin Mining Activity in ‘Pro-Innovation’ South Carolina]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150837</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150837/genesis-digital-assets-expands-bitcoin-mining-activity-pro-innovation-south-carolina"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T13:01:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The mining firm is launching three locations in South Carolina, with its CEO citing the state’s “abundance of clean electricity” for the move.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Krantz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Worldcoin? Sam Altman's Eye-Scanning Global ID 'Orb' Project Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150832</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-worldcoin-the-app-and-token-that-protects-your-personhood"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T11:44:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin has introduced a concept called “proof of personhood" to keep AI bots out of its global financial network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Reiff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LeetSwap DEX Pauses Trading on Base Due to Potential Exploit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150826</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150826/leetswap-dex-pauses-trading-base-due-potential-exploit"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T10:58:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The decentralized exchange team pulls the circuit breaker to pause trading as their trading pools are potentially compromised.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Reboot Pitches New Offshore Exchange for Users]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150825</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150825/ftx-reboot-pitches-new-offshore-exchange-dotcom-users"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T10:48:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The FTX reboot is rolling out a new offshore entity, offering claimants the opportunity to hold equity securities, tokens, or other interests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IRS Says Staking Rewards Are Taxable Income in Latest Revenue Ruling]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150817</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150817/irs-says-staking-rewards-is-taxable-income-latest-revenue-ruling"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T10:20:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto investors who earn staking rewards are now required to report these earnings as part of their gross income for tax purposes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Industry Still Isn’t Close to Solving the Blockchain Trilemma: Offchain Labs Chief Strategy Officer]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150816</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150816/industry-still-isnt-close-solving-the-blockchain-trilemma-offchain-labs-chief-strategy-officer"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T08:52:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solving the famed trilemma “would be a huge breakthrough,” but it would also need to inspire developers, said the Offchain Labs’ exec.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly,Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain Sleuths Link BALD Liquidity Rug Pull to Sam Bankman-Fried]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150780</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150780/bald-token-liquidity-rug-pull-linked-to-sam-bankman-fried"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T01:01:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The disgraced FTX founder is fingered by some who believe he removed liquidity from the BALD meme coin—before putting some back.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Wall Street Interest in Bitcoin Scare Cypherpunks Away?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150762</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150762/wall-street-institutional-mainstream-interest"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T23:50:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As big banks develop an appetite for crypto, privacy-centric users are increasingly wary of newcomers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Judge Refuses to Dismiss SEC Lawsuit Against Terraform Labs Despite Ripple Ruling]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150770</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150770/judge-refuses-dismissal-sec-terraform-labs-lawsuit-despite-ripple-ruling"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T23:37:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ruling found that crypto "falls far short" of having the significance needed for Congress to review regulation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt AI, Edited by Ryan Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hasbro Flirts With AI as Dungeons &#038; Dragons Game Sites Push Back]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150765</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150765/dungeons-dragons-hasbro-ai-xplored-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T22:34:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hasbro taps Xplored to infuse AI into gameplay, adding real-time responses to player decisions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How an Ethereum Bot Used Uniswap to Save $5.4 Million From Curve Exploit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150713</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150713/how-ethereum-uniswap-save-5-4-million-curve-exploit"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T22:24:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The MEV bot’s white-hat operator returned the funds to Curve Finance, which may have otherwise been lost to malicious hackers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yuga Labs to Acquire Roar Studios for AI Expertise]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150757</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150757/yuga-labs-roar-studios-acquisition-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T21:48:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eric Reid, Roar Studios founder and CEO, will head Yuga Labs’ upcoming Otherside game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Barbie's Margot Robbie Says Bitcoin Is for 'Kens'—While Mattel Pushes NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150755</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150755/barbie-margot-robbie-bitcoin-ken-mattel-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T21:10:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The actress dunked on the cryptocurrency as a stereotypically male conversation topic in a recent interview promoting "Barbie."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Art Showdown: How Top Tools MidJourney, Stable Diffusion v1.5, and SDXL Stack Up]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150714</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150714/ai-art-comparison-midjourney-stable-diffusion-sdxl-dall-e"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T20:58:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A clash of titans in AI tech has accelerated a generative image creation arms race. Which tool takes top honors?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BALD Meme Coin on Coinbase Layer-2 Goes to Zero as Dev Pulls Liquidity]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150693</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150693/following-meme-coin-mania-on-coinbases-base-one-token-appears-to-be-a-rug"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T19:39:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The BALD token exploded with popularity yesterday, but its deployers have since run off with millions of dollars in liquidity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ron DeSantis Promises to End 'Biden's War on Bitcoin', Toss CBDC 'Into the Trash Can']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150711</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150711/ron-desantis-biden-war-on-bitcoin-crypto-trash-cbdc"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T19:31:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Florida governor is among a number of presidential candidates who have expressed support for the leading cryptocurrency.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Is Only Network Ready for Gaming: Solana Foundation's Johnny Lee]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5OvV3ZXn/solana-is-only-network-ready-for-gaming-solana-foundations-johnny-lee</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5OvV3ZXn/solana-is-only-network-ready-for-gaming-solana-foundations-johnny-lee"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T17:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Foundation General Manager Johnny Lee tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how the Solana network will tackle the scaling problem that blockchain games pose for the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi Contagion? Curve Finance Exploit Ripples Across Industry]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150679</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150679/defi-contagion-curve-finance-exploit-ripples-across-industry"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T17:09:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smart contracts built using older Vyper versions are vulnerable to hacks, according to the programming language’s developers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi,Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether Reports $850 Million Q2 Profit, $72 Billion Exposure to US Treasuries]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150678</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150678/tether-reports-850-million-q2-profit-72-billion-exposure-to-us-treasuries"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T16:49:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Altogether Tether has about $72.5 billion worth of U.S. Treasury Bills backing its USDT stablecoin, according to the report.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Com2uS Is Going "Full Speed" on Crypto Gaming: Kyu Lee]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pYMZRoYy/com2us-is-going-full-speed-on-crypto-gaming-kyu-lee</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pYMZRoYy/com2us-is-going-full-speed-on-crypto-gaming-kyu-lee"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kyu Lee is the President of game studio Com2uS USA. In an interview, he shares the studio's approach to Web3 and crypto gaming with Decrypt GG's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Discord Game with AI and Blockchain: 'Alchemy: Battle for Ankhos' Creative Lead Alex Finden]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mF18GHGo/building-a-discord-game-with-ai-and-blockchain-alchemy-battle-for-ankhos-creative-lead-alex-finden</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mF18GHGo/building-a-discord-game-with-ai-and-blockchain-alchemy-battle-for-ankhos-creative-lead-alex-finden"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T21:55:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Jason Nelson interviews Alchemy: Battle for Ankhos Creative Director Alex Finden at the Solana PlayGG event in San Diego, California.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Big Respect Between Ethereum and Cosmos Developer Communities': dYdX Foundation CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/XU5MbCGE/big-respect-between-ethereum-and-cosmos-developer-communities-dydx-foundation-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/XU5MbCGE/big-respect-between-ethereum-and-cosmos-developer-communities-dydx-foundation-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T13:24:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CEO of the dYdX Foundation Charles d'Haussy unpacks the decision behind moving one of the largest decentralized exchange protocol's over to its very own chain built on Cosmos. A key driver, he told Decrypt at this year's EthCC event, was that instead of launching on a rollup or another layer-1, launching a fully customized chain will allow dYdX to fine tune the network for its product's needs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Staking Solution Lido 'Had Perfect Product Market Fit' at Launch, Says DAO's Biz Dev Contributor]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/fUHhelhV/ethereum-staking-solution-lido-had-perfect-product-market-fit-at-launch-says-daos-biz-dev-contributor</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/fUHhelhV/ethereum-staking-solution-lido-had-perfect-product-market-fit-at-launch-says-daos-biz-dev-contributor"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T08:43:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marin Tvrdić, a business development contributor to the Lido DAO, sat down with Decrypt during this year's EthCC to break down how the liquid staking protocol has managed such a massive lead, how it plans to keep that lead, and the protocol's new dual-governance tokenomics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's Going to Stop All the DeFi Hacks? 'Standards,' Says OpenZepplin Security Architect]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/aYNuFdAi/whats-going-to-stop-all-the-defi-hacks-standards-says-openzepplin-security-architect</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/aYNuFdAi/whats-going-to-stop-all-the-defi-hacks-standards-says-openzepplin-security-architect"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T08:04:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenZeppelin's security solutions architect Michael Lewellen sat down with Decrypt to discuss how the industry can become a little safer for users at this year's EthCC Paris. The key? Introducing security standards across the industry so folks know what an audit actually means and where risks lie, be it bad faith actors or poor implementation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Ev.io' Game Review: Earn Solana While Blasting Enemies]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/2ZmkuhL2/evio-game-review-earn-solana-while-blasting-enemies</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/2ZmkuhL2/evio-game-review-earn-solana-while-blasting-enemies"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T22:21:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ev.io is a web-based first-person shooter that's free to play, but lets NFT holders earn in-game currency that can be redeemed for Solana (SOL). Decrypt contributor Ryan Gladwin shares his review of the fun throwback to Quake-style blasting, albeit with a modern crypto twist.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Moving Fast and Breaking Things Isn't the Web3 Ethos': MetaMask Product Lead]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/l1EbLgl3/moving-fast-and-breaking-things-isnt-the-web3-ethos-metamask-product-lead</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/l1EbLgl3/moving-fast-and-breaking-things-isnt-the-web3-ethos-metamask-product-lead"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T15:45:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Account abstraction this, smart wallets that. Discussions at EthCC Paris about improving user experience have pointed at industry leader MetaMask as an example of what not to do. But that may soon change, with a host of updates and optimizations coming to crypto's number one wallet, said its product lead Alex Jupiter. It still may take some time, though, before these changes take effect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling Smart Wallets on Starknet 'Was The Winning Combination', Says Argent Co-Founder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/gnBsxw4D/scaling-smart-wallets-on-starknet-was-the-winning-combination-says-argent-co-founder</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/gnBsxw4D/scaling-smart-wallets-on-starknet-was-the-winning-combination-says-argent-co-founder"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T07:35:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Argent co-founder Julien Niset told Decrypt at EthCC Paris that he wants to make crypto wallets disappear. Or at least how they're currently conceived. From clunky seed phrases to a stiff user experience, Argent hopes to make using crypto a little less intimidating and a whole lot more fun.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Mighty Action Heroes' Open Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/litL6kKs/inside-mighty-action-heroes-open-beta</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/litL6kKs/inside-mighty-action-heroes-open-beta"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T18:23:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mighty Action Heroes is the flagship blockchain title from Mighty Bear Games. But is the browser-based battle royale shooter worth checking out? Decrypt's Kate Irwin offers her thoughts and a first look at the upcoming game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dr. Disrespect's 'Deadrop': Early Access Gameplay From Snapshot VI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/8l21EHoa/dr-disrespects-deadrop-early-access-gameplay-from-snapshot-vi</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/8l21EHoa/dr-disrespects-deadrop-early-access-gameplay-from-snapshot-vi"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T18:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin playtests Dr. Disrespect and Midnight Society's first-person shooter Deadrop and shares the latest game updates, as well as her opinions on the game in development. Currently, Deadrop offers Polygon Founders Pass NFTs with no other crypto plans revealed just yet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['More and More' Game Publishers Will Embrace NFTs: Mythical Games CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/wBWogSkl/more-and-more-game-publishers-will-embrace-nfts-mythical-games-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/wBWogSkl/more-and-more-game-publishers-will-embrace-nfts-mythical-games-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T22:28:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the wake of EA Sports and Fortnite creator Epic Games embracing Nike's NFT platform, Mythical Games CEO John Linden tells Decrypt's Andrew Hayward how quickly he expects to see more major traditional game publishers enter the blockchain space and how quickly the industry will scale.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gran Saga Unlimited Early Access: Inside the Anime MMORPG on Aptos]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JeFWMVwo/gran-saga-unlimited-early-access-inside-the-anime-mmorpg-on-aptos</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JeFWMVwo/gran-saga-unlimited-early-access-inside-the-anime-mmorpg-on-aptos"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T21:46:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin plays Gran Saga: Unlimited's second community playtest, reports her findings, and offers her opinion and insights on the upcoming game, which will offer optional Aptos NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[100 Thieves' Moe Says Blockchain Games Will 'Eventually' Be Accepted by Livestreamers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/xHhh62ID/100-thieves-moe-says-blockchain-games-will-eventually-be-accepted-by-livestreamers</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/xHhh62ID/100-thieves-moe-says-blockchain-games-will-eventually-be-accepted-by-livestreamers"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T16:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[100 Thieves content creator and gamer Moe also goes by "Yassuo" online after his favorite League of Legends character. Decrypt's Kate Irwin asks him about 100 Thieves' future crypto plans and whether Moe thinks creators like xQc and Pokimane might ever come around to blockchain games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Games of the Future Are Going to Be Different," Says Splinterlands Cofounder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/sQv6zcil/games-of-the-future-are-going-to-be-different-says-splinterlands-cofounder</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/sQv6zcil/games-of-the-future-are-going-to-be-different-says-splinterlands-cofounder"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T20:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Splinterlands Cofounder Matt Rosen tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about how the game has evolved over its five-year history and why he doesn't listen to the FUD around crypto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Champions Ascension: Like 'For Honor' with NFTs?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/gvM9ajww/inside-champions-ascension-like-for-honor-with-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/gvM9ajww/inside-champions-ascension-like-for-honor-with-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T22:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plai Labs Marketing Director Payton Kaleiwahea tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about player response to the combat game Champions Ascension in development, which offers arena combat, raid bosses, AI landscape features, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Activision VP Michael Lee: Gaming Is Crypto's 'Killer App']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/M9ulXrb3/ex-activision-vp-michael-lee-gaming-is-cryptos-killer-app</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/M9ulXrb3/ex-activision-vp-michael-lee-gaming-is-cryptos-killer-app"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Activision Vice President Michael Lee is now the SVP of Growth at Matter Labs. At the 3XP gaming conference, Lee sat down with Decrypt's Kate Irwin to discuss crypto gaming and give his predictions for the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>