<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-01-01T05:15:41.735Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-01-01T05:15:41.735Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Could Approve Spot Bitcoin ETFs by Tuesday or Wednesday, Sources Say]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7486806dd1</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/sec-could-approve-spot-bitcoin-etfs-by-tuesday-or-wednesday-sources-say/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-01T04:39:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) could make a decision regarding the approval of spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) on Tuesday or Wednesday, according to a report. Anticipation for the first-ever U.S. spot bitcoin ETFs intensified last week as prominent asset managers updated their filings with the SEC.
 
Green Light Imminent? SEC Could Make a Decision by Tuesday/Wednesday
 
Market participants are buzzing with anticipation as major asset management firms scramble to secure regulatory approval for the first-ever spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) in the U.S.
 
Applicants, including Blackrock, Vaneck, Valkyrie, Bitwise, Invesco, Fidelity, Wisdomtree, and the Ark Invest/21shares joint venture all submitted revised filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange C…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generative AI Reshapes Enterprise Data Management in 2023 – A Year of Transformations]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19143192/Generative-AI-Reshapes-Enterprise-Data-Management-in-2023-A-Year-of-Transformations</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19143192/Generative-AI-Reshapes-Enterprise-Data-Management-in-2023-A-Year-of-Transformations"/>
        <updated>2024-01-01T04:10:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the ever-evolving landscape of enterprise data management (EDT), the year 2023 witnessed a paradigm shift, driven by the infusion of generative AI technologies. These advancements have not only reshaped how businesses approach data but have also set the stage for a data-centric future. As we...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harvard Scholars Choose the Word of 2023 – A Multidisciplinary Analysis]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19143176/Harvard-Scholars-Choose-the-Word-of-2023-A-Multidisciplinary-Analysis</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19143176/Harvard-Scholars-Choose-the-Word-of-2023-A-Multidisciplinary-Analysis"/>
        <updated>2024-01-01T03:39:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the ever-evolving post-pandemic landscape, where words hold the power to encapsulate the essence of an entire year, Harvard scholars weigh in on the pivotal term that best defines 2023. Amidst varied choices from renowned dictionaries, Harvard faculty members across disciplines share their...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Price Could Start 2024 With A Strong Increase If It Holds This Support]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19143170/Ethereum-Price-Could-Start-2024-With-A-Strong-Increase-If-It-Holds-This-Support</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19143170/Ethereum-Price-Could-Start-2024-With-A-Strong-Increase-If-It-Holds-This-Support"/>
        <updated>2024-01-01T03:19:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum price is correcting gains below the $2,350 zone. ETH could attempt a fresh increase unless there is a close below the $2,200 support. Ethereum is correcting gains and trading below the $2,350 level. The price is trading below $2,320 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. There is a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF launch may be a ‘let down’ but could attract trillions over time]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19143169/Bitcoin-ETF-launch-may-be-a-let-down-but-could-attract-trillions-over-time</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19143169/Bitcoin-ETF-launch-may-be-a-let-down-but-could-attract-trillions-over-time"/>
        <updated>2024-01-01T03:05:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Investors may be disappointed by the initial performance of spot Bitcoin ETFs, but don’t underestimate its impact over the long term, says VanEck adviser Gabor Gurbacs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chief Justice Roberts Examines the Impact of AI in Federal Courts]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19143166/Chief-Justice-Roberts-Examines-the-Impact-of-AI-in-Federal-Courts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19143166/Chief-Justice-Roberts-Examines-the-Impact-of-AI-in-Federal-Courts"/>
        <updated>2024-01-01T03:03:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a year-end report that steered clear of Supreme Court ethics and legal controversies surrounding Donald Trump, Chief Justice John Roberts took a deep dive into the intricate world of artificial intelligence (AI) within the federal courts. Labeling AI as the “latest technological frontier,”...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SBF trial decision criticized by Coinbase’s top lawyer and RFK Jr]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19143161/SBF-trial-decision-criticized-by-Coinbases-top-lawyer-and-RFK-Jr</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19143161/SBF-trial-decision-criticized-by-Coinbases-top-lawyer-and-RFK-Jr"/>
        <updated>2024-01-01T02:56:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a significant development in the high-profile case against Sam Bankman-Fried, former CEO of FTX and Alameda Research, U.S. prosecutors have announced their decision not to pursue additional charges against him. The dropped charges include foreign bribery, bank fraud, and illegal political...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Starts 2024 In A Range, Can The Bulls Take Over?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19143160/Bitcoin-Price-Starts-2024-In-A-Range-Can-The-Bulls-Take-Over</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19143160/Bitcoin-Price-Starts-2024-In-A-Range-Can-The-Bulls-Take-Over"/>
        <updated>2024-01-01T02:48:07.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase ‘Extensively Prepared’ for Spot Bitcoin ETF Approval]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7486888830</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/coinbase-extensively-prepared-for-spot-bitcoin-etf-approval/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-01T02:37:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto exchange Coinbase says that it has “extensively prepared” for spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) approvals by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). Most spot bitcoin ETF applicants have named the Nasdaq-listed crypto platform as the custodian for their bitcoin.
 
Coinbase Gets Ready for Spot Bitcoin ETF Launches
 
As the deadline approaches for the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to decide whether to approve a spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF), Coinbase (Nasdaq: COIN) says it has extensively prepared its systems to custody BTC for spot bitcoin ETF issuers.
 
Most spot bitcoin ETF applicants have named the Nasdaq-listed crypto platform as the custodian of their bitcoin, including Blackrock, the world’s largest asset manager, Ark Invest, Bitwise, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is buying Bitcoin right now a good strategy?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19143148/Is-buying-Bitcoin-right-now-a-good-strategy</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19143148/Is-buying-Bitcoin-right-now-a-good-strategy"/>
        <updated>2024-01-01T02:30:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Miners are selling a large volume of their coins, putting BTC at risk of another correction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pro XRP lawyer John Deaton spotlights Warren’s lack of action in FTX case]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19143144/Pro-XRP-lawyer-John-Deaton-spotlights-Warrens-lack-of-action-in-FTX-case</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19143144/Pro-XRP-lawyer-John-Deaton-spotlights-Warrens-lack-of-action-in-FTX-case"/>
        <updated>2024-01-01T02:21:36.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Orbit Bridge, hacked for $82 million in major crypto breach]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19143131/Orbit-Bridge-hacked-for-82-million-in-major-crypto-breach</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19143131/Orbit-Bridge-hacked-for-82-million-in-major-crypto-breach"/>
        <updated>2024-01-01T01:48:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a significant security breach, hackers have successfully targeted Orbit Bridge, a key component of the Orbit Chain protocol, resulting in a substantial financial loss. The incident unfolding just hours before the New Year has prompted widespread concern across the cryptocurrency community....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Analysts Upbeat for 2024 After a Year of Building in 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19143124/Crypto-Analysts-Upbeat-for-2024-After-a-Year-of-Building-in-2023</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19143124/Crypto-Analysts-Upbeat-for-2024-After-a-Year-of-Building-in-2023"/>
        <updated>2024-01-01T01:21:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As we enter 2024, numerous crypto analysts are anticipating and speculating on the outlook for the new year, predominantly expressing a bullish sentiment for the crypto market. Several analysts pointed towards a potential for a bull market in 2024. Crypto Analysts Forecast Potential Outlook...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu token’s $44.64 million transfer sparks market buzz]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19143118/Shiba-Inu-tokens-4464-million-transfer-sparks-market-buzz</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19143118/Shiba-Inu-tokens-4464-million-transfer-sparks-market-buzz"/>
        <updated>2024-01-01T01:20:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whale Alert, a prominent blockchain tracker and analytics system, has reported a significant transfer of Shiba Inu (SHIB) tokens, a remarkable development in the cryptocurrency sector. An astonishing 4.24 trillion SHIB tokens, equivalent to approximately $44.64 million, were moved from one...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trader Predicts Rallies for Ethereum Following Strong December, Updates Outlook on Two ETH Challengers]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19143112/Trader-Predicts-Rallies-for-Ethereum-Following-Strong-December-Updates-Outlook-on-Two-ETH-Challengers</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19143112/Trader-Predicts-Rallies-for-Ethereum-Following-Strong-December-Updates-Outlook-on-Two-ETH-Challengers"/>
        <updated>2024-01-01T01:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can Solana (SOL) Continue Its Path Up in 2024?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19143114/Can-Solana-SOL-Continue-Its-Path-Up-in-2024</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19143114/Can-Solana-SOL-Continue-Its-Path-Up-in-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-01-01T01:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP triumphs with 5 million holders in a groundbreaking milestone]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19143110/XRP-triumphs-with-5-million-holders-in-a-groundbreaking-milestone</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19143110/XRP-triumphs-with-5-million-holders-in-a-groundbreaking-milestone"/>
        <updated>2024-01-01T00:53:49.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche Foundation to Hop Onto the Meme Coin Train, Announces Investment in Selected Projects]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748670a9a6</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/avalanche-foundation-to-hop-onto-the-meme-coin-train-announces-investment-in-selected-projects/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-01T00:35:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Avalanche Foundation, an institution that funds avalanche initiatives, has recently announced that it will start investing in meme coins. These purchases will be made using funds from the $100 million Culture Catalyst fund launched in 2022, and the tokens will be selected based on their number of holders, liquidity thresholds, and project maturity, among other elements.
Avalanche to Invest in Meme Coins Using $100 Million Culture Catalyst Fund
The Avalanche Foundation has announced that it is taking a position in meme coins. In a recent X post, the foundation revealed that it will invest in selected meme coins, broadening its portfolio as part of a comprehensive move to embrace “a more complete spectrum of possibilities.”
This investment will be made using Culture Catalyst, a fund laun…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase’s top lawyer, RFK jr., and more slam decision to drop second SBF trial]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19143091/Coinbases-top-lawyer-RFK-jr-and-more-slam-decision-to-drop-second-SBF-trial</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19143091/Coinbases-top-lawyer-RFK-jr-and-more-slam-decision-to-drop-second-SBF-trial"/>
        <updated>2024-01-01T00:05:54.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Orbit Cross-Chain Bridge Hit For $82 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19143090/Orbit-Cross-Chain-Bridge-Hit-For-82-Million</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19143090/Orbit-Cross-Chain-Bridge-Hit-For-82-Million"/>
        <updated>2024-01-01T00:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Orbit Bridge kicks off the new year as the first crypto protocol to suffer from a hack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s Why Bitcoin (BTC) Price Could Drop to $32,000 in January 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19143087/Heres-Why-Bitcoin-BTC-Price-Could-Drop-to-32000-in-January-2024</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19143087/Heres-Why-Bitcoin-BTC-Price-Could-Drop-to-32000-in-January-2024"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T23:41:32.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto entrepreneurs: Top winners and losers of 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19143067/Crypto-entrepreneurs-Top-winners-and-losers-of-2023</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19143067/Crypto-entrepreneurs-Top-winners-and-losers-of-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s a look at some of the biggest winners and losers for crypto in 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maelstrom CIO Arthur Hayes Alerts Big Banks Will Eventually Cannibalize Tether’s Business Model]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748678b963</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/maelstrom-cio-arthur-hayes-alerts-big-banks-will-eventually-cannibalize-tethers-business-model/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T22:39:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arthur Hayes, CIO of Maelstrom and former CEO of Bitmex, discussed the eventual demise of Tether and other stablecoin companies. Hayes explained that Tether’s business model, which consists of taking dollars and investing in treasuries, will eventually be cannibalized by big banks like JPMorgan when they get allowed to issue fiat-backed stablecoins.
Arthur Hayes Warns About Banks Replacing Tether and Other Stablecoin Companies
Arthur Hayes, the former CEO of Bitmex and CIO of Malestrom, a crypto-focused early-stage investment fund, has stated that he expects big banks to take over the stablecoin business, now dominated by Tether, the company behind USDT.
At Laura Shin’s Unchained podcast, Hayes explained that while Tether has configured itself to be a great product in the crypto market, it…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Orbit Chain’s bridge reportedly hacked for $81.5 million]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19143045/Orbit-Chains-bridge-reportedly-hacked-for-815-million</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19143045/Orbit-Chains-bridge-reportedly-hacked-for-815-million"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T22:37:18.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unprecedented Downturn: Over 5,700 Crypto ATMs Decommissioned in 2023, Marking First Annual Decline]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7486611c17</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/unprecedented-downturn-over-5700-crypto-atms-decommissioned-in-2023-marking-first-annual-decline/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T20:40:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto automated teller machines (ATMs) have experienced a decline this year, marking the first downturn since October 2013, with the total count dipping from 39,350 to the present 33,620. Approximately 5,730 cryptocurrency ATMs have been decommissioned, constituting a 14.56% decrease from the peak in December 2022.
 
Over 5,700 Crypto ATMs Vanish in Historic 2023 Downturn
 

 
This year marks an unprecedented shift in the landscape of crypto-centric ATMs, witnessing their first annual reduction since their inception. Data from coinatmradar.com shows that in December 2022, there existed 39,350 machines distributing crypto assets such as bitcoin (BTC) and ethereum (ETH). From that peak, the landscape has changed, with more than 14% of the original 39,000 units, totaling 5,730 machines, bein…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum’s Path Forward: Vitalik Buterin Unveils Roadmap Enhancements]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74866ac074</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ethereums-path-forward-vitalik-buterin-unveils-roadmap-enhancements/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T18:39:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent update, Ethereum co-founder Vitalik Buterin released an updated 2023 roadmap for the blockchain platform, detailing notable improvements and steadfast progress. Despite similarities to the previous year’s roadmap, the updated version underscores Ethereum’s evolving technical journey with goals aimed at improving scaling, security, and decentralization.
 
Ethereum Co-Founder Drops Updated Roadmap on Social Media
 

 
Following his recent blog post, Vitalik Buterin, the prominent co-founder of Ethereum, released a sequence of X posts concerning the network’s strategic direction. One of the critical updates highlighted by Buterin is the advancement towards single slot finality (SSF) in the Ethereum proof-of-stake (PoS) design.
 

 
Currently, the consensus protocol can take up to …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biggest Crypto and NFT Games of 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210698</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210698/biggest-crypto-nft-games-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T18:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Numerous crypto and NFT games made waves this year with early access launches and full releases. These are the ones to play.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Behind Bryan Johnson's $4 Million Bid for Immortality]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211346</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211346/behind-bryan-johnsons-4-million-bid-for-immortality"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T18:05:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The serial entrepreneur ruminates on what his “don’t die” mantra means for mere mortals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Crystal Ball 2024: Bitcoin Meets TradFi—For Real]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211244</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211244/crypto-crystal-ball-2024-bitcoin-meets-tradfi-real"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T17:15:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Analysts weigh in on when, if ever, Bitcoin and the crypto market will begin to sway the global economy. Hint: pretty soon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[December 2023 Sees Record Bitcoin Mining Revenue: $1.51 Billion Amassed With Soaring Onchain Fees]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74865dacbd</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/december-2023-sees-record-bitcoin-mining-revenue-1-51-billion-amassed-with-soaring-onchain-fees/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T16:38:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In December, bitcoin miners garnered the highest monthly revenue of the year, amassing $1.51 billion. Additionally, this month marked a record in fee collection, with miners securing $324.83 million in onchain transaction fees.
 
Bitcoin Miners Smash Records — Highest Monthly Haul of $1.51 Billion in December 2023
 

 
December 2023 has set a new benchmark for monthly revenue garnered by bitcoin (BTC) miners through block discovery and transaction verification. By Dec. 31, 2023, a total of $1.51 billion was amassed, including $324.83 million in onchain fees. This surpasses the former monthly revenue record set in May, where miners collected a total of $919.22 million, with $125.92 million from onchain fees.
 

 

 

 
In July, miners collected a total of $865 million, with $19.21 million from fees. December, however, marked a significant increase, standing 1.64 times greater than May’s record, representing a growth of 64.27% or an additional $590.78 million. At the moment, according to bitinfocharts.com, December’s onchain transaction rates are soaring, with the average fee at 231 satoshis per virtual byte (sats/vB) or $20.86 per transaction.
 

 

 

 
On Dec. 31, 2023, the median-sized fee is noted at $9.60 per transaction or 106.3 sats/vB. Moreover, on Dec. 17, 2023, fees spiked to as much as $40 per transfer, averaging around $37.43 per transaction — the year’s peak in on-chain fees, surpassing the previous high of $31 on May 8, 2023.
 

 
Also, on Dec. 17, the hash price of Bitcoin — the value of a single petahash per second (PH/s) produced daily — hit a 2023 zenith of $133.62 per PH/s, exceeding the earlier record of $125.64 per PH/s on May 8. Despite the high onchain fees, miners face a backlog of over 496,000 unconfirmed transactions and congestion of 430 blocks.
 

 
What do you think about the record-breaking haul bitcoin miners gathered in December 2023? Share your thoughts and opinions about this subject in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Mining Pools Dominated in 2023, Discovering Over 84% of Bitcoin’s Blocks]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748641db5b</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/5-mining-pools-dominated-in-2023-discovering-over-84-of-bitcoins-blocks/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T14:37:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past year, statistics reveal that 54,002 bitcoin blocks have been mined from Dec. 30, 2022, to Dec. 30, 2023. Leading the industry this year, Foundry USA topped the charts by mining 16,492 blocks in the past 12 months. Additionally, miners navigated through a total of 27 difficulty adjustments, predominantly increases, yet successfully propelled the hashrate to an unprecedented lifetime peak.
 
2023: A Record-Breaking Year in Bitcoin Mining Amidst Technological Triumphs and Upcoming Halving Challenges
 

 
In 2023, bitcoin miners had a prosperous year, uncovering over 54,000 bitcoin (BTC) blocks, each comprising 6.25 freshly minted bitcoins along with the fees tied to every discovered block. Archived data collected from btc.com shows that the leading mining pools for the year incl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ETF Fever Continues, Gensler Warns Against Crypto’s ‘Wild West’ of Permissionless Exchange, Latam Update — Week in Review]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7486352b55</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/etf-fever-continues-gensler-warns-against-cryptos-wild-west-of-permissionless-exchange-latam-update-week-in-review/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T12:38:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Chair Gary Gensler has repeated earlier warnings about crypto “non-compliance” being a global “Wild West,” as speculative fever for BTC exchange-traded funds continues to swelter, with monolithic asset manager Blackrock revealing a plan to seed its own ETF with $10 million on Jan. 3. This and more just below, in the year’s final Bitcoin.com News Week in Review.
 

 

 
SEC Chair Gary Gensler Issues Crypto Warnings as Anticipation of Spot Bitcoin ETF Approval Soars
 

 
U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Chairman Gary Gensler has issued warnings regarding cryptocurrency investments. “There is a lot of noncompliance in the crypto space,” he stressed, emphasizing that it “undermines confidence when so many people have been hurt and all …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week on Crypto Twitter: Ethereum vs. Solana Rivalry Heats Up]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211298</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211298/this-week-on-crypto-twitter-ethereum-vs-solana-rivalry-heats-up"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T12:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After weeks of non stop gains, Solana advocates found themselves playing defense this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Year Of Ethereum: ETH Long-Term Holder Percentage Surpasses BTC]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748632b9c5</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-long-term-holders-percentage-surpasses-btc/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T11:38:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The percentage of long-term ETH holders has skyrocketed this year to surpass Bitcoin for the second time ever. According to data from on-chain analytics platform IntoTheBlock, Ethereum has done pretty well in its percentage of long-term holders this year, with over 70% of investors currently holding on to their assets for more than a year, a new milestone for the blockchain.
 
ETH Long-Term Holders Now Top BTC
 
Ethereum’s price activity has largely underperformed this year when compared to Bitcoin. But this isn’t surprising, as Bitcoin has led the entire industry in bullish metrics and investor confidence this year. However, data from IntoTheBlock suggest more Ethereum investors are holding onto ETH for the long haul, hopefully with the belief that it will continue to rise substantially i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: EU Represents Just 6% of Bitcoin Mining Hashrate, US Significantly Leads China]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74863fffa8</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/report-eu-represents-just-6-of-bitcoin-mining-hashrate-us-significantly-leads-china/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T10:39:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The countries in the European Union collectively account for 6% of the Bitcoin network’s hashrate while the U.S. has emerged as the world’s number one bitcoin miner, a new report has said. The economic bloc’s bitcoin mining prospects are however being hamstrung by geopolitical tensions and the region’s energy dependence.
 
The EU’s Bitcoin Mining Prospects
 
According to the latest Bankless Times report on bitcoin mining, the 28 countries comprising the European Union (EU) collectively account for 6% of the Bitcoin network’s hashrate. On the other hand, Ireland, whose 2023 gross domestic product (GDP) of $115 billion is nearly 160 times less than the European Union’s GDP, accounts for 2% of the Bitcoin network’s hashrate.
 
Despite having the potential to increase its share of the Bitcoin …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analyst Sets $8 Trillion Target For Crypto Market Cap In 2025]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748625b131</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/analyst-set-8-trillion-target-for-crypto-market-cap/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T09:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the year drawing to an end, crypto investors and enthusiasts definitely have their eyes set on the future and what the digital asset market holds for them in the coming years. Despite a slow start to the year, the final months of 2023 have looked favorable for the cryptocurrency landscape, with the bull cycle seeming to be in full gear. 
 
There has been broad commentary on the potential of the ongoing bull run and how it could impact the crypto market. A crypto researcher with the pseudonym Ether NasyonaL is one of the latest entities to discuss the current cycle and its future trajectory.
 
Total Market Cap To Hit $8 Trillion By 2025: Analyst
 
In a recent post on the X platform, crypto analyst Ether NasyonaL put forward an exciting projection for the digital asset market over the c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Opeyemi Sule</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Veteran Trader Peter Brandt Issues Scam Proprietary Trading Platform Warning]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74862291b0</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/veteran-trader-peter-brandt-issues-scam-proprietary-trading-platform-warning/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T08:39:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to Peter Brandt, legitimate proprietary trading firms neither charge fees on traders nor impose “restrictions on trading style or markets.” The veteran trader branded as scams any prop firm that fails to adhere to the operating conditions that he outlined. 
 
Legitimate Prop Firms
 
Veteran trader Peter Brandt has warned fellow traders to be on the lookout for scammers who project themselves as bona fide proprietary trading platforms. In a warning shared via X, Brandt listed some attributes of what he sees as “legitimate ‘we-fund-you’ prop firms.”
 
 
Here is how legitimate "we-fund-you" prop firms operate
-No fees charged to traders – EVER
-Actual real $ funding
-Set drawdown from initial funding level
-No restrictions on trading style or markets
Anything different than this is …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin Reveals Ethereum’s Roadmap For 2024]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7486284970</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/vitalik-buterin-reveals-ethereums-roadmap-for-2024/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T07:26:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum founder Vitalik Buterin has shared the crypto project’s roadmap for 2024. In a series of posts on X on December 30, Buterin spoke extensively on Ethereum’s gameplan for the new year, which he claims is quite similar to the plan for 2023, albeit with a few changes.
 
 
Ethereum Roadmap 2024
 
According to information revealed by Buterin, the main focus of Ethereum for 2024 centers around six key goals, namely the Merge, the Surge, the Scourge, the Verge, the Purge, and the Splurge.
 
The Ethereum Merge aims to create an ideal, simple, robust, and decentralized proof-of-stake (PoS) network. 
 
The Merge occurred in September 2022 with the integration of the Ethereum mainnet with the Beacon Chain, thus marking the end of the proof-of-work consensus algorithm. Speaking on post-Merge i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Semilore Faleti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Billionaire Mark Cuban: SEC Doesn’t Protect Anyone, Current Crypto Regulation Inadequate]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74862bf82a</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/billionaire-mark-cuban-sec-doesnt-protect-anyone-current-crypto-regulation-inadequate/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T06:39:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mark Cuban, a Shark Tank star and the billionaire owner of the NBA team Dallas Mavericks, says the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) doesn’t protect anyone, calling the regulator “the Quickbooks of financial regulation.” He stressed that the Howey Test isn’t enough to cover every crypto situation.
 
Mark Cuban Slams SEC: They Don’t Protect Anyone
 
Shark Tank star and the owner of the NBA team Dallas Mavericks, Mark Cuban, slammed the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) in a post on social media platform X Thursday.
 
Regarding whether the current securities law is sufficient to regulate crypto, Cuban said: “All you need to know is that Howey was not enough to cover every situation, so Reves came along.” Reves v. Ernst & Young is a Supreme Court case related to the de…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitwise Plans to Seed Spot Bitcoin ETF With $200 Million, SEC Filing Shows]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7486184182</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitwise-plans-to-seed-spot-bitcoin-etf-with-200-million-sec-filing-shows/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T03:38:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitwise has revealed in an amended filing with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) a plan to seed its spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) with $200 million. This significantly exceeds Blackrock’s $10 million seed commitment for its spot Bitcoin ETF that’s planned for Jan. 3.
 
Bitwise’s $200 Million Plan to Seed Spot Bitcoin ETF
 
Bitwise is one of the spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) applicants that submitted an amended filing (S-1) to the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) on Friday. Once launched, Bitwise’s spot bitcoin ETF will trade under the ticker symbol BITB.
 
According to the firm’s filing with the SEC, an unnamed entity “has indicated an interest in purchasing an aggregate of up to $200 million of shares in this offering from authorized participants or in the marketplace through broker-dealers.” Commenting on the asset manager’s filing, Bloomberg ETF analyst Eric Balchunas pointed out on social media platform X:
 

Bitwise S-1 has been filed and it looks like someone (I wonder who) is going to seed BITB with $200m, which blows away Blackrock’s $10m (that we know of). That’s gonna be huge help in early days of race.
 
However, Bitwise cautioned: “Because indications of interest are not binding agreements or commitments to purchase, this potential purchaser could determine to purchase more, fewer or no shares.”
 
Last week, Blackrock revealed in an amended filing with the SEC a plan to seed its spot bitcoin ETF with $10 million on Jan. 3.
 
Earlier this month, Bitwise unveiled 10 crypto predictions for 2024, including its expectation for bitcoin to trade above $80,000. The asset manager also believes that “spot bitcoin ETFs will be approved, and collectively they will be the most successful ETF launch of all time.” Moreover, Bitwise expects spot bitcoin ETFs to “capture 1% of the $7.2 trillion U.S. ETF market, or $72 billion in AUM.”
 
What do you think about Bitwise planning to seed its spot bitcoin ETF with $200 million? Let us know in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blackrock Names JPMorgan as Authorized Participant for Spot Bitcoin ETF Despite Jamie Dimon Wanting to Ban Crypto]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7486003557</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/blackrock-names-jpmorgan-as-authorized-participant-for-spot-bitcoin-etf-despite-jamie-dimon-wanting-to-ban-crypto/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T01:36:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blackrock, the world’s largest asset manager, has named JPMorgan as a lead authorized participant for its spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF). This followed JPMorgan CEO Jamie Dimon stating in a congressional hearing that bitcoin and cryptocurrency are used primarily for criminal purposes and that he would close down crypto if he were the government.
 
JPMorgan Named Authorized Participant by Blackrock for Spot Bitcoin ETF
 
On the final day of the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC)’s deadline, Blackrock, the world’s largest asset manager, submitted an updated filing for its spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF). The SEC gave spot bitcoin ETF applicants until Friday to submit their amended filings in order to be included in the first batch of decisions in early January. Mo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOJ’s Decision on SBF Case Outrages Crypto Industry — Coinbase Calls It ‘Miscarriage of Justice’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74860865d2</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/dojs-decision-on-sbf-case-outrages-crypto-industry-coinbase-calls-it-miscarriage-of-justice/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T23:36:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The decision by the U.S. Department of Justice (DOJ) not to pursue a second trial against disgraced FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF) has outraged the crypto industry. Crypto exchange Coinbase calls the decision a “miscarriage of justice.” One lawyer opined, “Ask yourself why is this case being dropped in an election year,” noting that SBF gave the Biden administration $10 million and had personal meetings with U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Chairman Gary Gensler and SEC staff.
 
DOJ’s Decision on SBF Trial Outrages Crypto Industry
 
The U.S. Department of Justice (DOJ) has decided not to pursue a second trial against former FTX CEO Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF). The second trial, which had been slated to start in March, addresses an additional set of criminal counts against Ban…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bit Mining Sells Btc.com’s Mining Operations for $5 Million]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7487f16cd8</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bit-mining-sells-btc-coms-mining-operations-for-5-million/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T21:32:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Friday, Bit Mining Limited declared it had sold the mining pool operations of Btc.com to a Hong Kong limited liability company for $5 million. This transaction is anticipated to bolster the total equity of Bit Mining’s shareholders, contingent upon certain concluding conditions.
 
BTCM Offloads Btc.com Mining Pool for $5 Million
 
Bit Mining (NYSE: BTCM) has revealed that it divested its mining pool division related to Btc.com for a sum of $5 million. The sale was made to Esport-Win Limited, a firm based in Hong Kong. The company, listed on the NYSE and engaged in mining and blockchain infrastructure, reported that while the pool had generated $593.2 million in yearly revenue, it incurred a net operating loss of $2.6 million over the full year.
 
BTCM expressed anticipation that the div…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Striking Similarities Between Dogecoin And PEPE Suggests An Impending Breakout]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7487ffb6c8</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/similarities-dogecoin-and-pepe/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T20:09:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Max Schwartzman, the CEO of crypto analysis platform Because Bitcoin, has drawn similarities between meme coins Dogecoin (DOGE) and PEPE. If history is to repeat itself, then a price breakout could be on the horizon for PEPE. 
 
PEPE Sharing A Similar Pattern As DOGE In 2020
 
In a post on his X (formerly Twitter) platform, Schwartzman drew the crypto community’s attention to “some striking similarities” between PEPE in 2023 and DOGE in 2020. From the accompanying chart that he shared, one could see that PEPE’s price movement in 2023 is identical to DOGE’s in 2020.
 
 
 
If PEPE is to continue moving in a similar pattern, then the meme coin’s price could break out in 2024. PEPE’s price has been consolidating since November, just like DOGE’s price did between May 2020 and the new year befor…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biggest Gaming Fails and Blunders of 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210770</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210770/biggest-gaming-fails-blunders-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T20:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From Logan Paul's NFT game lawsuit to leaked seed phrases and digital lumps of coal, here are 2023's biggest gaming-related fails.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Crystal Ball 2024: Will a Bitcoin ETF Be a Game-Changer?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211243</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211243/crypto-crystal-ball-2024-will-bitcoin-etf-game-changer"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T18:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A spot Bitcoin ETF is most likely around the corner in the United States. Will it deliver at the scale everyone in crypto is banking on?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Bitcoin Dips, Ordinals Mania Continues, Solana Slows]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211190</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211190/this-week-in-coins-bitcoin-dips-ordinals-mania-continues-solana-slows"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T18:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meme coin mania also slowed down this week. But investors are still interested in the potential of Bitcoin's blockchain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biggest NFT Stories of 2023: From Bitcoin Ordinals to Blur's Surge]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211265</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211265/biggest-nft-stories-2023-bitcoin-ordinals-blur-surge"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T17:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was a bumpy, yet transformative year for NFTs and on-chain media across Ethereum, Bitcoin, and beyond. Here’s a look back.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Is Being Flooded With Thousands of New Tokens as Traders Hunt for Next 1,000x]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211234</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211234/solana-being-flooded-thousands-new-tokens-traders-hunt-next-1000x"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T16:07:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After BONK's recent boom and the ecosystem's rebound, Solana is seeing more new tokens created than ever before. Who's behind them?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia Makes a Slower GPU for China Under New U.S. Trade Restrictions]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211222</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211222/nvidia-rtx-4090d-gpu-chinese-market"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T05:08:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new GPU specifically designed for the Chinese market won’t be a top performer, but will still be good enough for gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ESL Faceit Group Exploring Blockchain 'Opportunistically,' Says Exec]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/yvrs4lBx/esl-faceit-group-exploring-blockchain-opportunistically-says-exec</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/yvrs4lBx/esl-faceit-group-exploring-blockchain-opportunistically-says-exec"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T02:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Braithwaite—ESL Faceit Group's VP of Game Ecosystems, Mobile, and Snapdragon Pro Series—shares the esports firm's approach to blockchain technology with GG's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VanEck Joins Bitcoin ETF Ad War With New Teaser Trailer]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211215</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211215/vaneck-joins-bitcoin-etf-ad-war-with-new-teaser-trailer"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T23:06:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The investment firm teased the as-of-yet non-existent financial product days before the latest of several supposed deadlines the SEC faces to approve one.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock Bitcoin ETF Names JP Morgan, Jane Street as Authorized Participants]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211208</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211208/blackrock-bitcoin-etf-jp-morgan-jane-street"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T21:37:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The amendment is one of the last steps in the application process, experts say.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Free Money': These Are the Hottest Airdrops Around Right Now]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209179</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209179/free-money-hottest-airdrops-around-right-now"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T20:50:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATED: More and more airdrops are coming, including from Jupiter, Portal, Blast, and Frame, plus Solana Saga owners can claim more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Got 'Worthless' NFTs? This Startup Buys JPEGs for a Penny to Harvest Tax Losses]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211186</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211186/got-worthless-nfts-startup-buys-jpegs-penny-harvest-tax-losses"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T19:16:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unsellable says it has helped NFT collectors realize $4.2 million worth of tax losses to date by buying up their illiquid assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Token ORDI Surges to New High, Nearing Top 50 Coins]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211185</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211185/bitcoin-token-ordi-surges-new-high-nearing-top-50-coins"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T18:44:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price of ORDI, the biggest token minted on the Bitcoin network, is surging again today—and is one of this week's best-performers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF Race Could Get Tighter After This Deadline]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211188</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211188/bitcoin-etf-race-amendment-deadline"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T18:14:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fund managers vying to release a spot Bitcoin ETF have until today to file a key amendment to their applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gamers Bash Xbox for Controversial Art Apparently Made by AI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211178</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211178/gamers-bash-xbox-controversial-art-apparently-made-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T16:54:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aiming to promote the human creativity behind indie games, Xbox instead enrages gamers by apparently using AI-generated art.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These Are the High-Profile Spot Bitcoin ETF Applications Currently in Play]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=62912</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/62912/high-profile-bitcoin-etf-applications"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T15:30:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. SEC has dragged its heels on approval of a Bitcoin spot ETF—but analysts are optimistic that there's light at the end of the tunnel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin: Web3 Vision Has 'Faded' Due to Rising Transaction Fees]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211148</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211148/vitalik-buterin-web3-vision-has-faded-due-to-rising-transaction-fees"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T13:12:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Degen gamblers" have become "the only audience that remains willing to pay" when transaction fees soar, Buterin said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche Foundation to Invest in Meme Coin Collection]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211145</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211145/avalanche-foundation-to-invest-in-meme-coin-collection"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T10:50:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price of Avalanche-based meme coins including Husky Avax and Coq Inu rose by double-digits on the news.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Ernie Bot from Baidu Reaches 100 Million Users in China]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211138</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211138/baidu-ernie-bot-ai-chatbot-china"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T02:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Baidu's conversational AI demonstrates swift traction at home, even as it looks to close the gap globally.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Most Powerful Generative AI Text Tools of 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211128</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211128/decrypt-emerge-best-large-language-models-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T01:02:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whatever your style, there will always be a Large Language Model (LLM) out there for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Judge Sides With SEC Over Do Kwon, Says UST, LUNA Are Securities]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211129</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211129/judge-sides-with-sec-over-do-kwon-says-ust-luna-are-securities"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T23:49:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The summary judgment removes one of the biggest questions looming over Kwon’s trial, which will now focus solely on allegations of fraud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GG's 2023 Year in Review: Stories That Rocked the Gaming World]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211122</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211122/ggs-2023-year-review-stories-rocked-gaming-world"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T22:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From layoffs to GTA 6 and Microsoft acquiring Activision, these are the stories that defined 2023 in gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[India Will Block Binance, Kraken, and Other Exchanges in Crypto Crackdown]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211114</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211114/india-block-binance-kraken-other-exchanges-crypto-crackdown"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T20:32:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[India's Financial Intelligence Unit said the crypto exchanges were operating illegally in the country. Now their websites will be blocked.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$14 Billion in Bitcoin Options Expire Tomorrow—Here’s Why It Matters]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211113</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211113/14-billion-bitcoin-options-expire-tomorrow-why-it-matters"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T19:40:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's $14 billion worth of Bitcoin options expiring on Friday. The split between puts and call shows investors are feeling bullish.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Traders May Be Lining Up to 'Sell the News' on ETF Approval]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211108</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211108/bitcoin-traders-sell-news-etf-approval"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T18:37:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price of Bitcoin could plunge if a spot exchange-traded fund (ETF) is approved in the U.S. in January, CryptoQuant claims.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blast Deposits Top $1.1 Billion Ahead of Ethereum L2 Launch and Airdrop]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211107</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211107/blast-deposits-top-1-1-billion-ahead-ethereum-l2-launch-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T18:11:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Paradigm-backed Ethereum scaler’s rollout has been controversial, but that isn’t stopping users from buying in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Dips Below $100 as Meme Coin Trading Reverses Course]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211101</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211101/solana-dips-below-100-meme-coin-trading-bonk"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T16:51:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SOL may have burned a little too hot a little too fast, now falling 7% in 24 hours.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cathie Wood's ARK Sells Remaining GBTC Shares, Buys $100M in Bitcoin Futures ETF]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211088</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211088/cathie-woods-ark-sells-remaining-gbtc-shares-buys-100m-in-bitcoin-futures-etf"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T13:52:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The asset manager offloaded 2.25 million GBTC shares and purchased 4.32 million shares of the ProShares Bitcoin Strategy ETF.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PancakeSwap's CAKE Jumps 7% on Proposal to Slash Token Supply by 300 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211085</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211085/pancakeswaps-cake-jumps-5-on-proposal-to-slash-token-supply-by-300-million"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T10:45:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PancakeSwap's CAKE token jumped by 4% following the proposal, which would see its maximum supply reduced from 750 million to 450 million.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Dumps Millions in Ethereum After Disastrous NFT Redux]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211064</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211064/trump-dumps-millions-in-eth-after-disastrous-nft-redux"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T00:53:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The former president has cashed out $2.4 million worth of ETH in the last three weeks, Arkham reports.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Biggest Space Stories of 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211059</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211059/the-biggest-space-stories-of-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T23:53:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even amid an avalanche of AI news, space exploration still managed to make headlines this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Biggest Crypto Airdrops of 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211031</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211031/biggest-crypto-airdrops-2023-arbitrum-blur-celestia-jito"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T23:03:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The top token handouts of the year netted users over $4.5 billion worth of free crypto. Here are 2023's biggest crypto airdrops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Gaming Predictions: Will 2024 Be the Breakout Year?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210772</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210772/crypto-gaming-predictions-2024-breakout-year"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T22:29:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto industry leaders remain optimistic about the future of blockchain gaming. Here's what they expect in 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brakes on Bonk: Solana Meme Coin Down 56% From All-Time High]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211030</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211030/bonk-solana-based-meme-coin-slows-down"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T21:41:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The meme token is now well below the all-time high it touched two weeks ago.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Game On: The Hottest Upcoming Gaming Token Airdrops]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211029</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211029/game-on-hottest-upcoming-gaming-token-airdrops"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T21:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From Portal to Saga, these are the token airdrops that crypto gamers should be paying close attention to right now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI Trained AI Models on Copyrighted Work, Says NYT Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211006</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211006/openai-trained-ai-models-on-copyrighted-work-says-nyt-lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T19:02:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Current methods for training AI on copyrighted work means “less journalism will be produced, and the cost to society will be enormous,” says the NYT.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wildcard's Plans for 2024 with Founders Paul and Katy Bettner]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/TI3aFBhO/wildcards-plans-for-2024-with-founders-paul-and-katy-bettner</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/TI3aFBhO/wildcards-plans-for-2024-with-founders-paul-and-katy-bettner"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T21:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wildcard developers Paul and Katy Bettner tell Decrypt's Kate Irwin about why they see their game as a "Web3 game," not a crypto game, and share why they've stuck with their initial vision despite the challenging broader market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt and Rug Radio Merge to Create Global Web3 Publishing Company]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/VTEBYFD8/decrypt-and-rug-radio-merge-to-create-global-web3-publishing-company</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/VTEBYFD8/decrypt-and-rug-radio-merge-to-create-global-web3-publishing-company"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T17:04:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt and Rug Radio have announced their intent to merge, creating the world’s biggest decentralized publishing company. Codenamed [REDACTED], the alliance is aimed at revolutionizing tech-media, bringing together the forces of content creation and consumption.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['If You Play Well, You're Gonna be Rewarded': How FPS Web3War is Bringing 'Skill-to-Earn' to Crypto Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Jl5AEFuD/if-you-play-well-youre-gonna-be-rewarded-how-fps-web3war-is-bringing-skill-to-earn-to-crypto-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Jl5AEFuD/if-you-play-well-youre-gonna-be-rewarded-how-fps-web3war-is-bringing-skill-to-earn-to-crypto-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T10:20:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roll1ng Thund3rz co-founder Valentin Cobelea and Zilliqa CEO Matt Dyer joined Decrypt to discuss how the new FPS game Web3War is shaking up the crypto gaming space with a novel "skill to earn" mechanic that rewards players for high-quality gameplay.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating peaceful money & taking over your local government w/ Joseph Schiarizzi]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zb0VG27G/creating-peaceful-money-taking-over-your-local-government-w-joseph-schiarizzi</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zb0VG27G/creating-peaceful-money-taking-over-your-local-government-w-joseph-schiarizzi"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T23:23:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week our host Reza Jafery is joined by Joseph Schiarizzi, founder of OpenDollar and prolific solidity developer. 


We discuss: 
- Onchain beer
- Taking over your local government
- His Emmy and 3 patents?!?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INTERVIEW: Ember Sword CEO Says NFT Games Are More 'Transparent']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/M9OHCVpA/interview-ember-sword-ceo-says-nft-games-are-more-transparent</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/M9OHCVpA/interview-ember-sword-ceo-says-nft-games-are-more-transparent"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T21:58:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ember Sword CEO Mark Laursen shares why some big game studios "irk" him—and why he got into game development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Director Jordan Bayne on the State of Film3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZLoEDkL9/director-jordan-bayne-on-the-state-of-film3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZLoEDkL9/director-jordan-bayne-on-the-state-of-film3"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T00:11:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the 2023 Film3 Summit, Jordan Bayne—director and founder of The Squad—spoke with Decrypt's Sander Lutz about how the Film3 world has progressed over the last year and what decentralized technologies can offer to creators that want to buck the Hollywood system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>