<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-10-15T08:17:00.461Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-10-15T08:17:00.461Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critic Adam Cochran Issues Final Warning on Binance Risky Business]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18969844/Critic-Adam-Cochran-Issues-Final-Warning-on-Binance-Risky-Business</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18969844/Critic-Adam-Cochran-Issues-Final-Warning-on-Binance-Risky-Business"/>
        <updated>2023-10-15T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent tweet, the renowned Binance critic Adam Cochran released what he called his last round of FUD attacks on Binance. Cochran called the piece his last warning against the exchange, believing he has convinced enough people about the risk associated with using Binance. Yet, he shared...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ferrari Starts Accepting Crypto Payments for Luxury Sports Cars]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b7dab547</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ferrari-starts-accepting-crypto-payments-for-luxury-sports-cars/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-15T07:41:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ferrari has reportedly begun accepting payment in cryptocurrency. The Italian luxury sports car manufacturer cited requests from both the market and dealers as the primary motivation for this decision. “This will help us connect to people who are not necessarily our clients but might afford a Ferrari,” said an executive of the company.
 
Ferrari Begins Accepting Cryptocurrencies
 
Italian luxury sports car automaker Ferrari has begun accepting payment in cryptocurrency for its luxury sports cars in the U.S., Reuters reported Saturday, noting that the company also plans to expand the cryptocurrency payment option to Europe.
 
Ferrari’s chief marketing and commercial officer, Enrico Galliera, told the news outlet that the decision to accept crypto payments was in response to requests from th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beware: Volatility Very High in This Altcoin – Up 50 Percent in 5 Minutes]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18969828/Beware-Volatility-Very-High-in-This-Altcoin-Up-50-Percent-in-5-Minutes</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18969828/Beware-Volatility-Very-High-in-This-Altcoin-Up-50-Percent-in-5-Minutes"/>
        <updated>2023-10-15T07:36:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price of this altcoin, known for its negative funding rates, is still facing great volatility today. Continue Reading: Beware: Volatility Very High in This Altcoin – Up 50 Percent in 5 Minutes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 5 Global Banks Are Now Onboarded to Use XRP Through Volante]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18969827/Top-5-Global-Banks-Are-Now-Onboarded-to-Use-XRP-Through-Volante</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18969827/Top-5-Global-Banks-Are-Now-Onboarded-to-Use-XRP-Through-Volante"/>
        <updated>2023-10-15T07:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to WallStreetBulls, a financial blog for crypto and stock market news, some of the top 5 global banks have been onboarded to use XRP through Volante, a leading global provider of cloud payments and financial messaging solutions. WallStreetBulls considers that a significant update for...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano Founder Dismisses ETHGate Theory Rumors: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18969804/Cardano-Founder-Dismisses-ETHGate-Theory-Rumors-Report</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18969804/Cardano-Founder-Dismisses-ETHGate-Theory-Rumors-Report"/>
        <updated>2023-10-15T07:04:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto space, fully open to controversies and scandals, recently caught attention with Cardano founder Charles Hoskinson’s contentious comments on the ETHGate Conspiracy Theory. In a recent AMA session on October 8, Hoskinson, who is also a co-founder of Ethereum, dispelled the ETHGate...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ‘One-Two Punch’ Narrative Can Do Damage to BTC Bears, Says Top Trader – Here’s What He Means]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18969803/Bitcoin-One-Two-Punch-Narrative-Can-Do-Damage-to-BTC-Bears-Says-Top-Trader-Heres-What-He-Means</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18969803/Bitcoin-One-Two-Punch-Narrative-Can-Do-Damage-to-BTC-Bears-Says-Top-Trader-Heres-What-He-Means"/>
        <updated>2023-10-15T07:04:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A trader who caught the crypto breakout earlier this year says two well-known narratives could spell the end for Bitcoin (BTC) bears. In a new strategy session, analyst DonAlt tells his 53,500 YouTube subscribers that the potential approval of a spot-based Bitcoin exchange-traded fund along with...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All Videos from Europe's Largest Bitcoin Conference Now Available]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b7c63fc2</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/watch-all-talks-from-europes-largest-bitcoin-conference-now-available-"/>
        <updated>2023-10-15T07:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Europe's largest Bitcoin conference, Bitcoin Amsterdam, is now accessible to a global audience, as all video from the event has been uploaded to video platforms including YouTube, Rumble, and X. 
Concluding this Friday, the event featured a remarkable lineup of speakers and discussions on Bitcoin and the global freedom movement. 
The second year for the event, organizers estimate nearly 2,500 enthusiasts came from around the world to discuss how Bitcoin is leading to a new age of financial freedom for citizens around the world. 
Key Highlights from Day One include:

Edward Snowden discusses Bitcoin : The renowned whistleblower expressed his excitement about Bitcoin, underscoring the significance of financial privacy and decentralization in an increasingly surveilled world. Reiterating his …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reed Macdonald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nigerian gov supports AI initiatives with $290K in grants]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18969791/Nigerian-gov-supports-AI-initiatives-with-290K-in-grants</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18969791/Nigerian-gov-supports-AI-initiatives-with-290K-in-grants"/>
        <updated>2023-10-15T06:55:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The recently introduced Nigeria Artificial Intelligence Research Scheme is designed to facilitate the widespread utilization of AI to drive economic advancement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin: Will these reasons expedite mass adoption?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18969784/Bitcoin-Will-these-reasons-expedite-mass-adoption</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18969784/Bitcoin-Will-these-reasons-expedite-mass-adoption"/>
        <updated>2023-10-15T06:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of Bitcoin’s major traits is that its deflationary characteristics make it an appealing long-term investment. But there is also another trait that often goes overlooked - Bitcoin’s immutability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-US Politician: BTC is Reaching $15T Cap, FED System is Broken]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18969773/Ex-US-Politician-BTC-is-Reaching-15T-Cap-FED-System-is-Broken</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18969773/Ex-US-Politician-BTC-is-Reaching-15T-Cap-FED-System-is-Broken"/>
        <updated>2023-10-15T06:11:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent interview, Anthony Scaramucci, the managing partner of digital asset investment firm SkyBridge Capital and former White House Director of Communications, shared his vision for the future of money. He expressed his belief, particularly highlighting the transformative power of Bitcoin,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A look at the crypto DeFi market: TVL declining during the past 6 months but good numbers for Ethereum Layer-2s]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18969793/A-look-at-the-crypto-DeFi-market-TVL-declining-during-the-past-6-months-but-good-numbers-for-Ethereum-Layer-2s</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18969793/A-look-at-the-crypto-DeFi-market-TVL-declining-during-the-past-6-months-but-good-numbers-for-Ethereum-Layer-2s"/>
        <updated>2023-10-15T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto hacks: the 10-year history of billion-dollar attacks on cryptocurrencies]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18969794/Crypto-hacks-the-10-year-history-of-billion-dollar-attacks-on-cryptocurrencies</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18969794/Crypto-hacks-the-10-year-history-of-billion-dollar-attacks-on-cryptocurrencies"/>
        <updated>2023-10-15T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[With Bitcoin’s Fourth Halving Under 200 Days Out, What’s at Stake for Miners?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b7cc965e</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/with-bitcoins-fourth-halving-under-200-days-out-whats-at-stake-for-miners/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-15T05:39:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With fewer than 200 days to go, anticipation mounts for the halving, a four-year event that halves the supply rate. Bitcoin’s fourth halving is projected to take place on or around April 24, 2024. This comprehensive guide will help you understand the halving’s effects and what to anticipate.
 
The Countdown to Halving and Understanding the Halving Mechanism
 
By current measurements, 193 days remain until the halving, set for April 2024. In essence, the Bitcoin halving, coded into Bitcoin by its founder, Satoshi Nakamoto, happens every 210,000 blocks, roughly every four years. When the network hits a certain block number, the mining reward — the bitcoin amount miners earn for verifying transactions — is halved.
 
For instance, the initial mining reward was 50 bitcoins per block, and it fel…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Decides to List an Altcoin in Futures, Which Soared 90 Percent Today]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18969736/Binance-Decides-to-List-an-Altcoin-in-Futures-Which-Soared-90-Percent-Today</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18969736/Binance-Decides-to-List-an-Altcoin-in-Futures-Which-Soared-90-Percent-Today"/>
        <updated>2023-10-15T05:29:06.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Latin America takes global lead in preference for centralized exchanges: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18969726/Latin-America-takes-global-lead-in-preference-for-centralized-exchanges-Report</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18969726/Latin-America-takes-global-lead-in-preference-for-centralized-exchanges-Report"/>
        <updated>2023-10-15T05:02:42.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How XRP sent USDC out of the prized crypto index]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18969716/How-XRP-sent-USDC-out-of-the-prized-crypto-index</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18969716/How-XRP-sent-USDC-out-of-the-prized-crypto-index"/>
        <updated>2023-10-15T04:30:32.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[G20 Calls for ‘Swift and Coordinated Implementation’ of IMF Crypto Roadmap]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b7b51a4f</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/g20-calls-for-swift-and-coordinated-implementation-of-imf-crypto-roadmap/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-15T03:39:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The G20 finance ministers and central bank governors have adopted the roadmap on crypto assets proposed by the International Monetary Fund (IMF) and the Financial Stability Board (FSB). “We call for swift and coordinated implementation of the G20 Roadmap,” the finance chiefs announced at their latest meeting.
 
G20 Finance Chiefs’ Communique on Crypto Assets
 
The G20 finance ministers and central bank governors convened in Marrakech, Morocco, on Oct. 12-13 where they discussed a range of topics, including crypto regulations.
 
In their communique released at the end of the two-day meeting, the G20 finance chiefs expressed their appreciation to the International Monetary Fund (IMF) and the Financial Stability Board (FSB) “for effectively putting together the IMF-FSB Synthesis Paper which t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Insights: Due diligence with crypto staking providers]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18969692/Insights-Due-diligence-with-crypto-staking-providers</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18969692/Insights-Due-diligence-with-crypto-staking-providers"/>
        <updated>2023-10-15T03:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JPMorgan CEO Warns of ‘Most Dangerous Time the World Has Seen in Decades’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b7bd27f4</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/jpmorgan-ceo-warns-of-most-dangerous-time-the-world-has-seen-in-decades/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-15T01:39:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JPMorgan Chase CEO Jamie Dimon has warned of “the most dangerous time the world has seen in decades.” The executive explained that “the war in Ukraine compounded by last week’s attacks on Israel may have far-reaching impacts on energy and food markets, global trade, and geopolitical relationships.”
 
Jamie Dimon’s Latest Warnings
 
The chairman and CEO of JPMorgan Chase, Jamie Dimon, issued a warning during the release of his company’s third-quarter 2023 earnings results that the world may be encountering the “most dangerous time” in decades.
 
“The war in Ukraine compounded by last week’s attacks on Israel may have far-reaching impacts on energy and food markets, global trade, and geopolitical relationships,” the JPMorgan boss detailed, emphasizing:
 

This may be the most dangerous time …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rich Dad Poor Dad: Robert Kiyosaki applies knowledge to Bitcoin! #bitcoin #crypto #shorts]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18969645/Rich-Dad-Poor-Dad-Robert-Kiyosaki-applies-knowledge-to-Bitcoin-bitcoin-crypto-shorts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18969645/Rich-Dad-Poor-Dad-Robert-Kiyosaki-applies-knowledge-to-Bitcoin-bitcoin-crypto-shorts"/>
        <updated>2023-10-15T01:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The lessons in Robert Kiyosaki's Rich Dad, Poor Dad apply to Bitcoin. It's not about how much Bitcoin will be tomorrow, but how much you are buying TODAY!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[California Gov. Newsom greenlights crypto regulation bill for 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18969642/California-Gov-Newsom-greenlights-crypto-regulation-bill-for-2025</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18969642/California-Gov-Newsom-greenlights-crypto-regulation-bill-for-2025"/>
        <updated>2023-10-15T00:50:09.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk's Favourite Coin's Future, Israel-Hamas War Impact And More: This Week In Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18969634/Elon-Musks-Favourite-Coins-Future-Israel-Hamas-War-Impact-And-More-This-Week-In-Crypto</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18969634/Elon-Musks-Favourite-Coins-Future-Israel-Hamas-War-Impact-And-More-This-Week-In-Crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-10-15T00:15:11.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$1,700,000,000,000 US Budget Deficit Shattered in 2023 As IMF Issues Warning on America’s ‘Worrying and Deteriorating’ Fiscal Trajectory]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18969632/1700000000000-US-Budget-Deficit-Shattered-in-2023-As-IMF-Issues-Warning-on-Americas-Worrying-and-Deteriorating-Fiscal-Trajectory</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18969632/1700000000000-US-Budget-Deficit-Shattered-in-2023-As-IMF-Issues-Warning-on-Americas-Worrying-and-Deteriorating-Fiscal-Trajectory"/>
        <updated>2023-10-15T00:04:35.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance.US Updates Crypto Listing Process, Says Exchange Considering Launching Trading Support for Aptos Rival]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18969627/BinanceUS-Updates-Crypto-Listing-Process-Says-Exchange-Considering-Launching-Trading-Support-for-Aptos-Rival</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18969627/BinanceUS-Updates-Crypto-Listing-Process-Says-Exchange-Considering-Launching-Trading-Support-for-Aptos-Rival"/>
        <updated>2023-10-15T00:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple’s Legal Chief Calls for ‘Rational’ Crypto Regulation — Urges US to Stop Elevating Politics Over Sound Policy]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b7a4ef08</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ripples-legal-chief-calls-for-rational-crypto-regulation-urges-us-to-stop-elevating-politics-over-sound-policy/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-14T23:35:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple’s chief legal officer says the U.S. needs to ”stop elevating politics over sound policy.” Noting that countries and regions outside of the U.S., such as Singapore, the U.K., the EU, and Japan, welcome crypto businesses, he emphasized: “I think we need a rational regulatory framework.” Moreover, he stressed that certain regulatory agencies in the U.S. are fighting over the control of the technology rather than focusing on the right policy outcome.
 
‘We Need a Rational Regulatory Framework’
 
Ripple’s chief legal officer, Stuart Alderoty, discussed U.S. cryptocurrency regulation on social media and in an interview with CNBC this week. He wrote on X Thursday:
 

We need to stop elevating politics over sound policy in the US, and look to the way that Singapore, UK, EU, & Dubai have set…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto In Hollywood: BTC, DOGE, and SHIB Accepted For Tickets To Taylor Swift’s New Movie]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b7a5a9dc</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/btc-doge-and-shib-taylor-swift/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-14T23:24:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks to a collaboration between crypto payment gateway BitPay and AMC, crypto owners can buy tickets to the highly anticipated Taylor Swift movie using crypto such as BTC, DOGE, and SHIB. BitPay recently announced on social media platform X that tickets to the Taylor Swift Eras Tour Movie can be purchased using Bitcoin, DOGE, ETH, SHIB, and more through its payment gateway. 
 
This is huge news for the crypto community as Taylor Swift is one of the biggest pop stars on the planet. A move such as this demonstrates the increasing use of cryptocurrencies across all sectors of the economy. 
 
 
 Exciting News for Taylor Swift Fans! 
 
Get ready for the Taylor Swift Eras Tour Movie, an immersive experience that brings you back to all of her unforgettable eras! And the best part? You can now p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Times get tougher for Yuga Labs NFTs as gaming rewards fail to deliver]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18969604/Times-get-tougher-for-Yuga-Labs-NFTs-as-gaming-rewards-fail-to-deliver</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18969604/Times-get-tougher-for-Yuga-Labs-NFTs-as-gaming-rewards-fail-to-deliver"/>
        <updated>2023-10-14T22:30:25.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Mulls Tighter Restrictions on AI Chip Shipments to Chinese Firms, Report]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b7ac99a4</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/us-mulls-tighter-restrictions-on-ai-chip-shipments-to-chinese-firms-report/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-14T21:44:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The government in Washington is reportedly considering further limiting China’s access to U.S. processors used in artificial intelligence (AI) applications. The current restrictions, which were introduced last year, allow Chinese companies to source the chips through overseas subsidiaries.
 
Washington Seeks to Further Curb Chinese Access to American AI Chips, Sources Say
 
The administration of President Joe Biden may broaden the curbs on the shipments of U.S. semiconductors used for AI to Chinese companies to include their units abroad, Reuters reported on Friday, quoting people familiar with the matter.
 
The measures announced in 2022 sought to thwart Beijing’s military advances by preventing the supply of American AI chips and chipmaking tools to China. However, the initial restrictio…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lubomir Tassev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Embrace Your Inner Witch with AI, Now Fluent in Occult Sciences]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201382</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201382/ai-occult-witch-mistral-trismegistus"/>
        <updated>2023-10-14T21:43:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral Trismegistus-7B is the latest LLM in town. It can help you read palms and instruct you on how to ride your flying broom.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Whales and Ethereum Whales Are Not the Same: Glassnode]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201674</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201674/bitcoin-ethereum-whale-comparison-glassnode"/>
        <updated>2023-10-14T21:31:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While BTC whales accumulate, ETH whales sell, according to Glassnode. What's going on?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Venezuela Offers ‘Unique Crypto Utility’ Amid Hyperinflation: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201669</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201669/venezuela-offer-unique-crypto-utility-amid-hyperinflation-report"/>
        <updated>2023-10-14T21:14:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Contrary to the assertions of cryptocurrency advocates, Venezuela is headed toward a “de-facto dollarization economy.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sega Exec Says Blockchain Gaming an 'Unknown World' Worth Exploring]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201492</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201492/sega-exec-says-blockchain-gaming-unknown-world-worth-exploring"/>
        <updated>2023-10-14T20:10:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sega is co-developing a trading card NFT game based on Sangokushi Taisen for Asia, and Sega's Co-COO is optimistic about its potential.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockfi CEO Blames FTX and Alameda Collapse for Firm’s Bankruptcy]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b7963464</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/blockfi-ceo-blames-ftx-and-alameda-collapse-for-firms-bankruptcy/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-14T19:35:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blockfi CEO Zac Prince testified Friday that the downfall of FTX contributed to his company’s bankruptcy. Prince appeared as a government witness in the fraud trial of former FTX boss Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF).
 
Blockfi’s Prince: Loans Wouldn’t Be Approved Knowing Alameda Used FTX Clients’ Funds
 
Blockfi’s Prince informed federal prosecutors that his company had loaned as much as $1.1 billion to Sam Bankman-Fried‘s trading company, Alameda Research. He stated that Blockfi wouldn’t have sanctioned the loans if they had been aware that Alameda was utilizing FTX client funds.
 
“No,” Prince responded when queried if he knew Alameda was using FTX customer funds. “That’s not appropriate,” he added. The trial’s testimony was covered by Inner City Press reporter Matthew Russell Lee and was broadc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Gains Major Recognition As One Of The Largest Crypto Assets]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b7971497</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/xrp-gains-major-recognition/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-14T19:24:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XRP has continued to record significant success on the back of Judge Analisa Torres’ ruling, which gave it a unique status following her declaration that the token isn’t a security. One such success recorded is the latest recognition of XRP by the Hong Kong Virtual Asset Consortium (HKVAC) in its latest crypto indices ranking.
 
HKVAC Includes XRP In Top 5 Crypto
 
In a statement released on October 13, the prominent rating agency stated that XRP will replace USDC and enter into the top 5 of its Cryptocurrency Global Large Top5 Index and Cryptocurrency Global Large Top5 Equal Weight Index. This top 5 index contains other foremost cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin, Ethereum, BNB, and USDT.
 
 
HKVAC noted that this change is part of its rebalancing results of the HKVAC Key Indexes and HKVAC Mar…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinkite's Newest Bitcoin Device Can Serve As A Lightning Wallet And Nostr Client]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b79311a4</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/coinkites-newest-bitcoin-device-can-serve-as-a-lightning-wallet-and-nostr-client"/>
        <updated>2023-10-14T18:36:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Satslink looks similar to the Coldcard Q1, but internally it's completely different.
Coinkite
 
    
Coinkite has announced their latest product, Satslink. The under-production device sits at the intersection of many different areas of communications and mobile hardware, empowering developers to build a whole slew of different applications.
Rather than leaning on an opinionated framework, Satslink leverages open and flexible hardware enclosed by the Coldcard Q1’s exterior to bring variety and flexibility to developers. Those in possession of this device can choose what to do with it, and let their builder mentalities run wild on the many different possibilities the piece of hardware can offer.
At its core, Satslink is a peer-to-peer, hackable multi-purpose device. It features a secure elem…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Namcios</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Cyberpunk 2077's Developer Needed AI to Complete 'Phantom Liberty']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201466</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201466/why-cyberpunk-2077-developer-needed-ai-complete-phantom-liberty"/>
        <updated>2023-10-14T18:26:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After the passing of actor Miłogost Reczek, CD Projekt Red used AI to recreate the voice of Viktor Vektor in Cyberpunk 2077: Phantom Liberty.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain Gaming Holds Strong in Q3, Amid Evolving Crypto Landscape]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b79fb06c</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/blockchain-gaming-holds-strong-in-q3-amid-evolving-crypto-landscape/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-14T17:44:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The blockchain gaming sector maintained its influential position in the third quarter of 2023 despite some decreases in momentum, according to Dappradar’s recent report. Although metrics such as unique active wallets and transactions dropped slightly, the report advises against viewing this as a sign of decreasing interest. Rather, it shows a changing landscape as other crypto sectors become more prominent.
 
Dappradar Report: Blockchain Gaming Sees Steady Growth
 
Dappradar’s Third Quarter Blockchain Gaming report underscores emerging trends, including the growth of casual gaming studios and “move-to-earn” applications, indicating diversifying user tastes. The report also mentions the ongoing dominance of established games like Alien Worlds and Splinterlands in wallet and transaction coun…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: War and Inflation Chill Crypto Investments]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201660</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201660/this-week-in-coins-israel-palestine-war-cpi-inflation"/>
        <updated>2023-10-14T17:35:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Israel–Palestine war and persistent inflation readings contributed to the downward price pressure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BOND Token Soars After BarnBridge Votes to ‘Comply’ With SEC]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b798d642</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/10/14/bond-token-soars-after-barnbridge-votes-to-comply-with-sec/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-14T17:31:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Securities regulators have been investigating the decentralized finance (DeFi) protocol since at least July.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Urges Court to Compel SEC Action on Rulemaking Petition]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b799775b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/coinbase-to-compel-sec-action-rulemaking-petition/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-14T17:24:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase has intensified efforts to force the hand of the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) on its crypto rulemaking petition. The firm has submitted a formal response to the Third Circuit regarding the SEC’s recent update on its rulemaking request.
 
Coinbase Files For Mandamus Again In Latest Response
 
As earlier reported by Bitcoinist, the SEC staff tendered a recommendation to the Commission on October 10, 2023, following Coinbase’s mandamus request in April. This mandamus petition sought a prompt response to the crypto company’s rulemaking appeal in July 2022.
 
Coinbase has, however, expressed dissatisfaction and frustration with the latest SEC update, believing it raises more questions than answers. The firm asserted that a “formal, public” response to the peti…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Opeyemi Sule</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NASA Tests Deep Space Communications on Six-Year Asteroid Mission]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201644</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201644/nasa-psyche-laser-communications-asteroid-mission"/>
        <updated>2023-10-14T17:01:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JPL’s Deep Space Optical Communication will harness lasers for superior data relay back to Earth during a six-year mission.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MetaMask Crypto Wallet Briefly Pulled from Apple App Store]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201645</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201645/metamask-crypto-wallet-removed-from-apple-app-store"/>
        <updated>2023-10-14T16:20:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The app was restored within hours, while other wallet apps remained available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Estate Stakes 5.5 Million SOL; Millions Locked Until 2028]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b78c0d2d</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ftx-estate-stakes-5-5-million-sol-millions-locked-until-2028/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-14T15:42:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain records have shed light on a development involving the trustees of the now-defunct exchange FTX, who are overseeing its bankruptcy proceedings. They have committed 5.5 million solana (SOL) for staking. Meanwhile, the current market value of FTX’s total solana assets is a hefty $1.16 billion. However, it’s worth highlighting that a significant portion of these assets will be held in a lock-up period, not to be fully released until 2028. 
 
Blockchain Unmasks Massive SOL Stake by FTX Trustees Amid Bankruptcy Proceedings
 
Whale Alert, on October 13, reported a transfer of 5.5 million SOL. Following this revelation, onchain researcher Ashpool identified that the sizable amount of SOL belonged to the FTX estate. Ashpool further mentioned that the funds were directed towards the validator Figment for the purpose of staking.
 

 
The outcome of SOL staking can vary. Some sources assert that SOL staking has traditionally offered around 5.5% APY. Yet, others suggest that SOL staking can yield as much as 14.47% APY, contingent on the staking platform chosen. Rewards for staking in Solana are distributed approximately every 2-3 days, albeit the precise frequency of rewards can fluctuate based on network conditions and other variables.
 
 
FTX’s estate holds roughly $1.16 billion in SOL, but not all of it is immediately accessible. 12 million of FTX’s SOL cache is scheduled to be released in increments every 30 days until 2027. An additional 34.52 million SOL is set to be gradually unlocked every month until 2028. Both of these caches are disbursing monthly SOL that FTX can either sell or stake. However, FTX has the option to sell the keys to the entire vested cache before its official release.
 
What do you think about the FTX estate staking 5.5 million SOL? Share your thoughts and opinions about this subject in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two-Sided Coin Control]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b78cae83</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/technical/two-sided-coin-control"/>
        <updated>2023-10-14T15:37:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article is featured in Bitcoin Magazine’s “The Withdrawal Issue”. Click here to subscribe now.
A PDF pamphlet of this article is available for download. 
Self custody is an essential requirement when using Bitcoin to fully benefit from all the properties that make Bitcoin valuable in the first place. To be able to truly transact without permission, benefiting from the censorship resistance of the network, you have to control your own keys. You can’t outsource that to someone else, you can’t trust the neutrality or honesty of a custodian, you must solely have direct control of corresponding private keys to your UTXOs. If you fail to do this, you will always be a second class user. Bitcoin as a system gives you almost total control over your own funds; control of custody, when it is spe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shinobi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deadline for SEC Appeal Against Grayscale’s Spot Bitcoin ETF Ruling Expires]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b7750790</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/deadline-for-sec-appeal-against-grayscales-spot-bitcoin-etf-ruling-expires/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-14T14:12:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. securities regulator has apparently missed a deadline to appeal a court ruling against its rejection of Grayscale’s spot bitcoin ETF application. Media reports, quoting sources familiar with the matter, unveiled ahead of the deadline that the agency was not planning to appeal the decision which potentially paves the way for the application’s review.
 
U.S. SEC Fails to Appeal Court Decision on Grayscale’s Application for Spot Bitcoin ETF
 
The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has not appealed a court decision in favor of Grayscale’s bid to convert its bitcoin trust (GBTC) to a spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF). The crypto asset manager had challenged the SEC’s move to deny the conversion. The regulator had 45 days to file an appeal and hasn’t done so at the time…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lubomir Tassev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biggest Movers: SHIB Hits 6-Day High to Start the Weekend]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b77010ec</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/biggest-movers-shib-hits-6-day-high-to-start-the-weekend/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-14T13:40:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Saturday saw shiba inu climb to its highest point since Monday, as bulls made a slight return to the market. The meme coin rose by as much as 4% on Saturday, as the global crypto market cap made gradual gains to start the weekend. Solana was another notable mover, climbing above the $22.00 zone.
 
Shiba Inu (SHIB)
 
Shiba inu (SHIB) rallied for a third straight session on Saturday, as the meme coin jumped nearly 4% higher in the day.
 
Following a low of $0.000006828 on Friday, SHIB/USD climbed to a peak of $0.000007099 to start the weekend.
 
This is the highest point that SHIB has hit since Monday, when price was trading at a high of $0.00000721.
 
 
The rally started after bulls rejected a breakout of a floor at $0.00000670 earlier this week, and they now look to be taking the coin to a resistance level of $0.00000760.
 
From the chart, it appears that the surge has resulted in the relative strength index (RSI) moving above its own ceiling at 45.00.
 
At the time of writing, price strength is at a reading of 46.39, with the next visible point of resistance at 51.00.
 
 
Solana (SOL)
 
Solana (SOL) extended its own gains to start the weekend, as the cryptocurrency finally rose above $22.00.
 
SOL/USD peaked at $22.20 earlier in today’s session, which comes following Friday’s low at the $21.39 level.
 
Earlier gains have since eased as the day matured, which came after bulls began to close previous positions.
 
 
One reason for this can be attributed to the RSI, which collided with a ceiling around the 53.00 region.
 
Currently, the index is tracking at 53.02, with solana trading at $21.92, as momentum begins to shift.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
Will solana remain below $22.00 for the rest of the weekend? Let us know your thoughts in the comments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Labs Asks Court To Compel Citadel To Provide Data Relating To UST Depeg]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b7717741</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/terraform-labs-ust-depeg/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-14T13:25:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a bid to defend itself against the “complex cryptocurrency action” brought against it by the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), Terraform Labs has once again filed a motion against Citadel Securities, asking the court to compel the market maker to provide certain documents. 
 
Citadel May Have Caused UST Depeg
 
In the court filing dated October 10, Terraform Labs, the company that developed the Terra blockchain and supported the UST stablecoin, alleged that UST’s collapse wasn’t caused by any instability in the token’s ecosystem but by the “concerted, intentional effort of certain third party market participants” who shorted and caused the token to de-peg from its dollar price.
 
 
One of these “third party market participants,” which Terraform suspects, happens to be Citadel…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Technical Analysis: BTC Falls on Saturday, Following Brief Spell Above $27,000]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b77fbf57</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-ethereum-technical-analysis-btc-falls-on-saturday-following-brief-spell-above-27000/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-14T12:20:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin retreated from a brief spell above $27,000 on Saturday, as uncertainty in the market remained high to start the weekend. The global cryptocurrency market was marginally higher to start the weekend, trading 0.42% higher as of writing. Ethereum continued to consolidate above a recent floor of $1,535.
 
Bitcoin
 
Bitcoin (BTC) retreated below the $27,000 level to start the weekend, after a late surge in price on Friday.
 
Following a low of $26,686.32 earlier in Friday’s session, BTC/USD peaked at a high of $27,092.70 as the day progressed.
 
Although BTC has since slipped, and is currently trading at $26,866.74, it is still higher than yesterday’s bottom.
 
 
The consolidation comes as the relative strength index (RSI) continues to hover above a floor at the 45.00 mark.
 
Whilst now tracking at 46.72, the next target is likely to be at a ceiling of 50.00, and if hit, bitcoin will be back above $27,000.
 
Overall, bitcoin is trading 4% lower than at the same point last week.
 
 
Ethereum
 
Ethereum (ETH) is largely unchanged at the time of writing, as the cryptocurrency consolidated to start the weekend.
 
ETH/USD reached a high of $1,571.75 on Friday, however has since fallen to a current reading of $1,546.80.
 
This is slightly higher than yesterday’s low at $1,538.09, which was marginally above a support point at $1,535.
 
 
The drop in price coincides with the RSI failing to breach its own point of resistance at the 40.00 mark.
 
Currently, price strength is at the 37.46 level, with the 10-day moving average continuing to trend downwards.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
Could ethereum fall under $1,700 this weekend? Leave your thoughts in the comments below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Won’t Appeal Grayscale Bitcoin ETF Ruling: Reports]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201493</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201493/sec-appeal-grayscale-bitcoin-etf"/>
        <updated>2023-10-13T21:49:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[But that doesn't mean a spot market Bitcoin ETF is a lock.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple’s Win Over SEC Gave XRP a Massive Boost—That’s All Gone Now]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201463</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201463/xrp-boost-from-ripple-sec-court-win-gone-now"/>
        <updated>2023-10-13T21:13:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XRP boomed in July following a federal judge's ruling. It has since crashed back down again.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Now Owns 'Call of Duty' Maker Activision Blizzard—What Happens Next?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201465</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201465/microsoft-owns-call-of-duty-publisher-activision-blizzard-what-happens-next"/>
        <updated>2023-10-13T20:57:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Xbox maker Microsoft just acquired Call of Duty, Diablo, Candy Crush, and Overwatch. What does it mean for players and the games they love?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Adds AI Features to Search and Browsing May Never Be the Same]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201468</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201468/google-ai-features-search-browsing"/>
        <updated>2023-10-13T20:33:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With tech giants racing to capitalize on generative AI, Google is infusing Search with creative new capabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Happens If the SEC Doesn't Appeal Grayscale Bitcoin ETF Ruling?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201464</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201464/what-happens-if-sec-doesnt-appeal-grayscale-bitcoin-etf-ruling"/>
        <updated>2023-10-13T20:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC shows no signs of fighting back against its court loss to Grayscale.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum, Solana and XRP Lead Losses in Rough Week for Crypto Market]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201453</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201453/ethereum-solana-xrp-rough-week-for-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-10-13T19:47:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the lowest price Ethereum has traded at in the past seven months.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There's a Film Festival Happening in Minecraft Right Now]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201433</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201433/film-festival-happening-minecraft-right-now"/>
        <updated>2023-10-13T19:13:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking to catch some independent cinema? You might be surprised at the locale—this festival is running inside a Minecraft game world. Here's why.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ali Shutler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Buy Taylor Swift Movie Tickets With Bitcoin, Dogecoin, and SHIB]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201448</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201448/you-can-buy-taylor-swift-movie-tickets-bitcoin-dogecoin-shib"/>
        <updated>2023-10-13T18:58:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tickets to the record-shattering Taylor Swift concert film can also be bought with ETH, XRP, and more via AMC and BitPay.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Just Deciphered an Ancient Herculaneum Scroll Without Unrolling It]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201411</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201411/ai-deciphered-herculaneum-scroll"/>
        <updated>2023-10-13T17:08:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The word "purple" has not been found in opened scroll fragments before.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt AI, Edited by Stacy Elliot</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Could Help Brain Surgeons Diagnose Tumors in Real Time]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201316</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201316/ai-could-help-brain-surgeons-diagnose-tumors-real-time"/>
        <updated>2023-10-13T16:05:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers introduce an AI model that diagnoses central nervous system tumors rapidly, achieving 90% accuracy in early testing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nitro Nation World Tour Review: Gear Up With NFTs—Or Face the Grind]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201289</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201289/nitro-nation-world-tour-review-gear-up-nfts-face-grind"/>
        <updated>2023-10-13T15:43:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[REVIEW: The latest Nitro Nation mobile game has some fun moments, but this drag-racer feels like a pay-to-win game at its core.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether CEO Steps Down, Naming Paolo Ardoino as Successor at Stablecoin Issuer]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201365</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201365/tether-ceo-steps-down-naming-paolo-ardoino-as-successor-at-stablecoin-issuer"/>
        <updated>2023-10-13T15:15:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paolo Ardoino has already acted as the face of the stablecoin giant for years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SBF Trial Live Updates: Caroline Ellison Considered Resigning Several Times]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199892</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199892/trial-sam-bankman-fried-live-blog-latest-news-insights"/>
        <updated>2023-10-13T12:45:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried faces seven criminal charges related to the dramatic collapse of his crypto empire. Here's the latest on his trial.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Terra? The Chaotic Algorithmic Stablecoin Protocol Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=94573</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-terra-algorithmic-stablecoin-protocol-explained"/>
        <updated>2023-10-13T12:40:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terra is a Cosmos-based protocol that powers a suite of algorithmic stablecoins, which aim to maintain their pegs using a coin called LUNA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Stevens,Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terra Says Citadel Securities Caused UST Stablecoin Depeg]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201342</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201342/terraform-labs-alleges-citadel-securities-behind-may-2022-ust-stablecoin-depeg-event"/>
        <updated>2023-10-13T11:03:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As for the evidence, Terraform points to an alleged conversation Citadel founder Ken Griffin had with a pseudonymous trader.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THORChain Soars 8% as DeFi Exchange Lifts Trading Pause]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201337</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201337/thorchain-soars-over-defi-exchange-lifts-trading-pause"/>
        <updated>2023-10-13T09:17:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THORChain's leading exchange also updated its terms of service, introducing new blocks on countries sanctioned by the United States.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Sparks Security Fears at US Space Force]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201321</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201321/ai-sparks-security-fears-us-space-force"/>
        <updated>2023-10-12T22:45:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Space Force put a stop to personal AI use on duty, joining companies wary of generative AI's implications on privacy and security.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uniswap Launches Mobile Ethereum Wallet on Android]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201327</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201327/uniswap-launches-mobile-ethereum-wallet-android"/>
        <updated>2023-10-12T22:36:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Launched in beta, Uniswap's wallet offers automatic switching between mainnet and layer-2 networks, along with other features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Now Add Thomas the Tank Engine to Starfield—Yes, Really]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201315</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201315/you-can-now-add-thomas-tank-engine-starfield-yes-really"/>
        <updated>2023-10-12T22:24:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Someone has created a mod that adds Thomas the Tank Engine to Skyrim creator Bethesda's latest game, Starfield. Now you can't unsee his face.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Senators Want to Ban AI Copycats Like Fake Drake and The Weeknd Song]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201305</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201305/senators-want-ban-ai-copycats-like-fake-drake-weeknd-song"/>
        <updated>2023-10-12T21:39:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new bipartisan bill proposed Thursday would create a new federal law forbidding the creation of AI-generated mimics of a person without their consent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Gaming Attracted $600M Worth of Q3 Investment Despite Bear Market]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201282</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201282/crypto-gaming-attracted-600m-worth-q3-investment-despite-bear-market"/>
        <updated>2023-10-12T21:04:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While the gaming industry continues to be plagued by mass layoffs, crypto gaming is still seeing many millions invested each quarter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There's Now a 'Stronger Possibility' Russian Actors Involved in $477 Million FTX Hack]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201290</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201290/theres-now-a-stronger-possibility-russian-actors-involved-in-477-million-ftx-hack"/>
        <updated>2023-10-12T21:02:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many funds stolen from the bankrupt exchange have been combined with those of Russian criminals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Melcogate: AI Blamed for Leaked Audio That Sparked Argentina Political Drama]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201268</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201268/melcogate-ai-blamed-for-leaked-audio-that-sparked-argentina-political-drama"/>
        <updated>2023-10-12T19:45:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Politicians in Argentina point fingers at AI for leaked audio used to allege a former central bank president of sexual harassment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fortnite Reddit Reward Token BRICK Surges 131%—Why?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201261</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201261/fortnite-reddit-reward-token-brick-surges-131-why"/>
        <updated>2023-10-12T19:26:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRICKs are booming, as Reddit’s Fortnite-inspired crypto token sees a substantial pop—and Reddit’s MOON token rose too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Voyager CEO Sued By CFTC and FTC for Misleading Customers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201276</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201276/ex-voyager-ceo-sued-by-cftc-ftc-for-misleading-customers"/>
        <updated>2023-10-12T19:14:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The government agencies say the company lied about how "safe" their customers' assets really were.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Favorite Solana Dips After Frequent Mentions in Sam Bankman-Fried's Trial]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201258</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201258/solana-ftx-fave-dips-bankman-frieds-criminal-trial"/>
        <updated>2023-10-12T19:03:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The asset was mentioned again during Bankman-Fried's trial. It's now down significantly compared to last week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Play 'Call of Duty: Modern Warfare III' Now—Here's How]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200458</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200458/play-call-duty-modern-warfare-3-now-open-beta-early-access"/>
        <updated>2023-10-12T18:17:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATE: The Modern Warfare III beta has extended from PlayStation to Xbox and PC as well. Here's how to get into Early Access today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CEO Pleads Guilty to Crypto Futures Cherry-Picking Scheme]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201248</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201248/ceo-pleads-guilty-to-cherry-picking-scheme-involving-crypto-futures-contracts"/>
        <updated>2023-10-12T17:39:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the first time a commodities trading advisor has been charged with a operating a fraudulent crypto trading scheme.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NBA's LaMelo and Lonzo Ball—And Their Dad—Star in NFT Game 'StrayShot']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201105</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201105/nba-lamelo-lonzo-ball-dad-star-nft-game-strayshot"/>
        <updated>2023-10-12T16:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NBA stars and their family have signed a deal to appear in the upcoming battle royale shooter StrayShot, which uses the SKALE blockchain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cathie Wood's Ark Invest Refiles Bitcoin ETF Application—Here's What's New]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201244</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201244/cathie-woodss-ark-invest-refiles-bitcoin-etf-application-heres-whats-new"/>
        <updated>2023-10-12T15:11:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The revised submission from Ark now includes risks of a change to Bitcoin’s code as well as how its custodian will handle assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why AI Arena is Building on Arbitrum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Gl80TQOm/why-ai-arena-is-building-on-arbitrum</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Gl80TQOm/why-ai-arena-is-building-on-arbitrum"/>
        <updated>2023-10-12T14:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI Arena CEO Brandon Da Silva and COO Wei Xie discuss the challenges that come with building on Ethereum, ETH sidechains, and layer-two blockchains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Compute Anything on Bitcoin? What You Need to Know About BitVM]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201067</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201067/compute-anything-on-bitcoin-what-you-need-to-know-about-bitvm"/>
        <updated>2023-10-12T14:20:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new Bitcoin proposal says anything can be computed on the network, but devs are split on whether that's a good idea.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alyssa Hertig</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pet3rPan_ on venture DAOs and blockchain games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DawNLI3O/pet3rpan-on-venture-daos-and-blockchain-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DawNLI3O/pet3rpan-on-venture-daos-and-blockchain-games"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T18:24:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the 4th episode of this time will be different.

Our guest for today's episode is Pet3rpan_ from Metacartel, 1kx, HydraVentures, and more!

https://twitter.com/pet3rpan_

This Time Will Be Different is sponsored by 1000x
https://decrypt.co/1000x]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Shrapnel's Marketplace, New Map, and 'AI Director' Feature]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/F5RQCmvH/inside-shrapnels-marketplace-new-map-and-ai-director-feature</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/F5RQCmvH/inside-shrapnels-marketplace-new-map-and-ai-director-feature"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T16:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin chats with Shrapnel's Head of Studio Don Norbury to get the latest updates on how the NFT-powered first-person sci-fi extraction shooter's development is progressing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Art of the Times': Art Blocks Founder Erick Calderon on the State of Generative Art]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zSjfRrl5/art-of-the-times-art-blocks-founder-erick-calderon-on-the-state-of-generative-art</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zSjfRrl5/art-of-the-times-art-blocks-founder-erick-calderon-on-the-state-of-generative-art"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T18:10:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Art Blocks founder and CEO Erick Calderon sat down with Sander Lutz, lead culture reporter at Decrypt's SCENE, at Art Blocks Marfa Weekend 2023. They discuss the evolution of the company and the generative art world, along with what draws art enthusiasts to be an active part of the community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt Learn: Digital Ownership Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/6udZCotB/decrypt-learn-digital-ownership-explained</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/6udZCotB/decrypt-learn-digital-ownership-explained"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T10:57:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most powerful aspects of blockchain technology is its ability to provide us genuine ownership of our digital assets. This is called digital ownership. In this video, we’ll deep dive into digital ownership, why it matters, and how web3 makes owning digital assets like our social networks, music libraries, personal data, and beyond possible. Author: Clarissa Watson, Senior Writer at Consensys.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Martin Shkreli on E/ACC and SBF in Prison]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QONaWXKZ/martin-shkreli-on-e-acc-and-sbf-in-prison</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QONaWXKZ/martin-shkreli-on-e-acc-and-sbf-in-prison"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T22:03:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reza Jafery and Martin Shkreli sit down for a casual conversation about the growing movement that is E/ACC, what songs they could recite at gunpoint, and whether or not SBF will thrive or just survive during his time in prison.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Can AI Do in Gaming?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JKuqCMao/what-can-ai-do-in-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JKuqCMao/what-can-ai-do-in-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T17:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI Arena CEO Brandon Da Silva and COO Wei Xie discuss how artificial intelligence can shape the video game experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['There Are No Real Standards': Ready Player Me CEO Timmu Tõke on Building for an Open Gaming Ecosystem]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TH3KEAI0/there-are-no-real-standards-ready-player-me-ceo-timmu-tke-on-building-for-an-open-gaming-ecosystem</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TH3KEAI0/there-are-no-real-standards-ready-player-me-ceo-timmu-tke-on-building-for-an-open-gaming-ecosystem"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T17:29:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Timmu Tõke, co-founder and CEO of Ready Player Me, joins Decrypt contributor Ryan Gladwin to discuss the startup's approach to powering avatars that are interoperable across games and metaverse platforms—and what's needed to convince the industry to adopt standards and open up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain Is 'Only Way' Forward for Gaming, Says Shrapnel Studio Head]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/fhoy7Z8f/blockchain-is-only-way-forward-for-gaming-says-shrapnel-studio-head</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/fhoy7Z8f/blockchain-is-only-way-forward-for-gaming-says-shrapnel-studio-head"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T21:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shrapnel Studio Head Don Norbury tells Kate Irwin the reasons why the upcoming first-person shooter game will offer a wide range of NFTs. He also reveals team-based gameplay plans and shares how game maps have already changed this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Social Media Sentiment Is Key to Crypto Price Discovery]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/981TBppa/social-media-sentiment-is-key-to-crypto-price-discovery</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/981TBppa/social-media-sentiment-is-key-to-crypto-price-discovery"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T23:47:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sacha Ghebali, Director of Strategy and Business Development at The TIE, says social media sentiment remains a key factor in price movements for major cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin and Ethereum. However, he notes that sentiment has turned more negative lately amid regulatory uncertainty. Ghebali believes events like the Ripple lawsuit ruling significantly impacted sentiment and prices. André Beganski interviewed him at Messari Mainnet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[500Altcoins discusses DeFi Summer and the Dubai Crypto Scene - This Time Will Be Different - Episode 2]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cI7p8AK3/500altcoins-discusses-defi-summer-and-the-dubai-crypto-scene-this-time-will-be-different-episode-2</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cI7p8AK3/500altcoins-discusses-defi-summer-and-the-dubai-crypto-scene-this-time-will-be-different-episode-2"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our host Reza Jafery is joined by Gareth Fenney aka 500Altcoins. They discuss the glory days of DeFi Summer and whether or not its a smart move for builders in the crypto space to relocate to Dubai.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralize Derivatives Trading with Custom Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/lfmwAjB9/decentralize-derivatives-trading-with-custom-blockchain</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/lfmwAjB9/decentralize-derivatives-trading-with-custom-blockchain"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T10:37:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Gogel of dYdX discusses how the decentralized exchange is building a custom blockchain to fully decentralize derivatives trading. He explained how the new dYdX chain will allow validators to run order books in memory, enabling decentralized order matching at scale. This shift aims to increase security and transparency for traders while maintaining the performance of centralized exchanges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Most Crypto Users Don't Trust Themselves to Keep Their Seed Phrase Safe: Ledger CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/0kYf2Qed/most-crypto-users-dont-trust-themselves-to-keep-their-seed-phrase-safe-ledger-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/0kYf2Qed/most-crypto-users-dont-trust-themselves-to-keep-their-seed-phrase-safe-ledger-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Stacy Elliott sat down with Ledger CEO Pascal Gauthier to discuss crypto custody post-FTX, and the hardware wallet manufacturer's controversial Ledger Recover service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Accounting Challenges and Opportunities]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/0Sezz6pZ/crypto-accounting-challenges-and-opportunities</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/0Sezz6pZ/crypto-accounting-challenges-and-opportunities"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As crypto matures, accounting and tax regulations are evolving. Amy Kalnoki of Bitwave explains how her company helps crypto companies properly account for digital assets. She notes the importance of flexibility as new crypto assets emerge and regulations change. Stacy Elliott interviewed her at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[India's 1% Crypto Tax Has Been a Nightmare for High-Frequency Traders, Says Shardeum CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/fxygwLvH/indias-1-crypto-tax-has-been-a-nightmare-for-high-frequency-traders-says-shardeum-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/fxygwLvH/indias-1-crypto-tax-has-been-a-nightmare-for-high-frequency-traders-says-shardeum-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As India figures out its regulatory approach to the crypto industry, one thing is clear to Shardeum co-founder Nischal Shetty: “If you're a high-frequency trader, you can't afford to lose a percentage every time you sell,” he told Decrypt's Andre Beganski at Messari Mainnet in New York. “That's something that's caused a lot of issues.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Newly Partnered with Visa, Solana Focuses on Reliability]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/MZoxvulr/newly-partnered-with-visa-solana-focuses-on-reliability</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/MZoxvulr/newly-partnered-with-visa-solana-focuses-on-reliability"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana has improved network reliability through upgrades like Quick and local fee markets. It recently partnered with Visa to allow settling transactions in USDC on Solana. This could enable merchants to receive instant payments and save on credit card processing fees. Stacy Elliott spoke with Austin Federa, Head of Strategy for the Solana Foundation, at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Need to Start Thinking About How we Make Crypto Easy to Use: Robinhood Crypto General Manager]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PLZ0FpdC/we-need-to-start-thinking-about-how-we-make-crypto-easy-to-use-robinhood-crypto-general-manager</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PLZ0FpdC/we-need-to-start-thinking-about-how-we-make-crypto-easy-to-use-robinhood-crypto-general-manager"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Stacy Elliott sat down with Robinhood Crypto general manager Johann Kerbrat at Messari Mainnet 2023, to talk about the trading platform's crypto wallet, onboarding new users through simplicity, and keeping platform fees sustainable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Developer-Friendly zkRollup to Scale Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/OvAFgxTd/building-a-developer-friendly-zkrollup-to-scale-ethereum</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/OvAFgxTd/building-a-developer-friendly-zkrollup-to-scale-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daniel Helm, head of Developer Relations at Scroll, discussess how they are building a zkRollup to scale Ethereum transactions and lower fees. He explained their focus on creating a seamless developer experience by maintaining Ethereum's ethos and tooling. Scroll aims to launch their mainnet soon, providing more scalable blockspace for Ethereum developers. Stacy Elliott of Decrypt interviewed him at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Regulation Threatens U.S. Dominance of Financial Markets, Says CoinRoutes CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/CrpvzFjL/regulation-threatens-us-dominance-of-financial-markets-says-coinroutes-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/CrpvzFjL/regulation-threatens-us-dominance-of-financial-markets-says-coinroutes-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dave Weisberger, Co-Founder and CEO of CoinRoutes, argued that excessive regulation in the U.S. threatens to undermine the country's long-standing dominance in global financial markets. He warned that other countries are embracing blockchain and crypto to build more efficient digital markets, which could cause the US to lose its competitive edge and trillions in GDP. Weisberger said CoinRoutes is now focusing more on expanding internationally due to restrictive policies in the U.S. He was interviewed by André Beganski of Decrypt at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin's Narrative Is Shifting Towards Layer-2 Solutions]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/axArPRp3/bitcoins-narrative-is-shifting-towards-layer-2-solutions</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/axArPRp3/bitcoins-narrative-is-shifting-towards-layer-2-solutions"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rich Rines, original Core DAO contributor and former Coinbase engineer, discusses how the narrative around Bitcoin is shifting in 2023. While Bitcoin remains digital gold, new layer 2 solutions are emerging to unlock more utility and value from the huge amounts of capital stored in Bitcoin. He says these innovations can benefit Bitcoin holders while keeping Bitcoin maximalists happy by building outside the base layer. André Beganski interviewed him at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>