<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-05-17T08:19:39.263Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-05-17T08:19:39.263Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin bridge XLink resurrection underway post $10M hack]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19496583/Bitcoin-bridge-XLink-resurrection-underway-post-10M-hack</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19496583/Bitcoin-bridge-XLink-resurrection-underway-post-10M-hack"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T08:13:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XLink faced a security breach involving almost $10 million, with $4.3 million recovered thanks to a friendly neighborhood whitehat hacker.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Opportunity? Crypto expert predicts ‘one last nuke’ for XRP]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19496573/Opportunity-Crypto-expert-predicts-one-last-nuke-for-XRP</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19496573/Opportunity-Crypto-expert-predicts-one-last-nuke-for-XRP"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T08:12:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As many assets in the cryptocurrency sector near the week’s end on a positive note, XRP seems to be one … Continue reading]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Donald Trump’s Recent Crypto-Friendly Stance Genuine Or Opportunistic? Experts Weigh In]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19496571/Is-Donald-Trumps-Recent-Crypto-Friendly-Stance-Genuine-Or-Opportunistic-Experts-Weigh-In</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19496571/Is-Donald-Trumps-Recent-Crypto-Friendly-Stance-Genuine-Or-Opportunistic-Experts-Weigh-In"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump's recent pro-crypto stance is seen as opportunistic by some, aligning with crypto entrepreneurs against stifling innovation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decreasing Bitcoin Supply on Exchanges Indicating Possible Bullish Shift]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7421f096de</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/decreasing-bitcoin-supply-on-exchanges-indicating-possible-bullish-shift/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T08:01:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s supply on exchanges has significantly decreased, reaching new lows amid a bullish market trend, which analysts interpret as a shift towards long-term holding rather than short-term trading. A report by Bybit claimed that the diminishing supply could deplete within the next nine months, driven by factors such as the recent Bitcoin halving event and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tim Draper Champions Blockchain Startups: Announces Major Partnership With Stellar]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7421f096d0</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/tim-draper-champions-blockchain-startups-announces-major-partnership-with-stellar/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T08:01:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Renowned venture capitalist Tim Draper announced a significant collaboration between Draper University and Stellar. The partnership aims to accelerate and fund up to 80 startups over the next two years, with these startups set to build on the Stellar blockchain platform. The initiative includes the Stellar Astro Hacker House and the Stellar Embark Accelerator, programs […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JPMorgan Names Key Reasons Why Bitcoin Price Won't Rally Hard]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19496576/JPMorgan-Names-Key-Reasons-Why-Bitcoin-Price-Wont-Rally-Hard</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19496576/JPMorgan-Names-Key-Reasons-Why-Bitcoin-Price-Wont-Rally-Hard"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T08:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JPMorgan believes that the Bitcoin price has limited upside due to these key factors]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin: the mining farm in China closed by Biden will pass to the Americans]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19496572/Bitcoin-the-mining-farm-in-China-closed-by-Biden-will-pass-to-the-Americans</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19496572/Bitcoin-the-mining-farm-in-China-closed-by-Biden-will-pass-to-the-Americans"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T07:50:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A strange turn in the case of the Chinese-owned mining farm near the Cheyenne missile base.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Exchange Binance Announces It Will Support More Network Upgrades And Hard Forks Of These Altcoins!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19496525/Bitcoin-Exchange-Binance-Announces-It-Will-Support-More-Network-Upgrades-And-Hard-Forks-Of-These-Altcoins</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19496525/Bitcoin-Exchange-Binance-Announces-It-Will-Support-More-Network-Upgrades-And-Hard-Forks-Of-These-Altcoins"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T07:50:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency exchange Binance announced that it provides full support for the network upgrade and Hard Fork of these altcoins. Continue Reading: Bitcoin Exchange Binance Announces It Will Support More Network Upgrades And Hard Forks Of These Altcoins!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[S15 E35: Nick Schteringart & Konstantin Wünscher on OpenDelta on Runes]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19496527/S15-E35-Nick-Schteringart-Konstantin-Wunscher-on-OpenDelta-on-Runes</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19496527/S15-E35-Nick-Schteringart-Konstantin-Wunscher-on-OpenDelta-on-Runes"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T07:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenDelta is a synthetic dollar (stablecoin) that's built on top of Bitcoin's newly-launched Runes protocol. In this episode, co-founders Nick Schteringart & Konstantin Wünscher discuss about how and why they built this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fantom Outperforms CoinDesk 20 Over Past Week as TVL Jumps]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19496521/Fantom-Outperforms-CoinDesk-20-Over-Past-Week-as-TVL-Jumps</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19496521/Fantom-Outperforms-CoinDesk-20-Over-Past-Week-as-TVL-Jumps"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T07:43:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FTM has gained 13% in the last week, and total value locked in Fantom briefly hit $200 million.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SWIFT China President Wen Yang on Overcoming Barriers in CBDC Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19496501/SWIFT-China-President-Wen-Yang-on-Overcoming-Barriers-in-CBDC-Systems</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19496501/SWIFT-China-President-Wen-Yang-on-Overcoming-Barriers-in-CBDC-Systems"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T07:37:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SWIFT China President Wen Yang discusses the challenges and solutions for cross-border CBDC interoperability and initiatives to bridge the technological gaps between different CBDC systems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFT Buyer Sues Dolce & Gabbana Over Value Loss]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19496528/NFT-Buyer-Sues-Dolce-Gabbana-Over-Value-Loss</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19496528/NFT-Buyer-Sues-Dolce-Gabbana-Over-Value-Loss"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T07:33:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A customer in the Southern District of New York has sued luxury fashion brand Dolce & Gabbana USA Inc., alleging the fashion house mismanaged a collection of NFTs, leading to a significant decline in their value. The lawsuit, filed by Luke Brown, as reported by Bloomberg, centers on the DGFamily...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[French Regulator Warns Investors For Using ByBit Despite Ban]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19496481/French-Regulator-Warns-Investors-For-Using-ByBit-Despite-Ban</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19496481/French-Regulator-Warns-Investors-For-Using-ByBit-Despite-Ban"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T07:28:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ByBit has been under scrutiny in France for its lack of non-compliance with current regulations and was blacklisted in 20 May 2022.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana leads as the fastest among large-scale blockchains — CoinGecko]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19496464/Solana-leads-as-the-fastest-among-large-scale-blockchains-CoinGecko</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19496464/Solana-leads-as-the-fastest-among-large-scale-blockchains-CoinGecko"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T07:21:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Research from CoinGecko says that Solana is the fastest among large-scale blockchains, with its actual daily average transactions per second (TPS) reaching a record high of 1,504 on April 6, 2023 as the meme coin mania took off. Such a statistic makes Solana roughly 46 times faster than...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Kazakhstan Earns Security Certifications, Hosts Successful Meetup]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19496474/Binance-Kazakhstan-Earns-Security-Certifications-Hosts-Successful-Meetup</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19496474/Binance-Kazakhstan-Earns-Security-Certifications-Hosts-Successful-Meetup"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T07:06:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance hosted its first major community meetup of 2024 in Kazakhstan on May 14, attracting over 700 attendees, according to a company announcement. The event, held at the Presidential Center in Astana, offered participants a chance to connect with fellow Web3 enthusiasts and learn about the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Rocket Fuel for Bitcoin’: Analyst Jamie Coutts Says This Catalyst Could Propel BTC to $150,000 This Cycle]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19496430/Rocket-Fuel-for-Bitcoin-Analyst-Jamie-Coutts-Says-This-Catalyst-Could-Propel-BTC-to-150000-This-Cycle</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19496430/Rocket-Fuel-for-Bitcoin-Analyst-Jamie-Coutts-Says-This-Catalyst-Could-Propel-BTC-to-150000-This-Cycle"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T07:04:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Real Vision analyst Jamie Coutts is saying that the performance of the US dollar against other major currencies will impact the price of Bitcoin (BTC). Coutts tells his 16,300 followers on the social media platform X that the US Dollar Index (DXY), a measure of the US dollar’s value compared to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DTCC and Chainlink Launch Pilot Program with US Banking Giants to Advance Tokenization in TradFi]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19496390/DTCC-and-Chainlink-Launch-Pilot-Program-with-US-Banking-Giants-to-Advance-Tokenization-in-TradFi</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19496390/DTCC-and-Chainlink-Launch-Pilot-Program-with-US-Banking-Giants-to-Advance-Tokenization-in-TradFi"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T06:49:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Depository Trust and Clearing Corporation (DTCC) has partnered with blockchain oracle Chainlink to conclude a pilot program involving several major banking firms in the United States.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Major Firms Invest $3.5 Billion in Spot Bitcoin ETFs Despite Recent Inflow Decline]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19496365/Major-Firms-Invest-35-Billion-in-Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-Despite-Recent-Inflow-Decline</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19496365/Major-Firms-Invest-35-Billion-in-Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-Despite-Recent-Inflow-Decline"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T06:44:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the past week, over 600 companies have disclosed substantial investments in spot Bitcoin exchange-traded...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Did FED’s Rate Cut Pushed Earlier After Positive Inflation Reports? WSJ Correspondent Clarified]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19496366/Did-FEDs-Rate-Cut-Pushed-Earlier-After-Positive-Inflation-Reports-WSJ-Correspondent-Clarified</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19496366/Did-FEDs-Rate-Cut-Pushed-Earlier-After-Positive-Inflation-Reports-WSJ-Correspondent-Clarified"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T06:41:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wall Street Journal reporter Nick Timiraos evaluated the possibility of an interest rate cut by the FED following positive inflation data. Continue Reading: Did FED’s Rate Cut Pushed Earlier After Positive Inflation Reports? WSJ Correspondent Clarified]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morgan Stanley Bets BIg on Crypto with $270 Million GBTC Stake]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19496395/Morgan-Stanley-Bets-BIg-on-Crypto-with-270-Million-GBTC-Stake</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19496395/Morgan-Stanley-Bets-BIg-on-Crypto-with-270-Million-GBTC-Stake"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T06:35:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a sign of growing mainstream adoption, financial giant Morgan Stanley revealed a hefty $269.9 million investment in Bitcoin through Grayscale’s GBTC trust, as disclosed in its first-quarter 13F filing. And as per CNBC, This positions the bank as a major holder of GBTC, trailing only...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin vs inflation; Can Bitcoin hedge against inflation?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19496329/Bitcoin-vs-inflation-Can-Bitcoin-hedge-against-inflation</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19496329/Bitcoin-vs-inflation-Can-Bitcoin-hedge-against-inflation"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T06:16:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As traditional fiat currencies face the specter of inflation due to various economic factors, alternative assets like Bitcoin (BTC) have … Continue reading]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Crypto, Pumping 12% On New Asset Tokenization Milestone, Is 'An Opportunity Of A Lifetime,' Says Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19496359/This-Crypto-Pumping-12-On-New-Asset-Tokenization-Milestone-Is-An-Opportunity-Of-A-Lifetime-Says-Analyst</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19496359/This-Crypto-Pumping-12-On-New-Asset-Tokenization-Milestone-Is-An-Opportunity-Of-A-Lifetime-Says-Analyst"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T06:13:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Popular cryptocurrency trader and analyst Michaël van de Poppe raised his bullish bets on Chainlink (CRYPTO: LINK) after the coin outperformed the broader market with double-digit gains. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Just Had A Game-Changing Moment, But Will Biden Veto?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7421e71872</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-game-changing-moment-will-biden-veto/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T06:10:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a potentially game-changing moment for the crypto sector, the US Senate has passed H.J. Res 109, a bill seeking to overturn the Securities and Exchange Commission’s (SEC) Staff Accounting Bulletin (SAB) No. 121 om Thursday, May 16. The bill was passed with substantial bipartisan support, receiving a 60-38 vote in the Senate and earlier approval from the House.
 
SAB 121, implemented in 2022, mandated digital asset custodians to list digital assets as liabilities on their balance sheets, a requirement widely criticized within the crypto community. Critics argue that this regulation unfairly treats customer-owned digital assets as the custodian’s liabilities, thereby necessitating equivalent cash reserves to offset these “liabilities.”
 
Why Yesterday’s Vote Is A Game-Changer For Crypto
 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aussie Frontman of BitConnect Pleads Guilty]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7421e03c6f</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/aussie-frontman-of-bitconnect-pleads-guilty/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T06:01:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BitConnect’s national promoter in Australia, John Bigatton, pled guilty to his role in promoting the scam after three and a half years of his indictment. He promoted the fraudulent cryptocurrency scheme on social media, hosted seminars across the country, and had face-to-face meetings with victims, persuading them to invest in the scheme.
Bigatton pled guilty to a criminal charge of offering unlicensed financial services before the Sydney District Court on 16 May and will receive his sentence on 5 July. He is facing a monetary penalty as well as jail time of up to two years.
A $2.4 Billion Crypto Scam
BitConnect was one of the largest cryptocurrency scams, duping investors of about US$2.4 billion globally. The scheme lured victims with absurdly high fixed interest rates.
As the Australian …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arnab Shome</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Restaking?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7421d4830c</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/what-is-restaking/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T04:16:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The concept of restaking introduces a groundbreaking way for people to utilize their staked cryptocurrency across various protocols simultaneously. This not only boosts reward potential but also significantly enhances the security and scalability of blockchain networks, benefiting the entire crypto ecosystem. Introduction to restaking A common occurrence In the rapidly evolving world of blockchain technology […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Sencil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Absent Since FTX 2022 Downfall, Sam Trabucco Breaks Silence With Letter Of Endorsement]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7421d627e3</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/absent-ftx-collapse-sam-trabucco-breaks-silence/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T04:01:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent development, Sam Trabucco, a key figure in Sam Bankman-Fried’s inner circle, has resurfaced after his absence from the public eye following the collapse of crypto exchange FTX in late 2022. 
 
According to Bloomberg, Trabucco has come forward to support Ryan Salame, another former FTX executive who awaits sentencing for his involvement in the platform’s downfall.
 
Sam Trabucco’s First Communication Since FTX Bankruptcy
 
Trabucco’s endorsement of Salame was expressed in a letter describing Salame as the “funniest, most passionate, most supportive friend” he has ever had. The letter, made public as part of court filings on Wednesday, marks Trabucco’s first communication since the days leading up to FTX’s bankruptcy in November 2022.
 
 
Formerly serving as the co-chief executiv…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Block Subsidiary, TBD, Partners With Chipper Cash for Quicker, More Affordable Remittances]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7421dcd62c</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/block-subsidiary-tbd-partners-with-chipper-cash-for-quicker-more-affordable-remittances/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T02:55:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TBD, a subsidiary of Block, owned by Jack Dorsey, has formed a partnership with Chipper Cash, an Africa-focused fintech company. This partnership aims to expedite consumer remittances and make them more affordable. According to a statement, Chipper Cash plans to use the decentralized exchange protocol of TBD. This will enable trusted transactions that comply with […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miners Under Distress: The Bullish Signal You Can’t Ignore]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7421de75fb</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-miner-price-electrical-cost-historically/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T02:38:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data suggests the Bitcoin “Miner Price” metric has fallen under the BTC Electrical Cost. Here’s what happened next the last few times.
 
Bitcoin Miner Price Has Declined Below Electrical Cost For Fifth Time Ever
 
In a new post on X, Capriole Investments founder Charles Edwards has pointed out a development that has recently occurred in the situation of the Bitcoin miners.
 
There are two relevant indicators here: Electrical Cost and Miner Price. The first measures the total daily cost that miners have to incur in electricity bills to mine 1 BTC.
 
 
The second one, the Miner Price, keeps track of the revenue that 1 BTC provides to the miners. This cohort earns their mining revenue through two modes: the block rewards and the transaction fees.
 
The former is paid out in BTC at a …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Legendary Investor Tim Draper Leads Bitcoin Lending Protocol Zest’s $3.5 Million Seed Round]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7421dbb486</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/legendary-investor-tim-draper-leads-bitcoin-lending-protocol-zests-3-5-million-seed-round/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T01:44:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Draper Associates, the VC firm led by the legendary investor Tim Draper, has led the $3.5 million seed round of Zest Protocol, a Stacks-based Bitcoin lending market. The round, which also had the participation of Binance Labs, Flow Traders, Trust Machines, and others, seeks to allow bitcoin holders to put their capital to use using […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum L2 Eclipse Appoints New CEO Amid Sexual Misconduct Allegations]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7421c70359</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-l2-eclipse-appoints-new-ceo-amid-sexual-misconduct-allegations/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T01:09:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neel Somani, Founder of Ethereum Layer-2 Blockchain Eclipse, has been replaced as Chief Executive Officer (CEO) due to accusations of sexual misconduct. Eclipse Labs announced Vijay Chetty, the company’s Chief Growth office (CGO), as the new CEO, taking over Somani’s responsibilities.
 
 
Ethereum L2 Eclipse Changes Leadership
 
Eclipse Labs is a software firm that “contributed to developing the first Ethereum layer-2 using the Solana Virtual Machine (SVM).” Per Neel Somani, “Eclipse is built to be Ethereum’s fastest layer-2, leveraging the best pieces of the modular stack available today.”
 
On Thursday, Eclipse Labs revealed that Vijay Chetty would be “effective immediately” elevated from his CGO position to become the company’s CEO. The new appointment came due to the “departure” of Som…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rubmar Garcia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI Will Mix ‘Authentic’ Reddit Content Into Its AI Training Data]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231160</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231160/openai-ai-training-reddit-content-deal"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T00:49:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reddit stock spiked on the news while critics of the social discussion platform predicted AI bias would get worse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Juno Addresses Banking Service Disruption — ‘This Is Outside Our Control’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7421c183b9</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/juno-addresses-banking-service-disruption-this-is-outside-our-control/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T00:43:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Juno Finance acknowledges the disruption in banking services and is collaborating with its brokerage and banking service providers, Synapse and Evolve Bank & Trust, to restore full service as soon as possible. Juno is a financial platform that integrates checking and savings accounts with cryptocurrency trading. “Currently, Evolve Bank & Trust has frozen all card […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morgan Stanley’s Bitcoin ETF Position Exposed: Filing Discloses $270 Million In Holdings]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7421ccf4cd</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/morgan-stanleys-bitcoin-etf-position-exposed/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T00:08:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent filing with the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), Morgan Stanley, the American multinational investment bank and financial services company, disclosed its substantial investments in the newly approved Bitcoin ETF market. 
 
The bank’s filing revealed holdings in two prominent Bitcoin exchange-traded funds: Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) and Ark Invest’s ETF.
 
Morgan Stanley’s Multi-Million Dollar Bet
 
According to Fintel data, Morgan Stanley purchased 31,712 shares of Ark’s 21Shares ETF (ARKB), while also allocating an impressive $269 million to the Grayscale ETF. This significant investment propelled Morgan Stanley into the top 20 list of Ark’s ETF investors and established it as the third-largest holder of GBTC ETF shares.
 
 
These developments come on the heels…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Can Detect Sarcasm With Help From ‘Friends’?—Yeah, Right!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231125</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231125/sarcasm-detector-ai-trained-on-tv-research-paper"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T23:55:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trained in part on TV sitcoms, researchers tout a new AI-powered tool that mixes voice input and emoji output to identify sarcasm with 75% accuracy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sony Puts Over 700 AI Firms on Blast Over Music Copyright Violations]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231115</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231115/sony-ai-training-declaration-700-tech-companies-on-notice"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T23:27:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The global music industry giant represents top artists that have already seen AI-generated knockoffs, from Michael Jackson to Celine Dion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOJ’s Unlawful Interpretation Threatens Bitcoin and Crypto Innovation, Lawmakers Warn]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7421c981d5</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/dojs-unlawful-interpretation-threatens-bitcoin-and-crypto-innovation-lawmakers-warn/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T23:23:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two U.S. senators have criticized the Department of Justice (DOJ)’s new interpretation of “money transmission,” which extends requirements to non-custodial software, citing concerns over its impact on crypto networks and financial innovation. “I’m concerned the DOJ’s interpretation would treat software developers as criminals for merely writing and publishing code used by others,” one of the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analyst Says Dogecoin Is Set To Breakout: How This Could Trigger Another Meme Coin Mania]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7421cb3abd</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-meme-coin-mania/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T23:07:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin is once again seeing an upside following the Bitcoin recovery above $66,000, which, in turn, triggered a broader crypto market recovery. Crypto analyst Crypto Scient expects this bullishness to continue going forward and eventually lead to the start of another meme coin mania.
 
Dogecoin Set To Kickstart Meme Coin Mania
 
Presently, the Dogecoin price is not as bullish as expected since it continues to struggle to break out of $0.15. However, it has not eroded expectations for the meme coin as crypto analysts continue to predict that its price still has room to rally.
 
 
 
 
Crypto Scient is the latest in the long line of analysts who believe this, expecting the meme coin to flip bullish at some point. As he explains, once the Dogecoin price flips bullish, it’ll trigger the start…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Did DeGods Leave Solana for Ethereum? 'I Was Just Being a Pussy', Says Founder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231123</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231123/why-degods-leave-solana-ethereum-being-pussy-founder"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T23:06:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once the top Solana NFT project, DeGods has faced ample challenges and criticism since bridging away. The founder addressed it all head-on.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erika Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$25M Sophisticated Ethereum Blockchain Exploit Leads to Arrests in US]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7421b14797</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/25m-sophisticated-ethereum-blockchain-exploit-leads-to-arrests-in-us/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T22:14:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Department of Justice (DOJ) has indicted two brothers for wire fraud and money laundering. They allegedly exploited the Ethereum blockchain to steal $25 million in cryptocurrency within 12 seconds. Using sophisticated techniques, they manipulated transactions and concealed their identities. If convicted, each faces up to 20 years in prison for each count. DOJ […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Canada’s Self-Proclaimed ‘Crypto King’ Faces Fraud And Money Laundering Charges – Details]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7421b25897</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/canada-proclaimed-crypto-king-faces-fraud-money/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T22:04:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aiden Pleterski, known in the crypto community as the “Crypto King,” and his associate Colin Murphy have been formally charged with serious financial offenses.
 
These charges emerged from an extensive joint investigation, Project Swan, conducted by the Durham Regional Police Service (DRPS) and the Ontario Securities Commission (OSC).
 
The investigation focused on allegations of fraud and money laundering centered in Ontario, particularly in Whitby and Oshawa, the respective residences of Pleterski and Murphy.
 
 
Investigation Details And Public Advisory
 
The authorities have levied multiple charges against Pleterski, including a fraud charge for over $5,000, laundering the proceeds of crime, and breaching a court order from May 14, 2024.
 
Given the gravity of these charges, Pleterski …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GTA 6 Preview: Everything You Need to Know About the New Grand Theft Auto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154049</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154049/grand-theft-auto-6-release-date-rumors-leaks-news"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T22:01:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATE: Rockstar Games has narrowed the release window for GTA 6. Here's when we'll be able to play the next Grand Theft Auto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin,Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Bitcoin Ponzi Scheme Paradox]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7421bc910d</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/guides/the-bitcoin-ponzi-scheme-paradox"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T21:45:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Ponzi scheme" has become a byword for all manner of financial frauds and monetary scams. When a rapid six month collapse erased $2T (trillion) from crypto market capitalization in 2022, mainstream media outlets were quick to again label cryptocurrencies, including Bitcoin, Ponzi schemes.
Writing in the Chinese People's Daily online edition, Shan Zhiguang and He Yifan, representing the Chinese Blockchain-based Services Network (BSN), claimed:

Ever since Satoshi Nakamoto released "Bitcoin: A Peer-to-Peer Electronic Cash System" in 2008, leading to the official birth of Bitcoin, the debate surrounding virtual currency (Cryptocurrency) has never stopped for a moment. [. . .] In its essence, the author believes that virtual currency is undoubtedly the largest Ponzi scheme in human history.

C…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Iain Davis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Jenndefer Became a Crypto Twitter Main Character via 'Fantasy Top']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231097</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231097/how-jenndefer-crypto-twitter-main-character-fantasy-top"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T21:29:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jennifer "Jenndefer" Duong has a brighter spotlight thanks to Fantasy Top and her content around Ethereum layer-2 network Blast. Here's her story.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erika Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden Order to Halt China-Tied Bitcoin Mine Beside Nuke Base Came as U.S. Firm Just Bought it]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7421bee866</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/05/16/biden-order-to-halt-china-tied-bitcoin-mine-beside-nuke-base-came-as-us-firm-just-bought-it/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T21:26:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[President Biden's emergency order to halt the Chinese-tied mining on the doorstep of a nuclear-missile base hit days after mining giant CleanSpark struck a deal to buy the property.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton, Aoyon Ashraf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Andrew Tate Plans to Invest Big in Bitcoin, Leaving Fiat Completely]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7421bf9dd6</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/andrew-tate-plans-to-invest-big-in-bitcoin-leaving-fiat-completely/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T21:21:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Andrew Tate, a British-American social media personality and former professional kickboxer, has announced a plan to invest significantly in bitcoin, expressing frustration with banks and their scams. “I’m about to leave fiat completely,” he stressed. “I’m done with the banks. I’m done with their money. Done with the scams.” Andrew Tate Plans to Shift ‘100M’ […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Meme Coin Marketplace Pump.fun Suffers $80 Million Exploit]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7421b8c434</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/solana-meme-coin-marketplace-pump-fun-suffers-80-million-exploit/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T21:11:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pump.fun, a Solana-based marketplace and deployment tool for meme coins, has acknowledged suffering an exploit dealing with the bonding curve contracts in its platform. While the protocol is still investigating the matter, it reported that “the TVL in the protocol right now is safe,” as it has upgraded the contracts to deal with the attack […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pump.fun Attacker Says He Wanted to 'Kill' Solana Meme Coin Launcher]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231099</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231099/pump-fun-attacker-wanted-kill-solana-meme-coin-launcher"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T20:51:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A purported former Pump.fun employee drained an estimated $2 million worth of Solana on Thursday. Here's why he did it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alameda's Sam Trabucco Resurfaces to Defend FTX Exec Ahead of Sentencing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231089</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231089/sam-trabucco-alameda-ryan-salame-ftx-sentencing"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T19:50:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trabucco said Salame was his “best friend” and deserves a “fair” punishment. Salame's lawyers are seeking no more than 18 months imprisonment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop Bull Roaring Kitty Is the 'Nihilist’s Warren Buffett', Says Hedge Fund Founder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231087</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231087/gamestop-bull-roaring-kitty-is-the-nihilists-warren-buffett-says-hedge-fund-founder"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T19:19:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People tribally follow both Warren Buffet and Roaring Kitty, Stratos founder Rennick Palley says—even though they’re polar opposites.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Notcoin’ Trading Volume Tops $1 Billion in 2024's Biggest Gaming Token Drop]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231080</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231080/notcoin-trading-1-billion-2024-biggest-gaming-token"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T18:45:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram-based game Notcoin dropped over 80 billion tokens to some 35 million players in an airdrop via The Open Network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Senate Votes to Kill SEC Anti-Crypto Policy—But Biden Plans to Veto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231075</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231075/senate-votes-kill-sec-anti-crypto-policy-biden-plans-veto"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T18:19:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Senate passed a resolution to rescind a SEC policy targeting banks that offer crypto services, with 12 Democrats joining Republicans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward,Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana, Ethereum Meme Coins Dip as GameStop Buzz Cools]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231049</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231049/solana-ethereum-meme-coins-dip-gamestop-buzz-cools"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T17:24:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The GameStop tribute coin GME and other Solana and Ethereum meme coins are sliding Thursday as the meme stock craze loses steam.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Do A Little With  Roger Dickerman]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/F6mt1fXu/we-do-a-little-with-roger-dickerman</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/F6mt1fXu/we-do-a-little-with-roger-dickerman"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T14:38:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We dive into Roger’s background in trading and fitness, his love of art, founding Artifex and 24 Hours of Art, the power of routines, and so much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop and AMC Plunge as Roaring Kitty Meme Stock Craze Fades]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231013</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231013/gamestop-amc-plunge-meme-stock-craze-fades"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T14:25:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Popular meme stocks GameStop and AMC fell sharply after U.S. markets opened on Thursday, trading 15% lower than their previous close.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a GameStop Options Trader Made 4,800% Profit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231000</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231000/how-gamestop-options-trader-made-4800-profit"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T13:20:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In less than a month, a GameStop whale pocketed $44 million thanks to the return of meme influencer Roaring Kitty.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mika Breaks Down Solana Congestion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/5lkvPCM1/mika-breaks-down-solana-congestion</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/5lkvPCM1/mika-breaks-down-solana-congestion"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T10:12:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rug Radio Creator and crypto influencer Mika explains what happened during Solana's Q1 2024 network congestion through Kraken's Learn Center.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF Inflows Top $303 Million, Buoyed by Fidelity and GBTC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230984</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230984/bitcoin-etf-inflows-top-303-million-buoyed-by-fidelity-and-gbtc"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T10:01:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. spot Bitcoin ETF inflows hit a two-week high of $303 million as the price of Bitcoin surged beyond $66,000.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bounces Past $66,000 as Inflation Slows in the US]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230985</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230985/bitcoin-above-66000-inflation-slows-in-us"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T09:35:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["US CPI numbers triggered a break out of the range across risk assets," Singapore firm QCP Capital wrote about the recent BTC rally.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oasys Expands Crypto Gaming Presence in Japan With SBI’s NFT Market]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230963</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230963/oasys-expands-crypto-gaming-presence-in-japan-with-sbis-nft-market"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T01:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gaming giants Ubisoft and Bandai Namco are building on Oasys, and now it’s making inroads in Japan via the SBINFT Market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Self-Custody Enshrined As a Right In Oklahoma]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230962</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230962/bitcoin-self-custody-right-law-mining-oklahoma"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T00:33:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A novel crypto bill protects citizens’ rights to hold, spend, and mine Bitcoin—as long as they do it quietly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI Loses Two More Leaders—What Does That Mean for AI Safety?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230945</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230945/open-ai-executive-departures-ai-safety"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T00:06:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ilya Sutskever and Jan Leike left the company yesterday, hours after the GPT-4o launch, Andrej Karpathy departed in February. All were focused on developing responsible AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop Bull Roaring Kitty Keeps Sharing Movie Memes—What's He Telling Us?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230894</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230894/gamestop-bull-roaring-kitty-movie-memes-whats-he-telling-us"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T23:35:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We broke down 10 of Roaring Kitty’s film and television references in his recent Twitter spree. How do they relate back to GameStop?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Things to Know Ahead of the ‘Notcoin’ Token Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230940</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230940/5-things-know-ahead-notcoin-token-launch"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T22:12:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When is the NOT token going live? What’s next for Notcoin? Should you stake your tokens? Here’s a final primer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin, Bitcoin Pump as GameStop Rally Cools]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230914</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230914/dogecoin-bitcoin-doge-btc-gamestop-rally"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T21:20:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the wake of a meme stock and meme coin frenzy, old-school cryptocurrencies are doing remarkably well.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Layer-2 Network Blast Reveals Airdrop Details]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230927</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230927/ethereum-layer-2-network-blast-reveals-airdrop-details"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T21:08:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Blast airdrop finally has a firm date, but it’s later than expected. More Ethereum tokens will be handed out as a make-good, however.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hedge Fund Nabbed Millions of GameStop, AMC Shares Before Meme Stocks Skyrocketed]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230901</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230901/hedge-fund-gme-amc-shares-before-meme-stock-surge"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T20:22:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Renaissance Technologies portfolio also included Bitcoin ETF shares, but the meme stocks saw eye-popping gains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood Boasts $5 Billion One-Day Trading Volume In GameStop Frenzy]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230872</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230872/robinhood-5-billion-one-day-trading-gamestop-gme-rally"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T18:52:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The trading app went offline overnight for upgrades to accommodate the rush of activity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is GameStop Trader Roaring Kitty Actually Back—Or Are We Being Punked?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230885</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230885/is-gamestop-trader-roaring-kitty-really-back"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T18:35:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The meme stock influencer’s apparent return to Twitter has fueled billions of dollars worth of stock and crypto pumps. But are the posts really from Keith Gill?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Notcoin? The Telegram-Based Game, NOT Token, and Future Plans]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=223640</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-notcoin-telegram-based-game-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T17:44:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATE: The NOT token is launching on Thursday, May 16. Get up to speed on the viral Telegram-based game before then.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery,Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vanguard's New CEO Is Big on Bitcoin—Will the Wall Street Giant Embrace BTC ETFs?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230871</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230871/vanguard-new-ceo-big-bitcoin-wall-street-giant-etfs"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T17:17:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Experts believe the new hire—who helped launch BlackRock's spot Bitcoin ETF—may change Vanguard's approach to crypto funds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feds Arrest Crypto Bros for 'Attacking Ethereum' With MEV Exploit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230874</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230874/feds-arrest-crypto-bros-attacking-ethereum-mev-exploit"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T16:35:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two brothers have been charged with allegedly "attacking Ethereum" via a MEV exploit that let them swipe $25 million within seconds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward,Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Game 'Nyan Heroes' Reveals Token Launch Amid Play-to-Airdrop Push]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230848</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230848/solana-game-nyan-heroes-token-launch-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T15:29:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overwatch-style shooter Nyan Heroes will launch its NYAN token via Bybit next week, with airdrop details coming soon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop Crashed 30%. Is the Roaring Kitty Rally Over?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230846</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230846/gamestop-crashed-30-roaring-kitty-rally-over"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T14:54:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meme stocks that surged after the influencer’s apparent return online took a beating as markets opened on Wednesday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Card Battler ‘Cross the Ages’ Launches CTA Token, Raises $3.5 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230840</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230840/ethereum-card-battler-cross-ages-cta-token"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T14:35:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Previously backed by Ubisoft and Square Enix, Cross the Ages expands its crypto offerings with a new CTA token amid a fresh fundraise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mika Explains the Bitcoin Halving]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/f9rUBkUS/mika-explains-the-bitcoin-halving</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/f9rUBkUS/mika-explains-the-bitcoin-halving"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T10:08:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rug Radio Creator and crypto influencer Mika explains the recent Bitcoin halving and how you can build your understanding through Kraken's Learn Center.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Neighbor Alice Season 1 Beta Goes Live]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/sGfYcHuB/my-neighbor-alice-season-1-beta-goes-live</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/sGfYcHuB/my-neighbor-alice-season-1-beta-goes-live"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T09:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rug Radio Creator Orangie plays the new season of multiplayer builder-game My Neighbor Alice and tries out all its features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Leads The Bounce]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QoXLhFzb/solana-leads-the-bounce</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QoXLhFzb/solana-leads-the-bounce"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T11:06:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto up despite ETF outflow, SOL outperforms. HK ETFs also see another net daily outflow. SOL flips ETH again in 24hr DEX volume. SOL revenue now 50% of ETH. Bitcoin above $1m by 2030: Dorsey. Bitcoin & Kucoin get license in India. Kraken tries to get SEC case dismissed. Stand with Crypto sets up election war chest. VIP customers make up two thirds of Binance volume. NOT to launch on Binance & OKX. TON up 20%, speculation it will be listed after NOT. Securitize & BlackRock look to launch on ARB. Franklin Templeton calls for ‘Base season’. EIGEN claims go live today, will be un-transferable. Eclipse founder leaves after harassment claims.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Manhattan’s Newest On-Chain Fashion Store: 9dcc]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Oyjyb2JX/inside-manhattans-newest-on-chain-fashion-store-9dcc</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Oyjyb2JX/inside-manhattans-newest-on-chain-fashion-store-9dcc"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T20:25:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At NFT NYC, Decrypt’s Sander Lutz explored the on-chain fashion brand’s latest pop-up, and spoke to its founder Gmoney about 9dcc’s future expansion plans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BTC Sinks Lower]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rUBpJmbc/btc-sinks-lower</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rUBpJmbc/btc-sinks-lower"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T19:54:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HK ETF volumes disappoint at $11M, crypto sinks. US ETFs see another $52M outflow, 4th straight day. EigenLayer FUD after 5% non-transferable airdrop. EigenLayer also geoblocks USA for claims. 5K+ withdrawals after EigenLayer announcement. Microstrategy bought another $8M BTC in April. Miner revenue drops to 2023 lows. Consensys vs SEC litigation will take years: Cowen. SEC had been investigating ETH for a year. Gensler may have misled Congress with ETH stance.KMNO hits $363M on launch. Decentralised Rune airdrop opens at $102M. Friend Tech airdrop delayed until Thursday. NFTfi airdrop claim today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Very Red Week For Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XVGCQVOH/a-very-red-week-for-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XVGCQVOH/a-very-red-week-for-crypto"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T19:54:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Majors hit locals lows, break key support levels. Liquidations hit $420M, funding remains neutral. ETFs saw $344M withdrawals in April. CZ gets 4-month jail sentence. FTX sells $232M locked SOL at ‘around $100’. Final integration of SOL Firedancer ‘well underway’. SOL, DOGE, XRP open interest down 51% in a month. BlackRock BUIDL largest tokenised treasury fund. Uniswap integrates with Robinhood connect. Stablecoin bill may be coming very soon. Gensler lied to Congress: McHenry. KSI steps back from crypto trading. Coinbase supports Lightning network. BCH creator arrested in Spain. EigenLayer sees 12K queued withdrawals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Full Send]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zCrCMabk/solana-full-send</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zCrCMabk/solana-full-send"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T19:51:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SOL leads majors higher, DEX volume flips ETH. ETH burn rate hits yearly low. BTC needs to reach $67k for a ‘higher high’. Robinhood receives Wells Notice from SEC. Only 10% of stablecoin transactions are real: Visa. May 15th will see corporate filings of BTC purchases. Hayes continues to OTC buy PENDLE. Cartier arrested for USDT money laundering. ENA up 20% on rumours of integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Memecoin Bounce]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yw5MtFvY/memecoin-bounce</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yw5MtFvY/memecoin-bounce"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T19:38:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto volatile but bounces after dovish Fed speech. ETFs see record $563m outflow. BlackRock ETF sees first outflow in 77 days. BlackRock expects more institutions to buy BTC. BNP bank buys BlackRock ETF. BTC continues to sit below STH average cost. Coinbase earnings today. Tether made $4.5bn profit in Q1. MicroStrategy building identity protocol on Ordinals. Dorsey’s Block Inc investigated in US. BlackRock leads investment in RWA firm. STX Nakamoto upgrade delayed by 8 weeks. LayerZero 1st snapshot taken ahead of airdrop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Do A Little With Mike Demarais]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ajrh0oiK/we-do-a-little-with-mike-demarais</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ajrh0oiK/we-do-a-little-with-mike-demarais"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T15:11:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mike dropped knowledge bombs from years of building in the trenches alongside some deep cuts on the early Williamsburg crypto mafia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eth Rally Fails]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Gj7TMrbP/eth-rally-fails</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Gj7TMrbP/eth-rally-fails"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T12:45:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto falls, ETH/BTC rally again marks mini sell-off. Yen carry-trade implosion linked to worries. ETH gas fees hit 6-month lows. 3rd straight week of institutional outflows. Slowing BTC ETF flows are just a pause: Bernstein. BTC now on track for 5 red weeks in a row. BTC may have topped, could hit $35k: Brandt. ETFs may become big sellers: Bianco. Consensys list 4 reasons ETH isn’t a security. Rumours continue to grow of EigenLayer airdrop. Perp DEX volumes continue fall, GMX underperforms. Wallets begin to block US users after Samourai case. WLD in reported partnership talks with OpenAI. Large unlocks this week for SUI, PYTH & MEME.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Sasha Stiles’ Experiential, AI-Infused NFT Drop with Bang & Olufsen]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/6Vi2IgYj/inside-sasha-stiles-experiential-ai-infused-nft-drop-with-bang-olufsen</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/6Vi2IgYj/inside-sasha-stiles-experiential-ai-infused-nft-drop-with-bang-olufsen"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T22:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At a launch party for the collection in New York’s SoHo neighborhood, the artist broke down her latest art experiment, “Four Core Texts,” with Decrypt’s Sander Lutz.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interview: How 'Notcoin' Will Evolve After the NOT Token Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PprnGP14/interview-how-notcoin-will-evolve-after-the-not-token-launch</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PprnGP14/interview-how-notcoin-will-evolve-after-the-not-token-launch"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Open Builders founder Sasha Plotvinov speaks with Decrypt's Sander Lutz at Token 2049 Dubai about how he envisions Notcoin's expansion and evolution after the token drop—into something akin to the "Netflix of social, viral games."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Magic Runes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IGWg0R64/magic-runes</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IGWg0R64/magic-runes"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T13:59:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC stables at $66k, liquidations in narrow range. BTC funding again turns negative in bullish sign. ETFs net inflow after Grayscale moves to lower fees. BTC demand 5x vs supply post-halving: Bitfinex. SOL congestion issue now largely solved. Two SEC lawyers resign after ‘gross abuse of power’. Ripple fights to lower $2bn SEC fine. SAFE trades at $2.8bn FDV after OKX lists. MANEKI hits $150m on first day, China memes pump. Memecoins are ‘black hole you can’t ignore’. DeGods up 20%, may switch back to SOL. Magic Eden launches Runes platform ahead of time.  Louis Vuitton gifts Pharrell jacket to NFT holders. Melania Trump launches necklace with SOL NFTs. Hoodie Punk trades for $620K.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Luxury Watches, Designer Shoes Will Soon Trade Like NFTs: Arianee CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/CSNQG2md/luxury-watches-designer-shoes-will-soon-trade-like-nfts-arianee-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/CSNQG2md/luxury-watches-designer-shoes-will-soon-trade-like-nfts-arianee-ceo"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arianee CEO Pierre-Nicolas Hurstel sat down with Rug Radio founder Farokh and Decrypt’s Sander Lutz at NFT Paris to discuss everything from the future of on-chain luxury to the secret hack to finding the best restaurants in France.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notcoin's Co-Creator Explains the Game's Token Delay—And When to Expect NOT Now]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/7Zx33xo5/notcoins-co-creator-explains-the-games-token-delayand-when-to-expect-not-now</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/7Zx33xo5/notcoins-co-creator-explains-the-games-token-delayand-when-to-expect-not-now"/>
        <updated>2024-04-22T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Notcoin co-creator Sasha Plotvinov spoke with Decrypt's Sander Lutz at Token 2049 Dubai to discuss why the NOT token launch was pushed back from the original 4/20 target, when to expect the listing, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TON’s Justin Hyun Breaks Down The Importance of USDT Coming to Telegram]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ODQI6ACA/tons-justin-hyun-breaks-down-the-importance-of-usdt-coming-to-telegram</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ODQI6ACA/tons-justin-hyun-breaks-down-the-importance-of-usdt-coming-to-telegram"/>
        <updated>2024-04-19T10:14:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Token 2049 in Dubai, The Open Network’s director of investments sat down with Decrypt’s Sander Lutz to discuss what he sees as the game-changing integration of USDT onto TON, and his plans for getting Telegram’s 900 million users to start using crypto in the immediate future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Influencer Ansem Explains His Meme Coin Thesis and Why He’s Bullish on Bitcoin Runes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/u9DHFoK0/crypto-influencer-ansem-explains-his-meme-coin-thesis-and-why-hes-bullish-on-bitcoin-runes</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/u9DHFoK0/crypto-influencer-ansem-explains-his-meme-coin-thesis-and-why-hes-bullish-on-bitcoin-runes"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T21:56:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ansem, the crypto trader who's amassed a sizable following on the back of meme coin Dogwifhat (WIF) and other calls, chats with Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz at Token 2049 Dubai about his meme coin thesis, why he's bullish on Bitcoin Runes, and what he sees ahead for the crypto markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Sander Lutz Braves the Dubai Floods for a Crypto Conference]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/mtjVHGa3/decrypts-sander-lutz-braves-the-dubai-floods-for-a-crypto-conference</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/mtjVHGa3/decrypts-sander-lutz-braves-the-dubai-floods-for-a-crypto-conference"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T21:33:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz reports from Dubai amid a historic storm that flooded the famed city, trudging through the streets to complete his essential task: Attending the Token 2049 crypto conference.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>