<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-02-23T21:12:38.401Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-02-23T21:12:38.401Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Goldman Sachs Economists Updated Their 2024 Interest Rate Cut Expectations: Pointed to This Month for the First Rate Cut! How Is Bitcoin Price Affected?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19275879/Goldman-Sachs-Economists-Updated-Their-2024-Interest-Rate-Cut-Expectations-Pointed-to-This-Month-for-the-First-Rate-Cut-How-Is-Bitcoin-Price-Affected</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19275879/Goldman-Sachs-Economists-Updated-Their-2024-Interest-Rate-Cut-Expectations-Pointed-to-This-Month-for-the-First-Rate-Cut-How-Is-Bitcoin-Price-Affected"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T21:05:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Goldman Sachs economists said they predicted the first interest rate cut would come in June. How will Bitcoin price be affected? Continue Reading: Goldman Sachs Economists Updated Their 2024 Interest Rate Cut Expectations: Pointed to This Month for the First Rate Cut! How Is Bitcoin Price Affected?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Digital Currency Group Alleges Bankruptcy Code Violations, Calls For Revamp Of NYAG And Genesis Settlement]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74db8ceba1</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/digital-currency-group-bankruptcy-code-violations/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T21:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a surprising twist, Digital Currency Group (DCG), the parent company of defunct crypto lender Genesis Capital, has contested the settlement agreement reached with the New York Attorney General’s (NYAG) office, citing alleged violations of the Bankruptcy Code. 
 
The legal saga, which saw the NYAG accusing Genesis and its collaborators of defrauding investors for over $3 billion, took an unexpected turn when DCG filed a court objection to the settlement.
 
Violation Of Bankruptcy Code? 
 
DCG’s objection, outlined in a recent court filing issued on Wednesday, revolves around the belief that the proposed settlement allows the Debtors (Genesis) to redistribute value from lower classes to preferred creditors, thereby violating the absolute priority rule. 
 
The objection argues that the New…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC seeks comments on Bitwise, Grayscale Bitcoin ETF options]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19275880/SEC-seeks-comments-on-Bitwise-Grayscale-Bitcoin-ETF-options</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19275880/SEC-seeks-comments-on-Bitwise-Grayscale-Bitcoin-ETF-options"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T21:04:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. SEC is seeking comments on a proposed rule change that would allow investors to trade options on Bitwise and Grayscale Bitcoin ETFs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX secures court approval to sell 8% Anthropic stake]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19275874/FTX-secures-court-approval-to-sell-8-Anthropic-stake</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19275874/FTX-secures-court-approval-to-sell-8-Anthropic-stake"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T21:02:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Defunct crypto exchange FTX has secured court approval to sell its stake in artificial intelligence (AI) startup Anthropic Holdings, potentially adding over $1 billion to its assets earmarked for repaying creditors. Delaware Bankruptcy Court Judge John Dorsey handed down the decision on Feb. 22,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking News: US Judge approves Binance’s $4.3B fine in plea deal]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19275875/Breaking-News-US-Judge-approves-Binances-43B-fine-in-plea-deal</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19275875/Breaking-News-US-Judge-approves-Binances-43B-fine-in-plea-deal"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T21:01:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Holdings Ltd., one of the world’s largest crypto exchanges, finds itself at the center of a landmark legal settlement in the United States. Recently, a federal judge has approved a plea deal that imposes a staggering $4.3 billion payment on Binance, marking one of the largest criminal...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Venture Capital Giant Andreessen Horowitz Pumps $100,000,000 Into Team Behind Ethereum Restaking Protocol]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19275867/Venture-Capital-Giant-Andreessen-Horowitz-Pumps-100000000-Into-Team-Behind-Ethereum-Restaking-Protocol</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19275867/Venture-Capital-Giant-Andreessen-Horowitz-Pumps-100000000-Into-Team-Behind-Ethereum-Restaking-Protocol"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T21:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Venture capital giant Andreessen Horowitz has invested $100 million in the development team behind EigenLayer, a restaking protocol built on Ethereum (ETH). Ali Yahya, a general partner at Andreessen Horowitz (also known as a16z), predicts that the EigenLayer will expand Ethereum’s capabilities....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Digital Currency Group Alleges Bankruptcy Code Violations, Calls For Revamp Of NYAG And Genesis Settlement]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19275873/Digital-Currency-Group-Alleges-Bankruptcy-Code-Violations-Calls-For-Revamp-Of-NYAG-And-Genesis-Settlement</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19275873/Digital-Currency-Group-Alleges-Bankruptcy-Code-Violations-Calls-For-Revamp-Of-NYAG-And-Genesis-Settlement"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T21:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a surprising twist, Digital Currency Group (DCG), the parent company of defunct crypto lender Genesis Capital, has contested the settlement agreement reached with the New York Attorney General’s (NYAG) office, citing alleged violations of the Bankruptcy Code. The legal saga, which saw the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Halving and BTC Price: Will This Time Be Different?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19275862/Bitcoin-Halving-and-BTC-Price-Will-This-Time-Be-Different</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19275862/Bitcoin-Halving-and-BTC-Price-Will-This-Time-Be-Different"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T20:59:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin is in a different place than it was four years ago, the last time the cryptocurrency underwent a halving. Here’s what you need to know.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nearly half of major airdrop tokens peak within two weeks: CoinGecko]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19275853/Nearly-half-of-major-airdrop-tokens-peak-within-two-weeks-CoinGecko</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19275853/Nearly-half-of-major-airdrop-tokens-peak-within-two-weeks-CoinGecko"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T20:58:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nearly half of the largest crypto airdrops have seen their peak values within the first two weeks of distribution, a Feb. 23 CoinGecko report shows. Specifically, 23 of the top 50 tokens distributed through airdrops, representing 46%, reached their highest prices during this period, highlighting...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Trader Updates Outlook on Bitcoin and Altcoins, Says Chainlink Could Explode by 123%]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19275839/Crypto-Trader-Updates-Outlook-on-Bitcoin-and-Altcoins-Says-Chainlink-Could-Explode-by-123</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19275839/Crypto-Trader-Updates-Outlook-on-Bitcoin-and-Altcoins-Says-Chainlink-Could-Explode-by-123"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T20:55:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A widely followed crypto analyst is taking a look at altcoins as Bitcoin (BTC) stumbles. Crypto trader Michaël van de Poppe tells his 695,000 followers on the social media platform X that Chainlink (LINK) could potentially reach $40 in the next few months, a huge 123% increase. “Chainlink had...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Now Move Brave Browser Rewards On-Chain With a Solana Wallet]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19275834/You-Can-Now-Move-Brave-Browser-Rewards-On-Chain-With-a-Solana-Wallet</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19275834/You-Can-Now-Move-Brave-Browser-Rewards-On-Chain-With-a-Solana-Wallet"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T20:50:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The privacy-focused, crypto-savvy web browser now allows BAT transfers to self-custody Solana wallets to streamline transactions and reduce fees.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a smart contract gets away with murder: A review of ‘The Oracle’]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19275838/How-a-smart-contract-gets-away-with-murder-A-review-of-The-Oracle</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19275838/How-a-smart-contract-gets-away-with-murder-A-review-of-The-Oracle"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T20:50:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re looking to learn more about how a blockchain oracle could potentially kill you,this is the book for you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Reddit’s IPO Filing Says About Crypto Regulation]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74db8f0de3</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2024/02/23/what-reddits-ipo-filing-says-about-crypto-regulation/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T20:47:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Of the Web 2 giants, the message board king is arguably most invested in crypto. Its filings to go public have interesting things to say about how a Silicon Valley company views digital asset regulation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Kuhn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Judge Signs Off on Binance's $4.3B Plea Deal With U.S. Prosecutors]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19275841/Judge-Signs-Off-on-Binances-43B-Plea-Deal-With-US-Prosecutors</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19275841/Judge-Signs-Off-on-Binances-43B-Plea-Deal-With-US-Prosecutors"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T20:44:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A federal judge approved the U.S. Department of Justice's $4.3 billion fine on Binance after the crypto exchange pleaded guilty to violating anti-money laundering laws last November.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Did Reddit Bet Its IPO On Bitcoin? 'Sounds Like A Stupid Decision,' Redditor Says]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19275840/Did-Reddit-Bet-Its-IPO-On-Bitcoin-Sounds-Like-A-Stupid-Decision-Redditor-Says</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19275840/Did-Reddit-Bet-Its-IPO-On-Bitcoin-Sounds-Like-A-Stupid-Decision-Redditor-Says"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T20:42:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reddit's recent strategic move to invest in Bitcoin (CRYPTO: BTC) and Ethereum (CRYPTO: read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Reddit’s IPO Filing Says About Crypto Regulation]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19275830/What-Reddits-IPO-Filing-Says-About-Crypto-Regulation</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19275830/What-Reddits-IPO-Filing-Says-About-Crypto-Regulation"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T20:40:16.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ronin Hacked Again? Here's What Happened to $9.7M]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19275817/Ronin-Hacked-Again-Heres-What-Happened-to-97M</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19275817/Ronin-Hacked-Again-Heres-What-Happened-to-97M"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T20:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Co-founders Jeff Zirlin and Aleksander Leonard Larsen confirmed the unauthorized transfer of ETH from a whale wallet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto miner ire over EIA survey bubbles over to the courtroom]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19275837/Crypto-miner-ire-over-EIA-survey-bubbles-over-to-the-courtroom</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19275837/Crypto-miner-ire-over-EIA-survey-bubbles-over-to-the-courtroom"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T20:34:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Texas Blockchain Council and Riot Platforms claims miners will be “irreparably harmed” by divulging data requested by the government agency]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin: How long-term holders could pull down BTC’s price]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19275810/Bitcoin-How-long-term-holders-could-pull-down-BTCs-price</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19275810/Bitcoin-How-long-term-holders-could-pull-down-BTCs-price"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T20:30:25.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Primed For Gargantuan Upsurge To $0.5 If This Happens]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19275806/Dogecoin-Primed-For-Gargantuan-Upsurge-To-05-If-This-Happens</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19275806/Dogecoin-Primed-For-Gargantuan-Upsurge-To-05-If-This-Happens"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T20:27:51.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$30 billion RIA Platform Carson Group Approves To Offer Spot Bitcoin ETFs To Clients]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19275798/30-billion-RIA-Platform-Carson-Group-Approves-To-Offer-Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-To-Clients</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19275798/30-billion-RIA-Platform-Carson-Group-Approves-To-Offer-Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-To-Clients"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T20:25:44.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Consolidates Post-Earnings Surge As Cathie Wood Offloads Stock: Will This Bull Flag Play Out?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19275825/Coinbase-Consolidates-Post-Earnings-Surge-As-Cathie-Wood-Offloads-Stock-Will-This-Bull-Flag-Play-Out</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19275825/Coinbase-Consolidates-Post-Earnings-Surge-As-Cathie-Wood-Offloads-Stock-Will-This-Bull-Flag-Play-Out"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T20:23:53.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Read Adam Back's Complete Emails with Bitcoin Creator Satoshi Nakamoto]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74db8a0952</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/technical/bitcoin-adam-backs-complete-emails-satoshi-nakamoto"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T20:22:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The full email correspondence between Hashcash inventor Adam Back and Bitcoin creator Satoshi Nakamoto is now public after being entered into the official court records in the U.K. this week. 
Detailed in the five emails below is the complete conversation between Nakamoto and Back, who was cited in the seminal Bitcoin white paper. In the emails, the two cryptography heavyweights can be seen for the first time discussing the work. 
Though Back has previously spoken publicly about the emails, hinting at the details of the conversation, and in particular how he neglected to read the white paper at first, the emails represent the first time that the full text has been made available.
Adam Back, a renowned figure in the cryptocurrency world, and the chief executive of Blockstream, has long been…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pete Rizzo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RIOT PLATFORMS AND TEXAS BITCOIN COUNCIL SEEK INJUCTION AGAINST EIA SURVEY]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74db8a0945</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/legal/miners-vs-the-eia-hearing-in-waco-texas"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T20:22:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today at 11:30a in Waco, Texas, the Texas Blockchain Council and Riot Platforms, Inc., asked a Federal District Judge Alan Albright for a temporary restraining order blocking the Energy Information Administration from enforcing their "emergency" survey.
At that hearing, the attorneys for the Government offered a voluntary declaration by EIA Administrator DeCarolis, offering a four-week pause on enforcement and collection. Judge Albright, recognizing that the Government's offer here was little more than an empty promise without some sort of enforcement mechanism, directed the Government to work with the Plaintiffs to craft a negotiated order that would fully bind the Government to:

Take down the survey for the agreed four-week period;
Provide notice that anyone who hasn't yet complied, that they don't need to comply right now; and
Provide an affirmation that any information which has been received so far, or which is received in the interim, shall be sequestered and not utilized by the Agency.

Also, this order will be National in scope, so every miner in the US is covered.
If the Government can't reach an agreement by 3pm Central today, the Judge indicated that he would issue a Temporary Restraining Order with the same effect as the above, but would accelerate the timetable to the permanent injunction hearing.
We'll know more in a few hours when the final order is entered, but it looks like for now at least, the EIA has been stalled in their (allegedly illegal) "emergency" data collection.
Here is a link to the case files.
This is a guest post by Colin Crossman. Opinions expressed are entirely their own and do not necessarily reflect those of BTC Inc or Bitcoin Magazine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Colin Crossman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Soaks In Over $607 Million Everyday, Will This 3X After Halving?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74db74352c</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-in-soaks-607-million-will-3x-before-halving/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T20:04:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Willy Woo, an on-chain Bitcoin (BTC) analyst, is sounding the bullish alarm, citing strong demand and dwindling supply as reasons for optimism. Taking to X, Woo noted that Bitcoin soaks in an average of $607 million daily as an asset in new investor demand. In comparison, only $46 million of new supply is being created through mining. 
 
Bitcoin Receives Over $607 Million In Value Everyday, What Happens After Halving?
 
The Bitcoin network is a proof-of-work platform reliant on miners for security and decentralization, rendering its transactions censorship-resistant and global. Though there are concerns about centralization, it appears that the broad network of miners holds more importance for the platform, explaining its colossal valuation. 
 
 
Miners are rewarded with 6.25 BTC after eve…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dalmas Ngetich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Freelance Marketplace Launches Where Users Get Paid In Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74db737e34</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/new-freelance-marketplace-launches-where-users-get-paid-in-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T19:07:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new development in the freelance industry has emerged with the launch of Plebwork, a dedicated marketplace where freelancers can earn Bitcoin for their work, according to a press release sent to Bitcoin Magazine. Launched today, Plebwork offers a unique platform for freelancers to connect with Bitcoin companies and receive payment directly into their Bitcoin wallets.

It’s 2024 and it’s time to earn #bitcoin for your work. pic.twitter.com/hLci3NBtBt
— Plebwork (@plebwork) February 23, 2024
  
  
  
Unlike traditional freelance platforms, Plebwork caters specifically to the Bitcoin community, providing a space where freelancers with expertise in Bitcoin-related skills can find part-time jobs with businesses operating in the Bitcoin space. Likewise, businesses seeking qualified part-time t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nik Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spot Bitcoin ETFs Surge to $14.6 Billion in BTC Holdings 43 Days Post-Launch]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74db7396a2</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/spot-bitcoin-etfs-surge-to-14-6-billion-in-btc-holdings-43-days-post-launch/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T19:07:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It has been 43 days since the debut of the spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) on the American stock market, and in this time, the nine newly launched bitcoin ETFs have accumulated 287,315 bitcoins, valued at approximately $14.6 billion. Leading the pack is Blackrock’s IBIT, boasting a staggering 126,950.12 bitcoins on its balance sheet. Bitcoin […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano Receives Nasty Blow As New Report Dubs It The King Of Dead Coins]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74db7c29c1</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/cardano-king-of-dead-coins/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T19:02:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recent report by AlphaQuest Research has listed Cardano as one of the top ecosystems with “dead coins,” highlighting the blockchain’s record number of failed cryptocurrency projects over the past few years. 
 
Cardano As Top Dead Coin Holder
 
Cryptocurrency research platform AlphaQuest, published a report spotlighting the leading categories of ecosystems featuring dead coins in 2024. According to the report, Cardano currently holds a prominent position as an ecosystem with one of the highest numbers of dead coins. 
 
 
AlphaQuest revealed that 74% of Cardano’s ecosystem projects have “become defunct.” In a similar vein, blockchain protocol, Terra Luna shares the spotlight with a matching 74% of failed crypto projects. 
 
The crypto company has outlined its criteria for determining what …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Satoshi Anticipated Bitcoin Energy Debate in Email Thread With Early Collaborators]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74db782f28</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2024/02/23/satoshi-anticipated-bitcoin-energy-debate-in-email-thread-with-early-collaborators/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T18:33:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Satoshi saw an irony in the debate between economic conservation and conservation in an email thread with an early collaborator Martii 'Sirius' Malmi.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Craig Wright Admits to Editing Bitcoin White Paper Presented in COPA Trial]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74db782f1b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/02/23/craig-wright-admits-to-editing-bitcoin-white-paper-presented-in-copa-trial/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T18:33:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[COPA's trial to find out whether or not Craig Wright is the pseudonymous creator of bitcoin Satoshi Nakamoto has completed its third week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camomile Shumba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GAIMIN Announces the World’s First L2 Gaming Blockchain on BNB Chain]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74db7bce99</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/gaimin-announces-the-worlds-first-l2-gaming-blockchain-on-bnb-chain/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T18:07:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GAIMIN, the world’s leading provider of DePIN (Decentralised Physical Infrastructure Networks) today announces the world’s first L2 blockchain focused on delivering Web3 technology and services to the gaming industry. The incorporation of Web3 technologies, such as blockchain, crypto currency based economies and owner retained NFTs within the gaming industry has been slow to develop, primarily […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Retail Traders Fuel February Crypto Rally, JPMorgan Analysis Shows]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74db645f75</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/retail-traders-fuel-february-crypto-rally-jpmorgan/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T18:03:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to a recent report from JPMorgan, it has come to light that retail traders played a pivotal role in driving the surge witnessed in the cryptocurrency market throughout February.
 
Retail Resurgence: Small-Scale Investors Propel Crypto Market Rally
 
The analysis conducted by JPMorgan’s research team, led by Managing Director Nikolaos Panigirtzoglou, revealed that the resurgence of “small-scale investors,” often referred to as ‘mom-and-pop’ traders, has been instrumental in propelling popular cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin to two-year peak this month.
 
 
This resurgence follows the market decline experienced in January, indicating renewed optimism among retail participants in the crypto space. The JPMorgan team noted:
 

We find that the retail impulse into crypto rebounded in …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling Liberty: Bitcoin's Tension Between Ideology and Adoption]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74db607818</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/scaling-liberty-bitcoins-tension-between-ideology-and-adoption"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T17:35:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since its inception over 15 years ago, Bitcoin has captured the imagination of libertarians, anarchists, and a variety of other advocates of individual liberty and financial sovereignty. To them, Bitcoin represented a revolutionary challenge to State-controlled money and authority. As such, it has come to symbolize a disruptive shift toward greater freedom and autonomy for individuals in modern society.
Yet as Bitcoin gains mainstream traction, there are more and more signs it may be shedding its revolutionary roots. The exponential growth in users and market value has corresponded with a dilution of the liberty-oriented ethos that initially defined the technology. In a future hyperbitcoinized world, will Bitcoin still embody the libertarian ideals that sparked so much excitement among its…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Matulef</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche Blockchain Faces Outage Amid Inscription Wave: AVA Labs Investigates]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74db6d020d</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/avalanche-blockchain-faces-outage-amid-inscription-wave-ava-labs-investigates/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T17:06:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Avalanche blockchain has encountered a disruption due to a “stall in block finalization.” AVA Labs’ co-founder, Kevin Sekniqi, suggested that the problem might stem from a recent surge in inscriptions. Avalanche Hits Snag as Block Finalization Stall Disrupts Service Avalanche (AVAX) is grappling with a service interruption, echoing challenges previously seen on the Solana […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken Fires Back At US SEC, Points To Legal Precedent]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74db6d77ee</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/kraken-respond-to-us-sec-points-to-legal-precedent/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T17:02:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a blow to the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), Kraken, the second largest cryptocurrency exchange in the US, has fired back at the agency regarding its lawsuit against the platform, citing a crucial aspect of Ripple’s case.
 
Kraken Responds to The US SEC 
 
Bill Morgan, a legal expert, shared the information concerning the lawsuit on the social media platform X (formerly Twitter) on Friday. “It is interesting how Kraken summarises and references a significant portion of the Ripple case,” Morgan stated. 
 
 
Morgan highlighted that Kraken bases its stance on the claim that the SEC has not been able to develop a direct connection between the issuers of certain coins, which the commission calls “crypto asset securities.” 
 
According to the summary of the SEC v. Rip…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Godspower Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CardanoGPT (CGI) Token Skyrockets Amid AI Crypto Frenzy, Urging Investors to Seize the Opportunity]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74db6b7e6f</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/cardanogpt-cgi-token-skyrockets-amid-ai-crypto-frenzy-urging-investors-to-seize-the-opportunity/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T16:25:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. In an electrifying surge that has captured the attention of the cryptocurrency world, CardanoGPT (CGI) witnessed a remarkable 40% increase in value within just 24 hours, following the unveiling of OpenAI’s groundbreaking Sora and a significant profit jump for Nvidia, a company that produces chips that most AI companies use. This surge positions […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analyst Says WIF Is Ready To Challenge Dogecoin And Shiba Inu With ‘Turbo Parabolic’ Rally]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74db573a10</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/wif-dogecoin-shiba-inu-parabolic/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T16:02:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto analyst Bluntz Capital recently provided a bullish narrative for the Dogwifhat (WIF) token. As part of his analysis, he suggested that the meme coin could go head-to-head with the foremost meme coins, Dogecoin (DOGE) and Shiba Inu (SHIB).
 
WIF To Go “Turbo Parabolic”
 
Bluntz hinted in an X (formerly Twitter) post that WIF’s next move to the upside could be the one that makes its price go “turbo parabolic.” He added that the meme coin would unlikely see any further pullback at the $0.50 resistance. From the accompanying chart the analyst shared, one could see that he was hinting at the meme coin hitting $1 when this parabolic move happened. 
 
 
Bluntz is known to be very bullish on the meme coin and has shared several technical analyses of the meme coin’s chart on his X platform. …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Lejilex vs. SEC, Crypto Goes on Offense in the Courts]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74db5c9981</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2024/02/23/in-lejilex-vs-sec-crypto-goes-on-offense-in-the-courts/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T15:30:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Texas-based crypto firm's new suit shows how the industry can use “impact litigation” to get regulatory clarity, lawyers Jake Chervinsky and Amanda Tuminelli write.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Chervinsky, Amanda Tuminelli</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Layer-1 Network Flare Raises $35M From Kenetic, Aves Lair]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74db5e2aea</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2024/02/23/layer-1-network-flare-raises-35m-from-kenetic-aves-lair/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T15:21:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Flare blockchain has raised $35 million in a private round that included investment from Kinetic, Aves Lair and others, according to a press release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Riot and Texas Blockchain Council Challenge US Government’s Bitcoin Mining Data Request in Court]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74db58d106</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/riot-and-texas-blockchain-council-challenge-us-governments-bitcoin-mining-data-request-in-court/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T15:04:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The publicly listed mining firm Riot Platforms and the Texas Blockchain Council have initiated legal proceedings against the U.S. Department of Energy (DOE) and other federal entities, aiming to obstruct what they deem an unauthorized data collection effort targeting the bitcoin mining industry. The legal battle underscores the escalating tension between bitcoin mining operations and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>