<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-07-23T14:12:18.257Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-07-23T14:12:18.257Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform, Do Kwon lawyers get creative, try to use Ripple ruling to dismiss their own suit]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18791018/Terraform-Do-Kwon-lawyers-get-creative-try-to-use-Ripple-ruling-to-dismiss-their-own-suit</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18791018/Terraform-Do-Kwon-lawyers-get-creative-try-to-use-Ripple-ruling-to-dismiss-their-own-suit"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform lawyers also asked the court overseeing the FTX case if they can issue subpoenas to gather wallet information in its case against the SEC]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Ripple Lawyer Likens Gensler to Flat-Earther in Stinging Crypto Critique]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18791012/Top-Ripple-Lawyer-Likens-Gensler-to-Flat-Earther-in-Stinging-Crypto-Critique</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18791012/Top-Ripple-Lawyer-Likens-Gensler-to-Flat-Earther-in-Stinging-Crypto-Critique"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T13:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stuart Alderoty, Ripple's top lawyer, likened SEC Chairman Gary Gensler to flat-earther in acerbic critique of his understanding of cryptocurrency industry]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Seeks Regulatory Nod, Applies For Crypto License In The UK]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18791009/Ripple-Seeks-Regulatory-Nod-Applies-For-Crypto-License-In-The-UK</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18791009/Ripple-Seeks-Regulatory-Nod-Applies-For-Crypto-License-In-The-UK"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T13:42:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After securing a major legal triumph against the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), Ripple, the blockchain payments firm, is now focusing on its expansion plans in Europe. Ripple’s move to apply for registration with the Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) and seek a payment institution...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Even if the SEC appealed, Ripple could win again, says pro-XRP lawyer John Deaton]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18790998/Even-if-the-SEC-appealed-Ripple-could-win-again-says-pro-XRP-lawyer-John-Deaton</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18790998/Even-if-the-SEC-appealed-Ripple-could-win-again-says-pro-XRP-lawyer-John-Deaton"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T13:39:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Renowned crypto lawyer John Deaton, who represents over 75,000 XRP holders, said on July 23 that an SEC appeal will not necessarily change the outcome of the Ripple ruling. In the ever-changing landscape of crypto regulations, the recent Ripple ruling has sparked hope and uncertainty for the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Americans bullish on cryptos despite growing regulatory concerns]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18790996/Americans-bullish-on-cryptos-despite-growing-regulatory-concerns</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18790996/Americans-bullish-on-cryptos-despite-growing-regulatory-concerns"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T13:30:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite the pessimism around regulatory oversight, Americans still find faith in the long-term prospects of cryptocurrencies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will the SEC’s Appeal in the Ripple-SEC Case Cause Trouble for XRP? Lawyer Answered]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18790977/Will-the-SECs-Appeal-in-the-Ripple-SEC-Case-Cause-Trouble-for-XRP-Lawyer-Answered</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18790977/Will-the-SECs-Appeal-in-the-Ripple-SEC-Case-Cause-Trouble-for-XRP-Lawyer-Answered"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T13:19:05.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk reveals why Dogecoin is his favorite cryptocurrency]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18790934/Elon-Musk-reveals-why-Dogecoin-is-his-favorite-cryptocurrency</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18790934/Elon-Musk-reveals-why-Dogecoin-is-his-favorite-cryptocurrency"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T12:43:06.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple v. SEC: XRP Advocate Unveils Explosive Appeal Details]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18790924/Ripple-v-SEC-XRP-Advocate-Unveils-Explosive-Appeal-Details</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18790924/Ripple-v-SEC-XRP-Advocate-Unveils-Explosive-Appeal-Details"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T12:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blackrock’s Bitcoin ETF Application Update, Warnings of Possible Reversal in XRP Ruling, and More — Week in Review]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7560a3c096</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/blackrocks-bitcoin-etf-application-update-warnings-of-possible-reversal-in-xrp-ruling-and-more-week-in-review/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T12:35:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Financial megalith Blackrock’s bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) application has now been accepted by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission, and added to the regulator’s docket. In related news, a former official from the SEC has said the recent ruling on XRP from the SEC v. Ripple case “resides on shaky ground” and is likely to be reversed. This and much more just below, in the latest Bitcoin.com News Week in Review.
 

 
SEC Accepts Blackrock’s Bitcoin ETF Application
 
The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has accepted the application for a bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) filed by asset manager Blackrock. The move indicates the regulator is preparing to seriously consider a bitcoin ETF and could eventually set the stage for wider adoption of crypto assets and produ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HEX: The tale of the crypto project that rewards you for locking away your money]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18790922/HEX-The-tale-of-the-crypto-project-that-rewards-you-for-locking-away-your-money</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18790922/HEX-The-tale-of-the-crypto-project-that-rewards-you-for-locking-away-your-money"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T12:30:16.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$ADA: Cardano’s Ecosystem Set for Major Boost as Mithril Nears Mainnet Release]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18790912/ADA-Cardanos-Ecosystem-Set-for-Major-Boost-as-Mithril-Nears-Mainnet-Release</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18790912/ADA-Cardanos-Ecosystem-Set-for-Major-Boost-as-Mithril-Nears-Mainnet-Release"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T12:19:56.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Black Swan Author Sees ‘Crypto Fad Starting to Peter out’ as Youngsters Turn to AI]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18790908/Black-Swan-Author-Sees-Crypto-Fad-Starting-to-Peter-out-as-Youngsters-Turn-to-AI</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18790908/Black-Swan-Author-Sees-Crypto-Fad-Starting-to-Peter-out-as-Youngsters-Turn-to-AI"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T12:14:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Taleb believes cryptocurrencies and Artificial Intelligence (AI) are both "infatuation."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former SEC Chief: Regulator Stands A Chance Of Winning Appeal Vs. Ripple]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7560adddfb</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/former-sec-chief-stands-chance-of-winning-appeal/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T12:10:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto space and the financial world at large are currently reacting to news that the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) may appeal the recent court ruling in its case against the blockchain company Ripple.
 
This development was revealed in the federal regulator’s latest petition in a separate ongoing lawsuit against Korean crypto investor Do Kwon and his company Terraform Labs, both of which are accused of committing fraud. 
 
 
Is The SEC Planning To Make An Appeal Against Ripple’s Victory?
 
On July 13, Ripple gained a significant victory over the U.S. regulator when a U.S. District Court ruled that the sale of the XRP tokens to retail investors did not breach U.S. securities law. However, the case was the opposite with regard to sales to institutional investors…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Semilore Faleti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amanda Cavaleri On Bitcoin Culture, Adoption And Preserving Wisdom For Future Generations]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7560ae8ef4</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/amanda-cavaleri-interview-on-bitcoin-culture-and-gender-gap"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T12:02:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin possesses a unique identity and qualities that are cemented on the foundation of decentralization. Almost everyone who is doing the work to understand Bitcoin will eventually run into the cold, hard fact that, at its core, Bitcoin is about freedom. To those who have enjoyed individual liberties for their entire lives, the concept of freedom may be watered down or under appreciated. For those who live without it, freedom and individual liberty become pursuits of great importance. 
Many people who are diving into Bitcoin will find themselves at a crossroads, having to choose between the speculative “get-rich-quick” mania of some crypto subcultures and the self-sovereign, owner-and-builder mentality that Bitcoin offers. 
Amanda Cavaleri embodies the latter. Humble, empathetic and gene…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Becca Bratcher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manipulation Claim in Binance-Listed Altcoin: Pump and Dump Scheme in Action?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18790885/Manipulation-Claim-in-Binance-Listed-Altcoin-Pump-and-Dump-Scheme-in-Action</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18790885/Manipulation-Claim-in-Binance-Listed-Altcoin-Pump-and-Dump-Scheme-in-Action"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T11:51:05.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big Sell-Off Coming for Altcoins, but Ethereum Could Be Exception, Says Crypto Analyst Nicholas Merten]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18790877/Big-Sell-Off-Coming-for-Altcoins-but-Ethereum-Could-Be-Exception-Says-Crypto-Analyst-Nicholas-Merten</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18790877/Big-Sell-Off-Coming-for-Altcoins-but-Ethereum-Could-Be-Exception-Says-Crypto-Analyst-Nicholas-Merten"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T11:45:17.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chainlink (LINK) Whales Are on Buying Spree, Here's What Caused It]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18790878/Chainlink-LINK-Whales-Are-on-Buying-Spree-Heres-What-Caused-It</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18790878/Chainlink-LINK-Whales-Are-on-Buying-Spree-Heres-What-Caused-It"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T11:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LINK catching eye of whales, with large-scale purchases hinting at increased confidence in token]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KuCoin Data Shows Varied Crypto Habits in France, Germany For Gen Z, Y, X]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18791001/KuCoin-Data-Shows-Varied-Crypto-Habits-in-France-Germany-For-Gen-Z-Y-X</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18791001/KuCoin-Data-Shows-Varied-Crypto-Habits-in-France-Germany-For-Gen-Z-Y-X"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T11:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB) Real-Life Component to Be Presented at Major Conference]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18790860/Shiba-Inu-SHIB-Real-Life-Component-to-Be-Presented-at-Major-Conference</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18790860/Shiba-Inu-SHIB-Real-Life-Component-to-Be-Presented-at-Major-Conference"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T11:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Power up Your Crypto Marketing With VERSE Token at Bitcoin.com News]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7560a99713</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/power-up-your-crypto-marketing-with-verse-token-at-bitcoin-com-news/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T11:24:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin.com News, an authoritative voice in the cryptocurrency landscape, offers an unmatched platform for crypto projects to garner worldwide recognition. This trusted source of comprehensive coverage on diverse crypto aspects, from token pricing to DeFi and NFTs, serves an engaged audience from over 200 countries.
 
Bitcoin.com News, with its 3 million plus social media followers, opens doors to flexible, budget-friendly advertising options. A broad array of formats, ranging from press releases to podcasts, newsletters, and more, are available to suit diverse requirements. Customizable campaign strategies enable precise targeting, ensuring optimum frequency and duration.
 
The professional team at Bitcoin.com News provides strategic support, assisting in crafting compelling messages, optimizing ads, and quantifying campaign results. As an added advantage, advertising costs can be conveniently settled using VERSE, Bitcoin.com’s own utility token, with an amazing 10% discount.
 
Advertising through Bitcoin.com News paves the way to a large, loyal audience of crypto enthusiasts, promoting brand awareness, boosting SEO, generating leads, and driving conversions. It’s an opportunity not to be missed for crypto projects seeking to gain momentum and expand reach.
 
About Bitcoin.com
 
Bitcoin.com is building products that give everyday people access to a vast world of opportunities to generate personal prosperity without limits. Since 2015, Bitcoin.com has been a global leader in introducing newcomers to cryptocurrency, featuring accessible educational materials, timely and objective news, and easy-to-use fully self-custodial products for buying, spending, trading, investing, and earning with crypto.
 
About Verse
 
VERSE is a rewards and utility token for users who contribute to and participate in the Bitcoin.com ecosystem. Launched in December 2022, the VERSE token is designed to expand access to decentralized finance and help unlock the economic freedom it provides.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Blood Money: Woman Gets 5 Years For Hiring Crypto Hitman To Kill Ex-Husband]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7560aac9bf</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-woman-gets-5-years-for-hiring-hitman/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T11:10:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a shocking revelation on the dark net, Bitcoin played a chilling role in a sinister plot masterminded by Kristy Lynn Felkins, a 38-year-old woman from Nevada.
 
Intent on carrying out an evil act, she sought the services of a hitman to execute a deadly plan targeting her ex-husband. As the cryptocurrency paved the way for anonymous transactions, it enabled the unfolding of a horrifying turn of events that shook the foundations of online anonymity and criminal intent.
 
The chilling narrative began in 2016 when Felkins initiated communication with an entity she believed to be a hitman-for-hire on a dark web platform. Unbeknownst to her, the website was a façade, a scam that preyed on unsuspecting customers seeking sinister services.
 
The supposed hitman, operating under pseudonyms, lure…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Potential SEC appeal in Ripple case ‘not even close to a setback’: lawyer]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18790828/Potential-SEC-appeal-in-Ripple-case-not-even-close-to-a-setback-lawyer</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18790828/Potential-SEC-appeal-in-Ripple-case-not-even-close-to-a-setback-lawyer"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T11:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Custody: The Frontlines of Operation Choke Point 2.0]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18790830/Crypto-Custody-The-Frontlines-of-Operation-Choke-Point-20</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18790830/Crypto-Custody-The-Frontlines-of-Operation-Choke-Point-20"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T10:55:42.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin can still hit $19K, warns trader ahead of BTC price ‘big move’]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18790820/Bitcoin-can-still-hit-19K-warns-trader-ahead-of-BTC-price-big-move</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18790820/Bitcoin-can-still-hit-19K-warns-trader-ahead-of-BTC-price-big-move"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T10:45:32.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Blood Money: Woman Gets 5 Years For Hiring Crypto Hitman To Kill Ex-Husband]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18790814/Bitcoin-Blood-Money-Woman-Gets-5-Years-For-Hiring-Crypto-Hitman-To-Kill-Ex-Husband</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18790814/Bitcoin-Blood-Money-Woman-Gets-5-Years-For-Hiring-Crypto-Hitman-To-Kill-Ex-Husband"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T10:43:47.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Singapore, US With Highest Public Debt per Capita, China Most Indebted in BRICS: Study]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756092a43c</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/singapore-us-with-highest-public-debt-per-capita-china-most-indebted-in-brics-study/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T09:34:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Singapore, the United States and Japan top the global chart in terms of sovereign debt per capita, according to research based on U.N. data. The burden of government debt for every American is 10 times heavier than that for a Chinese citizen, according to the study.
 
U.S. Ranks Second in the World by Debt per Citizen, China in Top 50
 
People in Singapore owed more than any other nation in 2022 as far as sovereign debt per capita is concerned, according to an analysis of data compiled by the United Nations. The share of each citizen of the city-state amounted to $117,400, according to the research conducted by the Russian RIA Novosti news agency.
 
The U.S. is second with $93,000 for each American. In June, the country’s debt surpassed the $32-trillion mark for the first time. That happen…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lubomir Tassev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Financial Woes: Binance France Discloses €4 Million Loss In 2022 Financial Reports]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7560997e6e</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/binance-france-face-4-million-loss-in-2022/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T08:09:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The French arm of Binance, established on November 8, 2021, disclosed its financial statement for the year 2022 on Friday. The leading auditing service firm RSM Paris audited the Binance platform and concluded that the exchange had faced a loss of €4 million in France. It happened because the revenue earned from the exchange’s services was less than its expenses.
 
The regulatory barriers mainly caused Binance France to bear losses in its initial financial period. Though the crypto exchange entered the French jurisdiction in November 2021, the platform started offering trading and custody service in mid-2022 due to legal limits, resulting in a mismatch in the revenue and cost.
 
 
The published statement covers 14 months of expenses from Binance France’s creation in November 2021 to Decemb…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kent Glory</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Copy Trading Has ‘Disrupted the Crypto Industry’ Says Bitget’s Gracy Chen]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75609baec6</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/copy-trading-has-disrupted-the-crypto-industry-says-bitget-ceo-gracy-chen/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T07:40:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Copy trading has disrupted the crypto industry and is increasingly the trading strategy preferred by less experienced traders says Gracy Chen, managing director of the crypto trading platform Bitget. While copy trading is gaining popularity globally, traders and prospective users from Africa appear more interested in the strategy than those from other regions.
 
Africa-Based Users More Interested in Copy Trading
 
According to Gracy Chen, the managing director of the crypto derivatives and copy trading platform Bitget, copying trading is a trading strategy which has not only “disrupted the crypto industry” but has become increasingly more popular with novice traders. She added that for some cases, copy trading has proven to be an effective strategy during the so-called “crypto winter.”
 
T…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Openai Announces Chatgpt App for Android Devices]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75608c0818</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/openai-announces-chatgpt-app-for-android-devices/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T05:40:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence (AI) research lab Openai announced it’s launching an Android version of its Chatgpt chatbot. The application, which will be available for download next week, comes after recent updates of Google’s Bard and a report revealing that Apple is working on its own chatbot service.
 
Android Users to Have Chatgpt in Their Pockets, Openai Says
 
Microsoft-funded AI developer Openai is releasing an Android app for its chatbot powered by artificial intelligence technology, Chatgpt. It will be rolling out to users next week, the company said, but can be pre-ordered in the Google Play Store since Friday.
 
 
Announcing ChatGPT for Android! The app will be rolling out to users next week, and you can pre-order in the Google Play Store starting today: https://t.co/NfBDYZR5GI
 
— Op…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lubomir Tassev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China’s Central Bank: Digital Yuan Transactions Reach $250 Billion]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75608b68b5</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/chinas-central-bank-digital-yuan-transactions-reach-250-billion/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T03:41:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[China’s central bank governor has revealed that transactions using the country’s central bank digital currency (CBDC) reached 1.8 trillion yuan ($250 billion) at the end of June. In addition, the People’s Bank of China (PBOC) official stated that digital yuan in circulation amounted to 16.5 billion yuan.
 
Latest Digital Yuan Stats
 
People’s Bank of China (PBOC) Governor Yi Gang disclosed the latest statistics on China’s central bank digital currency (CBDC) on Wednesday at a lecture organized by Singapore’s central bank, the Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS).
 
The Chinese central banker revealed that transactions utilizing China’s central bank digital currency, also called e-CNY, reached 1.8 trillion yuan ($250 billion) at the end of June. By comparison, approximately 100 billion in …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BRICS Currency Not on Agenda for Leaders’ Summit — Nations to Focus on De-Dollarization]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756072418c</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/brics-currency-not-on-agenda-for-leaders-summit-nations-to-focus-on-de-dollarization/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T01:39:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The heavily anticipated BRICS currency is not on the agenda to be discussed at the economic bloc’s upcoming leaders’ summit, according to South Africa’s diplomat in charge of BRICS relations. He clarified that the BRICS members will focus on de-dollarization and promoting the use of national currencies in international trade instead of the U.S. dollar.
 
BRICS to Focus on Reducing Dollar Reliance
 
The topic of a common BRICS currency is not on the agenda to be discussed at the economic group’s upcoming leaders’ summit, South Africa’s diplomat in charge of BRICS relations, Anil Sooklal, reportedly said Thursday.
 
South Africa, being the current chair of the BRICS group, will be hosting the summit in Johannesburg on Aug. 22-24. Sooklal explained that the BRICS nations (Brazil, Russia, Indi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Says XRP Ruling in Ripple Case ‘Wrongly Decided’ — Signals Appeal]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756078b82a</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/sec-says-xrp-ruling-in-ripple-case-wrongly-decided-signals-appeal/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-22T23:41:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has told a federal court that some portions of the Ripple ruling regarding XRP “were wrongly decided.” The regulator has asked the court to ignore parts of the ruling, noting that “SEC staff is considering the various available avenues for further review and intends to recommend that the SEC seek such review.”
 
SEC Disagrees With Ripple Ruling on Retail Investors
 
The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) stated in a new filing for its lawsuit against Terraform Labs and its co-founder Do Kwon that some decisions in the court ruling on the SEC v. Ripple case regarding XRP were wrong.
 
While noting that the Ripple ruling regarding institutional investors supports the SEC’s claims, the securities watchdog stated: “However, with resp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Americana Makes Its 'Phygital' Vault Service Available to the Public]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149673</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149673/americana-vault-physical-digital-blockchain"/>
        <updated>2023-07-22T21:52:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Both physical and digital assets can be securely stored and showcased. Here's how the "concierge vaulting" system works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephanie Hirschmiller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nigerian Social Payments Platform Bundle Ceases Crypto Exchange Operations]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75606009fc</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/nigerian-social-payments-platform-bundle-ceases-crypto-exchange-operations/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-22T21:38:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Nigerian social payments platform Bundle said on July 20 it was shutting down its crypto exchange services business and will now focus on its peer-to-peer platform known as Cashlink. Bundle said users must withdraw or convert their digital assets to the stablecoin tether on or before Aug. 30.
 
Bundle Says Transition Period Is to Last 60 Days
 
The Nigerian social payments platform, Bundle, said on July 20 that it was ceasing operations of its crypto exchange services and will now focus on the peer-to-peer platform known as Cashlink. In a statement, Bundle said the decision to shut down exchange services follows “shareholders’ decision to restructure the business to focus on Cashlink.”
 
Founded by Yele Bademosi, Bundle started operations in 2020 and at the time of the announcement the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Caitlin Long: The Fed Has Become an 'Unmovable Mountain']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149669</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149669/caitlin-long-federal-reserve-unmovable-mountain-custodia-lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2023-07-22T21:13:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Custodia CEO says The Federal Reserve welcoming a European firm but not hers is "very un-American."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Asserts Ripple XRP Case was 'Wrongly Decided', Signals Appeal]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149667</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149667/sec-ripple-xrp-terraform-labs-do-kwon-securities-howey-test"/>
        <updated>2023-07-22T19:49:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terra’s lawyers cited the Ripple XRP ruling in their latest filings, but the SEC says the ruling actually favors them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Charting Bitcoin’s Predictable Course: A Comprehensive Review of the Next 29 Reward Halvings]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75606f8fc0</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/charting-bitcoins-predictable-course-a-comprehensive-review-of-the-next-29-reward-halvings/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-22T19:39:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In under 280 days, Bitcoin’s blockchain will undergo its fourth reward halving event, slicing the block subsidy from 6.25 BTC to 3.125 BTC. The crypto community is abuzz with chatter, contemplating how these substantial decreases in block rewards will transpire over the ensuing two decades, and speculating on how miners will cope with the impending reductions. The following is a glimpse at the timeline of these subsidy transformations and a projection of the future rewards in the distant horizon.
 
From 50 to 1 Satoshi — Decoding Bitcoin’s Future Block Subsidy
 
A fortnight ago, Bitcoin.com News explored the looming Bitcoin halving and examined how bitcoin (BTC) miners will need to rely on a blend of inflated BTC prices and transaction fees to withstand their revenue being cut in half. At …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Canadian Police Warn of Surge in Home Invasion-Style Robberies Targeting Affluent Crypto Investors]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756057bec5</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/canadian-police-warn-of-surge-in-home-invasion-style-robberies-targeting-affluent-crypto-investors/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-22T17:45:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Canadian law enforcement reports that affluent cryptocurrency investors have become targets of home invasion-style robberies. Both Delta Police and Royal Canadian Mounted Police in Richmond have issued warnings after having dealt with multiple robberies involving prominent cryptocurrency investors over the past year.
 
Wealthy Crypto Investors Become Targets in Canada
 
Over the last 12 months, numerous home invasions have targeted wealthy digital currency investors throughout Canada. A press release from Delta Police headquarters reveals that both Delta and Richmond’s Royal Canadian Mounted Police (RCMP) have responded to several such incidents.
 
“It appears someone is targeting these victims for cryptocurrency, and we believe this public warning is necessary in the interest of public sa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Bitcoin and Ethereum Dip as Chainlink, XRP, XLM Lead Growth]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149657</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149657/this-week-on-crypto-twitter-bitcoin-and-ethereum-dip-as-chainlink-xrp-xlm-lead-growth"/>
        <updated>2023-07-22T17:08:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Also this week, the British treasury issued a firm no to those calling for crypto to be regulated as gambling.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[House Crypto Bill Won’t Restrain SEC and Could Threaten DeFi, Legal Experts Say]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149612</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149612/house-crypto-bill-sec-defi"/>
        <updated>2023-07-22T16:10:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The House bill aims to give the crypto industry the regulatory clarity it's been waiting for, but legal experts say there’s reason to remain cautious.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Targets $2,000 Bounce: Santiment Predicts August Rally Amid ‘Eerily Quiet’ Market]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75605a2ceb</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ethereum-targets-2000-bounce-santiment-predicts-august-rally-amid-eerily-quiet-market/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-22T15:44:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nestled in the second position of the cryptocurrency market cap hierarchy, ethereum (ETH) currently trades below the $1,900 per unit mark. However, the industry experts at Santiment predict a bullish upturn, indicating that the digital asset might claw its way back to the $2,000 territory in the coming month. In Santiment’s view, ethereum is reveling in its “under the radar” status, and researchers suggest while ether’s market performance has been lackluster, “patience tends to reward.”
 
‘Under the Radar,’ But Not For Long, Santiment Report Suggests
 
Similar to bitcoin (BTC) prices, ethereum (ETH) markets have been rangebound and have traded between the $1,830 mark and the $2,000 per unit range since the end of June. Furthermore, like BTC being stopped at the $31K mark, ETH prices have a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Dark Side Of Blockchain: ISIS And Supporters Use Crypto For Fundraising?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7560466cb1</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/isis-and-supporters-use-crypto-for-fundraising/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-22T15:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past few years, there have been rising concerns about the use of cryptocurrencies for illegal activities. Although the majority of these are overestimated, there is no denying that there are some bad actors trying to take advantage of the technology’s decentralized nature.
 
TRM Labs, a blockchain intelligence firm, recently published a report on the increasing use of crypto assets by terror organizations.
 
 
ISIS Allies Used Crypto To Raise Funds: TRM Labs
 
TRM Labs has unveiled its findings regarding cryptocurrency fundraising by ISIS and its supporters across Asia. In a report dated July 21, 2023, the blockchain intelligence company revealed the details of its investigation on the use of crypto assets in the world of terrorism.
 
According to TRM Labs, most of the transaction…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Opeyemi Sule</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why the Grammys Will Allow Songs Created With AI Help—At Least for Now]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149638</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149638/why-grammys-allow-songs-created-ai-help-harvey-mason-jr"/>
        <updated>2023-07-22T14:25:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recording Academy CEO Harvey Mason Jr. defends the move to allow AI-assisted music in Grammy nominations, but said there needs to be oversight.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biggest Movers: TRX Surges to 20-Month High on Saturday]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7560427f3f</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/biggest-movers-trx-surges-to-20-month-high-on-saturday/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-22T14:14:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tron was one of the notable movers on Saturday, as the token broke out of a key resistance level to start the weekend. The move came as the global crypto market cap mostly consolidated during Saturday’s session. Stellar was another exception, as the token rebounded from yesterday’s loss.
 
Tron (TRX)
 
Tron (TRX) was a notable gainer to start the weekend, with the price surging to a 20-month high.
 
After dropping to a low of $0.08035 on Friday, TRX/USD rallied to an intraday peak of $0.09317 earlier in the day.
 
This was the highest point tron has hit since December 2021, and comes following a breakout of a ceiling at $0.08600.
 
 
This coincides with the relative strength index (RSI) moving past its own ceiling at 70.00. It is now tracking at 71.35.
 
Earlier gains have since faded, with the token now back below the aforementioned resistance level of $0.08600.
 
This appears to be a result of traders capturing profits.
 
 
Stellar (XLM)
 
In addition to TRX, stellar was also largely in the green on Saturday, as the token rebounded from Friday’s losses.
 
XLM/USD rose to a high of $0.1674 to start the weekend, which comes a day after trading at a low of $0.1561.
 
This rally resulted in stellar breaking out of a recent resistance level of $0.1620, and edging closer to a 15-month high of $0.1959.
 
 
One of the reasons for today’s climb was the RSI racing past its own ceiling at the 70.00 mark.
 
Price strength is now overbought, which could prompt bears to reenter the market in anticipation of a sell-off.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
What was behind today’s rebound in stellar? Let us know your thoughts in the comments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Back To Terra? Interim CEO Welcomes Do Kwon’s Potential Return]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756043ba1a</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/back-to-terra-do-kwons-potential-return/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-22T14:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform’s recently appointed CEO, Chris Amani, embraces the possibility of Do Kwon’s return to the company, recognizing the colossal undertaking he faces in rejuvenating the failed stablecoin Terra (UST).
 
In a recent candid session via Twitter Spaces, Amani openly acknowledged Terraform’s past lapses in effectively communicating its current endeavors to the public. The new CEO humbly admitted the importance of addressing such shortcomings.
 
When asked about the potential return of Terra’s founder, Do Kwon, to the company, Amani’s response exuded an unmistakable warmth and openness. 
 

“Of course, he’s welcome back; that’s not even a question,” he quipped. “It could be 10 years from now.” 
 
The CEO’s words emphasize a willingness to embrace Kwon’s potential comeback, regardless of th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Endorses Pro-Crypto Ark Invest In Tesla Earnings Call]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756043ba0b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/musk-endorses-fund-manager-ark-invest-tesla-call/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-22T14:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk, the CEO of Tesla, recently praised ARK Invest’s analysis as “the best” during the last earnings call on July 20. This endorsement is noteworthy as ARK Invest, a pro-crypto asset manager, is one of the largest shareholders of Coinbase Global (COIN), the leading cryptocurrency exchange in the United States.
 
Musk said users should follow Ark Invest’s research, where they can preview Tesla’s short variances in gross margin and profitability. In his view, these variances are “minor” relative to the long-term picture and holding Tesla’s stock is a “big long-term investment”. 
 
Although Tesla posted all-time high quarterly revenue and stock prices briefly rose after the earnings call, prices slumped in the after-market hours and are lower as of July 22. At press time, Tesla’s stock …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dalmas Ngetich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It's Time to Flip the Hollywood Script on Its Head]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149564</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149564/time-flip-hollywood-script-sag-wga-strike-film3"/>
        <updated>2023-07-22T13:45:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amid strikes that have shut down Hollywood, Entertainmint CEO Genevieve Thiers argues that Film3 points the way to a more equitable path forward.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Genevieve Thiers</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI Brings ChatGPT to Android as AI Boom Continues]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149622</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149622/openai-brings-chatgpt-to-android-as-ai-boom-continues"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T22:48:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI wants to gain as many ChatGPT users as possible, and is going beyond web browsers by adding an Android app to its stable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Did You Miss Out on Hamster Races, Anon? HAMS Token Jumps 783%]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149615</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149615/did-you-miss-out-hamster-races-anon-hams-token-jumps"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T22:25:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Degens betting on the price of the HAMS token might be doing even better than degens betting crypto on the actual hamster races.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Meta's ChatGPT Killer Really Open Source?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149600</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149600/is-metas-chatgpt-killer-really-open-source"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T20:52:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Open Source Initiative told Meta’s Chief AI Scientist that the model they are promoting as Open Source is not really open source.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI, Google, Microsoft Promise White House to Keep AI Safe]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149585</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149585/openai-google-microsoft-promise-white-house-keep-ai-safe"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T17:59:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Industry leaders commit to safe, secure, and transparent development of artificial intelligence in agreement with the Biden administration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fed Bent the Rules in Rollout of Instant Payment Service FedNow, Says Custodia CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149565</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149565/fed-bent-the-rules-in-rollout-of-instant-payment-service-fednow-says-custodia-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T17:29:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Long pointed to public documents showing Adyen, a FedNow early adopter, got a federal master account in July 2020—a year before it had a U.S. branch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Human Artists Lose Ground in Legal Battle Against AI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149533</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149533/human-artists-lose-ground-in-legal-battle-against-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T16:45:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. District Judge William Orrick said artists should "provide more facts" to back up claims about alleged copyright infringement by AI companies]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Lawsuit Alleges SBF Brother Planned to Turn Island Nation Into Doomsday Bunker]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149537</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149537/ftx-lawsuit-alleges-sbf-brother-planned-to-turn-island-nation-into-doomsday-bunker"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T16:44:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gabriel Bankman-Fried allegedly planned to use Nauru as a shelter for effective altruists in the event of a global catastrophe.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitfinex Hackers Agree to Forfeit Billions in Bitcoin in Plea Deal]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149557</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149557/bitfinex-hackers-agree-to-forfeit-billions-in-bitcoin-in-plea-deal"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T16:27:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ilya Lichtenstein and his wife, Heather Morgan, will appear before a judge on August 3 and could face up to 20 years in prison.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to McNuggets Land: McDonald’s Launches Metaverse Game in ‘The Sandbox’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149551</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149551/welcome-mcnuggets-land-mcdonalds-launches-metaverse-game-sandbox"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T15:33:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[McDonald’s is the latest major brand to debut an immersive metaverse game experience—with NFT and crypto rewards, too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Drain $3 Million in Ethereum From DeFi Protocol Conic Finance]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149532</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149532/hackers-drain-3-2m-in-ethereum-from-defi-protocol-conic-finance"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T15:30:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new DeFi protocol, which went live in March, has lost more than 1,700 Ethereum.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DoJ Accuses SBF of Leaking Caroline Ellison's Diary to 'Discredit a Witness' in FTX Trial]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149499</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149499/doj-accuses-sbf-of-leaking-caroline-ellisons-diary-to-discredit-a-witness-in-ftx-trial"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T12:26:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried attempted to discredit Caroline Ellison by sharing her personal documents to the media, the DOJ alleges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Smart Wallet’ Provider Argent Launches NFT Marketplace Unframed on Starknet]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149493</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149493/smart-wallet-provider-argent-launches-nft-marketplace-unframed-starknet"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T12:01:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest launch "will push the boundaries of what NFT marketplaces can do,” said Argent co-founder Julien Niset.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China Targets Travelers With Digital Yuan as Tourist Season Looms]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149495</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149495/china-targets-travelers-with-digital-yuan-as-tourist-season-looms"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T11:33:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As China enters the summer vacation months, the government is actively promoting the digital yuan to travelers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Space Case? Melania Trump's Apollo 11 NFT Defies NASA Rules]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149481</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149481/space-case-melania-trumps-apollo-11-nft-defies-nasa-rules"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T02:46:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An NFT released by former First Lady Melania Trump features an iconic NASA photo, despite the agency's explicit prohibition on NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Canadians Are Having Crypto Stolen From Their Homes, Police Say]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149475</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149475/canada-crypto-stolen-homes-police"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T23:20:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authorities believe there may be a connection between several robberies that have occurred in Canada involving thieves searching for private keys linked to crypto funds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Funds Linked to Fentanyl Trade Come Mostly From Centralized Exchanges: Elliptic]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149462</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149462/crypto-funds-linked-fentanyl-trade-come-mostly-centralized-exchanges-elliptic"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T23:17:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain analytics firm Elliptic found that most crypto funds used in the fentanyl trade can be traced to centralized exchanges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Mighty Action Heroes' Puts a Fun Battle Royale Shooter in Your Browser]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149425</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149425/mighty-action-heroes-puts-fun-battle-royale-shooter-your-browser"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T23:11:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PREVIEW: Fast-paced battle royale game Mighty Action Heroes doesn't break new ground, but it offers up fun moments in its open beta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Now Bet Crypto on Hamster Races. What Could Go Wrong?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149448</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149448/you-can-now-bet-crypto-hamster-races-what-could-go-wrong"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T22:58:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new site is gripping crypto gamblers by letting them bet cryptocurrency on streamed races between members of the fluffy rodent breed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[House Republicans Introduce Bill That Aims to Bring Regulatory Clarity to Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149445</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149445/house-republicans-bill-regulatory-clarity-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T22:14:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bill is the product of extensive work by lawmakers on Capitol Hill.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Now Customize AI Chatbot ChatGPT to Respond the Way You Want]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149429</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149429/you-can-now-customize-ai-chatbot-chatgpt-act-way-you-want"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T22:05:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI unveils a "custom instruction" feature for ChatGPT users to enable personalized responses from the AI chatbot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Caroline Ellison Admits She Wasn’t 'Well Suited' to Run Alameda Research]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149424</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149424/caroline-ellison-admits-alameda-research"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T21:58:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In diary entries seen by the New York Times, Ellison also reportedly said it felt great when FTX blew up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coin Center Blasts 'Messy and Unconstitutional' Senate DeFi Bill]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149400</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149400/coin-center-blasts-messy-and-unconstitutional-senate-defi-bill"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T19:55:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Critics say new legislation will grant the U.S. Treasury overbroad authority while violating freedom of speech.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT Isn't All That Great at Cybersecurity: Immunefi]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149412</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149412/chatgpt-isnt-great-cybersecurity-immunefi"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T19:49:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security researchers see ChatGPT as a tool with plenty of potential, but it's dogged by how inaccurate it is at diagnosing security flaws.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Is Down Meme Dead? Devs Say Network Had 100% Uptime Since Feb]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149407</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149407/solana-is-down-meme-dead-devs-say-network-had-100-uptime-since-feb"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T19:35:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[But as the foundation told Decrypt in an email, that’s “no guarantees of future network performance.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Connor Sephton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Mighty Action Heroes' Open Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/litL6kKs/inside-mighty-action-heroes-open-beta</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/litL6kKs/inside-mighty-action-heroes-open-beta"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T18:23:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mighty Action Heroes is the flagship blockchain title from Mighty Bear Games. But is the browser-based battle royale shooter worth checking out? Decrypt's Kate Irwin offers her thoughts and a first look at the upcoming game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miner Hive Is Using Old Ethereum Rigs and AI to Make Ordinals Art]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149382</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149382/bitcoin-miner-hive-is-using-old-ethereum-rigs-and-ai-to-make-ordinals-art"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T17:50:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“We will create generative AI art with our own GPUs, on our own fine-tuned model of Stable Diffusion," the CEO told Decrypt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coutts Apologizes for 'Unbanking' Bitcoin-Friendly Nigel Farage]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149381</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149381/coutts-apologizes-for-unbanking-bitcoin-friendly-nigel-farage"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T17:43:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[High-end Coutts—which counts members of the Royal Family among its clientele—faced blow back after Farage said his account was closed over political views.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Connor Sephton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Binance US CEO Brian Brooks Joins Crypto Asset Manager Hashdex]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149368</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149368/former-binance-us-ceo-brian-brooks-joins-crypto-asset-manager-hashdex"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T16:33:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[His ill-fated stint at Binance US wasn't in a news release, which focused on his time as Coinbase's CLO and acting U.S. Comptroller of the Currency.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moonbirds Mythics NFTs Begin Reveal That Will Last at Least 200 Days]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149362</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149362/moonbirds-mythics-nfts-begin-reveal-last-least-200-days"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T16:15:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 20,000-strong Mythics NFT collection will be revealed gradually over the span of months as Moonbirds and Oddities holders claim them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lucy Harley-McKeown</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK Government Rejects Proposal to Classify Crypto as Gambling]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149343</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149343/uk-government-rejects-proposal-to-classify-crypto-as-gambling"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T13:24:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The government argued that classifying crypto asset trading as gambling would create a misalignment with global standards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Congressman Ritchie Torres: SEC Chair Gensler 'Intent on Sabotaging' Crypto Industry]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149337</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149337/congressman-ritchie-torres-sec-chair-gensler-intent-on-sabotaging-crypto-industry"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T13:05:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Congressman Ritchie Torres doubled down on his recent criticisms of Securities and Exchange Commission chair Gary Gensler.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dr. Disrespect's 'Deadrop': Early Access Gameplay From Snapshot VI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/8l21EHoa/dr-disrespects-deadrop-early-access-gameplay-from-snapshot-vi</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/8l21EHoa/dr-disrespects-deadrop-early-access-gameplay-from-snapshot-vi"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T18:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin playtests Dr. Disrespect and Midnight Society's first-person shooter Deadrop and shares the latest game updates, as well as her opinions on the game in development. Currently, Deadrop offers Polygon Founders Pass NFTs with no other crypto plans revealed just yet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['More and More' Game Publishers Will Embrace NFTs: Mythical Games CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/wBWogSkl/more-and-more-game-publishers-will-embrace-nfts-mythical-games-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/wBWogSkl/more-and-more-game-publishers-will-embrace-nfts-mythical-games-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T22:28:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the wake of EA Sports and Fortnite creator Epic Games embracing Nike's NFT platform, Mythical Games CEO John Linden tells Decrypt's Andrew Hayward how quickly he expects to see more major traditional game publishers enter the blockchain space and how quickly the industry will scale.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gran Saga Unlimited Early Access: Inside the Anime MMORPG on Aptos]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JeFWMVwo/gran-saga-unlimited-early-access-inside-the-anime-mmorpg-on-aptos</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JeFWMVwo/gran-saga-unlimited-early-access-inside-the-anime-mmorpg-on-aptos"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T21:46:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin plays Gran Saga: Unlimited's second community playtest, reports her findings, and offers her opinion and insights on the upcoming game, which will offer optional Aptos NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[100 Thieves' Moe Says Blockchain Games Will 'Eventually' Be Accepted by Livestreamers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/xHhh62ID/100-thieves-moe-says-blockchain-games-will-eventually-be-accepted-by-livestreamers</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/xHhh62ID/100-thieves-moe-says-blockchain-games-will-eventually-be-accepted-by-livestreamers"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T16:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[100 Thieves content creator and gamer Moe also goes by "Yassuo" online after his favorite League of Legends character. Decrypt's Kate Irwin asks him about 100 Thieves' future crypto plans and whether Moe thinks creators like xQc and Pokimane might ever come around to blockchain games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Games of the Future Are Going to Be Different," Says Splinterlands Cofounder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/sQv6zcil/games-of-the-future-are-going-to-be-different-says-splinterlands-cofounder</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/sQv6zcil/games-of-the-future-are-going-to-be-different-says-splinterlands-cofounder"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T20:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Splinterlands Cofounder Matt Rosen tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about how the game has evolved over its five-year history and why he doesn't listen to the FUD around crypto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Champions Ascension: Like 'For Honor' with NFTs?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/gvM9ajww/inside-champions-ascension-like-for-honor-with-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/gvM9ajww/inside-champions-ascension-like-for-honor-with-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T22:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plai Labs Marketing Director Payton Kaleiwahea tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about player response to the combat game Champions Ascension in development, which offers arena combat, raid bosses, AI landscape features, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Activision VP Michael Lee: Gaming Is Crypto's 'Killer App']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/M9ulXrb3/ex-activision-vp-michael-lee-gaming-is-cryptos-killer-app</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/M9ulXrb3/ex-activision-vp-michael-lee-gaming-is-cryptos-killer-app"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Activision Vice President Michael Lee is now the SVP of Growth at Matter Labs. At the 3XP gaming conference, Lee sat down with Decrypt's Kate Irwin to discuss crypto gaming and give his predictions for the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Behind the Scenes with AMGI Studios and My Pet Hooligan]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/eQ71oapI/behind-the-scenes-with-amgi-studios-and-my-pet-hooligan</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/eQ71oapI/behind-the-scenes-with-amgi-studios-and-my-pet-hooligan"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T21:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin goes to Burbank, California for a behind-the-scenes tour of AMGI Studios, the developers of upcoming game My Pet Hooligan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Legend of Arcadia Chose Sui Over EVM Chains]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/H6JSRJIk/why-legend-of-arcadia-chose-sui-over-evm-chains</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/H6JSRJIk/why-legend-of-arcadia-chose-sui-over-evm-chains"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T21:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Legend of Arcadia Executive Producer Andy Lee tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the game and why they switched from EVM to new protocol Sui.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rumble Racing Star Game Preview: Is This Mario Kart With NFTs?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/lXVkuaeq/rumble-racing-star-game-preview-is-this-mario-kart-with-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/lXVkuaeq/rumble-racing-star-game-preview-is-this-mario-kart-with-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T16:47:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin shares a first look at Delabs' upcoming lawn mower racing game Rumble Racing Star, which offers a large cast of quirky characters pulled from the worlds of Bored Ape Yacht Club, Pudgy Penguins, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Laguna Games Turned Down 'Game of Thrones' for Crypto Unicorns]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/IqET3GYs/why-laguna-games-turned-down-game-of-thrones-for-crypto-unicorns</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/IqET3GYs/why-laguna-games-turned-down-game-of-thrones-for-crypto-unicorns"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T21:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin chats with Laguna Games about why the team chose to move away from an offer with WB Games to develop a Game of Thrones licensed title—and made Crypto Unicorns instead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mythical Games CEO John Linden on NFL Rivals Topping 1M Downloads]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/nDhvMd8r/mythical-games-ceo-john-linden-on-nfl-rivals-topping-1m-downloads</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/nDhvMd8r/mythical-games-ceo-john-linden-on-nfl-rivals-topping-1m-downloads"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T23:49:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mythical Games just raised a $37 million Series C1 round on the back of the early success of NFL Rivals, which has already topped a million downloads in two months. Mythical CEO John Linden joins Decrypt's Andrew Hayward to discuss the launch and impact of NFL Rivals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Ava Labs Is Approaching Gaming on Avalanche]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/M4TqVEkK/how-ava-labs-is-approaching-gaming-on-avalanche</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/M4TqVEkK/how-ava-labs-is-approaching-gaming-on-avalanche"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T22:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At 3XP, Ava Labs Head of Gaming Ed Chang sat down with Decrypt's Kate Irwin to discuss some of the biggest Avalanche-based games on the horizon and how the company is approaching and thinking about Web3 gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ogimi Founder David Gull on Why AI Should Be Your Meditation Coach]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DnNqBruk/ogimi-founder-david-gull-on-why-ai-should-be-your-meditation-coach</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DnNqBruk/ogimi-founder-david-gull-on-why-ai-should-be-your-meditation-coach"/>
        <updated>2023-06-25T18:45:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ogimi founder David Gull speaks with Decrypt's Jason Nelson about its AI-driven meditation guides and how the technology can enable a more unique, custom-tailored meditation experience for users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VaynerSports Gaming VP Discusses Web3 Content Creators, Decentralized Streaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/1MvGbnK5/vaynersports-gaming-vp-discusses-web3-content-creators-decentralized-streaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/1MvGbnK5/vaynersports-gaming-vp-discusses-web3-content-creators-decentralized-streaming"/>
        <updated>2023-06-24T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Darren Glover, VP of Gaming at talent management agency VaynerSports, sat down with Decrypt's Kate Irwin at the 3XP expo to discuss the challenges faced by Web3-centric content creators, the current state of the esports market, and how decentralized streaming platforms can challenge centralized leaders like Twitch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>