<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-11-07T13:17:44.666Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-11-07T13:17:44.666Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden AI executive order 'certainly challenging' for open-source AI — industry insiders]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19021446/Biden-AI-executive-order-certainly-challenging-for-open-source-AI-industry-insiders</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19021446/Biden-AI-executive-order-certainly-challenging-for-open-source-AI-industry-insiders"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T13:08:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The executive order on AI safety from the Biden Administration has laid out its standards for the industry though its vagueness has raised concerns among the AI community over stifling innovation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFT Market Bounces Back with Double Sales Volume]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19021455/NFT-Market-Bounces-Back-with-Double-Sales-Volume</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19021455/NFT-Market-Bounces-Back-with-Double-Sales-Volume"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T13:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NFT market is showing signs of recovery with several consecutive periods of week-on-week increases in sales volume.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Baidu Shifts AI Chip Orders from Nvidia to Huawei Amidst U.S. Pressure]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19021456/Baidu-Shifts-AI-Chip-Orders-from-Nvidia-to-Huawei-Amidst-US-Pressure</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19021456/Baidu-Shifts-AI-Chip-Orders-from-Nvidia-to-Huawei-Amidst-US-Pressure"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T13:03:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a strategic move away from Nvidia, Baidu (9888.HK), one of China’s prominent AI firms, has placed orders for artificial intelligence chips from Huawei (HWT.UL), according to two anonymous sources. This development underscores growing signs that U.S. pressure is prompting Chinese tech...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk’s Grok Inspires Over 400 Cryptocurrencies, Some Resulting in Scams]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19021457/Elon-Musks-Grok-Inspires-Over-400-Cryptocurrencies-Some-Resulting-in-Scams</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19021457/Elon-Musks-Grok-Inspires-Over-400-Cryptocurrencies-Some-Resulting-in-Scams"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T13:03:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a surprising turn of events within the cryptocurrency market, more than 400 cryptocurrencies have recently emerged bearing the name of Elon Musk’s latest venture into artificial intelligence, Grok. Despite Musk’s previous disinterest in creating a cryptocurrency, his announcement regarding...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin open interest passes $15B as analyst warns of 20% BTC price dip]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19021447/Bitcoin-open-interest-passes-15B-as-analyst-warns-of-20-BTC-price-dip</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19021447/Bitcoin-open-interest-passes-15B-as-analyst-warns-of-20-BTC-price-dip"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T13:03:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The highest Bitcoin open interest levels in over six months come as analysis predicts that BTC price action will fail to flip $36,000 this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Blocked in Kazakhstan for Breaking New Digital Assets Law: Report]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a0c08dee</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/11/07/coinbase-blocked-in-kazakhstan-for-breaking-new-digital-assets-law-report/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T13:01:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issuance, circulation, and offering trading of "unsecured digital assets" is prohibited outside the country's financial center under laws that came into effect earlier this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandali Handagama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Mover Americas: Bitcoin Ordinals Protocol Token Jumps 50%]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19021442/First-Mover-Americas-Bitcoin-Ordinals-Protocol-Token-Jumps-50</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19021442/First-Mover-Americas-Bitcoin-Ordinals-Protocol-Token-Jumps-50"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T13:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest price moves in bitcoin [BTC] and crypto markets in context for Nov. 7, 2023. First Mover is CoinDesk’s daily newsletter that contextualizes the latest actions in the crypto markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiple buyers consider purchase and relaunch of ‘irreparable’ FTX]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19021448/Multiple-buyers-consider-purchase-and-relaunch-of-irreparable-FTX</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19021448/Multiple-buyers-consider-purchase-and-relaunch-of-irreparable-FTX"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T13:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rebooting a tarnished name is difficult and some firms are so utterly compromised by their failures that there is no real hope of rehabilitation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inscriptions cause sudden surge in Bitcoin mempool transactions]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19021454/Inscriptions-cause-sudden-surge-in-Bitcoin-mempool-transactions</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19021454/Inscriptions-cause-sudden-surge-in-Bitcoin-mempool-transactions"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T13:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quick Take This week saw an unexpected upsurge in the Bitcoin mempool transaction count. The increase has been primarily driven by a new wave of Inscriptions, which has pushed the 7-day moving average transaction count above 70,000. Upon further examination, it is evident that the surge in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring the Buzz: Dogecoin, XRP, and Everlodge Capture Attention]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19021458/Exploring-the-Buzz-Dogecoin-XRP-and-Everlodge-Capture-Attention</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19021458/Exploring-the-Buzz-Dogecoin-XRP-and-Everlodge-Capture-Attention"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T13:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Adds Four National Security Experts to its Global Advisory Council]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19021443/Coinbase-Adds-Four-National-Security-Experts-to-its-Global-Advisory-Council</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19021443/Coinbase-Adds-Four-National-Security-Experts-to-its-Global-Advisory-Council"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase has added four national security experts, including former U.S. Secretary of Defence Dr. Mark T. Esper, to its Global Advisory Council.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How agencies can play a role in NFT and digital collectable creation]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19021449/How-agencies-can-play-a-role-in-NFT-and-digital-collectable-creation</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19021449/How-agencies-can-play-a-role-in-NFT-and-digital-collectable-creation"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global AI Software Market to Skyrocket to $251 Billion by 2027, Forecast Reveals]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19021459/Global-AI-Software-Market-to-Skyrocket-to-251-Billion-by-2027-Forecast-Reveals</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19021459/Global-AI-Software-Market-to-Skyrocket-to-251-Billion-by-2027-Forecast-Reveals"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T12:58:14.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Government Plans to Use AI to Reduce Ministerial Workload and Slim Down Civil Service]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19021411/Government-Plans-to-Use-AI-to-Reduce-Ministerial-Workload-and-Slim-Down-Civil-Service</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19021411/Government-Plans-to-Use-AI-to-Reduce-Ministerial-Workload-and-Slim-Down-Civil-Service"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T12:53:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent interview with The Sunday Times, Deputy Prime Minister Oliver Dowden revealed the government’s intention to harness artificial intelligence (AI) to assist ministers in reducing their workload and streamlining the civil service. Dowden highlighted ongoing efforts to implement AI...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stock Traded Miners Now Hold $1.3 Billion Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19021425/Stock-Traded-Miners-Now-Hold-13-Billion-Bitcoin</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19021425/Stock-Traded-Miners-Now-Hold-13-Billion-Bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T12:53:51.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uniswap (UNI) Bullish Pattern Breakout Targets $6: Details]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19021426/Uniswap-UNI-Bullish-Pattern-Breakout-Targets-6-Details</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19021426/Uniswap-UNI-Bullish-Pattern-Breakout-Targets-6-Details"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T12:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Uniswap's breakout of bull flag on its four-hour chart aligns with $6 target]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Breakthrough in Hardware-Accelerated Machine Learning for IoT Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19021390/A-Breakthrough-in-Hardware-Accelerated-Machine-Learning-for-IoT-Applications</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19021390/A-Breakthrough-in-Hardware-Accelerated-Machine-Learning-for-IoT-Applications"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T12:49:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Infineon Technologies AG, a leading semiconductor manufacturer, has recently launched the PSoC Edge microcontroller, an innovative solution designed to revolutionize the landscape of hardware-accelerated machine learning (ML) for various applications within the Internet of Things (IoT) and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ben Armstrong Claims Ex-Associates Hijacked His Identity and Stole Luxury Car]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19021391/Ben-Armstrong-Claims-Ex-Associates-Hijacked-His-Identity-and-Stole-Luxury-Car</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19021391/Ben-Armstrong-Claims-Ex-Associates-Hijacked-His-Identity-and-Stole-Luxury-Car"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T12:47:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency influencer Ben Armstrong has initiated legal proceedings against former associates, alleging misconduct that extends to the unlawful appropriation of his Lamborghini and threats to his person, as outlined in a recent filing at the Superior Court of Cobb County, Georgia. Armstrong,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple (XRP) IPO Rumors And Why the Company is Unlikely to Go Public This Year: Expert]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19021388/Ripple-XRP-IPO-Rumors-And-Why-the-Company-is-Unlikely-to-Go-Public-This-Year-Expert</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19021388/Ripple-XRP-IPO-Rumors-And-Why-the-Company-is-Unlikely-to-Go-Public-This-Year-Expert"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T12:46:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["I suggest we temper our expectations with regards to Ripple IPO," Yassin Mobarak said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More Than 700,000 New Bitcoin Addresses Created in a Single Day As BTC Flirts With $35,000: Crypto Trader]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19021396/More-Than-700000-New-Bitcoin-Addresses-Created-in-a-Single-Day-As-BTC-Flirts-With-35000-Crypto-Trader</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19021396/More-Than-700000-New-Bitcoin-Addresses-Created-in-a-Single-Day-As-BTC-Flirts-With-35000-Crypto-Trader"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T12:45:48.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Targets $46,000 As DXY Receives Kiss Of Death]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19021394/Bitcoin-Price-Targets-46000-As-DXY-Receives-Kiss-Of-Death</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19021394/Bitcoin-Price-Targets-46000-As-DXY-Receives-Kiss-Of-Death"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T12:45:08.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South African Financial Giant Says It Will Inject Capital Into ZARP Stablecoin Network]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a0cc1ff5</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/south-african-financial-giant-says-it-will-inject-capital-into-zarp-stablecoin-network/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T12:38:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[South Africa’s Old Mutual Wealth and financial services provider Inves Capital recently revealed plans to inject liquidity into the ZARP stablecoin network. Inves Capital’s managing director said “crypto is entering a new phase” of growth and ZARP is set to “play a central role.”
 
‘Substantial Liquidity’ to Be Injected Into the ZARP Network
 
South African financial services giant Old Mutual Wealth and Inves Capital recently revealed their plan to financially back the zarp stablecoin project. In addition, the two organizations reportedly pledged to promote its use in decentralized finance (defi) protocols.
 
According to a Globalcrypto TV report, the planned injection of “substantial” of liquidity into the ZARP network would broaden Old Mutual Wealth’s relationship with the stablecoin project. As previously reported by Bitcoin.com News, the financial services giant has been the manager of the stablecoin project’s cash reserves since Sept. 2022.
 

 
Commenting on the two companies’ decision to enhance support for the stablecoin, Simon Dingle, the managing director Inves Capital, said:
 
“We are now extending our relationship to explore new frontiers in decentralised finance and provide deep liquidity to emerging capital markets. Crypto is entering a new phase of growth and ZARP is braced to play a central role in representing rand value in these exciting new protocols.”
 
Dingle, who also manages the stablecoin, suggested that South Africa’s decision to designate crypto assets as a financial product may have played a part in convincing Old Mutual and his firm.
 
Farhad Sader, the managing director of Old Mutual, said seeing “the potential application of the technology first-hand” made the decision to honor its pledge to extend its partnership with the stablecoin project easier.
 
Register your email here to get a weekly update on African news sent to your inbox:
 
 
What are your thoughts on this story? Let us know what you think in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SwissGold Crypto AG Launches Gold-Backed NFTs for Wealth Preservation]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a0cd9160</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/swissgold-crypto-ag-launches-gold-backed-nfts-for-wealth-preservation/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T12:28:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. Zug, Switzerland – SwissGold Crypto AG, a Swiss-regulated crypto issuer, introduces a novel solution to the wealth preservation challenge in times of inflation and uncertainty: gold-backed non-fungible tokens (NFTs).
 
Gold’s enduring stability, in contrast to depreciating fiat currencies, has made it a trusted wealth preserver for centuries. Following the US President’s 1971 decision to abandon the gold standard, major fiat currencies have suffered substantial devaluation, with the dollar losing as much as 97% of its value against gold.
 
As inflation rates rise, interest in alternative assets such as gold and cryptocurrencies has surged. While cryptocurrencies are volatile, gold remains a stable and reliable refuge in times of crisis, hyperinflation, conflict, or natural d…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Lead Dev Reveals The Next Step In Fulfilling Founder’s Vision]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a0ced6a3</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-lead-dev-on-fulfilling-founders-vision/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T12:20:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shytoshi Kusama, the anonymous Lead Developer for Shiba Inu, has shed more light on the future of SHIB and how the team intends to fulfill Shiba Inu founder Ryoshi’s vision in a foundational blog post dubbed Shibarium: The Foundational blog.
 
Shiba Inu Lead Developer On Founder’s Vision
 
The lead dev started off by highlighting some details about the decentralized nature of Shiba Inu in the blog post. However, more information on the project’s decentralized nature can be found in the Final Worldpaper. 
 
In the blog post, Shytoshi Kusama noted that the founder’s initial vision can be narrowed down to a simple mission of using Shiba Inu to save the world. However, the lead dev stated that the structural designs for fulfilling Ryoshi’s vision are complete and already on their way to being …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Godspower Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cogwise Real-Time Trading AI Model’s Test Phase Brilliance: Averaging 16.8% Weekly Returns]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a0c8bfed</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/cogwise-real-time-trading-ai-models-test-phase-brilliance-averaging-16-8-weekly-returns/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T12:08:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a groundbreaking development for the world of finance and investment, the Cogwise AI team has unveiled a cutting-edge feature that is poised to change the way traders make decisions. The innovative “AI News Aggregator” integrates advanced artificial intelligence and machine learning algorithms to provide real-time analysis of news and global trends, as well as predictions regarding the future movements of specific stocks and cryptocurrencies tied to the news. By monitoring an extensive array of news articles and social media posts from various sources in real-time, this trading bot identifies keywords and trends to predict how news events may influence particular stocks or cryptocurrencies. This revolutionary technology offers traders a distinct advantage by enabling them to stay ahead …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's Next for Sam Bankman-Fried's Legal Case?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a0ca9b40</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/11/07/whats-next-for-sam-bankman-frieds-legal-case/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T11:56:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The story of "United States v. Sam Bankman-Fried" isn't quite over yet. Now that he's been found guilty on seven different charges, a few different things are going to happen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SHIB, DOGE Top Open Futures Rankings as Bitcoin Rally Spurs Risk-Taking]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a0ca9b2c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/11/07/shib-doge-top-open-futures-rankings-as-bitcoin-rally-spurs-risk-taking/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T11:56:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SHIB and DOGE have seen highest percentage growth in futures open interest since Nov. 1, outshining bitcoin and ether in a sign of increased investor risk appetite in the crypto market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP, Cardano And Solana Lead Crypto Gains Over the Week]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204640</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204640/xrp-cardano-and-solana-lead-crypto-gains-over-the-week"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T11:05:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several altcoins are riding high, with XRP, ADA, and SOL all posting double-digit gains over the week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Insider Says Fraud Revelations Will Come In ‘Weeks Not Months’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a0b3065b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-fraud-revelations-weeks-not-months/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T11:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Steven Nerayoff, an attorney and former advisor to Ethereum (ETH), has made a series of alarming allegations against the platform’s founders, Vitalik Buterin and Joseph Lubin. As per a report from Bitcoinist, Nerayoff asserts that the extent of fraud in the Ethereum ecosystem surpasses the scale of the infamous FTX scandal involving Sam Bankman-Fried.
 
Nerayoff, in a statement, emphasized the severity of the alleged fraud, saying, “Ethereum is the fraudulent elephant in the room in plain sight 1000x bigger than SBF.”
 
His comments come as part of a broader campaign where he has been hinting at the release of evidence implicating Buterin and Lubin in significant fraudulent activities.
 
Alleged Ethereum Fraud Evidence To Be Published Soon
 
For months, Nerayoff has been hinting at his eff…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s Role as ‘Digital Gold’ Will Aid Further Demand, Traders Say]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a0b37123</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/11/07/bitcoins-role-as-digital-gold-will-aid-further-demand-traders-say/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T10:57:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Traders continue to point out bitcoin’s supposed role as ‘digital gold,’ amid economic headwinds in the U.S., as a possible price catalyst.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China Mulls Digital Yuan Settlements for Commodities]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a0bee158</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/china-mulls-digital-yuan-settlements-for-commodities/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T10:34:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The People’s Bank of China (PBOC) is considering using the digital yuan to settle services and commodities trades with Hong Kong. According to Di Gang, deputy director-general of the Digital Currency Institute of the PBOC, this would help companies avoid the difficulties of using a single high-cost, cross-border payment channel.
 
People’s Bank of China Eyes Digital Yuan Usage for Commodities and Services Settlements
 
The People’s Bank of China (PBOC) is examining the potential application of the Chinese central bank digital currency (CBDC), the digital yuan, for commodities and services settlements with Hong Kong. Di Gang, deputy director-general of the Digital Currency Institute of the PBOC, revealed the bank was considering this use case during the Hong Kong Fintech Week, an Asian fina…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Market Share Shake-Up: Binance's Spot Trading Slips to 40%]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a0b8251e</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/market-share-shake-up-binances-spot-trading-slips-to-40/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T10:26:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In  
a recent report by blockchain analytics firm 0xScope, a striking development in  
the cryptocurrency exchange landscape has been unveiled. The report, released  
on November 6, highlighted a significant decline in Binance's market share over  
the past year, attributing it to a possible shift in the exchange's listing  
strategy.
Binance's Market Share Trends
Binance  
has witnessed a notable decrease in its spot trading market share, which has  
dropped to 40% in late 2023 from 62% just a year ago. It means the firm has  
lost one-third of its market share in the past 12 months. The report also underscored  
the rise of the Korean crypto exchange Upbit, which has made gains during the  
same period. Upbit's spot market share surged from 5% to 15.3%.
When  
considering all crypto trad…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tareq Sikder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not Interested? Why SEC Can’t Find Crypto Experts To Work With The Agency]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a0ba9930</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-sec-struggles-to-hire-crypto-analysts/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T10:09:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) is facing a growing challenge in filling vacant Crypto Assets Specialist positions within its ranks. The Office of the Inspector General (OIG) of the SEC recently published its “2023 SEC OIG Management and Performance Challenges” report, shedding light on the persistent issue of staff shortages in the SEC’s digital currency division. 
 
With the regulatory body seeking to strengthen its oversight capabilities in the rapidly expanding world of crypto-assets, the shortage of qualified professionals has become a critical concern.
 
As of Sept. 30, 2023, the SEC reported that out of the 5,303 authorized positions in its office, a staggering 491 remained unfilled. This trend of increasing vacancy rates has persisted for the past four years, raisin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ben 'Bitboy' Armstrong Calls Himself a Victim in Latest Court Filing]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a0bb0adf</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/11/07/ben-bitboy-armstrong-calls-himself-a-victim-in-latest-court-filing/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T10:06:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The infleuncer formerly known as Bitboy has filed a lawsuit against several executives at his former employer alleging threats and coercion, and is asking for his Lamborghini back.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Ordinals Protocol Token ORDI Rockets 50% on Binance Listing]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a0a5d861</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/11/07/bitcoin-ordinals-protocol-token-ordi-rockets-50-on-binance-listing/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T09:47:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ordinals protocol lets users issue tokens, artwork, text, audio and video on the Bitcoin blockchain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Tax Platform Blockpit Buys Rival Accointing From Glassnode]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a0a1c405</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/11/07/crypto-tax-platform-blockpit-buys-rival-accointing-from-glassnode/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T09:19:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The "multi-million dollar" acquisition gives Austria-based Blockpit a footprint in the U.K.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t Rule Ethereum Out Yet: Institutional Investors Are Back With Massive Inflows]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a0a3574f</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-institutional-investors/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T09:08:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week, digital investment products saw a 6th consecutive week of inflows, pushing inflows into Ethereum to its highest point in more than a year. Ethereum’s price is also up by 5.72% in a 7-day timeframe, indicating the smart contract platform is now in a largely bullish sentiment.
 
Digital asset investment products have been witnessing inflows since the end of September and throughout October, mirroring the bullish sentiment in the larger crypto market.
 
Ethereum Sees Largest Inflow of Institutional Funds Since August 2022
 
After several months of lackluster interest and continued outflows from the institutional landscape, it appears major investors are gaining confidence in Ethereum once more. The latest weekly report from CoinShares shows digital asset investment products saw inf…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$300 Million Crypto Scam: Indian Authorities Arrest 8 Cops]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a0ad1338</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/300-million-crypto-scam-indian-authorities-arrest-8-cops/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T08:55:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Indian authorities have made eight fresh arrests in connection with a $300 million cryptocurrency scam that duped around 100,000 people, according to local news outlet The Times of India.
Unrevealing of a Massive Crypto Scam
Four police officers are among the most recent individuals who have been arrested. However, the rank or identity of those arrested remains unknown. The massive scam came to light in late September, and since then, the Indian authorities have made 18 arrests. However, its mastermind, Subhash Sharma, is still at large.
According to local reports, the crypto scam started in India in 2018. Its victims include 5,000 government officials and around 1,000 police personnel in a northern state of the country. In the past two years, around 56 complaints were filed against th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arnab Shome</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aave V2 Ethereum Market and Several Assets Paused — Team Says ‘No Funds Are at Risk’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a0afe4bb</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/aave-v2-ethereum-market-and-several-assets-paused-team-says-no-funds-are-at-risk/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T08:34:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The decentralized finance (defi) protocol Aave’s so-called guardian said on Nov. 4 it had paused the Aave V2 Ethereum Market and frozen “certain assets on Aave V3 on Polygon, Arbitrum, Optimism.” At the time when the update was issued, Aave said an analysis of what happened would be made available when the issue is resolved.
 
‘Temporary Prevention Measure’
 
On Nov. 4 the guardian of Aave, the open-source and non-custodial liquidity protocol, paused the Aave V2 Ethereum Market and certain assets on Aave V2 on Avalanche. It also froze assets on Aave 3 on three chains, namely: Polygon, Arbitrum and Optimism. The step, which has been framed as a “temporary prevention measure,” was taken after the Aave team received a report concerning the protocol.
 
 
Today we received a report of an issue …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Traders Are Earning 165% Yields By Staking a Token Named After Elon Musk’s Pet]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a0a915cd</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/11/07/crypto-traders-are-earning-165-yields-by-staking-a-token-named-after-elon-musks-pet/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T08:25:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers are trying to capture a piece of the global asset tokenization market as part of a new product in the Floki ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano and Polkadot Become Partner Chains, Key Insights Revealed]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a091d4c7</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/cardano-polkadot-partner-chains/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T07:17:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano and Polkadot have announced a strategic partnership, marking a significant milestone in the evolution of blockchain interoperability and scalability. This collaboration between two of the leading blockchain platforms is set to have far-reaching implications for the Web3 space.
 
Polkadot, in a recent tweet, emphasized the scope of this partnership: “Cardano will use Substrate, the foundation of the Polkadot SDK, to build out its ‘partner chain’ project — showcasing Substrate’s potential to expand across Web3, and its ease of use for other chains and ecosystems.”
 
Input Output Global (IOG), the driving force behind ADA, expressed high regard for Substrate. In a statement, they referred to it as a “proven open-source modular framework,” and announced their intention to contribute a …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best NFT Gags and References From the Viral 'Simpsons' Episode]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204605</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204605/best-nft-moments-from-viral-simpsons-episode"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T02:13:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From PFP collections like CryptoPunks to specific digital art references, the newest 'The Simpsons' episode dove deep into the NFT ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFT Traders Respond to 'Simpsons' Roasting by Spending Millions on Knockoff Collectibles]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204558</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204558/nft-traders-respond-simpsons-roasting-spending-millions-knockoff-collectibles"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T00:05:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Simpsons-themed NFT projects surged on Monday after the seminal sitcom bashed digital collectibles in the latest episode.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Good, the Bad, and the Ugly of Grok, Elon Musk's New AI Chatbot]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204584</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204584/the-good-the-bad-and-the-ugly-of-grok-elon-musks-new-ai-chatbot"/>
        <updated>2023-11-06T23:52:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is Elon Musk's latest tech marvel just another chatbot in the AI crowd?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yuga Labs Social Lead Resigns After Racist, Antisemitic Tweets Resurface]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204598</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204598/yuga-labs-bored-apes-bayc-employee-racist-antisemitic-tweets"/>
        <updated>2023-11-06T23:38:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bored Ape Yacht Club confirmed that the former employee resigned following social media backlash.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ava Labs Confirms Layoffs, Affecting 12% of Avalanche Studio's Employees]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204581</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204581/ava-labs-employees-report-layoffs-many-people-affected"/>
        <updated>2023-11-06T22:54:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ava Labs cuts, which occurred Monday, have reportedly impacted numerous teams including communications and marketing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Singularity Is Less Than 10 Years Away, Says AI Veteran]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204571</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204571/artificial-intelligence-singularity-ai-ben-goertzel-singularitynet"/>
        <updated>2023-11-06T22:39:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SingularityNET CEO Ben Goertzel discusses the inevitable next phase of AI evolution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ben ‘Bitboy’ Armstrong Really Wants His Lambo Back, Files Another Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204570</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204570/ben-bitboy-armstrong-really-wants-his-lambo-back-files-another-lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2023-11-06T22:17:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The YouTuber’s legal battles continue as a sixth complaint emerges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reddit Discovers Caroline Ellison May Have Appeared on 'Arthur'—And Is Predictably Ruthless]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204544</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204544/reddit-discovers-caroline-ellison-appeared-arthur-predictably-ruthless"/>
        <updated>2023-11-06T22:05:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blog linked to Caroline Ellison also reveals the disgraced ex-Alameda CEO may harbor frustration about her elementary school years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Warns Bitcoin SV Holders: Withdraw or Be Liquidated]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204564</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204564/coinbase-warns-bitcoin-sv-holders-liquidated"/>
        <updated>2023-11-06T22:02:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Those still holding Bitcoin SV on America’s biggest crypto exchange have until January 9 to withdraw it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vertu’s Luxury Crypto Phone is ‘Passport to the Web3 World’: CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204530</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204530/vertus-luxury-crypto-phone-is-passport-to-the-web3-world-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-11-06T20:29:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Metavertu II features Web3 tech including a decentralized identity system and secure element chip with ZK smarts—wrapped in alligator skin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s Everything OpenAI Announced at Its First Dev Day]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204516</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204516/heres-everything-announced-at-openais-dev-day"/>
        <updated>2023-11-06T20:23:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Led by CEO Sam Altman, OpenAI unveiled several new upgrades and tools to its suite of AI models, including ChatGPT.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI Unleashes GPT-4 Turbo, Expands Chatbot Customizability]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204515</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204515/openai-unleashes-gpt-4-turbo-expands-chatbot-customizability"/>
        <updated>2023-11-06T19:50:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The industry leader in generative AI chatbots, OpenAI's next update promises more nuanced, human-like conversations for more precise applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Pinch Nearly $1 Million in Crypto Via Fake Ledger App on Microsoft App Store]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204506</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204506/fake-ledger-app-microsoft-app-store-zachxbt"/>
        <updated>2023-11-06T19:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft’s official App Store served up fraudulent code crafted by crypto crooks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['The Simpsons' Skewered NFTs—But Not Before Cashing In on the Craze]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204491</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204491/simpsons-skewered-nfts-not-before-cashing-craze"/>
        <updated>2023-11-06T18:56:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NFTs were a punchline on 'The Simpsons' this weekend. But in 2021, the iconic show sold golden, Bart-themed digital collectibles to its fans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xbox Embraces Generative AI as Microsoft Unveils Tools for Game Devs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204480</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204480/xbox-embraces-generative-ai-microsoft-unveils-tools-game-devs"/>
        <updated>2023-11-06T17:24:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft and portfolio company Inworld AI are creating an AI toolkit for Xbox game developers to use AI to craft game dialogue and quests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Is Phantom Galaxies Releasing Two Versions of Its Game?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QtnWGSSJ/why-is-phantom-galaxies-releasing-two-versions-of-its-game</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QtnWGSSJ/why-is-phantom-galaxies-releasing-two-versions-of-its-game"/>
        <updated>2023-11-06T17:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animoca Brands-owned Blowfish Studios is building a space mech pilot game called Phantom Galaxies. Blowfish Cofounder Ben Lee tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about his plans for the game's release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum and Other Crypto Funds Nab $767 Million in Just 6 Weeks]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204481</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204481/bitcoin-ethereum-and-other-crypto-funds-nab-767-million-just-6-weeks"/>
        <updated>2023-11-06T17:05:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Institutions are showing sustained interest in crypto investment products, pushing a six-week inflows streak to $767 million.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Leads Crypto Market Rally, Soaring 12% Overnight]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204439</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204439/xrp-leads-crypto-market-rally-soaring-overnight"/>
        <updated>2023-11-06T15:49:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XRP is right now the biggest winner out of the top 20 biggest coins and tokens.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Self-Custodial Wallets Could Challenge Stablecoin Issuers' Ability to Satisfy Regulations: BoE]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204446</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204446/self-custodial-wallets-could-challenge-stablecoin-issuers-ability-satisfy-regulations-boe"/>
        <updated>2023-11-06T15:13:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bank of England's latest paper examines the regulatory challenges posed by unhosted crypto wallets in an economy powered by stablecoins.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is XRP? The Cryptocurrency Created by Ripple Founders]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=5709</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/ripple"/>
        <updated>2023-11-06T15:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XRP is a type of cryptocurrency designed to help banks move money more quickly, and cheaply than existing methods. It is largely spearheaded by Ripple.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Hussey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ApeFest Attendees Report Experiencing Eye Pain, Yuga Labs Says 'Less Than 1%' Affected]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204435</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204435/yuga-labs-says-less-than-1-apefest-attendees-suffering-eye-damage"/>
        <updated>2023-11-06T13:29:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yuga Labs told Decrypt that of the 2,250 ApeFest attendees, it has only been in direct contact with 15 people who claim to have been affected.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bored Ape Creator Yuga Labs and Magic Eden Launching Ethereum NFT Marketplace That Enforces Royalties]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204403</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204403/bored-ape-creator-yuga-labs-magic-eden-launching-ethereum-nft-marketplace-enforces-royalties"/>
        <updated>2023-11-04T12:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Magic Eden’s new Ethereum NFT marketplace will be “contractually obligated” to pay royalties. What does that mean for traders?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Predicts the End of All Jobs—Google AI Exec Disagrees]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204398</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204398/elon-musk-predicts-the-end-of-all-jobs-google-ai-exec-disagrees"/>
        <updated>2023-11-04T00:56:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DeepMind co-founder Mustafa Suleyman rebutted Musk's predictions at the AI Safety Summit in the UK.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Says xAI Chatbot Is ‘The Best that Currently Exists’ Ahead of Trial Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204388</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204388/elon-musk-says-xais-chatbot-is-ready-to-launch-calls-it-the-best-that-currently-exists"/>
        <updated>2023-11-03T21:17:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk is opening up xAI to a select group of users as he challenges OpenAI and ChatGPT.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Bitcoin Rally Cools and Solana Explodes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204370</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204370/this-week-in-coins-bitcoin-rally-cools-and-solana-explodes"/>
        <updated>2023-11-03T21:01:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s ETF hype-inspired rally may have run out of steam, but several leading altcoins still surged.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Sweepstakes Case Heads to the Supreme Court]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204381</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204381/dogecoin-sweepstakes-case-heads-to-the-supreme-court"/>
        <updated>2023-11-03T20:56:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Coinbase promotion tried to harness the popularity and whimsy of the memecoin, but participants say they missed the fine print.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt AI, Edited by Ryan Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFTs Are Back? Sales Jump 32% in October, Led by Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204379</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204379/nfts-back-sales-jump-32-october-led-ethereum-dappradar"/>
        <updated>2023-11-03T20:49:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After months of falling sales, the NFT market grew substantially in October, per data from DappRadar—even if it's still far from the peak.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Caroline Ellison and Sam Bankman-Fried’s Other Co-Defendants Go to Prison?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204376</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204376/caroline-ellison-sam-bankman-fried-co-defendants-prison"/>
        <updated>2023-11-03T20:18:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite delivering key testimony against their former boss, Caroline Ellison, Nishad Singh, and Gary Wang are each still facing decades behind bars.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenSea Slashes NFT Marketplace Staff by 50%]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204371</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204371/opensea-slashes-nft-marketplace-staff-50-layoffs"/>
        <updated>2023-11-03T19:13:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NFT marketplace OpenSea, valued at $13.3 billion in 2022, confirmed Friday that it has laid off about half of its staff.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoin Supply Has Bottomed Out—Is It Bullish for Crypto?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204360</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204360/stablecoin-supply-bottoms-out-bullish-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-11-03T18:51:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Investors are turning their cold hard cash into cold hard stablecoins. Next to rising prices, does this mark the beginning of a new bull?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Is Giving Away Free Gaming NFTs—Here's How to Claim]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151872</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151872/amazon-giving-away-free-gaming-nfts-how-claim"/>
        <updated>2023-11-03T18:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATE: Brawlers enters the ring with Amazon Prime Gaming, offering a free NFT fighter and other perks, while Mojo Melee launches a new NFT.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Is Handing Over Customer Crypto Trading Data to the FBI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204336</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204336/ftx-handing-over-customer-crypto-trading-data-fbi"/>
        <updated>2023-11-03T17:32:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Court records show that FTX bankruptcy advisers have given FBI offices information on customer accounts. What does that mean?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase 'Ready to Hit the Ground Running' on Bitcoin ETF Approval, Says COO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204329</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204329/coinbase-ready-hit-ground-running-bitcoin-etf-approval-coo"/>
        <updated>2023-11-03T15:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto analysts have speculated a spot Bitcoin ETF would be good for the asset's price, but Coinbase's COO underscored stability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Solana? A Scalable, Decentralized Network for Dapps]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=70377</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-solana-a-scalable-decentralized-network-for-dapps"/>
        <updated>2023-11-03T15:26:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana boasts impressive speeds and a burgeoning dapp ecosystem, but it's still on the proving grounds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Phillips,Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Drops 5% as FTX-Linked Address Moves SOL to Kraken, Binance]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204289</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204289/solana-plummets-ftx-linked-address-moves-sol-kraken-binance"/>
        <updated>2023-11-03T15:07:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FTX-linked addresses have had a busy 24 hours, with several large Solana transfers headed for some of the industry's largest exchanges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's Old Is New Again as Fortnite Goes 'OG' With Original Island]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=204320</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/204320/whats-old-new-again-fortnite-goes-og-original-island"/>
        <updated>2023-11-03T14:55:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fortnite gets an old-school overhaul with the new OG throwback season. Here’s what to expect from the popular shooter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sophie Maxx on NFTs, Augmented Reality, and Fashion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/VByufHjn/sophie-maxx-on-nfts-augmented-reality-and-fashion</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/VByufHjn/sophie-maxx-on-nfts-augmented-reality-and-fashion"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T23:37:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week our host is joined by Sophie Maxx (Web3Maxx) to discuss NFTs, augmented reality, the metaverse, how blockchain is sneaking into the fashion world, and more!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Questions With SCENE: Kevin Rose]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/u9LDX8Vr/5-questions-with-scene-kevin-rose</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/u9LDX8Vr/5-questions-with-scene-kevin-rose"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kevin Rose, co-founder and CEO of PROOF and co-creator of the hit Moonbirds NFT collection, joins 5 Questions with SCENE to answer some hard-hitting questions about his childhood dreams, his wife’s candy preferences, and his undying love of rap music.

Video shot and edited by Vincent Roazzi Jr.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Happened to Atari's Token? Inside Atari's Blockchain Plans]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/7OtQIdqa/what-happened-to-ataris-token-inside-ataris-blockchain-plans</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/7OtQIdqa/what-happened-to-ataris-token-inside-ataris-blockchain-plans"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T18:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin chats with Atari X director Tyler Drewitz about what happened with Atari's token plans, whether a token is coming, and what Atari games might be getting the blockchain treatment. Oh, and there's lots of Easter eggs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitch CEO Dan Clancy Is a 'Wild Card,' Says Marketing Director]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/qCOCtPKe/twitch-ceo-dan-clancy-is-a-wild-card-says-marketing-director</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/qCOCtPKe/twitch-ceo-dan-clancy-is-a-wild-card-says-marketing-director"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T20:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twitch Senior Director of Community Marketing Mary Kish speaks with Decrypt's Kate Irwin about Twitch CEO Dan Clancy, Ninja, Twitch's new simulcasting rules, the biggest differences between Twitch and rival platform Kick, and the role of esports on the streaming platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why NFT Paris has Launched a Loyalty Token]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/91tPVJff/why-nft-paris-has-launched-a-loyalty-token</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/91tPVJff/why-nft-paris-has-launched-a-loyalty-token"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T13:26:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NFT Paris founder Alexandre Tsydenkov told Decrypt what to expect from the upcoming 2024 edition of the conference, the launch of its loyalty token and its plans to create a Web3 loyalty program that rewards the most engaged members of the community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Game Review—Formula E: High Voltage Is a Fun Play-to-Earn Racer That Lacks Direction]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/hzkx0TDg/game-reviewformula-e-high-voltage-is-a-fun-play-to-earn-racer-that-lacks-direction</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/hzkx0TDg/game-reviewformula-e-high-voltage-is-a-fun-play-to-earn-racer-that-lacks-direction"/>
        <updated>2023-10-29T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Formula E: High Voltage is a play-to-earn racing game with a distinctive strategic approach. Decrypt contributor Ryan Gladwin put Animoca's web-based game through its paces in this review, highlighting the unique gameplay design, the role of NFTs and crypto, and where the game currently comes up short.

Follow Decrypt's GG on Twitter: https://twitter.com/ggdecrypt 

Check out GG for daily gaming news: https://decrypt.co/gg 

Subscribe to our GG newsletter with over 50,000 subscribers: https://decrypt.co/newsletters/gg 

Join our official Discord: https://discord.com/invite/3bc4QpA57C]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amanda Cassatt on Web3 Marketing and the early days of Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5Cm0ENyc/amanda-cassatt-on-web3-marketing-and-the-early-days-of-ethereum</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5Cm0ENyc/amanda-cassatt-on-web3-marketing-and-the-early-days-of-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T16:40:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week's episode, our host is joined by Amanda Cassatt! 

Amanda is the founder of Serotonin, a web3 marketing agency, the author of the first book ever published on web3 marketing, and led the marketing team that helped bring Ethereum to market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Midnight Society's Rob Bowling on Deadrop's New Cars and User-Generated Modes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/A0auyZzn/midnight-societys-rob-bowling-on-deadrops-new-cars-and-user-generated-modes</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/A0auyZzn/midnight-societys-rob-bowling-on-deadrops-new-cars-and-user-generated-modes"/>
        <updated>2023-10-22T01:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt reporter and GG producer Kate Irwin interviews Midnight Society Studio Head Rob Bowling about Deadrop's development and Snapshot VII.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Game Review: 'Raini: The Lords of Light' Brands Itself With Memes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/32YyJHCJ/game-review-raini-the-lords-of-light-brands-itself-with-memes</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/32YyJHCJ/game-review-raini-the-lords-of-light-brands-itself-with-memes"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T19:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Raini: Lords of Light is an NFT-optional card game bursting with crypto memes. From SBF to CZ and Elon, this free-to-play game has some truly wild animations. Decrypt contributor Ryan S. Gladwin shares his honest thoughts on the game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Art Blocks Marfa Weekend Recap]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/QaTBP6eO/art-blocks-marfa-weekend-recap</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/QaTBP6eO/art-blocks-marfa-weekend-recap"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T19:19:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Relive the Art Blocks Marfa Weekend 2023 event with this highlights video, produced by Vincent Roazzi Jr. for Decrypt Studios in partnership with Art Blocks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Phantom Galaxies: A Look Inside the Mech Shooter NFT Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QI1uDwQv/phantom-galaxies-a-look-inside-the-mech-shooter-nft-game</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QI1uDwQv/phantom-galaxies-a-look-inside-the-mech-shooter-nft-game"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T21:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animoca Brands and game studio Blowfish are developing Phantom Galaxies, an upcoming sci-fi mech shooter game inspired by mech battlers like Transformers. Decrypt's Kate Irwin asks Blowfish Studios Cofounder and Managing Director Ben Lee about what it's like to play the game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Clip: DeepMedia's DeepID Deepfake Detection Tool at Work]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/m4Vy4vhC/clip-deepmedias-deepid-deepfake-detection-tool-at-work</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/m4Vy4vhC/clip-deepmedias-deepid-deepfake-detection-tool-at-work"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T16:48:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A clip showcasing how DeepMedia's DeepID deepfake detection tool works. Courtesy: DeepMedia]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentraland AI World Fair Trailer]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/3tUb56Fv/decentraland-ai-world-fair-trailer</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/3tUb56Fv/decentraland-ai-world-fair-trailer"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A trailer for the AI World Fair event in metaverse game Decentraland, taking place from October 25-27. Courtesy: Decentraland.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BackTheBunny - Money, Conspiracy, Milady]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BRoKZzer/backthebunny-money-conspiracy-milady</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BRoKZzer/backthebunny-money-conspiracy-milady"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T19:48:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our host Reza Jafery sits down with BackTheBunny to dive deep into money, the fight against crypto that we're witnessing in real-time, and milady culture. 

Our Host: https://twitter.com/rezajafery
Our Guest: https://twitter.com/BackTheBunny

Our Sponsors
https://decrypt.co/1000x]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['A Grand Experiment': Shrapnel Studio Head Don Norbury Talks Game Economics]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Z2OMMsC5/a-grand-experiment-shrapnel-studio-head-don-norbury-talks-game-economics</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Z2OMMsC5/a-grand-experiment-shrapnel-studio-head-don-norbury-talks-game-economics"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T17:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How much of Shrapnel's in-game items are tradeable NFTs? Don Norbury, Studio Head at Shrapnel and CTO at game studio NEON, tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about Shrapnel's approach to game economics, including different game pricing models and how NFT game economies create different challenges for developers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trezor Safe 3 and Trezor Keep Metal Unboxing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/IjqnO9pR/trezor-safe-3-and-trezor-keep-metal-unboxing</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/IjqnO9pR/trezor-safe-3-and-trezor-keep-metal-unboxing"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T14:45:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trezor has launched the Safe 3, a hardware wallet aimed at "new entrants to crypto," alongside the new Keep Metal recovery seed storage device. We take a first look at what comes in the box.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why AI Arena is Building on Arbitrum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Gl80TQOm/why-ai-arena-is-building-on-arbitrum</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Gl80TQOm/why-ai-arena-is-building-on-arbitrum"/>
        <updated>2023-10-12T14:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI Arena CEO Brandon Da Silva and COO Wei Xie discuss the challenges that come with building on Ethereum, ETH sidechains, and layer-two blockchains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pet3rPan_ on venture DAOs and blockchain games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DawNLI3O/pet3rpan-on-venture-daos-and-blockchain-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DawNLI3O/pet3rpan-on-venture-daos-and-blockchain-games"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T18:24:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the 4th episode of this time will be different.

Our guest for today's episode is Pet3rpan_ from Metacartel, 1kx, HydraVentures, and more!

https://twitter.com/pet3rpan_

This Time Will Be Different is sponsored by 1000x
https://decrypt.co/1000x]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>