<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-09-30T06:17:49.828Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-09-30T06:17:49.828Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Buenos Aires to Bring Blockchain-Based Digital ID to Millions of Citizens]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b88a1668</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/buenos-aires-to-bring-blockchain-based-digital-id-to-millions-of-citizens/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T06:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The city of Buenos Aires has announced that it will roll out a blockchain-based, privacy-focused digital ID wallet starting in October. The Quarkid project, previously known as Tangoid, will allow its users to download a “self-sovereign” wallet to hold their birth and marriage certificates, with more digital documents to be added later this year.
Buenos Aires to Roll Out Blockchain-Based ID Program
The City of Buenos Aires government announced the deployment of a digital, blockchain-based “self-sovereign” ID project for its citizens. The wallet, called Quarkid, formerly known as Tangoid and scheduled to be operating by last January, will supposedly allow its users to exert full ownership of their data, granting only trusted and permissioned third parties access.
The Quarkid wallet will use…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried’s lawyer challenges US gov’t proposed jury questions]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18938660/Sam-Bankman-Frieds-lawyer-challenges-US-govt-proposed-jury-questions</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18938660/Sam-Bankman-Frieds-lawyer-challenges-US-govt-proposed-jury-questions"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T05:51:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried’s lawyer asserts that the proposed questions already insinuate his guilt in fraud and money laundering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spot Bitcoin ETFs Will Move the Needle for Institutional Adoption of Digital Assets in the U.S.]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18938637/Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-Will-Move-the-Needle-for-Institutional-Adoption-of-Digital-Assets-in-the-US</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18938637/Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-Will-Move-the-Needle-for-Institutional-Adoption-of-Digital-Assets-in-the-US"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T04:38:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spot Bitcoin and Ether ETFs available through trusted traditional financial institutions will break down barriers and streamline mainstream adoption]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arbitrum: Why traders should consider investing in ARB this quarter]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18938636/Arbitrum-Why-traders-should-consider-investing-in-ARB-this-quarter</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18938636/Arbitrum-Why-traders-should-consider-investing-in-ARB-this-quarter"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T04:30:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arbitrum might be entering a phase of aggressive growth. As such, it is important to keep track of key metrics that may offer insights into its trajectory.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ordinals Community Grapples With Numbering Controversy]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18938631/Ordinals-Community-Grapples-With-Numbering-Controversy</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18938631/Ordinals-Community-Grapples-With-Numbering-Controversy"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T04:29:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Ordinals Creator Casey Rodarmor Has Proposed To Make Ordinal Numbers ‘Unstable’ and Renumber All Existing Inscriptions]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried Trial: A Colossal Legal Showdown Starts Next Week]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b8734dfe</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/sam-bankman-fried-trial-a-colossal-legal-showdown-starts-next-week/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T04:08:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A calendar has been set for the upcoming trial of United States v. Bankman-Fried, with jury selection beginning October 3, 2023. The FTX founder, Sam Bankman-Fried, was denied temporary release from prison but will be allowed to use an “air-gapped,” internet-disabled laptop for note-taking in the courtroom. In the coming month and a half, the public will likely hear testimonies from FTX senior personnel such as Zixiao (Gary) Wang, Caroline Ellison, Nishad Singh, and Ryan Salame.
 
The Bankman-Fried Trial Kickoff
 
Next week, the co-founder and former FTX CEO Sam Bankman-Fried is set to face trial following charges leveled by the U.S. government. The litany of accusations against him includes wire fraud conspiracy, wire fraud, commodities fraud conspiracy, securities fraud conspiracy, and m…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Savings DAI Surpasses $1B TVL, But DAI Remains In Decline]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18938618/Savings-DAI-Surpasses-1B-TVL-But-DAI-Remains-In-Decline</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18938618/Savings-DAI-Surpasses-1B-TVL-But-DAI-Remains-In-Decline"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T03:48:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[sDAI TVL up 1,170% while DAI supply down 13% since mid-June]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOJ's Proposed Jury Questions 'Risks Tainting' Bankman-Fried's Panel, Defense Says]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b87f7e3f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/09/30/dojs-proposed-jury-questions-risks-tainting-bankman-frieds-panel-defense-says/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T03:13:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried's attorneys objected to some of the U.S. Department of Justice's proposed voir dire questions in a late Friday filing, saying they may miss potential juror bias or otherwise lead to jurors making assumptions about the case.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BRICS Reviewing Global Payments System to Bypass US Dollar and Circumvent SWIFT: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18938597/BRICS-Reviewing-Global-Payments-System-to-Bypass-US-Dollar-and-Circumvent-SWIFT-Report</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18938597/BRICS-Reviewing-Global-Payments-System-to-Bypass-US-Dollar-and-Circumvent-SWIFT-Report"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T03:08:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The global economic alliance known as BRICS is reportedly considering the launch of a global payments system that could sidestep the banking industry standard SWIFT. According to a new report from the Russian state-funded news organization TASS, the group’s finance ministers are evaluating the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Popular Analyst Forecasts Potential $XRP Price Breakout as Crypto Market Moves Sideways]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18938582/Popular-Analyst-Forecasts-Potential-XRP-Price-Breakout-as-Crypto-Market-Moves-Sideways</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18938582/Popular-Analyst-Forecasts-Potential-XRP-Price-Breakout-as-Crypto-Market-Moves-Sideways"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T02:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most cryptocurrencies have been trading sideways over the last few weeks with a few notable exceptions including MakerDAO’s $MKR. The native token of the XRP Ledger, $XRP, has been following the path of most other digital assets, but could soon breakout as well, according to a crypto analyst....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do Kwon dismisses Slack chat records as irrelevant evidence]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18938577/Do-Kwon-dismisses-Slack-chat-records-as-irrelevant-evidence</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18938577/Do-Kwon-dismisses-Slack-chat-records-as-irrelevant-evidence"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T02:23:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leaked Slack conversations between Terraform Labs co-founders Do Kwon and Daniel Shin have exposed their contemplation of orchestrating fraudulent transactions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Delays Decisions on More Bitcoin ETFs Including That of Blackrock]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b8642c13</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/sec-delays-decisions-on-more-bitcoin-etfs-including-that-of-blackrock/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T02:09:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has postponed its decisions on the spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) proposed by several companies. The delays of the applications of financial powerhouse Blackrock, asset manager Valkyrie and others come ahead of an expected government shutdown that would affect the SEC.
 
U.S. Securities Regulator Pushes Back Verdicts on Multiple Bitcoin ETF Applications
 
The future of a number of attempts to issue spot bitcoin ETFs in the United States remains unclear after the country’s regulatory body overseeing the securities market delayed its decisions again. The move concerns the high-profile application of investment giant Blackrock as well as those of Valkyrie, Bitwise, and Invesco, according to filings on Thursday.
 
The development follows…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lubomir Tassev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ETH Futures ETFs Get Set to Trade as Government Shut Down Looms]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18938558/ETH-Futures-ETFs-Get-Set-to-Trade-as-Government-Shut-Down-Looms</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18938558/ETH-Futures-ETFs-Get-Set-to-Trade-as-Government-Shut-Down-Looms"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T01:47:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On today's episode, NLW looks at a set of late breaking developments that could see ETH Futures ETF's trading next week, as well as the implications for crypto and the economy of a looming government shutdown. Enjoying this content?SUBSCRIBE to the Podcast: https://pod.link/1438693620Watch on...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOJ's Proposed Jury Questions 'Risks Tainting' Bankman-Fried's Panel, Defense Says]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18938546/DOJs-Proposed-Jury-Questions-Risks-Tainting-Bankman-Frieds-Panel-Defense-Says</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18938546/DOJs-Proposed-Jury-Questions-Risks-Tainting-Bankman-Frieds-Panel-Defense-Says"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T01:14:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried's attorneys objected to some of the U.S. Department of Justice's proposed voir dire questions in a late Friday filing, saying they may miss potential juror bias or otherwise lead to jurors making assumptions about the case.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price To Reach $170,000 in 2025 – Mathematical Model Predicts]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18938538/Bitcoin-Price-To-Reach-170000-in-2025-Mathematical-Model-Predicts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18938538/Bitcoin-Price-To-Reach-170000-in-2025-Mathematical-Model-Predicts"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T01:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bitcoin price is trading at $27,100 at the time of writing, marking a 60% decline from its all-time high of $69,000 in 2021. As the anticipation for the next bull market builds, questions arise regarding Bitcoin’s potential future prices. While most predictions are speculative, one analyst...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GMX Paid A Hefty Prize Because Of This Flaw]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b862232d</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/gmx-paid-a-hefty-prize-because-of-this-flaw/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T00:50:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GMX, a decentralized exchange, awarded Collider Research a $1 million bug bounty in 2022. This payout was in recognition of their discovery of a critical bug in GMX’s smart contracts that directly affected how the protocol tracks outstanding debt.
 
The Bug Affecting GMX And GLP
 
GMX has not provided more information on how the bug was patched and when. However, the DEX operator said the bug negatively impacted GMX v1 liquidity providers (LPs) as the code led to inaccuracies in quotes related to “the fair value of tokens.” Specifically, the bug affected the Global Liquidity Pool (GLP), causing it to deviate from its fair value. 
 
Since GMX supports up to 50X leverage, a system tracks debt borrowed by traders and how it is repaid. It is smart contract-driven, and the trader enters into de…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dalmas Ngetich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum’s Dencun upgrade gets a new touch — Here’s how]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18938524/Ethereums-Dencun-upgrade-gets-a-new-touch-Heres-how</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18938524/Ethereums-Dencun-upgrade-gets-a-new-touch-Heres-how"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T00:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During the ACDE meeting, the developers agreed to make some changes on EIP-4788. Other issues including the ZK function and Beacon roots were also discussed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Representative Introduces Legislation to Mandate Reporting of Off-Chain Crypto Transactions to the CFTC]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b86d2c02</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/us-representative-introduces-legislation-to-mandate-reporting-of-off-chain-crypto-transactions-to-the-cftc/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T00:10:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Virginia’s Democratic representative Don Beyer has ushered in a fresh bill mandating the documentation of off-chain transactions and over-the-counter (OTC) crypto engagements by cryptocurrency exchanges, to be catalogued in a repository under the purview of the U.S. Commodity Futures Trading Commission.
 
New Legislation Targets Off-Chain Transfers in Crypto Industry
 
Representative Don Beyer (D-VA), has unveiled a new legislative piece reportedly aimed at safeguarding stakeholders in the digital assets arena. Titled the “Off-Chain Digital Commodity Transaction Reporting Act,” this bill mandates “trading platforms to report all transactions to a repository registered with the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC).”
 
Beyer posits that crypto trading platforms bear the responsibility…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$58,000 Abruptly Vanishes From Bank Account, Says Couple – As Banking Giant Issues Complete Denial of Claims]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18938508/58000-Abruptly-Vanishes-From-Bank-Account-Says-Couple-As-Banking-Giant-Issues-Complete-Denial-of-Claims</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18938508/58000-Abruptly-Vanishes-From-Bank-Account-Says-Couple-As-Banking-Giant-Issues-Complete-Denial-of-Claims"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T00:04:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A trillion-dollar bank is rejecting a young couple who claims tens of thousands of dollars has disappeared from their account. 21 year-old Elli Houston and 23 year-old Trae Murphy say they initiated a $90,000 AUD transfer, worth about $58,000 USD, out of their Commonwealth Bank account back in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top-35 Altcoin Ignores Crypto Market Doldrums and Surges by Nearly 45% in the Past Month Amid Spike in Activity]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18938509/Top-35-Altcoin-Ignores-Crypto-Market-Doldrums-and-Surges-by-Nearly-45-in-the-Past-Month-Amid-Spike-in-Activity</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18938509/Top-35-Altcoin-Ignores-Crypto-Market-Doldrums-and-Surges-by-Nearly-45-in-the-Past-Month-Amid-Spike-in-Activity"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T00:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A top-35 altcoin has jumped by nearly 45% in the past month, dramatically outpacing most of a middling crypto market. The native governance token of the decentralized finance (DeFi) protocol Maker (MKR) is trading for $1,513 at time of writing, up from $1,047 one month ago. The 34th-ranked...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GMX Paid A Hefty Prize Because Of This Flaw]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18938505/GMX-Paid-A-Hefty-Prize-Because-Of-This-Flaw</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18938505/GMX-Paid-A-Hefty-Prize-Because-Of-This-Flaw"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T00:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GMX, a decentralized exchange, awarded Collider Research a $1 million bug bounty in 2022. This payout was in recognition of their discovery of a critical bug in GMX’s smart contracts that directly affected how the protocol tracks outstanding debt. The Bug Affecting GMX And GLP GMX has not...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Analyst Says COMP Price Will Reach $66 If This Happens]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b86ee35b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-analyst-comp-price-66/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T23:49:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week has seen the COMP price put on one of the most impressive rallies amid the bear market. The price recovery has seen the digital asset gain more than 22% over a 7-day period, cementing its position as a top gainer. But even with such an already significant gain, one analyst believes that the rally is far from over.
 
COMP Price Chart Shows Promise
 
In the analysis that presents one of the most bullish scenarios so far for the COMP price, a pseudonymous analyst who goes by MyCryptoParadise on TradingView has put forward that the altcoin could still rise another 50% from here.
 
 
The chart shared by the analyst points to a double bottom that was marked between August and September. At the end of this double bottom lies incredible promise for the COMP price, making a rise to $66 po…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Best Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Analyst Says COMP Price Will Reach $66 If This Happens]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18938472/Crypto-Analyst-Says-COMP-Price-Will-Reach-66-If-This-Happens</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18938472/Crypto-Analyst-Says-COMP-Price-Will-Reach-66-If-This-Happens"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T23:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week has seen the COMP price put on one of the most impressive rallies amid the bear market. The price recovery has seen the digital asset gain more than 22% over a 7-day period, cementing its position as a top gainer. But even with such an already significant gain, one analyst believes that the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LINK Price Primed For Meteoric Rise: Analyst Predicts 130% Rally To $18]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18938458/LINK-Price-Primed-For-Meteoric-Rise-Analyst-Predicts-130-Rally-To-18</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18938458/LINK-Price-Primed-For-Meteoric-Rise-Analyst-Predicts-130-Rally-To-18"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T23:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Scam Alert: CFTC Launches Lawsuit Against Mosaic Exchange]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b854209c</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-scam-cftc-lawsuit-against-mosaic-exchange/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T22:48:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a significant move targeting the crypto industry, the US Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) has filed a civil enforcement action against Mosaic Exchange Limited, a Pennsylvania limited liability company, and its owner and Chief Executive Officer, Sean Michael.
 
The complaint alleges that the defendants operated a fraudulent digital asset commodity scheme, deceiving investors and misappropriating customer funds.
 
Alleged Fraudulent Crypto Scheme
 
According to the complaint, the defendants fraudulently solicited and induced 17 individuals from the United States and other countries to invest hundreds of thousands of dollars’ worth of Bitcoin (BTC) and other funds. 
 
These funds were supposed to be traded on behalf of the customers in Bitcoin and other crypto assets. However, t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Analysts’ $XRP Price Prediction Suggests Potential Over 1,000% Surge to $6.7]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18938446/Crypto-Analysts-XRP-Price-Prediction-Suggests-Potential-Over-1000-Surge-to-67</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18938446/Crypto-Analysts-XRP-Price-Prediction-Suggests-Potential-Over-1000-Surge-to-67"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T22:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TRB rises 270% as whales pile up: What’s going on?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18938436/TRB-rises-270-as-whales-pile-up-Whats-going-on</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18938436/TRB-rises-270-as-whales-pile-up-Whats-going-on"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T22:30:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whale investors, who control more than 11% of the TRB's circulating supply, might influence the coin's next moves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Congress Demands Bitcoin Etf Approval | Gensler Gets Rekt]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18938429/CONGRESS-DEMANDS-BITCOIN-ETF-APPROVAL-GENSLER-GETS-REKT</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18938429/CONGRESS-DEMANDS-BITCOIN-ETF-APPROVAL-GENSLER-GETS-REKT"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T22:14:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dive into the drama as Congress demands Spot Bitcoin ETF approval and takes SEC Chairman Gary Gensler to task! The latest congressional session saw SEC Chairman Gary Gensler face tough questions from a number of Congressmen including a heated Tom Emmer, Patrick McHenry, Andy Barr, and Warren...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Traders Eye Bullish Silver Lining in Looming US Government Shutdown, Says Analyst]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b8577f17</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-traders-eye-bullish-silver-lining-in-looming-us-government-shutdown-says-analyst/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T22:12:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Numerous reports foretell an imminent U.S. government shutdown, given the anticipated failure of a spending bill to secure passage by Saturday evening — a measure meant to sustain operations till mid-November. On the cusp of this shutdown, bitcoin (BTC) has been on an ascent, catching the eye of many. Coinshares analyst Luke Nolan notes a buoyant sentiment among some traders, who view the government’s looming closure with a favorable lens.
 
Bitcoin Rides the Wave of Uncertainty as U.S. Braces for Government Shutdown
 

 
The U.S. government could shut down this weekend if Democrats and Republican policymakers can’t come to an agreement on spending. Currently, there’s a bill on the table that aims to extend the government’s pay until mid-November, but a number of Republicans and Kevin McCa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoin Legislation Looms Despite Threat of Government Shutdown]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199523</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199523/stablecoin-legislation-government-shutdown"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T22:05:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Things are complicated right now,” Congressman Patrick McHenry told Circle’s Chief Strategy Officer and Head of Global Policy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Sets Sights On $30,000 As Holder Metric Hits New All-Time High]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b851d132</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-price-30000-all-time-high/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T21:48:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bitcoin price has been gaining momentum and steadily rising back to a more bullish price position of $30,000. Despite market downturns, long-term holders of the cryptocurrency are increasing their investments in hopes of a significant bull run. s the holder metric hits a new all-time high.
 
Bitcoin Price Rises As Holder Metric Peaks
 
Bitcoin’s price has been consolidating for a while now, pushing past the $27,000 threshold and being traded presently at $27,047. The cryptocurrency is slowly moving towardsthe $30,000 mark, defying bearish expectations.  
 
 
Co-founder of Reflexivity Research, Will Clemente revealed a chart report illustrated by Glassnode, a blockchain data and intelligence platform, in an X (formerly Twitter) post on Thursday.
 
The chart revealed metrics of Bitcoin l…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Galaxy and Invesco Join Growing Ethereum ETF Race]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199379</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199379/galaxy-invesco-join-growing-ethereum-etf-race"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T21:46:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Galaxy and Invesco added their names to the Ethereum spot ETF field on Friday, even as worry of a government shutdown and SEC delays loom.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlockFi Says It's Taken Major Step Toward Emerging From Bankruptcy]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b85ea2ca</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/09/29/blockfi-says-its-taken-major-step-toward-emerging-from-bankruptcy/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T21:01:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The beleaguered lender’s restructuring plan may soon be finalized, pending a bankruptcy judge’s approval, BlockFi said in a notice to creditors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Napolitano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Most Pressing Issue on Ethereum is Validator Size Growth]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b85ea2c1</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/09/29/the-most-pressing-issue-on-ethereum-is-validator-size-growth/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T21:01:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If appetite for staking on Ethereum does not slow meaningfully over the next several months, the size of Ethereum’s validator set could become problematic for the blockchain, says Christine Kim, Vice President of Research at Galaxy Digital.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christine Kim</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s Slips Below $27K, But What Might Government Shutdown Mean for Prices]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b85fd8ce</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/09/29/bitcoins-slips-below-27k-but-what-might-government-shutdown-mean-for-prices/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T20:49:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The last time BTC posted a positive return during September was in 2016.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor, Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Collision: Coinbase’s CEO Brian Armstrong Challenges Chase UK’s Sudden Ban]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b8580010</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-collision-coinbases-ceo-challenges-chase-uk/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T20:48:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier this week, JPMorgan Chase UK, a standalone digital banking entity in the UK since 2021, delivered surprising news. They announced that their customers would no longer have the option to purchase crypto using Chase UK debit cards or via bank transfers. 
 
While such decisions aren’t entirely unprecedented, the rationale provided by the bank, concerns explicitly about rising digital currency-related frauds, raised eyebrows, especially within the community.
 
Brian Armstrong, the CEO of Coinbase, one of the largest digital currency exchanges in the world, didn’t mince his words when expressing his displeasure. 
 
During an interview with CNBC’s “Squawk Box” on Thursday, the CEO criticized the decision, emphasizing that private entities should not be in the business of “sidelining” an …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Three Arrows Capital Executive Su Zhu Arrested in Singapore]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b85bff12</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/former-three-arrows-capital-executive-su-zhu-arrested-in-singapore/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T20:10:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Su Zhu, a founding member of the now-insolvent Three Arrows Capital, was apprehended in Singapore at Changi Airport on Friday, as per the firm’s liquidator, Teneo. Zhu received a four-month prison sentence for failing to cooperate in the bankruptcy proceedings, Teneo revealed.
 
Crackdown at Changi Airport: 3AC’s Su Zhu Detained, Associate Kyle Davies Fugitive
 
Teneo, overseeing the liquidation of Three Arrows Capital, reported that co-founder Su Zhu was seized and sentenced to four months’ incarceration. His associate, Kyle Davies, remains at large; however, Teneo confirmed he was given an identical penalty.
 
Zhu allegedly tried to flee Singapore when he was intercepted at Changi Airport, situated approximately 25 miles east of Singapore’s Downtown Core. The Singapore court decreed that Zhu and Davies had not been collaborating with the liquidation procedure – an issue previously reported by the media months prior to his apprehension.
 
The defunct Singapore-based cryptocurrency hedge fund once supervised over $10 billion in assets at its height. However, a confluence of perilous trading tactics, Terra’s collapse, and plummeting cryptocurrency values obliterated the firm’s assets. Consequently, 3AC declared bankruptcy and was mandated to liquidate by a British Virgin Islands court on June 27, 2022.
 
Squawk Box posted on X that Kyle Davies, the co-founder of Three Arrows Capital, was asked if he was in Bali because Indonesia is one of seven countries that will not extradite him to the United States. While that interview was in November 2022, Davies is believed to be still in Bali.
 
What do you think about the 3AC co-founder’s arrest? Share your thoughts and opinions about this subject in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Long-Term Metrics Point To A Different Scenario Than 2019 Fakeout: Top Analyst]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b84659b9</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-metrics-point-to-a-different-scenario/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T19:48:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin traders and enthusiasts have been eagerly anticipating the next significant move in the cryptocurrency market, with memories of the 2019 fakeout rally still fresh in their minds. 
 
However, one prominent BTC trader, known as Dave the Wave on the social media platform X, is offering a reassuring perspective. According to Dave, the conditions that led to the 2019 fakeout rally are unlikely to repeat themselves in the current market cycle.
 
The 2019 fakeout rally left many Bitcoin investors disappointed. It was characterized by a sudden breakout that sent BTC prices soaring, only to see them crash back down just as rapidly.
 
 
This roller-coaster ride was attributed to Bitcoin spending only a short time in the “buy zone” before experiencing the wild price swings.
 
 
Those that hav…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quantum Leap: Researchers Achieve Major Milestone for Reliable Quantum Computers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199380</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199380/quantum-leap-researchers-achieve-major-milestone-for-reliable-quantum-computers"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T19:44:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers discovered a way to bring the industry closer to more reliable, powerful quantum computers less prone to errors or inaccuracies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gemini to Cease Offering Crypto Services in Netherlands in November]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b847c1bb</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/09/29/gemini-to-cease-offering-crypto-services-in-netherlands-in-november/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T19:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gemini said it is taking the step "due to requirements imposed by the De Nederlandsche Bank (DNB),"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Traders Eye $28K; Solana, Cardano and Tellor Lead Altcoin Bump]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b847c1b4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/09/29/bitcoin-traders-eye-28k-solana-cardano-and-tellor-lead-altcoin-bump/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T19:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Traders at Japanese exchange Bitbank said in a daily note that they expect bitcoin prices to move towards the $28,000 level, citing ETF optimism.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's Stopping Fortnite and Call of Duty From Using the Same Items? It's Not Just NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199378</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199378/whats-stopping-fortnite-call-duty-using-same-items-not-just-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T19:28:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Will the video game industry open up and play nice? These are the hurdles left to overcome to enable interoperable items at scale.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terra's Do Kwon Admits to Faking Trading Volume in Leaked Chat: Court Docs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199375</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199375/terras-do-kwon-admits-to-faking-trading-volume-in-leaked-chat-court-docs"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T19:15:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["I won't tell if you won't," Terra's Do Kwon said, according to SEC documents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unreported Cardano News: ADA Whale Shares “Bullish” Trading Project]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b84d1c8d</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/unreported-cardano-news-ada-whale-bullish-project/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T18:47:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A significant investor in this ADA ecosystem believes some Cardano news has gone unnoticed; this development could increase optimism in the network.  Via social media platform X, the pseudonym ADA investor made the case for the “bullish development” happening on this blockchain.
 
 
Positive Cardano News Go Under The Radar?
 
The pseudonym investor shared some of this unnoticed Cardano news, including launching several projects that could onboard more users on the network. These projects include OptionFlow, a trading platform offering access to decentralized derivatives, such as bonds, options, and others.
 
The platform recently launched its testnet and hinted at a “Phase 2” launch in the coming months. The ADA whale claims that Cardano will “shine” in offering derivative products. The Op…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reynaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cynthia Lummis: Bitcoin Is the Anti-CBDC]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b84eec02</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/technical/cynthia-lummis-bitcoin-is-the-anti-cbdc"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T18:33:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do We Need CBDCs? Bitcoin Backstage with Cynthia Lummis
In the world of digital currencies, two terms frequently come up for discussion - Central Bank Digital Currencies (CBDCs) and Bitcoin. Both have gained significant attention in recent years, with proponents and critics presenting their arguments. To shed light on this topic, we dive backstage with Cynthia Lummis, a prominent figure in the Bitcoin arena and a United States Senator.
YouTube Link: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xxQjrq50-BY
Understanding CBDCs: A Brief Overview
Before delving deeper, let's first understand what CBDCs are. CBDCs are digital currencies issued and regulated by central banks, designed to complement traditional cash and provide a secure and efficient means of payment. CBDCs can be either retail, accessible to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['There Are No Real Standards': Ready Player Me CEO Timmu Tõke on Building for an Open Gaming Ecosystem]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TH3KEAI0/there-are-no-real-standards-ready-player-me-ceo-timmu-tke-on-building-for-an-open-gaming-ecosystem</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TH3KEAI0/there-are-no-real-standards-ready-player-me-ceo-timmu-tke-on-building-for-an-open-gaming-ecosystem"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T17:29:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Timmu Tõke, co-founder and CEO of Ready Player Me, joins Decrypt contributor Ryan Gladwin to discuss the startup's approach to powering avatars that are interoperable across games and metaverse platforms—and what's needed to convince the industry to adopt standards and open up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoins Aren't Securities, Says Circle in SEC Lawsuits Against Binance]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199356</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199356/stablecoins-arent-securities-says-circle-in-sec-lawsuits-against-binance"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T16:03:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neither BUSD nor USDC is a security, Circle argued—but was careful to say it's not picking sides in the case.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Is Giving Away Free Gaming NFTs—Here's How to Claim]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151872</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151872/amazon-giving-away-free-gaming-nfts-how-claim"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T15:59:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATE: A new Mojo Melee champion NFT is now available for Amazon Prime subscribers, along with non-NFT items in Web3 game My Pet Hooligan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Arrows Capital Co-Founder Su Zhu Arrested in Singapore]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199354</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199354/three-arrows-capital-co-founder-su-zhu-arrested-in-singapore"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T15:47:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Su Zhu will serve a four-month sentence behind bars for not complying with court orders during 3AC's bankruptcy process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How On-Chain Attestations Unlock Blockchain’s Most Valuable Use Cases]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199326</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199326/how-on-chain-attestations-unlock-blockchains-most-valuable-use-cases"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T15:27:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KYC alone won’t cut it—to open up real world use cases for crypto, on-chain attestations are the solution for identity verification.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Graeme Moore</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$3 Billion in Bitcoin Options Expire Today—What Will That Do to BTC's Price?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199339</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199339/3-billion-bitcoin-options-expire-september-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T15:23:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Analysts say there's no sign that the expiring options will cause big swings in BTC's price.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Sam Bankman-Fried Ended Up in Jail]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199249</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199249/how-sam-bankman-fried-ended-up-in-jail"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T15:22:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Super Bowl streaming with a VPN and witness tampering concerns eventually led Sam Bankman-Fried back to jail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get Paid to Train AI? There’s a New Cryptocurrency for That]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199332</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199332/get-paid-train-ai-theres-new-cryptocurrency-that"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T13:31:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ta-Da will soon offer a native token for data contributions, introducing a new model for training artificial intelligence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenTrade Launches Tokenized Treasury Bills on Protocol Developed by Circle]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199291</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199291/opentrade-launches-tokenized-treasury-bills-on-protocol-developed-by-circle"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T12:59:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For every tokenized t-bill an investor purchases, OpenTrade will be buy an actual treasury bill and provide an on-chain identifier it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Market Flips Green Amid Ethereum Futures ETF Approval, Dollar Weakness]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199324</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199324/crypto-market-flips-green-amid-ethereum-futures-etf-approval-dollar-weakness"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T12:05:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With October around the corner, Bitcoin and Ethereum appear to be returning to better form.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ann Hirsch's 'Sacra Famiglia' Puts a Surreal AI Spin on Suburbia]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199099</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199099/ann-hirschs-sacra-famiglia-puts-surreal-ai-spin-suburbia"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T11:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artist Ann Hirsch's new web-browsing haunt "Sacra Famiglia" twists up family photos with the bizarre flourishes of generative AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cosmos Product Lead Says Ethereum Layer-2s Are Not the ‘Holy Grail’ of Scaling]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199312</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199312/cosmos-product-lead-says-ethereum-layer-2s-holy-grail-scaling"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T10:58:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Layer-2 networks are all the rage at the moment, but with user funds splintering across networks, the tech comes with its downsides.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[French Authorities Raid NVIDIA Offices Over Suspicions of Anti-Competitive Practices: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199310</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199310/french-authorities-raid-nvidia-offices-over-suspicions-anti-competitive-practices"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T10:46:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[French authorities have raided NVIDIA's offices in Paris and Nice as part of a wider probe into the firm's competitive practices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Real-World Passions Will Onboard the Next Wave of Crypto Adopters]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199155</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199155/real-world-passions-will-onboard-the-next-wave-of-crypto-adopters"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T09:34:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IRL experiences are key to on-chain identity and onboarding new users to the Web3 space, says MintPass founder Sam Simmons.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Delays Decision on Four Spot Bitcoin ETF Filings Ahead of Government Shutdown]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199305</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199305/sec-punts-four-spot-bitcoin-etf-filing-ahead-government-shutdown"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T09:15:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC's latest move is the second round of delays on the various spot Bitcoin ETF applications filed this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Musée d’Orsay Embraces NFTs in Push to Reach New Audiences]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199278</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199278/musee-dorsay-embraces-nfts-push-reach-new-audiences"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T06:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The French art museum announced a partnership with the Tezos Foundation that will bring its collections into conversation with on-chain digital artists and blockchain-backed experiences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Republican FCC Commissioner Calls Renewed Net Neutrality Push 'Unlawful']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199253</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199253/republican-fcc-commissioner-calls-renewed-net-neutrality-push-unlawful"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T00:31:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Digital rights group the Electronic Frontier Foundation praised the FCC’s move, emphasizing fair treatment of all data and warning against ISPs becoming gatekeepers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xbox Chat Was Used to Share Insider Trading Secrets, Says SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199252</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199252/xbox-chat-used-share-insider-trading-secrets-says-sec"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T00:16:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. regulator alleged that participants of an insider trading scheme used Xbox audio chat to share info, netting thousands in profits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Like We Were Talking in Person': Zuckerberg’s Metaverse Is Coming to Life]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199263</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199263/metaverse-zuckerberg-lex-fridman-future-ai-ultra-realistic-avatars"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T23:18:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mark Zuckerberg and Lex Fridman did a podcast on AI entirely in the metaverse—and we’ve come a long way from Meta’s legless avatars.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain Is 'Only Way' Forward for Gaming, Says Shrapnel Studio Head]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/fhoy7Z8f/blockchain-is-only-way-forward-for-gaming-says-shrapnel-studio-head</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/fhoy7Z8f/blockchain-is-only-way-forward-for-gaming-says-shrapnel-studio-head"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T21:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shrapnel Studio Head Don Norbury tells Kate Irwin the reasons why the upcoming first-person shooter game will offer a wide range of NFTs. He also reveals team-based gameplay plans and shares how game maps have already changed this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fortress CEO Responds to Ripple Backing Out of Acquisition]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199250</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199250/fortress-ceo-responds-to-ripple-backing-out-of-acquisition"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T21:13:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fortress CEO Scott Purcell said Ripple wants to stick with its current B2B focus.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Epic Games Is Jacking Up the Price of Fortnite V-Bucks]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199236</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199236/epic-games-jacking-up-price-fortnite-v-bucks"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T19:59:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alongside layoffs, Epic Games is also raising the price of Fortnite’s in-game currency, citing inflation and currency shifts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These Paris Fashion Week Outfits Transform Under Ultraviolet Light]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199218</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199218/anrealage-paris-fashion-week-outfits-transform-under-ultraviolet-light"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T19:13:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anrealage delivered a head-turning runway at Paris Fashion Week, spotlighting designer Kunihiko Morinaga's latest color-changing outfits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephanie Hirschmiller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gemini Calls Description of $218 Million Genesis Withdrawal ‘Pure Fantasy’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199204</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199204/gemini-calls-description-of-218-million-genesis-withdrawal-pure-fantasy"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T18:08:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gemini described the withdrawal as an attempt to bulk up Gemini Earn’s liquidity reserves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried Trial: All the Names You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=198989</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/198989/sam-bankman-fried-trial-all-the-names-you-need-to-know"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T17:39:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These are the big players you should know before tuning into Sam Bankman-Fried's trial next week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fortnite Maker Epic Games Cuts 830 Staff as CEO Calls Layoffs 'Only Way']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199202</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199202/fortnite-maker-epic-games-cuts-830-staff-ceo-calls-layoffs-only-way"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T17:19:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Epic CEO Tim Sweeney said the Fortnite studio is going through “a major structural change” due to tighter margins and new revenue models.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Futures ETF to Begin Trading as Rumors Swirl of Accelerated SEC Approvals]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199178</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199178/ethereum-futures-etf-to-begin-trading-as-rumors-swirl-of-accelerated-sec-approvals"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T16:36:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first launch of an Ethereum ETF in the United States appears imminent, but VanEck didn't provide a specific date.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IYK Raises $16.8 Million to Power Token-Enabled Fashion With NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199165</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199165/iyk-raises-16-8-million-power-token-enabled-fashion-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T16:01:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After working with Adidas, 9dcc, and more, IYK has launched a self-serve platform for creating NFC-chipped products.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Are Crypto Futures, Coinbase's Latest Offering?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=41419</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-are-bitcoin-futures-how-do-they-work"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T14:37:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Futures contracts have a long and storied history—but for Bitcoin traders, they’ve unlocked new strategies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Stevens,Scott Chipolina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Rolls Out Futures Trading for Retail Crypto Traders Globally]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199098</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199098/coinbase-rolls-out-futures-trading-retail-crypto-traders-globally"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T13:53:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto exchange has set its sights on global expansion amid ongoing legal challenges from the SEC in the U.S.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Chief Says Former Russia Unit CommEx 'Does Not Service US or EU Users']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199093</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199093/binance-chief-says-former-russia-unit-commex-does-not-service-us-eu-users"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T11:24:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As part of the recent sale, Binance CEO said that “a few ex-Binance CIS team members” may join the CommEx team.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Extends Deadline for Ark Invest, VanEck Spot Ethereum ETF Filings]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199090</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199090/sec-extends-deadline-ark-invest-vaneck-spot-ethereum-etf-filings"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T10:21:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Though VanEck and Ark Invest have been hit with delays, a futures-based ETF could see approval by next week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Price for Your Money? Liberty, Security, and CBDCs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=198753</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/198753/what-price-for-your-money-liberty-security-and-cbdcs"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T10:12:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CBDCs promise to energise economic growth through greater efficiency and security—at the cost of enshrining fiat’s dominance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Dob</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Urges Euro Users to Convert to Tether After Bank Partnership Ends]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199079</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199079/binance-urges-euro-users-to-convert-to-tether-after-bank-partnership-ends"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T09:46:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following Paysafe's unilateral split from Binance, users are advised to move their euro balances to Tether’s USDT.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Only Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Chainlink Are Meaningfully Decentralized: Sergey Nazarov]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199066</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199066/only-bitcoin-ethereum-chainlink-are-meaningfully-decentralized-sergey-nazarov"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T08:20:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amid falling bridges and staking cartels, industry experts like the Chainlink co-founder are again debating the age-old question of decentralization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Social Media Sentiment Is Key to Crypto Price Discovery]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/981TBppa/social-media-sentiment-is-key-to-crypto-price-discovery</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/981TBppa/social-media-sentiment-is-key-to-crypto-price-discovery"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T23:47:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sacha Ghebali, Director of Strategy and Business Development at The TIE, says social media sentiment remains a key factor in price movements for major cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin and Ethereum. However, he notes that sentiment has turned more negative lately amid regulatory uncertainty. Ghebali believes events like the Ripple lawsuit ruling significantly impacted sentiment and prices. André Beganski interviewed him at Messari Mainnet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[500Altcoins discusses DeFi Summer and the Dubai Crypto Scene - This Time Will Be Different - Episode 2]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cI7p8AK3/500altcoins-discusses-defi-summer-and-the-dubai-crypto-scene-this-time-will-be-different-episode-2</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cI7p8AK3/500altcoins-discusses-defi-summer-and-the-dubai-crypto-scene-this-time-will-be-different-episode-2"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our host Reza Jafery is joined by Gareth Fenney aka 500Altcoins. They discuss the glory days of DeFi Summer and whether or not its a smart move for builders in the crypto space to relocate to Dubai.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralize Derivatives Trading with Custom Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/lfmwAjB9/decentralize-derivatives-trading-with-custom-blockchain</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/lfmwAjB9/decentralize-derivatives-trading-with-custom-blockchain"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T10:37:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Gogel of dYdX discusses how the decentralized exchange is building a custom blockchain to fully decentralize derivatives trading. He explained how the new dYdX chain will allow validators to run order books in memory, enabling decentralized order matching at scale. This shift aims to increase security and transparency for traders while maintaining the performance of centralized exchanges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Newly Partnered with Visa, Solana Focuses on Reliability]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/MZoxvulr/newly-partnered-with-visa-solana-focuses-on-reliability</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/MZoxvulr/newly-partnered-with-visa-solana-focuses-on-reliability"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana has improved network reliability through upgrades like Quick and local fee markets. It recently partnered with Visa to allow settling transactions in USDC on Solana. This could enable merchants to receive instant payments and save on credit card processing fees. Stacy Elliott spoke with Austin Federa, Head of Strategy for the Solana Foundation, at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[India's 1% Crypto Tax Has Been a Nightmare for High-Frequency Traders, Says Shardeum CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/fxygwLvH/indias-1-crypto-tax-has-been-a-nightmare-for-high-frequency-traders-says-shardeum-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/fxygwLvH/indias-1-crypto-tax-has-been-a-nightmare-for-high-frequency-traders-says-shardeum-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As India figures out its regulatory approach to the crypto industry, one thing is clear to Shardeum co-founder Nischal Shetty: “If you're a high-frequency trader, you can't afford to lose a percentage every time you sell,” he told Decrypt's Andre Beganski at Messari Mainnet in New York. “That's something that's caused a lot of issues.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Accounting Challenges and Opportunities]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/0Sezz6pZ/crypto-accounting-challenges-and-opportunities</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/0Sezz6pZ/crypto-accounting-challenges-and-opportunities"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As crypto matures, accounting and tax regulations are evolving. Amy Kalnoki of Bitwave explains how her company helps crypto companies properly account for digital assets. She notes the importance of flexibility as new crypto assets emerge and regulations change. Stacy Elliott interviewed her at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Most Crypto Users Don't Trust Themselves to Keep Their Seed Phrase Safe: Ledger CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/0kYf2Qed/most-crypto-users-dont-trust-themselves-to-keep-their-seed-phrase-safe-ledger-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/0kYf2Qed/most-crypto-users-dont-trust-themselves-to-keep-their-seed-phrase-safe-ledger-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Stacy Elliott sat down with Ledger CEO Pascal Gauthier to discuss crypto custody post-FTX, and the hardware wallet manufacturer's controversial Ledger Recover service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Base as a 'Bridge, Not an Island']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/oZPr7bzY/base-as-a-bridge-not-an-island</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/oZPr7bzY/base-as-a-bridge-not-an-island"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase's Jesse Pollak, creator of layer-2 blockchain Base, says the launch of the network has exceeded expectations, even if plans changed along the way. He believes Arbitrum One will help bring billions onto blockchain by enabling seamless user experiences. Stacy Elliott interviewed him at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Explosive Growth Ahead for Enterprise Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/xXOrNbX9/explosive-growth-ahead-for-enterprise-blockchain</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/xXOrNbX9/explosive-growth-ahead-for-enterprise-blockchain"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paul Brody drives Ernst & Young (EY) initiatives and investments in blockchain technology across consulting, audit, and tax business lines. He says enterprise blockchain adoption is nearing an inflection point. Brody believes blockchains will one day handle 40 billion transactions daily across industries like automotive and pharma. Stacy Elliott interviewed him at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Regulation Threatens U.S. Dominance of Financial Markets, Says CoinRoutes CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/CrpvzFjL/regulation-threatens-us-dominance-of-financial-markets-says-coinroutes-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/CrpvzFjL/regulation-threatens-us-dominance-of-financial-markets-says-coinroutes-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dave Weisberger, Co-Founder and CEO of CoinRoutes, argued that excessive regulation in the U.S. threatens to undermine the country's long-standing dominance in global financial markets. He warned that other countries are embracing blockchain and crypto to build more efficient digital markets, which could cause the US to lose its competitive edge and trillions in GDP. Weisberger said CoinRoutes is now focusing more on expanding internationally due to restrictive policies in the U.S. He was interviewed by André Beganski of Decrypt at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Developer-Friendly zkRollup to Scale Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/OvAFgxTd/building-a-developer-friendly-zkrollup-to-scale-ethereum</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/OvAFgxTd/building-a-developer-friendly-zkrollup-to-scale-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daniel Helm, head of Developer Relations at Scroll, discussess how they are building a zkRollup to scale Ethereum transactions and lower fees. He explained their focus on creating a seamless developer experience by maintaining Ethereum's ethos and tooling. Scroll aims to launch their mainnet soon, providing more scalable blockspace for Ethereum developers. Stacy Elliott of Decrypt interviewed him at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin's Narrative Is Shifting Towards Layer-2 Solutions]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/axArPRp3/bitcoins-narrative-is-shifting-towards-layer-2-solutions</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/axArPRp3/bitcoins-narrative-is-shifting-towards-layer-2-solutions"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rich Rines, original Core DAO contributor and former Coinbase engineer, discusses how the narrative around Bitcoin is shifting in 2023. While Bitcoin remains digital gold, new layer 2 solutions are emerging to unlock more utility and value from the huge amounts of capital stored in Bitcoin. He says these innovations can benefit Bitcoin holders while keeping Bitcoin maximalists happy by building outside the base layer. André Beganski interviewed him at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Need to Start Thinking About How we Make Crypto Easy to Use: Robinhood Crypto General Manager]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PLZ0FpdC/we-need-to-start-thinking-about-how-we-make-crypto-easy-to-use-robinhood-crypto-general-manager</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PLZ0FpdC/we-need-to-start-thinking-about-how-we-make-crypto-easy-to-use-robinhood-crypto-general-manager"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Stacy Elliott sat down with Robinhood Crypto general manager Johann Kerbrat at Messari Mainnet 2023, to talk about the trading platform's crypto wallet, onboarding new users through simplicity, and keeping platform fees sustainable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On-Chain Gaming Poised for Mass Adoption]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/6ZryETKh/on-chain-gaming-poised-for-mass-adoption</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/6ZryETKh/on-chain-gaming-poised-for-mass-adoption"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T02:23:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jack O'Holleran is CEO and co-founder of SKALE Labs. He explains how on-chain gaming is ready for the mainstream after overcoming early challenges like high fees and poor user experience. Companies can now build blockchain games that look and feel like traditional games, and scalability improvements allow games to support hundreds of millions of players without performance issues. He was interviewed by André Beganski at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Blockchains Boom Creates Opportunity and Challenges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/7Ys4Rxay/new-blockchains-boom-creates-opportunity-and-challenges</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/7Ys4Rxay/new-blockchains-boom-creates-opportunity-and-challenges"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T02:07:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Billy Sebell of the XDC Foundation discussed the proliferation of new layer-1 and layer-2 blockchain solutions. While this expands possibilities, he noted projects must still attract users amidst growing competition. Sebell highlighted the benefits of targeting niche use cases and bringing real-world assets on-chain via tokenization. He was interviewed by André Beganski of Decrypt at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accessible Self-Custody for Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/kA1Bqu4H/accessible-self-custody-for-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/kA1Bqu4H/accessible-self-custody-for-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T00:52:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dave Lemke is the CFO & CCO at Giddy, creators of a crypto wallet with decentralized private key security. He explains how their solution allows self-custody while still being recoverable. He highlighted increasing demand for self-custody after the FTX collapse. Lemke also touched on upcoming US crypto regulations and Getty's roadmap to simplify staking and other complex processes. Stacy Elliott interviewed him at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defi Education Fund Advocates for Responsible Crypto Regulation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/xD0CzPUF/defi-education-fund-advocates-for-responsible-crypto-regulation</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/xD0CzPUF/defi-education-fund-advocates-for-responsible-crypto-regulation"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T00:32:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amanda Tuminelli of the Defi Education Fund discusses the need for sensible crypto regulation. She says regulators should work with the industry to understand how protocols work before proposing expansive rules that could stifle innovation. Stacy Elliott of Decrypt interviewed her at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Train Your Own AI-Powered Fighter? Inside AI Arena]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qTBh0ayt/train-your-own-ai-powered-fighter-inside-ai-arena</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qTBh0ayt/train-your-own-ai-powered-fighter-inside-ai-arena"/>
        <updated>2023-09-25T20:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is AI Arena? Decrypt's Kate Irwin dives into the upcoming video game in an interview with the game's founders, AI Arena CEO Brandon Da Silva and COO Wei Xie.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>