<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-10-06T01:03:32.656Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-10-06T01:03:32.656Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ledger Faces Industry Downturn: Announces 12% Workforce Reduction]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74bc176138</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ledger-announces-12-workforce-reduction-today/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T00:55:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to a recent report by Bloomberg, Ledger, a prominent hardware wallet manufacturer catering to crypto investors, has announced a 12% reduction in its workforce as part of a strategic effort to navigate an extended industry downturn. 
 
The decision comes in response to macroeconomic challenges that have hindered revenue generation, prompting the company to prioritize the long-term sustainability of its business.
 
Market Challenges Force Ledger CEO To Make ‘Difficult Decisions’
 
Ledger’s CEO and Chairman, Pascal Gauthier, highlighted the need to make difficult decisions in the face of prevailing market conditions. In an email sent to staff, Gauthier acknowledged the impact of macroeconomic headwinds and emphasized the importance of preserving resources for the company’s future. G…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk hits at SEC, DOJ amid suit to force testimony in Twitter probe]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18951170/Elon-Musk-hits-at-SEC-DOJ-amid-suit-to-force-testimony-in-Twitter-probe</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18951170/Elon-Musk-hits-at-SEC-DOJ-amid-suit-to-force-testimony-in-Twitter-probe"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T00:21:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk claims the SEC and DOJ are abusing their regulatory powers for personal and political gain to receive punitive action.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 Ultra High Potential Altcoins For 2024 Crypto Bull Run]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18951168/3-ULTRA-HIGH-POTENTIAL-ALTCOINS-FOR-2024-CRYPTO-BULL-RUN</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18951168/3-ULTRA-HIGH-POTENTIAL-ALTCOINS-FOR-2024-CRYPTO-BULL-RUN"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T00:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[​​In times of market uncertainty, one thing never goes out of style. Infrastructure. The tools that ALL projects need. Not some, not most, but all. And today, we have 3 great Web3 infrastructure projects to share with you:1. PARSIQ - https://bit.ly/Check-PARSIQ2. Openfabric AI -...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JPMorgan CEO Warns of 2 ‘Extraordinary’ Storm Clouds Hitting US Economy With Potential ‘Bad Outcomes’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74bc1c62fe</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/jpmorgan-ceo-warns-of-2-extraordinary-storm-clouds-hitting-us-economy-with-potential-bad-outcomes/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T00:07:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JPMorgan Chase CEO Jamie Dimon has warned of two “extraordinary” things happening today that may have “bad outcomes” for the U.S. economy. Moreover, the executive has urged investors and businesses to be prepared for higher interest rates. “I don’t think inflation will keep going down,” he noted, adding that in the worst-case scenario, you will see “a lot of people struggling.”
 
Jamie Dimon’s Storm Clouds
 
JPMorgan Chase CEO Jamie Dimon shared his economic outlook in an interview with Bloomberg earlier this week. Regarding the broader U.S. economy, he said:
 

There are two things which are extraordinary today, which may have different outcomes — think of them as storm clouds.
 
“We don’t know if they are going to hit, when they are going to hit, what they are going to do, so I’m not pre…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[27% of US Female Crypto Investors Spend Profits on Children’s Education: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18951169/27-of-US-Female-Crypto-Investors-Spend-Profits-on-Childrens-Education-Report</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18951169/27-of-US-Female-Crypto-Investors-Spend-Profits-on-Childrens-Education-Report"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T00:03:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency exchange Bitget has disclosed that 27% of female investors in the United States invest in crypto to cover their children’s education expenses. Meanwhile, the survey findings further reveal that approximately 19% of Chinese investors have dedicated a minimum of $100,000 to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Keep an Eye’ on Bitcoin Cash (BCH), These Three Altcoins as One Key Metric Hits a Three-Month High: Santiment]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18951156/Keep-an-Eye-on-Bitcoin-Cash-BCH-These-Three-Altcoins-as-One-Key-Metric-Hits-a-Three-Month-High-Santiment</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18951156/Keep-an-Eye-on-Bitcoin-Cash-BCH-These-Three-Altcoins-as-One-Key-Metric-Hits-a-Three-Month-High-Santiment"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T00:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A handful of altcoins are seeing a “major surge” in address activity, according to the crypto analytics firm Santiment. The firm notes that Bitcoin Cash (BCH), Smooth Love Potion (SLP), Mask Network (MASK) and Civic Pass (CVC) have all hit three-month highs in terms of daily active address...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ledger Faces Industry Downturn: Announces 12% Workforce Reduction]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18951155/Ledger-Faces-Industry-Downturn-Announces-12-Workforce-Reduction</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18951155/Ledger-Faces-Industry-Downturn-Announces-12-Workforce-Reduction"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T00:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to a recent report by Bloomberg, Ledger, a prominent hardware wallet manufacturer catering to crypto investors, has announced a 12% reduction in its workforce as part of a strategic effort to navigate an extended industry downturn. The decision comes in response to macroeconomic...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside the trial: SBF faces his former friends]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18951148/Inside-the-trial-SBF-faces-his-former-friends</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18951148/Inside-the-trial-SBF-faces-his-former-friends"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T23:58:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried's lawyers appeared to struggle with cross-examining today's witnesses, two of whom were longtime friends.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breakout Of The Decade: Roadmap Of Algorand (ALGO) To Reach $300]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74bc1da79c</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/algorand-algo-breakout-300/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T23:55:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Algorand (ALGO) has struggled greatly throughout the bear market after failing to launch in the 2020/2021 bull market. This has seen the altcoin’s price decline more than 96% from its 2019 all-time high price. However, investors have not lost hope in the coin as one crypto analyst sees an incredible bullish launch in the future of the asset.
 
Algorand (ALGO) To Reach $300
 
In an incredibly bullish post made back in July, pseudonymous crypto analyst Divergencemaker83 on TradingView gave what is arguably one of the most bullish outlooks for Algorand (ALGO). The forecast predicts that the altcoin’s price will rise as high as $300.
 
 
This is interesting because a move to $300 would mean a 10x from its previous all-time high, as well as a 300,000% increase from its current price of $0.11. S…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Best Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chainlink (LINK) Primed for $10 Surge Amid Low Exchange Deposits]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18951149/Chainlink-LINK-Primed-for-10-Surge-Amid-Low-Exchange-Deposits</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18951149/Chainlink-LINK-Primed-for-10-Surge-Amid-Low-Exchange-Deposits"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T23:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chainlink (LINK) has captured headlines recently, after soaring 38% in value in September. 2023. Significantly, this rise positioned it among the top-performing assets in the top 20 crypto rankings. Besides this impressive feat, there’s a prevailing sentiment. The momentum suggests that October...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Important Message For Bitcoin And Crypto Holder]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18951129/IMPORTANT-MESSAGE-FOR-BITCOIN-AND-CRYPTO-HOLDER</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18951129/IMPORTANT-MESSAGE-FOR-BITCOIN-AND-CRYPTO-HOLDER"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T23:20:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s chat]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breakout Of The Decade: Roadmap Of Algorand (ALGO) To Reach $300]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18951114/Breakout-Of-The-Decade-Roadmap-Of-Algorand-ALGO-To-Reach-300</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18951114/Breakout-Of-The-Decade-Roadmap-Of-Algorand-ALGO-To-Reach-300"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T23:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Algorand (ALGO) has struggled greatly throughout the bear market after failing to launch in the 2020/2021 bull market. This has seen the altcoin’s price decline more than 96% from its 2019 all-time high price. However, investors have not lost hope in the coin as one crypto analyst sees an...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Fees At Lowest Since Nov. 2022, Bottom Signal?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74bc1bf891</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-fees-lowest-since-nov-2022-bottom-signal/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T22:55:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data shows that the last time the Ethereum transaction fees dipped towards lows this deep, the cryptocurrency’s price reached its bottom.
 
Ethereum Average Transaction Fees Has Dropped To Just $1.13 Now
 
According to data from the on-chain analytics firm Santiment, the cryptocurrency has observed particularly low fees this week. The “average fees” here refers to a metric measuring the average fees (in USD) the users attach to their Ethereum transfers.
 
Generally, this indicator’s value depends on the traffic the ETH network receives. Whenever the mempool is congested with transfers, some transactions may be stuck waiting for long, as the validators only have a limited capacity to process the transfers.
 
 
Those who want their transfers to go through as soon as possible may attach highe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hououin Kyouma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ledger reduces staff by 12% as controversial Recover feature looms]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18951102/Ledger-reduces-staff-by-12-as-controversial-Recover-feature-looms</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18951102/Ledger-reduces-staff-by-12-as-controversial-Recover-feature-looms"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T22:40:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hardware wallet manufacturer Ledger announced in a blog post on Oct. 5 that it will lay off a significant percentage of its staff while continuing operations. The company’s CEO, Pascal Gauthier, wrote in a letter: “Macroeconomic headwinds are limiting our ability to generate revenue, and in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friend.tech Responds to SIM Swap Attacks with Enhanced Security Measures]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18951084/Friendtech-Responds-to-SIM-Swap-Attacks-with-Enhanced-Security-Measures</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18951084/Friendtech-Responds-to-SIM-Swap-Attacks-with-Enhanced-Security-Measures"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T22:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized social network platform Friend.tech announced an improvement to the protocol’s security, allowing users to add and remove various login methods from their accounts. On October 4, Friend.tech announced on X (previously Twitter) the update on its login method, saying, “You can now...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Customers May Get Full Payout Thanks To Google & Amazon]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18951074/FTX-Customers-May-Get-Full-Payout-Thanks-To-Google-Amazon</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18951074/FTX-Customers-May-Get-Full-Payout-Thanks-To-Google-Amazon"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T22:27:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Customers of the collapsed crypto exchange FTX may eventually get their money back, thanks to FTX's early investment in Claude's parent company Anthropic, an Open AI rival now seeing a massive influx of investment from Google and Amazon.FTX invested $500 million in Anthropic back in April 2022,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feds Flag More Bitcoin, Ethereum Addresses Tied to Chinese Fentanyl Trade]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200366</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200366/feds-flag-more-bitcoin-ethereum-addresses-tied-chinese-fentanyl-trade"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T22:27:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The list of 17 addresses associated with the fentanyl trade also includes the first set of sanctioned wallets connected to Tron.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feds Flag More Bitcoin, Ethereum Addresses Tied to Chinese Fentanyl Trade]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18951089/Feds-Flag-More-Bitcoin-Ethereum-Addresses-Tied-to-Chinese-Fentanyl-Trade</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18951089/Feds-Flag-More-Bitcoin-Ethereum-Addresses-Tied-to-Chinese-Fentanyl-Trade"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T22:27:17.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Better Way to Distribute Crypto Ecosystem Grants]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74bc0711f8</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/10/05/a-better-way-to-distribute-crypto-ecosystem-grants/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T22:23:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Token project treasuries, foundations and grant programs are a necessary lifeline during the bear market. But this funding could be more fairly disbursed, Lunar Strategy's Tim Haldorsson writes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Haldorsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE BITCOIN SAVINGS REVOLUTION | Saifedean Ammous]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18951090/THE-BITCOIN-SAVINGS-REVOLUTION-Saifedean-Ammous</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18951090/THE-BITCOIN-SAVINGS-REVOLUTION-Saifedean-Ammous"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T22:17:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us as Saifedean Ammous, the esteemed author of 'The Bitcoin Standard' and economic advisor to President Bukele of El Salvador, dives deep into how Bitcoin encourages a lowering of time preference, promoting savings and investment over mindless consumption. Ammous challenges the Keynesian...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“This Isn’t a Ponzi Scheme”]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18951073/This-Isnt-a-Ponzi-Scheme</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18951073/This-Isnt-a-Ponzi-Scheme"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T22:16:03.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['We're Creating Our Own Thing': Art Blocks Founder Erick Calderon on the State of Generative Art]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200327</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200327/video-interview-art-blocks-founder-erick-calderon-state-generative-art"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T22:13:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Erick Calderon sits down for a video interview to discuss his company's string of recent successes at Art Blocks' annual Marfa Weekend event.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['We're Creating Our Own Thing': Art Blocks Founder Erick Calderon on the State of Generative Art]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18951069/Were-Creating-Our-Own-Thing-Art-Blocks-Founder-Erick-Calderon-on-the-State-of-Generative-Art</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18951069/Were-Creating-Our-Own-Thing-Art-Blocks-Founder-Erick-Calderon-on-the-State-of-Generative-Art"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T22:13:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Erick Calderon sits down for a video interview to discuss his company's string of recent successes at Art Blocks' annual Marfa Weekend event.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tales From the FTX Bean Bag: Witness Reveals Bankman-Fried’s Financial Missteps and Personal Entanglements]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74bc00c974</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/tales-from-the-ftx-bean-bag-witness-reveals-bankman-frieds-financial-missteps-and-personal-entanglements/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T22:05:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During the Sam Bankman-Fried trial this week, Adam Yedidia, a close friend and former employee of the ex-FTX chief, delivered his testimony. Yedidia had a brief stint as an intern at Alameda Research, a quantitative trading firm linked to FTX, before he transitioned to FTX’s Hong Kong office in early 2021. Additionally, he was part of the FTX executive team residing at the Albany Place luxury resort in the Bahamas.
 
Ex-FTX Developer Talks $8 Billion Code Glitch and Use of Client Funds
 
On Thursday, Yedidia returned to the witness stand for his second day. As Wednesday’s session concluded, he revealed that he got a call informing him that Alameda was misusing client funds. Disturbed by this revelation, Yedidia stepped down. Soon after, FTX faced bankruptcy, grappling with liquidity challe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Prediction: BitMEX Founder Projects BTC to Soar Up To $1 Million By 2026]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18951062/Bitcoin-Price-Prediction-BitMEX-Founder-Projects-BTC-to-Soar-Up-To-1-Million-By-2026</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18951062/Bitcoin-Price-Prediction-BitMEX-Founder-Projects-BTC-to-Soar-Up-To-1-Million-By-2026"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T22:04:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent interview, the enigmatic founder of BitMEX, Arthur Hayes, boldly projected a mind-boggling price range of $750,000 to $1 million for Bitcoin by 2026.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Swan Seeks to Boost Custody Offerings With Blockstream Partnership]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74bc0135d6</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/swan-seeks-to-boost-custody-offerings-with-blockstream-partnership"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T22:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, Blockstream, a global leader in Bitcoin infrastructure, announced a partnership with Swan Bitcoin, a prominent Bitcoin-only financial services company, to launch Swan Vault, enabling customers to safeguard their Bitcoin via collaborative custody, according to a press release sent to Bitcoin Magazine. Swan Vault is powered by Blockstream Jade, an open-source Bitcoin hardware wallet.
"Integrating Blockstream Jade's multi-signature and hardware-based authentication into Swan Vault elevates the standards of Bitcoin collaborative custody," said Swan Bitcoin CEO Cory Klippsten. “The user-centric focus on security is a key aspect of this partnership.”
This partnership attempts to address a common concern among Bitcoin investors – the secure storage of their assets. While many Bitcoin investors prioritize security, they may lack expertise in key management and multi-signature technology. Swan Vault, backed by Blockstream Jade, aims to bridge this gap by providing a collaborative custody solution for BTC holders. This allows customers to maintain full control over their Bitcoin holdings while enjoying a user friendly experience for setting up their wallets and conducting transactions.
"In bringing our technical expertise into the mix with Swan’s user-centric approach, we are advancing the practice of collaborative custody in the Bitcoin ecosystem" said Adam Back, CEO at Blockstream. "It's aimed at driving adoption and making collaborative custody a normalized practice in the Bitcoin industry.”
Swan Vault is the latest product to offer collaborative Bitcoin custody solutions, joining Unchained, Casa, and Nunchuk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nik Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Released its 11th Proof of Reserve Report: Here’s How Much Bitcoin and Altcoins the Exchange Holds]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18951049/Binance-Released-its-11th-Proof-of-Reserve-Report-Heres-How-Much-Bitcoin-and-Altcoins-the-Exchange-Holds</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18951049/Binance-Released-its-11th-Proof-of-Reserve-Report-Heres-How-Much-Bitcoin-and-Altcoins-the-Exchange-Holds"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T22:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Fees At Lowest Since Nov. 2022, Bottom Signal?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18951051/Ethereum-Fees-At-Lowest-Since-Nov-2022-Bottom-Signal</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18951051/Ethereum-Fees-At-Lowest-Since-Nov-2022-Bottom-Signal"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T22:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[El Salvador’s Latest Initiative Reiterates Country’s Commitment To Its Bitcoin Strategy]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74bc01a824</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/el-salvador-bitcoin-strategy/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T21:55:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[El Salvador, a leader in embracing Bitcoin (BTC) as a legal tender, has taken a significant step forward in launching its first local Bitcoin mining pool “Lava Pool”. This step marks a pivotal landmark for the country, in its ambitions to harness renewable energy sources for cryptocurrency mining.
 
El Salvador’s Latest Bitcoin Mining Pool
 
El Salvador‘s Bitcoin mining pool Lava Pool will be spearheaded by Volcano Energy in conjunction with Luxor Technologies – a firm well known for its expertise in providing Bitcoin mining software and services.
 
 
The Lava Pool project will make use of Luxor’s Hashrate Forward Marketplace to automate risk management techniques now employed by other significant Bitcoin mining companies to reduce market volatility.
 
For starters, Volcano Energy’s projec…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Better Way to Distribute Crypto Ecosystem Grants]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18951033/A-Better-Way-to-Distribute-Crypto-Ecosystem-Grants</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18951033/A-Better-Way-to-Distribute-Crypto-Ecosystem-Grants"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T21:52:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Token project treasuries, foundations and grant programs are a necessary lifeline during the bear market. But this funding could be more fairly disbursed, Lunar Strategy's Tim Haldorsson writes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Even the Worst Version of Claude AI Is Better Than GPT 3.5, Researchers Say]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200345</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200345/even-the-worst-version-of-claude-ai-is-better-than-gpt-3-5-researchers-say"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T21:36:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic’s models are available for free—and every single one beats OpenAI’s free model according to a new global ranking.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blackbird, Crypto Restaurant App, Raises $24M in Funding Led by A16z]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74bc0c02a4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/10/05/blackbird-crypto-restaurant-app-raises-24m-in-funding-led-by-a16z/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T21:29:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The target audience is restaurant users, but the blockchain-based project comes with its own "Flypaper" and fungible FLY tokens.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lyllah Ledesma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried: the Liar?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74bc0c2dd4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/10/05/sam-bankman-fried-the-liar/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T21:28:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's not yet clear whether the disgraced FTX founder will testify in his fraud trial. But can you even take him at his word?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Kuhn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Insider Gary Wang: Sam Bankman-Fried Allowed Alameda to Withdraw Unlimited Funds]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200344</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200344/ftx-insider-gary-wang-sam-bankman-fried-allowed-alameda-to-withdraw-unlimited-funds"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T21:19:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FTX co-founder Gary Wang testified on Thursday, saying that company insiders committed fraud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott,André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Cyberpunk 2077' Goes Hollywood as Game Sells 25 Million Copies]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200338</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200338/cyberpunk-2077-goes-hollywood-game-sells-25-million-copies"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T20:57:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hollywood production company Anonymous Content plans to craft a live-action story set in the world of Cyberpunk 2077. Here's what we know so far.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BREAKING: SEC Sues Dogecoin Bull Elon Musk, Seeks Testimony On Twitter Purchase]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74bc0f50d5</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/breaking-sec-lawsuit-elon-musk-twitter-purchase/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T20:54:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has taken legal action against Elon Musk, the billionaire entrepreneur and Dogecoin supporter, seeking to compel his testimony regarding the acquisition of Twitter. 
 
SEC Fires Legal Salvo At Elon Musk
 
Attorneys representing the SEC alleged that Musk failed to appear for a scheduled testimony on September 15, violating a subpoena. 
 
 
The investigation focuses on potential securities fraud related to the purchase of Twitter shares while Musk was buying stock in the company. Musk’s purchase of Twitter, now known as X, took place last year in a deal valued at approximately $44 billion.
 
In a complaint filed in the Northern District of California, the SEC expressed concern over Musk’s refusal to comply with the administrative subpoena. 
 
T…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Employees Unearthed Alameda’s $65 Billion Backdoor Months Before Collapse]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74bc0f50d0</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ftx-alamedas-65-billion-backdoor-before-collapse/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T20:54:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the trial of Sam Bankman-Fried, the founder of the now-defunct crypto exchange FTX, got underway, the testimony of witnesses shed light on a report by The Wall Street Journal. 
 
The report revealed that the company’s employees had uncovered a secret link between the exchange and an affiliated trading firm, raising concerns about potential fraudulent activities. 
 
These revelations raise questions about what the firm’s leadership knew regarding problematic features that form the basis of the prosecution’s case.
 
FTX Employees’ Discovery Raises Questions
 
According to The Journal, employees discovered a backdoor connection between FTX and Alameda Research in May 2022, several months before the exchange’s collapse. 
 
This feature allowed Alameda, a sister trading company controlled by…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Against the Odds: Bitcoin Sees Fewest Obituaries in Ten Years]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74bc0b6098</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/against-the-odds-bitcoin-sees-fewest-obituaries-in-ten-years/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T20:11:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With two-thirds of the year done, the Bitcoin Obituaries list has recorded a decline in memorials compared to the last ten years, tallying just seven so-called bitcoin death announcements in 2023. The last sentiment of demise was voiced by tech magnate Chamath Palihapitiya, who proclaimed “crypto is dead in America” last April.
 
Bitcoin’s Steady 2023: Only 7 ‘Deaths’ So Far
 
Since April 27, 2023, spanning roughly 161 days, Bitcoin and the broader crypto realm have been free from any death proclamations. The Bitcoin Obituaries list on 99bitcoins.com reveals a tally of just seven such deaths this year, marking the fewest since 2012. For context, the list documented a lone eulogy in 2010, six in 2011, and a singular one in 2012.
 
 
Come 2013, the narrative shifted with a surge to 17 record…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bored Ape Creator Yuga Labs Invests in Spatial Computing Startup to Power 'Otherside']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200313</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200313/bored-ape-maker-invests-spatial-computing-startup-power-otherside"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T20:01:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hadean will establish a U.S. team to help Yuga Labs build out tech for the Bored Ape Yacht Club-themed Otherside metaverse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Expert Exposes Alleged ‘Web of Deception’ By Tron’s Justin Sun]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74bdf53393</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-expert-web-of-deception-tron-justin-sun/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T19:52:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an in-depth analysis shared on X (formerly Twitter), Bitcoin expert Dylan LeClair has pulled back the curtain on a purported “web of deception” attributed to Justin Sun, Tron’s founder. LeClair’s detailed examination touches on several nuanced movements within the crypto-sphere, and the findings present potentially alarming implications for the broader ecosystem.
 
Bitcoin Pundit Raises Grave Accusations
 
LeClair meticulously unveils what he believes to be a series of opaque transactions, particularly involving USDT and its alleged replacement, stUSDT, on the crypto exchange Huobi, rebranded as HTX after its acquisition by Sun in late 2022.
 
Starting his investigation, the Bitcoin expert remarked, “In late 2022, Justin Sun reportedly acquired a controlling stake in Huobi, now named HT…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried Trial: All the Names You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=198989</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/198989/sam-bankman-fried-trial-all-the-names-you-need-to-know"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T19:43:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These are the big players you should know before tuning into Sam Bankman-Fried's trial next week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Canadian Securities Regulator Softens Stance of Stablecoin Regulations]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74bdf61cde</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/canadian-securities-regulator-softens-stance-of-stablecoin-regulations/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T19:43:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Canadian Securities Administrators (CSA) has clarified  
its stance on regulating stablecoins. This move aims to establish a balance  
between investor protection and promoting innovation within the Canadian crypto  
market, the regulator said. 
  
  
In a statement published by the Ontario Securities  
Commission (OSC), the CSA said it may permit continued trading of stablecoins  
subject to its terms and conditions. 
  
  
Stan Magidson, the CSA's Chair and the CEO of the Alberta  
Securities Commission, said: "The transparency of value-referenced crypto  
assets about the composition and adequacy of their reserves and their  
governance are critical issues that must be addressed to protect Canadian  
investors and the integrity of our capital markets. This interim framework, which w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Enters ‘Quiet Bull Market’ as Safe Haven from Bond Market Turmoil, Analyst Says]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74bdf77cc6</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/10/05/bitcoin-enters-quiet-bull-market-as-safe-haven-from-bond-market-turmoil-analyst-says/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T19:30:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Investment research firm ByteTree upgraded bitcoin’s price outlook to “bull” from “neutral” as the crypto benefits as a “safe haven” amid an equity and bond sell-off.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Financial Services Firm Swan Unveils 'Collaborative Custody' Service]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74bdf77cbe</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/10/05/bitcoin-financial-services-firm-swan-unveils-collaborative-custody-service/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T19:30:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Swan and Blockstream's aim is to allow users to retain ultimate control of their bitcoin (BTC) while knowing that is stored in a highly secure way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deadmau5-Backed Nitro Nation NFT Racing Game Hits iOS and Android]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200314</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200314/deadmau5-backed-nitro-nation-nft-racing-game-ios-android"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T19:03:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mythical Games, the maker of NFL Rivals, has released a mobile racing game called Nitro Nation World Tour with optional NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale Wins Court Case vs. SEC: Bitcoin ETF on the Horizon?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74bdf2d898</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/markets/grayscale-wins-court-case-vs-sec-bitcoin-etf-on-the-horizon"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T19:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale Investments LLC, one of the world's largest crypto asset managers, has secured an unexpected court win against the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). A three-judge panel in DC's Court of Appeals in Washington ruled that the SEC's denial of Grayscale's proposal was "arbitrary and capricious" in that the SEC failed to explain the difference in treatment between spot bitcoin ETFs and futures bitcoin ETFs. 
The landmark ruling is believed to be a boon to an industry fraught with regulatory uncertainty. Grayscale—said to be the equivalent of a crypto Goldman Sachs for large OTC trades—could pave the way for future decisions that favor the first Bitcoin ETF or any product of its kind. Moreover, the court ruling may have set a new trajectory for bitcoin, creating the foundatio…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ivan Serrano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Lewis Was Charmed by Sam Bankman-Fried – But So Was Everyone Else]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74bdf362db</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/10/05/michael-lewis-was-charmed-by-sam-bankman-fried-but-so-was-everyone-else/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T18:54:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Lewis is getting slammed for a relatively sympathetic portrayal of SBF. The larger question is: Why did so many people fall under Sam’s spell?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emily Parker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tokenized Asset Industry To Reach $16 Trillion: 3 Crypto That Will Make You A Millionaire]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74bdf3c097</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/tokenized-asset-crypto-millionaire/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T18:52:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The tokenized assets industry is already ramping up with a number of crypto emerging that are taking advantage of the rising interest. Forecasts for this industry have been more than encouraging with multiple studies showing it will be a trillion-dollar industry. Given this, there are certain cryptos that are well-positioned to profit immensely from this growth.
 
A report from Boston Consulting Group puts the total market cap of the tokenized assets industry at $16 trillion in 2030 which is just seven years from now. During this time, a number of cryptocurrencies will surge alongside. Here are the top 3 picks that could make you a millionaire.
 
XRP Leads Crypto Harnessing Tokenized Assets
 
Ripple, the company behind the XRP token, has been getting deeply involved in the tokenized assets…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are Developers Leaving Crypto? Here’s What’s Going On]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200328</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200328/are-developers-leaving-crypto-heres-whats-going-on"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T18:40:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you look at open source crypto projects, active developers are at a 3-year low. But that's not necessarily bad, says a16z.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Sluggish After Sunday Surge—But Toncoin, Aave and Maker Make Gains]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200319</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200319/bitcoin-sluggish-toncoin-aave-and-maker-make-gains"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T18:20:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin's price hasn't moved much, but a number of DeFi tokens are on the up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Art of the Times': Art Blocks Founder Erick Calderon on the State of Generative Art]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zSjfRrl5/art-of-the-times-art-blocks-founder-erick-calderon-on-the-state-of-generative-art</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zSjfRrl5/art-of-the-times-art-blocks-founder-erick-calderon-on-the-state-of-generative-art"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T18:10:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Art Blocks founder and CEO Erick Calderon sat down with Sander Lutz, lead culture reporter at Decrypt's SCENE, at Art Blocks Marfa Weekend 2023. They discuss the evolution of the company and the generative art world, along with what draws art enthusiasts to be an active part of the community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK Won’t Be ‘Copying’ MiCA: Crypto Parliamentary Group Chair]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200289</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200289/uk-wont-be-copying-mica-crypto-parliamentary-group-chair"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T15:20:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Speaking at CCDAS 2023, Dr. Lisa Cameron MP said that the UK is exploring a “bespoke approach” to crypto regulation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOJ Lays Claim to 2 Luxury Jets Allegedly Owned by Sam Bankman-Fried]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200296</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200296/doj-lays-claim-2-luxury-jets-allegedly-owned-sam-bankman-fried"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T14:28:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Island Air Capital has disputed the DOJ's move to forfeit the two jets totaling $28 million, claiming the aircrafts belonged to it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Trial of Sam Bankman-Fried: Live Blog, Latest News and Insights]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199892</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199892/trial-sam-bankman-fried-live-blog-latest-news-insights"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T14:19:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried faces seven criminal charges related to the dramatic collapse of his crypto empire. Here's the latest on his trial.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sui Foundation Announces Ecosystem Fund Worth Over $50M]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200295</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200295/sui-foundation-announces-ecosystem-fund-worth-over-50m"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T13:12:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The foundation will reclaim 117 million SUI tokens worth $51.3 million from market makers to strengthen its DeFi ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong Police, SFC Launch Task Force to Monitor Crypto Exchanges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200269</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200269/hong-kong-police-sfc-launch-task-force-monitor-exchanges"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T11:07:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong's police force and leading securities regulator are integrating their efforts to monitor illegal exchange activities after the JPEX incident.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt Learn: Digital Ownership Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/6udZCotB/decrypt-learn-digital-ownership-explained</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/6udZCotB/decrypt-learn-digital-ownership-explained"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T10:57:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most powerful aspects of blockchain technology is its ability to provide us genuine ownership of our digital assets. This is called digital ownership. In this video, we’ll deep dive into digital ownership, why it matters, and how web3 makes owning digital assets like our social networks, music libraries, personal data, and beyond possible. Author: Clarissa Watson, Senior Writer at Consensys.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friend.tech Users Robbed of $385,000 in Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200274</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200274/friend-tech-users-robbed-385000-ethereum-yesterday"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T10:32:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto sleuth ZachXBT identified yet another swatch of SIM Swap attacks on four different Friend.tech users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Just 2% of Firms Cashing In on AI Hype Will Survive, Says Bitpanda CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200268</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200268/just-2-of-firms-cashing-in-on-ai-hype-will-survive-says-bitpanda-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T10:09:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“The crypto bros are now the AI bros” Bitpanda’s CEO Eric Demuth said, comparing the latest investment wave to previous booms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alys Key</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ZK-Proofs ‘Particularly Relevant in Financial Services’: Google Cloud Web3 Lead]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200136</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200136/zk-proofs-particularly-relevant-in-financial-services-google-cloud-web3-lead"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T09:19:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Cloud’s Web3 engineering lead highlighted use cases for on-chain privacy preserving technologies like ZK-proofs at CCDAS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Canva Bolsters AI Toolkit with Video Generation by Runway]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200251</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200251/canva-ai-magic-generative-tool-runway"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T01:43:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To fight deepfakes, Canva’s new platform restricts its AI from generating images of celebrities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Warner Music’s Head of NFTs and AI Departs: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200244</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200244/warner-musics-head-of-nfts-and-ai-departs-report"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T00:27:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oana Ruxandra, Warner’s chief digital officer, is officially departing the label after spearheading its aggressive push to embrace emerging technologies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Social Protocol Stars Arena Takes on Friend.Tech While Boosting AVAX]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200242</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200242/stars-arena-social-token-friend-tech-avax"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T00:14:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Stars Arena thrives, the AVAX token rides the wave, while some users remain skeptical.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried Trial Invoked Dogecoin and Solana on Day One—But Not FTT]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200236</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200236/sam-bankman-fried-trial-ftt-bitcoin-ethereum-dogecoin-solana"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T23:57:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was the shocking slide in the value of FTX's token that marked the final days of the doomed exchange.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Pours AI Powers Into Its New Pixel Phone and Home Assistant]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200223</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200223/google-ai-assistant-bard-pixel-phone-photo-editing"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T23:17:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just announced, an AI-powered multimodal super assistant, AI-powered photo editors, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Polygon in Trouble? Another Executive Departs Amid Crypto Market Downturn]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200194</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200194/polygon-in-trouble-executive-departures"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T22:47:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The co-founder's exit extends a long list of similar departures from prominent crypto projects in 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Latin American Crypto Scene Shows No Signs of Stopping: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200221</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200221/latin-american-crypto-scene-shows-no-signs-of-stopping-report"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T22:24:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As investor motivations shift over time, regulation continues to be the region's number one hurdle.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nintendo 3DS and Wii U Going Offline in 2024—Here's Why]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200206</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200206/nintendo-3ds-wii-u-going-offline-2024-heres-why"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T22:06:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nintendo is sunsetting online services for its Nintendo 3DS and Wii U consoles, with a few exceptions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Ubisoft Execs Arrested in France Amid Sexual Harassment Investigation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200177</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200177/former-ubisoft-execs-arrested-in-france-amid-sexual-harassment-investigation"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T21:34:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two ex-Ubisoft executives accused of enabling or committing sexual harassment and assault are among those detained by French police this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China May Be Reversing Its Anti-Crypto Stance: Chainalysis]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200213</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200213/hong-kong-crypto-mainland-china-chainalysis"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T21:29:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong has seen a surge in cryptocurrency activity that rivals mainland China.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Craig Wright Is Not Satoshi Nakamoto': Drama Inspires Bitcoin Banger]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200193</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200193/craig-wright-not-satoshi-nakamoto-drama-inspires-bitcoin-banger"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T20:42:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Musician Jonathan Mann has crafted a catchy tune about the latest twists around Craig Wright, who claims to have invented Bitcoin]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chain Letters: MoMA Launches 'Postcard' NFT Art Project]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200146</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200146/chain-letters-moma-launches-postcard-nft-art-project"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T20:23:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The MoMA Postcard program is designed to onboard the museum’s community to the potential of art created on the blockchain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Government Debt Grows by $275 Billion in One Day]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200179</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200179/national-debt-33-trillion-275-billion-in-one-day"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T19:51:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Analysts look at Bitcoin's deflationary prospects amid surging debt levels, which raise concerns about the nation's ability to fund essential services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Starbucks Is Selling Pumpkin Spice Latte NFTs—No, Really]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200163</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200163/starbucks-selling-pumpkin-spice-latte-nfts-no-really"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T18:33:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Will Pumpkin Spice Latte aficionados go for $20 NFTs inspired by the popular seasonal drinks? Starbucks is about to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['He Kept Lying': Prosecutors Unload on Sam Bankman-Fried as Defense Tries to Shift Blame]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200161</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200161/he-kept-lying-sbf-trial-opening-statements"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T18:26:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The DOJ said Sam Bankman-Fried confided in his inner circle about lying to cover his tracks. The defense called transfers to Alameda "loans."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo,André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Emerge: Decrypt's New Hub Exploring Beyond the Cutting Edge]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199925</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199925/emerge-emerging-technology-news-hub"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T18:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Step through our portal to the far side of the future, where AI is only the beginning.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-BlackRock Director Says SEC Will Approve a Bitcoin ETF in '3 to 6 Months']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200129</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200129/ex-blackrock-director-says-sec-will-approve-bitcoin-etf-3-6-months"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T16:02:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two former managing directors at BlackRock say that U.S. approval of a spot Bitcoin ETF is basically a done deal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 12 People Who Will Decide Sam Bankman-Fried's Fate]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199907</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199907/jurors-who-will-decide-sam-bankman-frieds-fate"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T15:55:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The jurors who will decide Sam Bankman-Fried's fate include a retired corrections officer, librarian, and former prosecutor.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo,André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Martin Shkreli on E/ACC and SBF in Prison]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QONaWXKZ/martin-shkreli-on-e-acc-and-sbf-in-prison</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QONaWXKZ/martin-shkreli-on-e-acc-and-sbf-in-prison"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T22:03:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reza Jafery and Martin Shkreli sit down for a casual conversation about the growing movement that is E/ACC, what songs they could recite at gunpoint, and whether or not SBF will thrive or just survive during his time in prison.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Can AI Do in Gaming?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JKuqCMao/what-can-ai-do-in-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JKuqCMao/what-can-ai-do-in-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T17:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI Arena CEO Brandon Da Silva and COO Wei Xie discuss how artificial intelligence can shape the video game experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['There Are No Real Standards': Ready Player Me CEO Timmu Tõke on Building for an Open Gaming Ecosystem]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TH3KEAI0/there-are-no-real-standards-ready-player-me-ceo-timmu-tke-on-building-for-an-open-gaming-ecosystem</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TH3KEAI0/there-are-no-real-standards-ready-player-me-ceo-timmu-tke-on-building-for-an-open-gaming-ecosystem"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T17:29:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Timmu Tõke, co-founder and CEO of Ready Player Me, joins Decrypt contributor Ryan Gladwin to discuss the startup's approach to powering avatars that are interoperable across games and metaverse platforms—and what's needed to convince the industry to adopt standards and open up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain Is 'Only Way' Forward for Gaming, Says Shrapnel Studio Head]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/fhoy7Z8f/blockchain-is-only-way-forward-for-gaming-says-shrapnel-studio-head</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/fhoy7Z8f/blockchain-is-only-way-forward-for-gaming-says-shrapnel-studio-head"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T21:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shrapnel Studio Head Don Norbury tells Kate Irwin the reasons why the upcoming first-person shooter game will offer a wide range of NFTs. He also reveals team-based gameplay plans and shares how game maps have already changed this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Social Media Sentiment Is Key to Crypto Price Discovery]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/981TBppa/social-media-sentiment-is-key-to-crypto-price-discovery</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/981TBppa/social-media-sentiment-is-key-to-crypto-price-discovery"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T23:47:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sacha Ghebali, Director of Strategy and Business Development at The TIE, says social media sentiment remains a key factor in price movements for major cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin and Ethereum. However, he notes that sentiment has turned more negative lately amid regulatory uncertainty. Ghebali believes events like the Ripple lawsuit ruling significantly impacted sentiment and prices. André Beganski interviewed him at Messari Mainnet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[500Altcoins discusses DeFi Summer and the Dubai Crypto Scene - This Time Will Be Different - Episode 2]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cI7p8AK3/500altcoins-discusses-defi-summer-and-the-dubai-crypto-scene-this-time-will-be-different-episode-2</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cI7p8AK3/500altcoins-discusses-defi-summer-and-the-dubai-crypto-scene-this-time-will-be-different-episode-2"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our host Reza Jafery is joined by Gareth Fenney aka 500Altcoins. They discuss the glory days of DeFi Summer and whether or not its a smart move for builders in the crypto space to relocate to Dubai.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralize Derivatives Trading with Custom Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/lfmwAjB9/decentralize-derivatives-trading-with-custom-blockchain</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/lfmwAjB9/decentralize-derivatives-trading-with-custom-blockchain"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T10:37:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Gogel of dYdX discusses how the decentralized exchange is building a custom blockchain to fully decentralize derivatives trading. He explained how the new dYdX chain will allow validators to run order books in memory, enabling decentralized order matching at scale. This shift aims to increase security and transparency for traders while maintaining the performance of centralized exchanges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Accounting Challenges and Opportunities]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/0Sezz6pZ/crypto-accounting-challenges-and-opportunities</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/0Sezz6pZ/crypto-accounting-challenges-and-opportunities"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As crypto matures, accounting and tax regulations are evolving. Amy Kalnoki of Bitwave explains how her company helps crypto companies properly account for digital assets. She notes the importance of flexibility as new crypto assets emerge and regulations change. Stacy Elliott interviewed her at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Most Crypto Users Don't Trust Themselves to Keep Their Seed Phrase Safe: Ledger CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/0kYf2Qed/most-crypto-users-dont-trust-themselves-to-keep-their-seed-phrase-safe-ledger-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/0kYf2Qed/most-crypto-users-dont-trust-themselves-to-keep-their-seed-phrase-safe-ledger-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Stacy Elliott sat down with Ledger CEO Pascal Gauthier to discuss crypto custody post-FTX, and the hardware wallet manufacturer's controversial Ledger Recover service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[India's 1% Crypto Tax Has Been a Nightmare for High-Frequency Traders, Says Shardeum CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/fxygwLvH/indias-1-crypto-tax-has-been-a-nightmare-for-high-frequency-traders-says-shardeum-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/fxygwLvH/indias-1-crypto-tax-has-been-a-nightmare-for-high-frequency-traders-says-shardeum-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As India figures out its regulatory approach to the crypto industry, one thing is clear to Shardeum co-founder Nischal Shetty: “If you're a high-frequency trader, you can't afford to lose a percentage every time you sell,” he told Decrypt's Andre Beganski at Messari Mainnet in New York. “That's something that's caused a lot of issues.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Newly Partnered with Visa, Solana Focuses on Reliability]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/MZoxvulr/newly-partnered-with-visa-solana-focuses-on-reliability</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/MZoxvulr/newly-partnered-with-visa-solana-focuses-on-reliability"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana has improved network reliability through upgrades like Quick and local fee markets. It recently partnered with Visa to allow settling transactions in USDC on Solana. This could enable merchants to receive instant payments and save on credit card processing fees. Stacy Elliott spoke with Austin Federa, Head of Strategy for the Solana Foundation, at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Need to Start Thinking About How we Make Crypto Easy to Use: Robinhood Crypto General Manager]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PLZ0FpdC/we-need-to-start-thinking-about-how-we-make-crypto-easy-to-use-robinhood-crypto-general-manager</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PLZ0FpdC/we-need-to-start-thinking-about-how-we-make-crypto-easy-to-use-robinhood-crypto-general-manager"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Stacy Elliott sat down with Robinhood Crypto general manager Johann Kerbrat at Messari Mainnet 2023, to talk about the trading platform's crypto wallet, onboarding new users through simplicity, and keeping platform fees sustainable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Regulation Threatens U.S. Dominance of Financial Markets, Says CoinRoutes CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/CrpvzFjL/regulation-threatens-us-dominance-of-financial-markets-says-coinroutes-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/CrpvzFjL/regulation-threatens-us-dominance-of-financial-markets-says-coinroutes-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dave Weisberger, Co-Founder and CEO of CoinRoutes, argued that excessive regulation in the U.S. threatens to undermine the country's long-standing dominance in global financial markets. He warned that other countries are embracing blockchain and crypto to build more efficient digital markets, which could cause the US to lose its competitive edge and trillions in GDP. Weisberger said CoinRoutes is now focusing more on expanding internationally due to restrictive policies in the U.S. He was interviewed by André Beganski of Decrypt at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Developer-Friendly zkRollup to Scale Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/OvAFgxTd/building-a-developer-friendly-zkrollup-to-scale-ethereum</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/OvAFgxTd/building-a-developer-friendly-zkrollup-to-scale-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daniel Helm, head of Developer Relations at Scroll, discussess how they are building a zkRollup to scale Ethereum transactions and lower fees. He explained their focus on creating a seamless developer experience by maintaining Ethereum's ethos and tooling. Scroll aims to launch their mainnet soon, providing more scalable blockspace for Ethereum developers. Stacy Elliott of Decrypt interviewed him at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin's Narrative Is Shifting Towards Layer-2 Solutions]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/axArPRp3/bitcoins-narrative-is-shifting-towards-layer-2-solutions</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/axArPRp3/bitcoins-narrative-is-shifting-towards-layer-2-solutions"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rich Rines, original Core DAO contributor and former Coinbase engineer, discusses how the narrative around Bitcoin is shifting in 2023. While Bitcoin remains digital gold, new layer 2 solutions are emerging to unlock more utility and value from the huge amounts of capital stored in Bitcoin. He says these innovations can benefit Bitcoin holders while keeping Bitcoin maximalists happy by building outside the base layer. André Beganski interviewed him at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Explosive Growth Ahead for Enterprise Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/xXOrNbX9/explosive-growth-ahead-for-enterprise-blockchain</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/xXOrNbX9/explosive-growth-ahead-for-enterprise-blockchain"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paul Brody drives Ernst & Young (EY) initiatives and investments in blockchain technology across consulting, audit, and tax business lines. He says enterprise blockchain adoption is nearing an inflection point. Brody believes blockchains will one day handle 40 billion transactions daily across industries like automotive and pharma. Stacy Elliott interviewed him at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Base as a 'Bridge, Not an Island']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/oZPr7bzY/base-as-a-bridge-not-an-island</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/oZPr7bzY/base-as-a-bridge-not-an-island"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase's Jesse Pollak, creator of layer-2 blockchain Base, says the launch of the network has exceeded expectations, even if plans changed along the way. He believes Arbitrum One will help bring billions onto blockchain by enabling seamless user experiences. Stacy Elliott interviewed him at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On-Chain Gaming Poised for Mass Adoption]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/6ZryETKh/on-chain-gaming-poised-for-mass-adoption</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/6ZryETKh/on-chain-gaming-poised-for-mass-adoption"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T02:23:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jack O'Holleran is CEO and co-founder of SKALE Labs. He explains how on-chain gaming is ready for the mainstream after overcoming early challenges like high fees and poor user experience. Companies can now build blockchain games that look and feel like traditional games, and scalability improvements allow games to support hundreds of millions of players without performance issues. He was interviewed by André Beganski at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>