<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-06-19T06:22:47.107Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-06-19T06:22:47.107Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arkham Offers a $150,000 Bounty for the Identity of Alleged Donald Trump’s DJT Token Creator]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740a07beb2</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/arkham-offers-a-150000-bounty-for-the-identity-of-alleged-donald-trumps-djt-token-creator/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T06:21:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arkham, a cryptocurrency analytics platform, has put a bounty of 100,000 ARKM, valued at $150,000, for information leading to the reveal of the creator of DJT, a Solana token linked to the former President and current Republican presidential candidate Donald Trump. While the token was issued with Trump’s involvement according to sources, there has not […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto News Today: Ethereum Price Jumps on SEC Probe Clarity]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19601198/Crypto-News-Today-Ethereum-Price-Jumps-on-SEC-Probe-Clarity</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19601198/Crypto-News-Today-Ethereum-Price-Jumps-on-SEC-Probe-Clarity"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T06:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitwise updates S-1 for Ethereum ETF with $2.5M seed funding, Pantera Capital interest, and SEC feedback. The SEC's enforcement division announced it is concluding its Ethereum investigation, but Consensys indicates the battle continues. Major Events To WatchCrypto Fear and Greed Index:The...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitwise’s amended Ethereum ETF filing says Pantera interested in $100M buy]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19601148/Bitwises-amended-Ethereum-ETF-filing-says-Pantera-interested-in-100M-buy</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19601148/Bitwises-amended-Ethereum-ETF-filing-says-Pantera-interested-in-100M-buy"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T06:03:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Asset management firm Bitwise has disclosed Pantera is interested in buying its upcoming spot Ether ETF, but it could spend more, less — or nothing at all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily Discussion, June 19, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19601176/Daily-Discussion-June-19-2024</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19601176/Daily-Discussion-June-19-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T06:03:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Please utilize this sticky thread for all general Bitcoin discussions! If you see posts on the front page or /r/Bitcoin/new which are better suited for this daily discussion thread, please help out by directing the OP to this thread instead. Thank you! If you don't get an answer to your...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s Rising Difficulty Points To $100,000 Value By Year’s End, Says Market Analyst]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740a021352</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-rising-difficulty-points-100000-year-end/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T06:02:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Market expert and Bitcoin advocate Timothy Peterson has highlighted the importance of Bitcoin’s growth rate in difficulty as a potential indicator for a surge in its price amid a sharp correction in recent days that led to a price drop below $65,000 for the largest cryptocurrency on the market. 
 
In a recent social media post, Peterson suggested that the network’s expanding difficulty, a key metric that measures the computational effort required to mine new blocks on the blockchain, could pave the way for Bitcoin to reach $100,000 by the end of the year. 
 
Bitcoin’s Difficulty-Price Relationship
 
Peterson noted that BTC’s difficulty is a vital aspect of its decentralized nature, automatically adjusting every two weeks to maintain an average block creation time of approximately 10 minute…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s Rising Difficulty Points To $100,000 Value By Year’s End, Says Market Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19601139/Bitcoins-Rising-Difficulty-Points-To-100000-Value-By-Years-End-Says-Market-Analyst</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19601139/Bitcoins-Rising-Difficulty-Points-To-100000-Value-By-Years-End-Says-Market-Analyst"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T06:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Market expert and Bitcoin advocate Timothy Peterson has highlighted the importance of Bitcoin’s growth rate in difficulty as a potential indicator for a surge in its price amid a sharp correction in recent days that led to a price drop below $65,000 for the largest cryptocurrency on the market....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Is Closing Investigation into Ethereum as a Security]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740a028fc0</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/sec-is-closing-investigation-into-ethereum-as-a-security/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T05:58:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) is closing its investigation into Ethereum, the second-largest cryptocurrency by market capitalisation, as a security, Consensys confirmed today (Wednesday).
Ethereum Is Not a Security
“The Enforcement Division of the SEC has notified us that it is closing its investigation into Ethereum 2.0,” the tweet by the company stated, adding: “This means that the SEC will not bring charges alleging that sales of ETH are securities transactions.”
Consensys further confirmed that the decision came after the US-based blockchain firm sent a letter to the regulator on June 7 asking to “confirm that the May ETH ETF approvals, which were premised on ETH being a commodity, meant the agency would close its Ethereum 2.0 investigation.”

The decision follows a lett…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arnab Shome</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Institutional DeFi players will bring commercial real estate onchain: KPMG exec]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19601109/Institutional-DeFi-players-will-bring-commercial-real-estate-onchain-KPMG-exec</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19601109/Institutional-DeFi-players-will-bring-commercial-real-estate-onchain-KPMG-exec"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T05:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi activity from institutions would be more “permissioned” as market participants will want to know who they’re dealing with, KPMG’s Kunal Bhasin said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB) and Dogecoin (DOGE) Now Owned by Major VR Gaming Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19601112/Shiba-Inu-SHIB-and-Dogecoin-DOGE-Now-Owned-by-Major-VR-Gaming-Platform</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19601112/Shiba-Inu-SHIB-and-Dogecoin-DOGE-Now-Owned-by-Major-VR-Gaming-Platform"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T05:42:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prominent metaverse firm The Sandbox has announced that it now holds SHIB and DOGE]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Market Surge As Ethereum (ETH) Delcared As Commodity By SEC, Ends Investigation!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19601084/Crypto-Market-Surge-As-Ethereum-ETH-Delcared-As-Commodity-By-SEC-Ends-Investigation</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19601084/Crypto-Market-Surge-As-Ethereum-ETH-Delcared-As-Commodity-By-SEC-Ends-Investigation"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T05:35:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite the market leader, the BTC price recorded a correction of 0.51% within the past day, the Ethereum token has surged 3.26% in valuation following the conclusion of the ongoing investigation by the SEC. Furthermore, top Ethereum-based tokens have displayed a similar trend by adding...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Patrick McHenry Explains FIT21's Passage]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740a0d436d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/06/19/patrick-mchenry-explains-fit21s-passage/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T05:34:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Congressman Patrick McHenry (R-N.C.) chairs the powerful House Financial Services Committee, and has been the leading Republican on the panel for years. Last year, he spent a few weeks as the Speaker Pro Tempore of the House of Representatives, after lawmakers voted to oust then-speaker Kevin McCarthy (R-Calif.). McHenry announced his retirement in December and will leave office when his term expires this coming January. He spoke virtually at Consensus 2024 in Austin at the end of May.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oil land buyer LandBridge makes a nod to crypto miners in $320M IPO]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19601078/Oil-land-buyer-LandBridge-makes-a-nod-to-crypto-miners-in-320M-IPO</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19601078/Oil-land-buyer-LandBridge-makes-a-nod-to-crypto-miners-in-320M-IPO"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T05:30:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LandBridge has a huge amount of land in the middle of America’s oil country, but it also says it can make big money off crypto miners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Closes Ethereum 2.0 Investigation]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740a0dc0eb</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/sec-closes-ethereum-2-0-investigation/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T05:30:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Consensys has announced that the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has decided to close its investigation into Ethereum 2.0. This decision implies that the SEC will not allege that sales of ETH are securities transactions. The announcement follows a request from Consensys to the SEC to affirm that the approval of ETH exchange-traded funds […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Patrick McHenry Explains FIT21's Passage]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19601077/Patrick-McHenry-Explains-FIT21s-Passage</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19601077/Patrick-McHenry-Explains-FIT21s-Passage"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T05:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Congressman Patrick McHenry (R-N.C.) chairs the powerful House Financial Services Committee, and has been the leading Republican on the panel for years. Last year, he spent a few weeks as the Speaker Pro Tempore of the House of Representatives, after lawmakers voted to oust then-speaker Kevin...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can Cardano (ADA) Reclaims This Resistance and Gain Bullish Momentum?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19601066/Can-Cardano-ADA-Reclaims-This-Resistance-and-Gain-Bullish-Momentum</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19601066/Can-Cardano-ADA-Reclaims-This-Resistance-and-Gain-Bullish-Momentum"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T05:28:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA) extended losses and tested the $0.360 zone. ADA is now rising and might attempt to clear the $0.400 resistance zone. ADA price remained in a bearish zone and settled below $0.40. The price is trading below $0.400 and the 100-hourly simple moving average. There is a connecting...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Retail Crowd Still Missing, Can They Push BTC Above $70K?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19601060/Bitcoin-Retail-Crowd-Still-Missing-Can-They-Push-BTC-Above-70K</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19601060/Bitcoin-Retail-Crowd-Still-Missing-Can-They-Push-BTC-Above-70K"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T05:24:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Research reveals the retail crowd is not yet present in the current bitcoin market cycle, but investor fear persists.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creator of DJT exposed for insider trading and connection to Barron Trump]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19601046/Creator-of-DJT-exposed-for-insider-trading-and-connection-to-Barron-Trump</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19601046/Creator-of-DJT-exposed-for-insider-trading-and-connection-to-Barron-Trump"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T05:16:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The DJT token drama just got messier. Martin Shkreli, the infamous “Pharma Bro” who spent years in prison for financial crimes, has been forced to hop on X Spaces to tell the world he’s the creator of DJT. This comes amid allegations of insider trading and connections to high-profile figures, as...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Bet Gone Wrong: Taiwanese Man Faces Charges For Betting On Presidential Elections]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740a0feb19</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-bet-gone-wrong-taiwanese-faces-charges-bet/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T05:11:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A man has been accused of breaking Taiwan’s President and Vice President Election Recall Act after using an online crypto-gambling site to wager on the presidential elections. Thirty people have been detained in Taiwan for betting on the country’s electoral results.
 
 
Man Detained For $500 Crypto Betting
 
On Monday, Taiwanese news outlet LTN revealed a man is facing charges for allegedly breaking the election recall act at the end of 2023. The Prosecutor’s office in the Shilin District accused a man with the last name “Chen” of using the crypto-betting site Polymarket to wager around $500 on the presidential election.
 
Seemingly, Chen used his phone to access Polymarket’s website and bet 472.17 USDC on Ko Wen-je’s victory during the presidential elections. Additionally, he bet another …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rubmar Garcia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Martin Shkreli Claims Of Co-creating DJT token: ZachXBT]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19601031/Martin-Shkreli-Claims-Of-Co-creating-DJT-token-ZachXBT</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19601031/Martin-Shkreli-Claims-Of-Co-creating-DJT-token-ZachXBT"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T05:06:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Martin Shkreli has claimed that he has co-created the DJT, a Solana token themed after Donald Trump, as revealed by ZachXBT on X. ZachXBT further supported the alleged link between DJT and Shkreli with data indicating a large DJT holder selling off $832,000 worth of tokens for USDC stablecoin....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy Leads Bitcoin Capital Markets]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19601021/MicroStrategy-Leads-Bitcoin-Capital-Markets</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19601021/MicroStrategy-Leads-Bitcoin-Capital-Markets"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T05:04:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent research report, Bernstein revealed that MicroStrategy is pioneering BTC capital markets. Analysts wrote that MSTR is the only corporation that has developed institutional demand for Bitcoin-linked convertibles. To date, MicroStrategy has raised $4 billion of convertible debt only to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia Becomes The World’s Largest Company By Market Cap!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19601020/Nvidia-Becomes-The-Worlds-Largest-Company-By-Market-Cap</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19601020/Nvidia-Becomes-The-Worlds-Largest-Company-By-Market-Cap"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T05:01:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia has become the World’s largest company by Market cap as it surged by 3.28%. It outpaced Microsoft to grab the top spot with its market cap soaring above $3.3 trillion. Apple stands third with a market cap of $3.279 trillion. This year, Nvidia made excellent gains posting...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apexrom (APR) Debuts on ProBit Global: Pioneering a User-Centric Crypto Ecosystem]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19601055/Apexrom-APR-Debuts-on-ProBit-Global-Pioneering-a-User-Centric-Crypto-Ecosystem</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19601055/Apexrom-APR-Debuts-on-ProBit-Global-Pioneering-a-User-Centric-Crypto-Ecosystem"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T05:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apexrom has secured a listing on the ProBit Global exchange for its APR token. Apexrom aims to provide a robust platform where users maintain significant control and visibility over their assets. One standout feature is the Prz Games Platform, which merges NFTs and play-to-earn games. Apexrom is...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin & MicroStrategy’s concerning parallels: Peter Schiff issues warning]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19601016/Bitcoin-MicroStrategys-concerning-parallels-Peter-Schiff-issues-warning</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19601016/Bitcoin-MicroStrategys-concerning-parallels-Peter-Schiff-issues-warning"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T05:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Could hedge funds crashing MSTR actually lead to a Bitcoin price collapse, as Schiff suggests?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Bet Gone Wrong: Taiwanese Man Faces Charges For Betting On Presidential Elections]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19601018/Crypto-Bet-Gone-Wrong-Taiwanese-Man-Faces-Charges-For-Betting-On-Presidential-Elections</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19601018/Crypto-Bet-Gone-Wrong-Taiwanese-Man-Faces-Charges-For-Betting-On-Presidential-Elections"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T05:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A man has been accused of breaking Taiwan’s President and Vice President Election Recall Act after using an online crypto-gambling site to wager on the presidential elections. Thirty people have been detained in Taiwan for betting on the country’s electoral results. Related Reading: New South...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Soars Above $3,500 After SEC Clears Regulatory Hurdles]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19601030/Ethereum-Soars-Above-3500-After-SEC-Clears-Regulatory-Hurdles</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19601030/Ethereum-Soars-Above-3500-After-SEC-Clears-Regulatory-Hurdles"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T04:59:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum’s value surged beyond $3,500 following the conclusion of the US Securities and Exchange Commission’s (SEC) prolonged investigation. Previously, there were looming doubts about Ethereum potentially being classified as an unregistered security. This uncertainty had been a significant...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s Declining Volatility Signals Maturity]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19601002/Bitcoins-Declining-Volatility-Signals-Maturity</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19601002/Bitcoins-Declining-Volatility-Signals-Maturity"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T04:57:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to Kaiko data, Binance and Bybit witnessed the most Bitcoin sales last week. BTC dipped by just over 4% last week, with selling outpacing buying on nearly all exchanges. Won trading slowed significantly in the Q2. The weekly trading volume of the four largest exchanges in South Korea...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stand With Crypto Endorses 18 New House and Senate Candidates]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740a0b8def</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/stand-with-crypto-endorses-18-new-house-and-senate-candidates/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T04:39:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stand With Crypto, a crypto and blockchain-focused political action committee (PAC), has decided to endorse 18 additional House and Senate candidates from both parties to get crypto-friendly allies to achieve positive results in the upcoming elections. Among the favored are Kirsten Gillibrand, Rick Scott, Dan Goldman, Young Kim, and House hopefuls Blake Masters and Sarah […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Users Flee Network After Bearish Price, But Ethereum Continues To Break Records]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740bf6f5f0</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-users-flee-bearish-price-ethereum-break/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T04:10:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data shows that Bitcoin has been seeing an exodus of investors recently, while the Ethereum network has continued to grow.
 
Total Amount Of Bitcoin Holders Have Just Seen Largest Drop Since March
 
According to data from the on-chain analytics firm Santiment, the Total Amount of Holders indicator has just seen its largest 3-day drawdown for Bitcoin since March.
 
 
As the metric’s name already implies, the “Total Amount of Holders” keeps track of the total number of wallets on a given cryptocurrency network currently carrying a non-zero balance.
 
When the value of this metric goes up, it suggests that either new investors are joining the blockchain or old ones who had left earlier are coming back. The indicator also naturally rises when existing users create new addresses for pr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez Bashes Fairshake Involvement in New York Democratic Party Primaries]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740bf1f1f9</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/alexandria-ocasio-cortez-bashes-fairshake-involvement-in-new-york-democratic-party-primaries/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T03:41:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New York Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez has criticized the involvement of Fairshake, a crypto-focused super PAC, in New York’s 16th congressional district democratic party elections. Ocasio-Cortez qualified the media campaign against incumbent Jamaal Bowman, valued at over $2 million, as “corruption” and a “core threat to American democracy” on social media. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez Tells Crypto PAC […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rise Of Crypto Scams: Fake Websites And Misinformation Plague The Industry]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740bfd15b2</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/rise-of-crypto-scams-fake-websites-misinformation/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T03:09:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recent reports reveal a surge in fraudulent activities within the crypto space, ranging from fake websites featuring fabricated team members to misleading press releases about fundraising and partnerships with prominent industry players. 
 
As the crypto market experiences a resurgence and attracts retail and institutional investors, the risk of falling victim to these scams is higher than ever. 
 
The Dark Side Of Crypto?
 
In a disturbing case reported by Bloomberg, individuals unrelated to the crypto industry found their headshots displayed on websites of crypto startups, falsely claiming their involvement as team members. 
 
Jakob-Moritz Eberl, a social scientist at the University of Vienna with no association with cryptocurrencies, discovered his picture on the websites of InfinitySta…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why UK Crypto Manager Tap Global Is Entering the US—Despite an Uncertain Regulatory Environment]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235989</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235989/why-uk-crypto-manager-tap-global-is-entering-the-us-despite-an-uncertain-regulatory-environment"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T03:02:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tap Global said it's eliminated regulatory risk it may face, "as long as we don't do anything completely stupid or illegal or fraudulent."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Charges Empire Market Operators in $430M Dark Web Scheme — They Face Maximum Sentence of Life in Prison]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740bffddd0</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/us-charges-empire-market-operators-in-430m-dark-web-scheme-they-face-maximum-sentence-of-life-in-prison/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T02:41:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Homeland Security Investigations has charged two men for operating Empire Market, a dark web marketplace, facilitating $430 million in illegal transactions. The defendants face severe penalties, including life imprisonment. “During the investigation, federal law enforcement seized cryptocurrency valued at $75 million at the time of the seizures, as well as cash and precious […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analyst Calls Dogecoin, Shiba Inu, FLOKI ‘Dino Coins’, Here’s What It Means]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740bfb2311</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-shiba-inu-floki-dino-coins/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T02:06:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A crypto analyst has shed light on the performance of meme coins and altcoins in the upcoming bull run. He has labeled popular meme-based cryptocurrencies like Dogecoin (DOGE), Shiba Inu (SHIB), and FLOKI, as “Dino Coins,” emphasizing that these tokens could potentially skyrocket during the altcoin season.
 
Dogecoin, Meme Coins Expected To Lead Altcoin Season
 
In a rather lengthy X (formerly Twitter) post, a crypto analyst identified as ‘Vapor’ shared detailed insights on the crypto market’s bullish outlook. He referred to meme coins like PEPE, Dogwifhat (WIF), BONK, Dogecoin, Shiba Inu and Floki as “blue chip” meme coins, which have achieved a significant level of stability and acceptance in the market, fueled by their extensive communities and listings on top tier Centralized Exchanges…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analyst: Bank of Thailand Boosts Gold Reserves to Push De-Dollarized Trading System Fueled by CBDC]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740be580cc</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/analyst-bank-of-thailand-boosts-gold-reserves-to-push-de-dollarized-trading-system-fueled-by-cbdc/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T01:42:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bank of Thailand might be increasing its gold reserves to power a de-dollarized trading system, according to Jan Nieuwenhuijs, a gold market analyst. Nieuwenhuijs states that the Bank of Thailand’s constant gold purchases might indicate the nation is preparing to address the possible trade imbalances derived from using Mbridge, a CBDC cross-border settlement project. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Is Dropping Its Investigation Into Ethereum, Consensys Says]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236039</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236039/sec-dropping-ethereum-investigation-consensys"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T01:21:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ethereum giant has pushed back against regulatory pressure over the world's second largest cryptocurrency.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Kawailani Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Bank Vaults To Wallets: Here’s How Two Bankers Used Crypto To Launder Millions]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740be0d9f2</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/heres-how-two-bankers-used-crypto-launder-millions/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T01:05:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A local Chinese bank, the Bank of Huludao, has recently discovered an “intricate embezzlement” and money laundering scheme via crypto orchestrated by two of its top former executives.
 
The scandal, which has sent ripples through the financial community, involved the illicit transfer of a staggering 1.8 billion yuan (approximately $248 million). This discovery highlights the vulnerabilities within financial institutions and the methods individuals use to exploit these systems for personal gain.
 
 
Cryptocurrency And Cross-Border Laundering
 
As reported by the Chinese news outlet The National Business Daily, the scheme was not just confined to the misappropriation of funds but extended to “sophisticated laundering tactics” involving cryptocurrency.
 
Detailed investigations and court docu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Working With 10 Governments Globally, CEO Reveals in Rediscovered Interview]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740bec46a5</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ripple-working-with-10-governments-globally-ceo-reveals-in-rediscovered-interview/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T00:29:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a resurfaced video clip, Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse stated that his crypto firm is collaborating with around 10 governments globally on central bank digital currencies (CBDCs). “A central bank digital currency is a stablecoin. It’s just issued by the government,” the executive described. Ripple CEO on Working With Governments Worldwide A video clip surfaced […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LandBridge IPO Aims For $1.6 Billion Valuation, Sees Bitcoin Mining As Growth Vector]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740beea28d</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/landbridge-ipo-bitcoin-mining-as-growth-vector/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T00:04:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LandBridge is seeking to raise $319 million through an initial public offering (IPO) in the United States, targeting a valuation of $1.6 billion. 
 
While the IPO piqued interest—dominating headlines—Matthew Sigel, the Head of Digital Assets at VanEck, noted that LandBridge, quoting an unnamed official, is keen on tapping into opportunities presented by Bitcoin mining activities.
 
Is Bitcoin Mining A Growth Vector? LandBridge Sees An Opportunity
 
LandBridge owns over 220,000 acres in the oil-rich Permian Basin. It generates revenue by leasing land and selling extracted resources, including oil and natural gas. This focus on royalty contracts aims to shield the company from the price volatility common in the commodity market.
 
However, while the firm is keen to expand deeper into the com…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dalmas Ngetich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop Meme Coin on Solana Plummets as GME Fever Cools]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236035</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236035/gme-solana-meme-coin-plummets-gamestop-mania-fades"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T23:48:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the hype surrounding the return of Roaring Kitty fades, the Solana meme coin GME has plunged.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Reiff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Balaji Srinivasan Explains Why Crypto Will Dominate Post-AI Money Systems]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740beb193d</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/balaji-srinivasan-explains-why-crypto-will-dominate-post-ai-money-systems/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T23:20:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Balaji Srinivasan argues that in the era of AI, money will become cryptocurrency, providing digital scarcity to complement AI’s digital abundance. “AI is digital abundance but it doesn’t make everything abundant. Crypto is digital scarcity and complements AI’s abundance. So money after AI is crypto,” he detailed. ‘Money Itself Becomes Cryptocurrency’ Balaji Srinivasan, a prominent […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance CEO Predicts Bitcoin Rally Above $80,000, But What Will Drive It?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740bd4bc48</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/binance-ceo-bitcoin-80000/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T23:04:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Chief Executive Officer (CEO), Richard Teng has made a bullish prediction for Bitcoin, the world’s largest cryptocurrency. Despite BTC’s recent downward trend, Teng foresees the cryptocurrency hitting $80,000 in this market cycle, citing the influence of Spot Bitcoin ETFs and Spot Ethereum ETFs as potential drivers.
 
Bitcoin Predicted To Hit $80,000 In 2024
 
In a recent interview on the YouTube channel, Bankless, Teng shared his 2024 prediction for Bitcoin, foreseeing major gains ahead for the pioneer cryptocurrency. 
 
The Binance CEO disclosed that in 2023, he had initially predicted BTC would hit an all-time high of $80,000. However, with the significant market changes brought about by the approval and launch of Spot Bitcoin ETFs, he now anticipates Bitcoin surpassing $80,000 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Wall Street Firm Says Best Bitcoin Mining Stock Isn't a US Company]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236028</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236028/bitdeer-btdr-undervalued-cantor-fitzgerald"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T22:54:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cantor Fitzgerald believes the market is underestimating Bitdeer (BTDR), whose stock is up 50% this month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple CEO: Pro-Crypto Stance Will Win Votes in Upcoming Elections]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740bd18876</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ripple-ceo-pro-crypto-stance-will-win-votes-in-upcoming-elections/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T22:20:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse expressed his view on the political landscape in the U.S. regarding cryptocurrency regulation on social media platform X on Monday. “You’ll hear this a lot more in the next few months in the U.S. — candidates will only gain votes for being pro-crypto, and absolutely lose them for being anti-crypto. There’s […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘PixelTap’ Daily Combo Guide: How to Earn Millions of Free Coins in the Pixelverse Telegram Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235998</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/pixeltap-daily-combo-guide-earn-free-coins-pixelverse-telegram-game"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T22:12:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram game PixelTap lets you battle robots to earn coins ahead of a token airdrop—and you can earn way more with this easy bonus.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$367 Million Crypto Longs Flushed After Altcoin Market Crash]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740bd3286b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/367-million-crypto-longs-flushed-altcoin-crash/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T22:05:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data shows the cryptocurrency derivatives market has suffered a high amount of liquidations in the past day after the crash the altcoins have seen.
 
Altcoin Longs Witness Squeeze, Ethereum Leads In Liquidations
 
The past day has been a volatile time for the cryptocurrency market, with the majority of the altcoins suffering from drops of more than 5%. As is generally the case, this sector-wide volatility has resulted in chaos over at the derivatives side.
 
 
According to data from CoinGlass, the derivatives market has observed contracts worth almost $429 million finding liquidation over the last 24 hours.
 

 
 
A contract is said to be “liquidated” when the platform with which it’s open has to forcibly close it up after accumulating losses of a certain degree (the exact figure may diffe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rumored Trump Token DJT Flying as Traders Bet on Whether It's Legit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236002</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236002/trump-djt-token-solana-meme-coin-polymarket-bets-official"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T22:02:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Polymarket’s traders leaned toward “no,” a former drug firm executive declared it a “100% chance.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Holding Off on Vision Pro 2 in Favor of Cheaper Model: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235994</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235994/cheaper-apple-vision-pro-report"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T21:28:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple is reportedly prioritizing a budget model of the Vision Pro after consumers bristled at the first headset's sizable asking price.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Kawailani Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin and Ethereum Joint ETF Could Come to US via Hashdex]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235987</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235987/bitcoin-ethereum-joint-etf-us-hashdex"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T20:32:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hashdex has filed for a combined spot Bitcoin and Ethereum ETF in the United States, building on recent SEC crypto fund approvals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia Flips Microsoft to Become World's Most Valuable Company, Thanks to AI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235988</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235988/nvidia-flips-microsoft-top-tech-company"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T20:04:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia's market cap hits $3.34 trillion, fueled by its intense focus on artificial intelligence and expanded robotics research.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Hamster Kombat' and Beyond: You Can Earn Crypto by Playing These Telegram Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235797</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235797/hottest-telegram-games-earn-crypto"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T19:28:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hamster Kombat is leading the next wave of buzzy Telegram games that let you earn tokens in upcoming airdrops. Here’s what else to play.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bull Market Is Losing Its Momentum, Analysts Warn]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235984</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235984/bitcoin-bull-market-losing-momentum-warn-analysts"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T19:12:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Demand from new investors for BTC is subsiding, which could push short-term investors to start panic selling en masse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethena Tokenomics Change Sparks Community Outrage]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235981</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235981/ethena-ena-tokenomics-change-sparks-uproar"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T18:50:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A hefty 50% lock-up requirement has prompted a drop in the price of the ENA token.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarang Khaitan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 140 - MARKETS DOWN BAD]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/7BwSoeRf/fomo-hour-140-markets-down-bad</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/7BwSoeRf/fomo-hour-140-markets-down-bad"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T17:35:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC touches 1-month lows, dominance hits 56%. $500m of liquidations in fall, $146m ETF outflows. VanEck to launch first ETF in Australia. Coinbase to launch pre-market trading. 56% of Fortune 500 building in web3. Uphold to delist USDT in EU due to MiCA. TON flips DOGE in sell-off. Base DEX users now 2nd place after SOL. Ethena launches staking & restaking with Symbiotic. Lens aiming to raise $50m at $500m valuation. Two ‘crazy’ MATIC announcements coming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Holy Tokens? The Vatican Library Is Giving Donors Soulbound NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235956</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235956/holy-tokens-vatican-library-giving-donors-nfts"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T17:03:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Vatican Library unveiled a new initiative to preserve its manuscript collection, rewarding social media users and donors with NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Gaming Network Ronin to Launch Layer-2 Chains—Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235967</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235967/ethereum-gaming-network-ronin-layer-2-chains"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T16:47:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ethereum network behind Pixels and Axie Infinity will let game developers deploy their own dedicated chains built on Polygon tech.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop Flat as Meme Stock Craze Powers Down]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235964</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235964/gamestop-flat-meme-stock-craze-powers-down"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T16:34:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is the Roaring Kitty buzz all gone? GameStop is barely budging Tuesday after an underwhelming shareholders meeting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Vanta DAO’s Path to Decentralization]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233755</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233755/inside-vanta-daos-path-to-decentralization"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T14:01:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Investment DAO Vanta is handing over ownership of the syndicate to its community of NFT holders. Here’s how it works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Bridge Router Protocol to Wants to Build Its Own L1 With Strategic Funding]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235925</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235925/ethereum-bridge-router-protocol-strategic-funding"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T13:01:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Router Protocol, a bridge that connects Ethereum and BNB Chain, says it'll use new funding to build its own L1.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wonder Godzo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Futures Funding Rates Show Traders Are Still Bullish Despite Rout]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235917</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235917/bitcoin-traders-still-bullish-futures-contract-funding-rates"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T12:08:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's an indicator there are more traders opening long than short positions—and they think their gains will eventually outweigh the cost.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Major UK Political Parties Have ‘Missed Opportunity’ on Crypto, Experts Say]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235914</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235914/major-uk-political-parties-have-missed-opportunity-on-crypto-experts-say"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T11:29:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the UK general election nears, major parties have released their manifestos. But, not a single one has mentioned cryptocurrencies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Still in the Red as Fed Pessimism Sets In and BTC Miner Selling Continues]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235896</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235896/bitcoin-fed-pessimism-btc-miner-selling"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T10:35:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[But the sluggishness may be short-lived, said Wintermute: "Bank of Canada and the European Central Bank have already initiated rate cuts."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarang Khaitan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Drake Just Lost $500,000 in Bitcoin Betting on the NBA Finals]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235888</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235888/drake-lost-500000-bitcoin-betting-nba-finals"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T03:15:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Famed rapper Drake blew a heap of Bitcoin on the Mavericks—and he could lose the same amount in the NHL’s Stanley Cup Finals, too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Prices Dive as Crypto Liquidations Near $500 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235880</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235880/bitcoin-ethereum-prices-down-500-million-liquidations"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T03:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Long positions on Ethereum, Bitcoin, Dogecoin and other coins got rekt in a big way late Monday, continuing the bleeding from earlier.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Kawailani Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Licensing Questions Plague Stability AI as SD3 Image Generator Gets Banned]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235866</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235866/sd3-license-stability-ai-civit-ai-ban"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T01:30:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A leading AI image generator is mired in controversy, and community hub CivitAI is shutting it out for now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Meme Coin DJT on Solana Skyrockets Amid Rumors It's Official Token]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235871</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235871/djt-solana-meme-coin-skyrockets"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T01:11:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With zero evidence of a Trump link, one Solana meme coin has more than doubled in price and seen $129 million in trades based on a rumor.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Kawailani Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Runway's New Gen-3 AI Video Generator Draws High Praise]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235842</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235842/runway-gen-3-ai-video-better-than-sora"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T23:45:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A preview of Runway's next-generation tool is described as smooth, realistic, and “better than Sora.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fake Medical Implant Lands Florida CEO Six Years in Prison]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235828</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235828/fake-stimwave-pain-implant-prison-sentence"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T23:12:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Laura Perryman was found guilty of selling a dummy device that claimed to relieve chronic pain but was actually “inert.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creators of Fortnite-Like Ethereum Game 'OpenSeason' Reveal Token Airdrop]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235813</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235813/fortnite-like-ethereum-game-openseason-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T22:24:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fractional Uprising NFT holders will not only receive the airdrop, but also have a say in funding future games from the OpenSeason maker.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Dogecoin, and Ethereum Volatility Drive $290 Million in Liquidations]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235816</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235816/bitcoin-dogecoin-ethereum-volatility-290-million-liquidations"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T21:26:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Swings in the price of Bitcoin and other top coins Monday appear to have triggered a wave of liquidations, mostly on long positions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not Lovin' It? McDonald's Bails on AI Drive-Thru Trial]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235788</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235788/not-lovin-it-mcdonalds-bails-on-ai-drive-thru-trial"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T20:26:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[McDonald's says AI still has potential, as Wendy's and other fast food competitors continue their AI order-taking tests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VanEck to Launch First Bitcoin ETF on Australian Securities Exchange]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235786</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235786/bitcoin-etf-australia-asx-vaneck-approval"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T19:45:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After three years of effort, the firm is bringing Bitcoin ETFs to Australia's largest trading exchange on Thursday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop Stock Plummets as Shareholder Meeting Avoids Roaring Kitty Hype]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235781</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235781/gamestop-plummets-shareholder-meeting-roaring-kitty"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T18:38:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price of GameStop fell Monday after an anticipated GME meeting came and went without mentioning the meme stock influencer Keith Gill.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Congressman Says He Bought Velodrome Token—What Is That?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235773</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235773/what-is-velodrome-finance-velo-token"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T18:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The little-known VELO token is up 15% on Monday after the project turned up in Rep. Mike Collins’ financial disclosures.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Heroes of Mavia' Will Soon Let You Earn Its Ethereum Token on iOS and Android]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235763</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235763/heroes-mavia-integrating-ethereum-token-ios-android"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T17:36:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the second phase of the game begins, Heroes of Mavia is starting to implement ways to use and earn MAVIA tokens. Here's how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 139 - WHATS THE NEXT META?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zEW6uY5Z/fomo-hour-139-whats-the-next-meta</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zEW6uY5Z/fomo-hour-139-whats-the-next-meta"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T17:32:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC again breaks $66k, dominance rises. Fear & Greed index hits 3 month low. Whales continue to be in accumulation mode. Miners 33 days into capitulation, average 41 days. Financial advisors not buying BTC yet: BlackRock. Crypto funds saw $600m outflows last week. ZKsync airdrop live, prices at $5bn FDV. ZKsync defend sybil measures. Low float, high FDV coins get hammered again. Tether launches product backed by Gold. Korean exchanges reviewing 600 coins for delisting. ETH ETF ‘sell the rumour, buy the news event’. BTC ETF basis buyers roughly 15% of demand. CVX bounces 100% after loan liquidation. TON sees fastest user growth in crypto history. APT may flip SOL in 1-3 years: Hayes. Crypto lifetime funding eclipses $100bn. SEC claims $876m Ripple fine still fair. Gensler could cost Biden election: Cuban.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Telecom Giant Coolpad to Drop $13.5M on Bitcoin Mining Rigs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235715</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235715/chinese-telecom-giant-coolpad-to-drop-13-5m-on-bitcoin-mining-rigs"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T17:19:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The move into Bitcoin mining marks a significant shift for Coolpad, which has traditionally focused on the smartphone market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Minsberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether Drops Another Dollar-Pegged Stablecoin—But It's Backed By Gold]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235764</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235764/tether-dollar-pegged-stablecoin-backed-gold"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T17:17:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tether aUSDT uses overcollateralized gold reserves to maintain its peg, rather than the usual model of using government debt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 138 - MORE CELEB COINS!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/KzCZzgqx/fomo-hour-138-more-celeb-coins</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/KzCZzgqx/fomo-hour-138-more-celeb-coins"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T18:05:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Altcoins bleed out heavy, BTC dominance rises towards 60%. Miners continue to be large BTC sellers, whales accumulate. ETF inflows slow, hedge fund allocations point to basis trades. ETH ETFs approvals see little movement, coming 'in the summer’. Stocks continue to hit ATHs as CPI & PPI both come in soft. TON performs best in L1s, active wallets eclipse ETH. Andrew Tate joins celebrity memecoin meta, DADDY hits $350m. SOL DEX volumes eclipse ETH in memecoin frenzy. Curve founder defaults on CRV debt as DeFi coins tumble. Terraform Labs & Do Kwon to pay $4.5bn fine to SEC. BAMK hits $350m in Runes as it issues BTC stablecoin. Gaming tokens face huge sell-off, PRIME changes tokenomics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 137 - CRYPTO DIPS FURTHER]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mJ28rAx5/fomo-hour-137-crypto-dips-further</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mJ28rAx5/fomo-hour-137-crypto-dips-further"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T15:46:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto falls after slightly hawkish Fed speech. BTC whales buy $1.4bn in 24hrs. Miners continue to be large sellers of BTC. BTC ETFs see $100m inflows. MicroStrategy to raise $500m to buy BTC. Egorov CRV debt positions begin to liquidate  . Circle to support SOL for wallets. 4% of Turkey GDP used to buy stablecoins. QuantMatter say $11m stolen from OKX account. Biden to use Coinbase for crypto donations. Terraform Labs & Do Kwon set to pay $4.5bn fine. Franklin Templeton write report on SOL DePin. TON flips ETH for active addresses. Moonpay & Paypal integration goes live in EU & UK.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 136 - FIRST MOTHER, NOW DADDY?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LEzSMpGz/fomo-hour-136-first-mother-now-daddy</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LEzSMpGz/fomo-hour-136-first-mother-now-daddy"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T18:01:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETFs see another $200m outflows. Another $190m of liquidations in volatility. $1.2bn BTC leaves exchanges in a day. ETF flows largely driven by basis trades: Pal. ‘Perfect setup’ for longs into macro news today. ETH ETF approvals ‘expected this month’. Crypto in best place it has ever been: Circle CEO. China’s ICBC calls ETH ‘digital oil’. Trump wants ‘made in the USA’ BTC. Crypto hacks $19bn since 2011. Symbiotic restaking protocol sees $150m inflows. Polygon launches $720m grants program. ZKsync accused of insider allocations. CRV drop leaves $90m loans at risk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Has AI Already Changed Gaming Forever?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mZlR3He5/has-ai-already-changed-gaming-forever</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mZlR3He5/has-ai-already-changed-gaming-forever"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T19:51:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt’s Sander Lutz and Rug Radio creator Puke sat down with Simon Davis of Mighty Bear Games and VC Kyle Klemmer to discuss how AI has already remade the gaming industry—for better and for worse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 135 - BTC FALLS ON OUTFLOWS]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/bA3jJ5aA/fomo-hour-135-btc-falls-on-outflows</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/bA3jJ5aA/fomo-hour-135-btc-falls-on-outflows"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T19:03:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto falls as ETFs see first outflow in 19 days. Short positions grow on downwards move in BTC. BTC short-term realised price now at $64k. ETH ETF issuers still waiting for SEC response. UK ETNs continue to see tiny volume. SOL validators get kicked out for sandwich attacks. ZKsync airdrop happening next week. ZKsync to give 17.8% to the community. OP launches Fraud Proofs. Bitfarms plans poison pill to counter takeover bid. OKX sees outflows after security incidents. Bybit considers shutting China offices. COIN may get added to S&P500.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 134 - EU SNAP ELECTIONS LAND]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pZksMKIV/fomo-hour-134-eu-snap-elections-land</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pZksMKIV/fomo-hour-134-eu-snap-elections-land"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T15:46:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Volatility remains low, TL continues to be divisive. 2nd highest weekly close ever for BTC. Crypto funds saw $2bn inflows last week. Rumour that BlackRock will apply for SOL ETF. Base TVL hits $8bn, top of L2s for activity. zk Sync hint at TGE this week. PENDLE enters top 5 for DeFi TVL. Berachain v2 testnet goes live.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 133 - RUGGED BY HOGEN?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MSvAS9qX/fomo-hour-133-rugged-by-hogen</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MSvAS9qX/fomo-hour-133-rugged-by-hogen"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T17:26:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC still just below ATH after $218m ETF inflows. BTC OI hits record $37bn as long-short ratio rises. Amount of ETH on exchanges lowest since 2015. Franklin Templeton explores broader crypto fund. Mining stocks rise on takeover frenzy. Kraken considers $100m funding round. Binance reinstates crypto buys with Mastercard. Phantom & Jito partner for native staking.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 132 - CRYPTO STRENGTH IS GROWING]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/bQBFWC0w/fomo-hour-132-crypto-strength-is-growing</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/bQBFWC0w/fomo-hour-132-crypto-strength-is-growing"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T19:49:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto consolidates near ATH, $488m ETF inflow. BTC correlation to tech stocks highest since 2023. BTC options anticipate $74-80k move. ETH to $22k by 2030: VanEck. Robinhood to acquire Bitstamp.
Coinbase launches Smart Wallet. ByBit opens up explicitly to China users. Global liquidity breaks out to $94T. US President given new powers to block crypto. Cramer & Gensler continue to bash crypto. Gensler hints at prolonged ETH ETF process. Stand with Crypto PAC hits 1m advocates. Turkey denies plans to tax crypto. EigenLayer surpasses $20bn TVL. IONET to launch on Binance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webinar: Unleashing The Power Of Permissionless Markets With Vega Protocol]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OvA845JA/webinar-unleashing-the-power-of-permissionless-markets-with-vega-protocol</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OvA845JA/webinar-unleashing-the-power-of-permissionless-markets-with-vega-protocol"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T08:23:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join our expert panel for an insightful discussion on Vega Protocol's revolutionary approach to decentralized derivatives trading. Discover how Vega's permissionless markets enable anyone to create and trade futures and perpetuals on a fully decentralized network. Explore the potential of Vega's innovative features, such as the ability to add new assets, transfer network assets, and adjust network parameters—as well as the protocol's active markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 131 - BIG BITCOIN INFLOWS!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/a37DNT7n/fomo-hour-131-big-bitcoin-inflows</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/a37DNT7n/fomo-hour-131-big-bitcoin-inflows"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T17:06:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETFs see large $900M inflows, biggest in weeks. $800M of shorts would be liquidated above $72K. BTC to $100K if it breaks $73K in a week: Novogratz. BNB hits new ATH, breaks $100B market cap. FTX reaches $200M tax settlement with IRS. Most investors should hold BTC: Fidelity. Tether CEO criticises EU on stablecoin regulation. Japanese exchange raises $320M to recover funds. ETH ETFs could see $4B inflows in 5 months: K33. Paradigm propose MEV taxes. StarkWare plans ZK scaling for BTC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 130 - $DOG TARGETS 1B MC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ke2mFBwr/fomo-hour-130-dog-targets-1b-mc</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ke2mFBwr/fomo-hour-130-dog-targets-1b-mc"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T22:05:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Runes & Ordinals soar as DOG passes $900M. rekt Brands opens up its shares claim for NFT holders. BTC led NFT trading volume with $6.3M on the day. NodeMonkes +10% 0.289, Puppets +35% at 0.198. Runes up by DOG which soared 23% to $922M mc. BUS won the Blast Jackpot last night for a 3% win. Memecoin majors are mostly red this AM. Trader buys 10k SOL of GME. Base brings back Onchain Summer. Dapper settles massive lawsuit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 129 - ROARING RETURNS, AGAIN!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ABOejLBT/fomo-hour-129-roaring-returns-again</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ABOejLBT/fomo-hour-129-roaring-returns-again"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T21:42:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto bounces, BTC breaks 2-week downtrend. BTC low volatility points to trend continuation. BTC will top at $150k in September 2025: Brandt. $3bn ETH withdrawn from exchanges since ETF. ETH ETF inflows imply ‘base case’ price $5.3k. ETH ETF inflows won’t be like BTC: Fireblocks. BTC logo projected on ECB building. Ethena USDe hits $3bn market cap in 4 months. Maple launches DeFi institutional lending platform. OKX launches in the Netherlands. Matter Labs drops ZK ticker. Linea shuts down chain after hack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 128 - PUMP DOT FUN KEEPS PUMPING!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cziNL3TF/fomo-hour-128-pump-dot-fun-keeps-pumping</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cziNL3TF/fomo-hour-128-pump-dot-fun-keeps-pumping"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T21:41:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto nears break-out then falls on Trump verdict. 13 straight days of BTC ETF inflows, BTC whale accumulation ‘echoes 2020’. Crypto apps next year will onboard millions: Burniske. Elon denies talking crypto policy with Trump. RFK has bought 21 BTC during campaign. TON market cap falls after updating supply data. a16z donates $25m to crypto PAC. Vitalik sends 30ETH to Tornado devs. DBS Bank in Singapore custodies $650m ETH. Backlash grows over zkSync using ZK ticker. Implementing FIT21 a slow process: CFTC. Pierce recommends UK & US cross-border sandbox. Vitalik writes blog on block size wars. Hong Kong government expresses support for web3. Do Kwon & Terraform reach settlement with SEC. Large unlocks for a number of alts next month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 127 - CELEB COINS CRASH!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mGbE2GHV/fomo-hour-127-celeb-coins-crash</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mGbE2GHV/fomo-hour-127-celeb-coins-crash"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T20:28:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NYSE to launch BTC options. CME has ‘no plans’ to offer SOL futures. Stablecoin market cap rises to 2 year high. Inflation below 3.3% ‘means BTC ATH’. Crypto market cap heading to $200T: Yat Siu. Gemini recovers $2.2bn for Earn users. PayPal stablecoin will offer ‘confidential transfers’. Mastercard launches Crypto Credential pilot on BTC. Layer Zero launches on SOL. L2s are cultural extensions of ETH: Vitalik. FTX’s Salame says he will share story. SEI announces 27m SEI airdrop. ASI merger complete, to launch June 13th.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 126 - MEMECOIN MADNESS!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/eA3xqKLr/fomo-hour-126-memecoin-madness</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/eA3xqKLr/fomo-hour-126-memecoin-madness"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T21:30:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock ETF flips Grayscale in size. BTC ETFs see 11 straight days of inflows. ZKasino gives 72hours for ETH withdrawals. ENS to migrate to L2. ADA drops out of top 10 coins. Salame sentenced to 7.5 years in jail. Riot Platforms attempts takeover of Bitfarms. Ripple donates $25m to Fairshake PAC. Pump(.)fun launches live streaming. Iggy Azelea MOTHER coin leads celeb tokens. Beeple Everyday features many coins. Runes bounce, DOG hits $560m. PEPE active wallets double during rally. Cristiano Ronaldo launches 4th NFT. Friend Tech announces club wars.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum DN-404 Tokens Are a Sensation in Asia. Are They the West’s Next Big Trend?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/drcV3Zte/ethereum-dn-404-tokens-are-a-sensation-in-asia-are-they-the-wests-next-big-trend</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/drcV3Zte/ethereum-dn-404-tokens-are-a-sensation-in-asia-are-they-the-wests-next-big-trend"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T19:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz and Rug Radio creator Pukerainbow sat down for a conversation with some of the biggest adopters involved in Ethereum’s newest trend: dividing NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Buying Crypto Simplified with Mika]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/Z9rxTcnJ/buying-crypto-simplified-with-mika</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/Z9rxTcnJ/buying-crypto-simplified-with-mika"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T16:54:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the first part of our series turning crypto beginners into crypto pros, Rug Radio creator Mika guides you through the process of purchasing cryptocurrency using crypto exchange Kraken.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 125 - ETH NEARS 4K]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BrgFfEe8/fomo-hour-125-eth-nears-4k</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BrgFfEe8/fomo-hour-125-eth-nears-4k"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T17:40:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH leads rally on continued bullish ETF sentiment. Previous anti-crypto Trump comments highlighted. Wave of influencers and celebrities hacked, release coins. Phantom becomes no.1 finance app in the US. Argentina & El Salvador hold talks on BTC adoption. LINK to have large announcement on May 30th. PEPE, MOG, TURBO, TRUMP hit ATHs in ETH memes. MOG up 60%, mentioned in Beeple Everyday. Caitlyn Jenner hacker releases JENNER coin. Garga outlines future plans for BAYC. Friend Tech founder offers $200k to migrate off Base.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>