<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-07-27T02:26:09.656Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-07-27T02:26:09.656Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lawyer Outlines 4 Options SEC Could Proceed in Ripple Case Over XRP]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7566c04dcb</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/lawyer-outlines-4-options-sec-could-proceed-in-ripple-case-over-xrp/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T02:09:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lawyer has outlined four potential next steps that the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) could take following the ruling on the Ripple case regarding XRP. “I expect the SEC to file a request for interlocutory appeal within the next 2 weeks,” he opined, asserting that it would be in the best interests of Ripple and the XRP community for the SEC to start the appeal process now.
 
4 Options SEC Could Take Next in Ripple Case
 
Lawyer James Murphy outlined in a series of tweets on Tuesday four options the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) could take in the Ripple case following the ruling by District Judge Analisa Torres regarding XRP. The SEC has indicated that it will appeal the court decision.
 
“There’s a lot of debate about what the SEC will do next in the Ripple…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are Chainalysis’ Tools Scientifically Sound? Executive’s Statement Casts Doubt]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799163/Are-Chainalysis-Tools-Scientifically-Sound-Executives-Statement-Casts-Doubt</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799163/Are-Chainalysis-Tools-Scientifically-Sound-Executives-Statement-Casts-Doubt"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T02:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An executive for on-chain analytics firm Chainalysis was the source of controversy following a recent statement. According to a court filing, the company’s Director of Investigation Solutions for government applications, Elizabeth Bisbee, provided testimony in the case against Roman Sterlingov....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ether edge up after Fed raises interest rates as expected; Solana leads winners]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799155/Bitcoin-Ether-edge-up-after-Fed-raises-interest-rates-as-expected-Solana-leads-winners</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799155/Bitcoin-Ether-edge-up-after-Fed-raises-interest-rates-as-expected-Solana-leads-winners"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T01:58:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin gained Thursday morning in Asia, but not enough to breach US$29,500 after the Fed raised interest rates by the expected quarter point.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto payment gateway CoinsPaid suspects Lazarus Group in $37M hack]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799147/Crypto-payment-gateway-CoinsPaid-suspects-Lazarus-Group-in-37M-hack</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799147/Crypto-payment-gateway-CoinsPaid-suspects-Lazarus-Group-in-37M-hack"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T01:40:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CoinsPaid said it is now working with Estonian law enforcement and several blockchain security firms are assisting to minimize the impact of the July 22 exploit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto bills pass congressional committee in 'huge win' for US crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799127/Crypto-bills-pass-congressional-committee-in-huge-win-for-US-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799127/Crypto-bills-pass-congressional-committee-in-huge-win-for-US-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T01:26:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two crypto regulatory bills have been passed by the United States House Financial Services Committee United States in one day.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[House Financial Services Committee Votes in Favor of Crypto, Blockchain Bills]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7566c3f6fb</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/07/27/house-financial-services-committee-votes-in-favor-of-crypto-blockchain-bills/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T01:24:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The House Financial Services Committee advanced a set of crypto bills after a landmark markup on Wednesday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De, Elizabeth Napolitano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robert F. Kennedy Jr. Says He Bought 14 Bitcoin for His Kids]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799129/Robert-F-Kennedy-Jr-Says-He-Bought-14-Bitcoin-for-His-Kids</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799129/Robert-F-Kennedy-Jr-Says-He-Bought-14-Bitcoin-for-His-Kids"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T01:19:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Democratic candidate for U.S. President also blasted banks for succumbing to political pressure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Charges Quantstamp $28 million For Conducting an Unregistered Initial Coin Offering]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799123/SEC-Charges-Quantstamp-28-million-For-Conducting-an-Unregistered-Initial-Coin-Offering</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799123/SEC-Charges-Quantstamp-28-million-For-Conducting-an-Unregistered-Initial-Coin-Offering"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T01:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quantstamp, a blockchain security firm, has been ordered by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to return $28 million raised in a 2017 unregistered initial coin offering (ICO).  On July 21st, the SEC accused Quantstamp of conducting an unregistered ICO, during which they sold their...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Federal prosecutors want Sam Bankman-Fried’s bail revoked]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799118/Federal-prosecutors-want-Sam-Bankman-Frieds-bail-revoked</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799118/Federal-prosecutors-want-Sam-Bankman-Frieds-bail-revoked"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T01:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Federal prosecutors have requested that Sam Bankman-Fried’s bail be revoked as the former FTX CEO awaits trial, the Associated Press reported on July 26. Earlier, prosecutors alleged that Bankman-Fried leaked the personal writings of Caroline Ellison to the New York Times. Ellison was formerly...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russian CBDC Pilot Launch News Draws Mixed Reactions from Biz Community]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799117/Russian-CBDC-Pilot-Launch-News-Draws-Mixed-Reactions-from-Biz-Community</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799117/Russian-CBDC-Pilot-Launch-News-Draws-Mixed-Reactions-from-Biz-Community"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T01:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Russian business community and financial experts have spoken about the potential pitfalls – and possible advantages – of a digital ruble as Moscow prepares for the August launch of a CBDC pilot. Izvestia quoted Sergey Katyrin, the President of the Russian Chamber of Commerce and Industry, as...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC’s Crossroads On Ripple Case Appeal: Here’s What This Crypto Lawyer Says]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7566cfb0aa</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/secs-crossroads-on-ripple-case-appeal-crypto-lawyer/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T00:37:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto lawyer and XRP advocate John Deaton has put forward a viewpoint, underlining that either of the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission’s (SEC) probable routes of action in its case against payment company Ripple could significantly influence the future of the crypto landscape.
 
Deaton’s assertions shed light on the situation’s complexity and the potential impact of the SEC’s final decision.
 
Potential SEC Paths: Unique Case Argument Or Acceptance Of Verdict?
 
According to Deaton, the SEC might opt for one of two directions in the aftermath of the SEC vs. Ripple case. One potential route could involve arguing “facts and circumstances” to present XRP’s case as unique.
 
 
I believe this is he biggest and hottest debate at the SEC and I believe there are Senior SEC officials who ar…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[House Financial Services Committee Votes in Favor of Crypto, Blockchain Bills]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799091/House-Financial-Services-Committee-Votes-in-Favor-of-Crypto-Blockchain-Bills</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799091/House-Financial-Services-Committee-Votes-in-Favor-of-Crypto-Blockchain-Bills"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T00:35:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The House Financial Services Committee advanced a set of crypto bills after a landmark markup on Wednesday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Faces Uncertain Future as Traders Brace for Potential Downside]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799086/Bitcoin-BTC-Faces-Uncertain-Future-as-Traders-Brace-for-Potential-Downside</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799086/Bitcoin-BTC-Faces-Uncertain-Future-as-Traders-Brace-for-Potential-Downside"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T00:22:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) faced the threat of further declines over the weekend as the July 23...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Mover Asia: Bitcoin Post-Fed Rate Hike Fizzles. Will BTC's Recent Low Volatility Last Much Longer?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7566c9aab8</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/07/26/first-mover-asia-bitcoin-post-fed-rate-hike-fizzles-will-btcs-recent-low-volatility-last-much-longer/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T00:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[zkSync Era launched only in March but has more daily active addresses than Arbitrum and Optimism, the two largest scaling solutions by total value locked, underscoring the rising interest in its potential airdrop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Rubin, Sage D. Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[White House Says US Policy Allows Partners to Seek BRICS Membership]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7566ca4074</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/white-house-says-us-policy-allows-partners-to-seek-brics-membership/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T00:06:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The White House has affirmed that U.S. policy does not ask partners to choose between the U.S. and other countries, including the BRICS nations. “The U.S. does not want to limit countries’ partnership with other countries,” said Press Secretary Karine Jean-Pierre. More than 40 countries have expressed interest in joining the BRICS group, and around 70 leaders have been invited to the economic bloc’s summit in August.
 
White House on US Partners’ Interest in Joining BRICS
 
While House Press Secretary Karine Jean-Pierre was asked in a press briefing on Monday about U.S. partners seeking membership in the BRICS economic bloc. The BRICS group comprises Brazil, Russia, India, China, and South Africa.
 
“Algeria and Egypt, which are two partners of the U.S. … have applied to join BRICS … and r…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC’s Crossroads On Ripple Case Appeal: Here’s What This Crypto Lawyer Says]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799057/SECs-Crossroads-On-Ripple-Case-Appeal-Heres-What-This-Crypto-Lawyer-Says</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799057/SECs-Crossroads-On-Ripple-Case-Appeal-Heres-What-This-Crypto-Lawyer-Says"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T00:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto lawyer and XRP advocate John Deaton has put forward a viewpoint, underlining that either of the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission’s (SEC) probable routes of action in its case against payment company Ripple could significantly influence the future of the crypto landscape. Deaton’s...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Memecoin Magic Heating Up As Dogecoin, Shiba Inu and Apecoin Social Buzz Rises, Says Analytics Firm]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799051/Memecoin-Magic-Heating-Up-As-Dogecoin-Shiba-Inu-and-Apecoin-Social-Buzz-Rises-Says-Analytics-Firm</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799051/Memecoin-Magic-Heating-Up-As-Dogecoin-Shiba-Inu-and-Apecoin-Social-Buzz-Rises-Says-Analytics-Firm"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T00:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto analytics platform Santiment says that three memecoins are taking off even as Bitcoin’s (BTC) price declines. Santiment says that the market caps are increasing for memecoin projects Dogecoin (DOGE), Shiba Inu (SHIB) and ApeCoin (APE). APE is the digital asset associated with the Bored...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Mover Asia: Bitcoin Post-Fed Rate Hike Fizzles. Will BTC's Recent Low Volatility Last Much Longer?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799044/First-Mover-Asia-Bitcoin-Post-Fed-Rate-Hike-Fizzles-Will-BTCs-Recent-Low-Volatility-Last-Much-Longer</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799044/First-Mover-Asia-Bitcoin-Post-Fed-Rate-Hike-Fizzles-Will-BTCs-Recent-Low-Volatility-Last-Much-Longer"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T23:52:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[zkSync Era launched only in March but has more daily active addresses than Arbitrum and Optimism, the two largest scaling solutions by total value locked, underscoring the rising interest in its potential airdrop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EthCC Paris: Celo contributor explains move to Eth L2 and why ‘thousands’ of chains will follow suit]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799043/EthCC-Paris-Celo-contributor-explains-move-to-Eth-L2-and-why-thousands-of-chains-will-follow-suit</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799043/EthCC-Paris-Celo-contributor-explains-move-to-Eth-L2-and-why-thousands-of-chains-will-follow-suit"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T23:41:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[cLabs CTO discusses the plan to transition Celo to an Ethereum Layer 2 and why 'thousands' of chains could soon integrate with Ethereum.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bearish Signal? Litecoin’s Daily Trading Volume Plunges 28% Ahead Of Halving]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7566b4a9b2</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/litecoin-daily-trading-volume-plunges/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T23:37:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Litecoin has been one of investors’ favorites over the last couple of months due to its consistent uptrend coming out of the month of June. However, recent data suggests that the interest in the digital asset may be waning even as its halving event draws closer than ever, a development that could deeply impact the altcoin’s ability to recover.
 
Litecoin Daily Trading Volume Falls By 28%
 
Litecoin’s volume was on the rise especially with its price surging above the $100 level just a few weeks ago. But with the drawdown that the altcoin has seen during this time, its trading volume has also nosedived with significant daily declines.
 
 
In the early hours of Wednesday, data from Coinmarketcap shows that the Litecoin trading volume had fallen by 28% compared to its previous day’s volumes. L…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Best Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bearish Signal? Litecoin’s Daily Trading Volume Plunges 28% Ahead Of Halving]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799002/Bearish-Signal-Litecoins-Daily-Trading-Volume-Plunges-28-Ahead-Of-Halving</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799002/Bearish-Signal-Litecoins-Daily-Trading-Volume-Plunges-28-Ahead-Of-Halving"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T23:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Litecoin has been one of investors’ favorites over the last couple of months due to its consistent uptrend coming out of the month of June. However, recent data suggests that the interest in the digital asset may be waning even as its halving event draws closer than ever, a development that...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Pre-Halving Patterns Suggest Bull Market Is Not Starting In 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799006/Bitcoin-Pre-Halving-Patterns-Suggest-Bull-Market-Is-Not-Starting-In-2023</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799006/Bitcoin-Pre-Halving-Patterns-Suggest-Bull-Market-Is-Not-Starting-In-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T23:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bitcoin halving is arguably the most important event for the blockchain due to its function. As such, it has played a significant role in when the crypto bull market starts and how long it lasts in most cases. Although there have been slight deviations in how it triggers each bull market,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin (WLD): ALL-IN Altcoin or STAY AWAY!?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799001/Worldcoin-WLD-ALL-IN-Altcoin-or-STAY-AWAY</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799001/Worldcoin-WLD-ALL-IN-Altcoin-or-STAY-AWAY"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T23:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin is developed by open ai and Sam Altman, and consists of a privacy-preserving digital identity (World ID) and, where laws allow, a digital currency (WLD) received simply for being human.Did you know that Bybit is giving out up to $81,000 in bonuses? Just click this link to find out more...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta’s metaverse money pit sinks by $3.7B as CEO eyes Threads retention]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18798990/Metas-metaverse-money-pit-sinks-by-37B-as-CEO-eyes-Threads-retention</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18798990/Metas-metaverse-money-pit-sinks-by-37B-as-CEO-eyes-Threads-retention"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T22:51:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meanwhile, Meta's metaverse-building business has racked up around $21 billion in losses since the start of 2022.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Surpasses $29.6K After Fed's Rate Hike; CoinDesk Market Index Jumps 1.2%]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7566b126dc</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/07/26/crypto-markets-today-btc-eth-doge-ogn-comp-xlm-sol-price-analysis/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T22:46:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few more Fed rate hikes are likely, but "the hardest work is done," one expert said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Rubin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Alchemy: Battle for Ankhos' RPG Mashes Up Discord, Generative AI, and Solana NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18798986/Alchemy-Battle-for-Ankhos-RPG-Mashes-Up-Discord-Generative-AI-and-Solana-NFTs</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18798986/Alchemy-Battle-for-Ankhos-RPG-Mashes-Up-Discord-Generative-AI-and-Solana-NFTs"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T22:40:16.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin ($DOGE) Price Could Skyrocket 23,000% if It Repeats Historic Pattern, Analyst Suggests]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18798985/Dogecoin-DOGE-Price-Could-Skyrocket-23000-if-It-Repeats-Historic-Pattern-Analyst-Suggests</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18798985/Dogecoin-DOGE-Price-Could-Skyrocket-23000-if-It-Repeats-Historic-Pattern-Analyst-Suggests"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T22:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The meme-inspired cryptocurrency Dogecoin ($DOGE) has formed a chart pattern that suggests the price of the cryptocurrency may surge over 23,000%, akin to a rise it experienced last year when the same pattern was formed on its chart. The chart pattern was first spotted by popular cryptocurrency...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FDUSD: Is Binance’s Latest Addition Another Stablecoin By Tron’s Justin Sun?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7566b1e0e3</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/binance-stablecoin-fdusd-linked-tron-justin-sun/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T22:37:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance, the leading crypto exchange, has added a new stablecoin to its platform – First Digital USD (FDUSD) today. The stablecoin, issued by First Digital Trust, a Hong Kong-based digital asset custodian, has attracted attention and sparked controversy within the crypto community. With allegations linking FDUSD to Justin Sun who is also allegedly behind TrueUSD (TUSD), the launch has left traders and investors questioning its credibility.
 
On June 1, First Digital Group announced the launch of FDUSD, a stablecoin pegged to the U.S. dollar. Initially issued on the Ethereum and Binance Smart Chain (BNB) networks, the stablecoin aims to provide users with a reliable and efficient means of conducting transactions. Data shows that the current total circulation of FDUSD is only about 10.11 mil…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[For Crypto Investors Down Bad in Hector, the DAO Can’t Die Fast Enough]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7566b3aca4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/07/26/for-crypto-investors-down-bad-in-hector-the-dao-cant-die-fast-enough/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T22:18:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hector Network will take six to 12 months to hold a liquidation. Token holders want their money back sooner.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Auradine Unveils Teraflux, New Line of US-Crafted Bitcoin Mining Rigs Providing Up to 270 TH/s]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7566bcb08e</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/auradine-unveils-teraflux-new-line-of-us-crafted-bitcoin-mining-rigs-providing-up-to-270-th-s/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T22:07:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to a press release published July 25, 2023, Auradine, a new competitor in the blockchain infrastructure sector, is entering the application-specific integrated circuit (ASIC) bitcoin mining industry with a line of bitcoin mining rigs known as the Teraflux series. Auradine’s new machines boast hashrates between 185 terahash per second (TH/s) and 270 TH/s.
 
Auradine Introduces Teraflux Bitcoin Miners
 
Auradine, a firm launched in 2022, recently emerged from stealth mode, revealing it raised $81 million in a Series A funding round in mid-May 2023. Celesta Capital and Mayfield led the funding round, with other participants including Marathon Digital Holdings, Cota Capital, DCVC and Stanford University. On Tuesday, the company announced a new line of miners, the Teraflux line, which…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Discord Game with AI and Blockchain: 'Alchemy: Battle for Ankhos' Creative Lead Alex Finden]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mF18GHGo/building-a-discord-game-with-ai-and-blockchain-alchemy-battle-for-ankhos-creative-lead-alex-finden</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mF18GHGo/building-a-discord-game-with-ai-and-blockchain-alchemy-battle-for-ankhos-creative-lead-alex-finden"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T21:55:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Jason Nelson interviews Alchemy: Battle for Ankhos Creative Director Alex Finden at the Solana PlayGG event in San Diego, California.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Private Banking Firm With $14B Assets Starts First Crypto Fund of Spain]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7566b84c2e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/07/26/private-banking-firm-with-14b-assets-starts-first-crypto-fund-of-spain/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fund will be accessible to professional investors only and will be audited by PwC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrés Engler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RFK Jr. Confirms Bitcoin Purchases]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7566b84c25</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/07/26/rfk-jr-confirms-bitcoin-purchases/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. presidential candidate said her purchased two bitcoin for each of his seven children.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandy Betz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paradigm Moves $3.5M in MakerDAO's MKR Tokens Following Peer a16z's Maneuver]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7566bbd7bf</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/07/26/paradigm-moves-35m-in-makerdaos-mkr-tokens-following-peer-a16zs-maneuver/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T20:54:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paradigm Capital's transfer follows venture capital firm a16z depositing $7 million of MKR to Coinbase.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining Computing Power May Drop as Much as 30% After Halving: Experts]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7566a598f7</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/07/26/bitcoin-mining-computing-power-may-drop-as-much-as-30-after-halving-experts/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T20:37:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Machine efficiency and low cost of power are key to surviving the bitcoin halving.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliza Gkritsi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tim Draper Predicts Bitcoin Will Outpace Fiat Currencies, Asserts Its Superiority Over Traditional Banking]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7566a0e1d2</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/tim-draper-predicts-bitcoin-will-outpace-fiat-currencies-asserts-its-superiority-over-traditional-banking/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T20:05:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Renowned bitcoin investor and venture capitalist, Tim Draper, envisions a future where bitcoin emerges as a formidable competitor to the world’s fiat currencies. During a recent interview with Fox News, Draper argued that bitcoin’s inherent safety and superiority surpass those of traditional banking systems and government-controlled fiat currencies.
 
Venture Capitalist Tim Draper Says Bitcoin Is ‘Transforming the Way Currency and Commerce Is Done’
 
Tim Draper, a prominent advocate of bitcoin (BTC), has recently revised his prediction for the timeline when he anticipates BTC to reach $250,000 per unit. In an interview with Fox News published on Wednesday, Draper discussed the leading cryptocurrency asset on Fox Business’ “Claman Countdown” broadcast. Throughout the interview, Draper empha…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stellar, Ripple and Solana-Based Investment Funds See AUM Spike in July]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7566a2b911</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/07/26/stellar-ripple-and-solana-based-investment-funds-see-aum-spike-in-july/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T19:47:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The large gains began following Ripple’s partial court victory over the SEC in the middle of the month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lyllah Ledesma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Justice Department Wants to Jail Sam Bankman-Fried]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7566a2b8e7</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/07/26/us-justice-department-wants-to-jail-sam-bankman-fried/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T19:47:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A prosecutor said that "no set of release conditions can secure the safety of the community."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Liquidations Top Market As DOGE Continues Upwards Push]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7566a3b724</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-liquidations-top-doge-continues-upwards/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T19:38:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data shows that Dogecoin futures liquidations have been the highest in the sector during the past day as the coin has continued its upward push.
 
Dogecoin Liquidations Spike, Majority Are Short Contracts
 
The last few days have been great for DOGE holders as the memecoin has finally showed some promising potential toward the upside, after what had been a rather extended period of stagnation.
 
During this latest surge, some interesting positive signs have appeared for the asset, with perhaps the most significant of them being the cryptic hints related to possible Dogecoin integration on Twitter that Elon Musk has provided recently.
 

 
 
Dogecoin has been one of the best performers in the market recently, and the cryptocurrency’s momentum may not be fading just yet, as its trading volum…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hououin Kyouma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why France Is Emerging as a European Crypto Hub]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7566af018b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/07/26/why-france-is-emerging-as-a-european-crypto-hub/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T19:07:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The country is setting policies meant to attract Web3 companies, as it fosters its wider tech industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ken Timsit</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Federal Reserve Raises Federal Funds Rate by 25bps Amidst Moderate Economic Growth]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7566a887c2</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/federal-reserve-raises-federal-funds-rate-by-25bps-amidst-moderate-economic-growth/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T18:53:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the latest Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC) report, it was stated that the U.S. economy has been experiencing moderate growth and members of the committee have decided to raise the federal funds rate by 25 basis points (bps) in order to keep a handle on inflation. 
 
Fed Raises Benchmark Bank Rate by 25bps
 
The U.S. Federal Reserve once again hiked the federal funds rate by 25bps after pausing the month prior. It was widely accepted that a 25bps rise was in the cards as CME’s Fedwatch tool said the probability was 99%. In the statement on Wednesday, the FOMC said that the U.S. banking system was sound and resilient.
 
Nevertheless, it expressed concern that tighter credit conditions for households and businesses might have a negative impact on economic activity, hiring, and inflati…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Big Respect Between Ethereum and Cosmos Developer Communities': dYdX Foundation CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/XU5MbCGE/big-respect-between-ethereum-and-cosmos-developer-communities-dydx-foundation-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/XU5MbCGE/big-respect-between-ethereum-and-cosmos-developer-communities-dydx-foundation-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T13:24:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CEO of the dYdX Foundation Charles d'Haussy unpacks the decision behind moving one of the largest decentralized exchange protocol's over to its very own chain built on Cosmos. A key driver, he told Decrypt at this year's EthCC event, was that instead of launching on a rollup or another layer-1, launching a fully customized chain will allow dYdX to fine tune the network for its product's needs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Staking Solution Lido 'Had Perfect Product Market Fit' at Launch, Says DAO's Biz Dev Contributor]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/fUHhelhV/ethereum-staking-solution-lido-had-perfect-product-market-fit-at-launch-says-daos-biz-dev-contributor</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/fUHhelhV/ethereum-staking-solution-lido-had-perfect-product-market-fit-at-launch-says-daos-biz-dev-contributor"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T08:43:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marin Tvrdić, a business development contributor to the Lido DAO, sat down with Decrypt during this year's EthCC to break down how the liquid staking protocol has managed such a massive lead, how it plans to keep that lead, and the protocol's new dual-governance tokenomics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Ev.io' Game Review: Earn Solana While Blasting Enemies]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/2ZmkuhL2/evio-game-review-earn-solana-while-blasting-enemies</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/2ZmkuhL2/evio-game-review-earn-solana-while-blasting-enemies"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T22:21:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ev.io is a web-based first-person shooter that's free to play, but lets NFT holders earn in-game currency that can be redeemed for Solana (SOL). Decrypt contributor Ryan Gladwin shares his review of the fun throwback to Quake-style blasting, albeit with a modern crypto twist.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Moving Fast and Breaking Things Isn't the Web3 Ethos': MetaMask Product Lead]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/l1EbLgl3/moving-fast-and-breaking-things-isnt-the-web3-ethos-metamask-product-lead</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/l1EbLgl3/moving-fast-and-breaking-things-isnt-the-web3-ethos-metamask-product-lead"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T15:45:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Account abstraction this, smart wallets that. Discussions at EthCC Paris about improving user experience have pointed at industry leader MetaMask as an example of what not to do. But that may soon change, with a host of updates and optimizations coming to crypto's number one wallet, said its product lead Alex Jupiter. It still may take some time, though, before these changes take effect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling Smart Wallets on Starknet 'Was The Winning Combination', Says Argent Co-Founder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/gnBsxw4D/scaling-smart-wallets-on-starknet-was-the-winning-combination-says-argent-co-founder</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/gnBsxw4D/scaling-smart-wallets-on-starknet-was-the-winning-combination-says-argent-co-founder"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T07:35:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Argent co-founder Julien Niset told Decrypt at EthCC Paris that he wants to make crypto wallets disappear. Or at least how they're currently conceived. From clunky seed phrases to a stiff user experience, Argent hopes to make using crypto a little less intimidating and a whole lot more fun.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Mighty Action Heroes' Open Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/litL6kKs/inside-mighty-action-heroes-open-beta</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/litL6kKs/inside-mighty-action-heroes-open-beta"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T18:23:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mighty Action Heroes is the flagship blockchain title from Mighty Bear Games. But is the browser-based battle royale shooter worth checking out? Decrypt's Kate Irwin offers her thoughts and a first look at the upcoming game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dr. Disrespect's 'Deadrop': Early Access Gameplay From Snapshot VI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/8l21EHoa/dr-disrespects-deadrop-early-access-gameplay-from-snapshot-vi</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/8l21EHoa/dr-disrespects-deadrop-early-access-gameplay-from-snapshot-vi"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T18:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin playtests Dr. Disrespect and Midnight Society's first-person shooter Deadrop and shares the latest game updates, as well as her opinions on the game in development. Currently, Deadrop offers Polygon Founders Pass NFTs with no other crypto plans revealed just yet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['More and More' Game Publishers Will Embrace NFTs: Mythical Games CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/wBWogSkl/more-and-more-game-publishers-will-embrace-nfts-mythical-games-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/wBWogSkl/more-and-more-game-publishers-will-embrace-nfts-mythical-games-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T22:28:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the wake of EA Sports and Fortnite creator Epic Games embracing Nike's NFT platform, Mythical Games CEO John Linden tells Decrypt's Andrew Hayward how quickly he expects to see more major traditional game publishers enter the blockchain space and how quickly the industry will scale.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gran Saga Unlimited Early Access: Inside the Anime MMORPG on Aptos]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JeFWMVwo/gran-saga-unlimited-early-access-inside-the-anime-mmorpg-on-aptos</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JeFWMVwo/gran-saga-unlimited-early-access-inside-the-anime-mmorpg-on-aptos"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T21:46:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin plays Gran Saga: Unlimited's second community playtest, reports her findings, and offers her opinion and insights on the upcoming game, which will offer optional Aptos NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[100 Thieves' Moe Says Blockchain Games Will 'Eventually' Be Accepted by Livestreamers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/xHhh62ID/100-thieves-moe-says-blockchain-games-will-eventually-be-accepted-by-livestreamers</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/xHhh62ID/100-thieves-moe-says-blockchain-games-will-eventually-be-accepted-by-livestreamers"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T16:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[100 Thieves content creator and gamer Moe also goes by "Yassuo" online after his favorite League of Legends character. Decrypt's Kate Irwin asks him about 100 Thieves' future crypto plans and whether Moe thinks creators like xQc and Pokimane might ever come around to blockchain games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Games of the Future Are Going to Be Different," Says Splinterlands Cofounder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/sQv6zcil/games-of-the-future-are-going-to-be-different-says-splinterlands-cofounder</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/sQv6zcil/games-of-the-future-are-going-to-be-different-says-splinterlands-cofounder"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T20:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Splinterlands Cofounder Matt Rosen tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about how the game has evolved over its five-year history and why he doesn't listen to the FUD around crypto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Champions Ascension: Like 'For Honor' with NFTs?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/gvM9ajww/inside-champions-ascension-like-for-honor-with-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/gvM9ajww/inside-champions-ascension-like-for-honor-with-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T22:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plai Labs Marketing Director Payton Kaleiwahea tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about player response to the combat game Champions Ascension in development, which offers arena combat, raid bosses, AI landscape features, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Activision VP Michael Lee: Gaming Is Crypto's 'Killer App']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/M9ulXrb3/ex-activision-vp-michael-lee-gaming-is-cryptos-killer-app</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/M9ulXrb3/ex-activision-vp-michael-lee-gaming-is-cryptos-killer-app"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Activision Vice President Michael Lee is now the SVP of Growth at Matter Labs. At the 3XP gaming conference, Lee sat down with Decrypt's Kate Irwin to discuss crypto gaming and give his predictions for the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Behind the Scenes with AMGI Studios and My Pet Hooligan]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/eQ71oapI/behind-the-scenes-with-amgi-studios-and-my-pet-hooligan</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/eQ71oapI/behind-the-scenes-with-amgi-studios-and-my-pet-hooligan"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T21:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin goes to Burbank, California for a behind-the-scenes tour of AMGI Studios, the developers of upcoming game My Pet Hooligan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Legend of Arcadia Chose Sui Over EVM Chains]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/H6JSRJIk/why-legend-of-arcadia-chose-sui-over-evm-chains</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/H6JSRJIk/why-legend-of-arcadia-chose-sui-over-evm-chains"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T21:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Legend of Arcadia Executive Producer Andy Lee tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the game and why they switched from EVM to new protocol Sui.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rumble Racing Star Game Preview: Is This Mario Kart With NFTs?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/lXVkuaeq/rumble-racing-star-game-preview-is-this-mario-kart-with-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/lXVkuaeq/rumble-racing-star-game-preview-is-this-mario-kart-with-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T16:47:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin shares a first look at Delabs' upcoming lawn mower racing game Rumble Racing Star, which offers a large cast of quirky characters pulled from the worlds of Bored Ape Yacht Club, Pudgy Penguins, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Laguna Games Turned Down 'Game of Thrones' for Crypto Unicorns]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/IqET3GYs/why-laguna-games-turned-down-game-of-thrones-for-crypto-unicorns</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/IqET3GYs/why-laguna-games-turned-down-game-of-thrones-for-crypto-unicorns"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T21:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin chats with Laguna Games about why the team chose to move away from an offer with WB Games to develop a Game of Thrones licensed title—and made Crypto Unicorns instead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>