<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-11-30T15:14:49.945Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-11-30T15:14:49.945Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy Bought $600M of BTC in November, Increased Holdings by 10%]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7491b674cd</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/11/30/microstrategy-bought-600m-of-btc-in-november-increased-holdings-by-10/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T15:12:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy is also looking to raise up to $750 million in a sale of class A common stock.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Given Green Light to Sell $873M in Assets Managed by Grayscale, Bitwise]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7491b6fe7d</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/ftx-given-green-light-to-sell-873m-in-assets-managed-by-grayscale-bitwise/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T15:09:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recent court ruling has granted FTX permission to  
sell approximately $873 million worth of assets held in trust. Around $700  
million of these assets are from Grayscale's primary offering, the Grayscale  
Bitcoin Trust (GBTC). 
The approval, dated November 29 and issued by a  
Delaware bankruptcy court, enables the defunct crypto exchange to liquidate  
holdings in trusts managed by Grayscale Investments and Bitwise. It marks a  
significant step in repaying creditors impacted by the collapse of the  
exchange.
The authorization was prompted by a motion filed by  
FTX's debtors on November 3, requesting the sale of six cryptocurrency trusts,  
including the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC), Grayscale Ethereum Trust (ETHE),  
and Bitwise 10 Crypto Index Fund. 
FTX's Grayscale Trust Asset…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinGecko Report Declares Web3 Gaming a Dying Trend]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19075514/CoinGecko-Report-Declares-Web3-Gaming-a-Dying-Trend</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19075514/CoinGecko-Report-Declares-Web3-Gaming-a-Dying-Trend"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T15:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite commanding a significant percentage of the industry’s activity, Web3 Games are struggling to stay alive.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Sentiment On Verge Of Extreme Greed: What It Means]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7491b02f9e</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-sentiment-verge-extreme-greed-what-it-means/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T15:01:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data shows the Bitcoin market sentiment is right on the edge of venturing into extreme greed. Here’s what this means for the cryptocurrency’s price.
 
Bitcoin Fear & Greed Index Is Sitting Just Below Extreme Greed Right Now
 
The “Fear & Greed Index” is an indicator that tells us about the sentiment shared by the majority of the investors in the Bitcoin and wider cryptocurrency sector.
 
According to Alternative, its creator, the index takes into account these factors when calculating the mentality: volatility, market volume, social media sentiment, market cap dominance, and Google Trends.
 
 
The Fear & Greed Index uses a numeric scale that runs from 0-100 to denote the sentiment. Values of the metric above the 54 mark suggest greed among traders, while those below 46 imply the presence o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Sentiment On Verge Of Extreme Greed: What It Means]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19075507/Bitcoin-Sentiment-On-Verge-Of-Extreme-Greed-What-It-Means</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19075507/Bitcoin-Sentiment-On-Verge-Of-Extreme-Greed-What-It-Means"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T15:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data shows the Bitcoin market sentiment is right on the edge of venturing into extreme greed. Here’s what this means for the cryptocurrency’s price. Bitcoin Fear & Greed Index Is Sitting Just Below Extreme Greed Right Now The “Fear & Greed Index” is an indicator that tells us about the sentiment...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood (HOOD) Extends Trading Services To The UK]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19075472/Robinhood-HOOD-Extends-Trading-Services-To-The-UK</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19075472/Robinhood-HOOD-Extends-Trading-Services-To-The-UK"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T15:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood, a major player in the United States financial technology industry is set to stretch out its trading services in the United Kingdom for the purpose of growing its business globally. Robinhood To Offer US Stock Trading In the UK Co-founder and Chief Executive Officer (CEO) of Robinhood...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celsius Opens Withdrawal Options for Eligible Cryptocurrency Investors]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19075464/Celsius-Opens-Withdrawal-Options-for-Eligible-Cryptocurrency-Investors</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19075464/Celsius-Opens-Withdrawal-Options-for-Eligible-Cryptocurrency-Investors"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T15:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the dynamic world of cryptocurrency, Celsius’ journey stands out as a tale of upheaval and change. The cryptocurrency lending platform, despite facing bankruptcy, has taken a notable step forward. Recently, Celsius has initiated the process of allowing withdrawals for a select group of users....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX wins approval to sell its Grayscale and Bitwise trust assets]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19075463/FTX-wins-approval-to-sell-its-Grayscale-and-Bitwise-trust-assets</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19075463/FTX-wins-approval-to-sell-its-Grayscale-and-Bitwise-trust-assets"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T14:55:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FTX estate has received approval from a Delaware bankruptcy court to sell trust assets, including approximately $873 million worth of shares in Grayscale and Bitwise investment funds. The court document filed on Friday allows the debtors to execute sales of the trust assets at their discretion,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto market in limbo as technicals hint Bulls vs. Bears fight ahead]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19075467/Crypto-market-in-limbo-as-technicals-hint-Bulls-vs-Bears-fight-ahead</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19075467/Crypto-market-in-limbo-as-technicals-hint-Bulls-vs-Bears-fight-ahead"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T14:52:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The general cryptocurrency market has been on a bullish momentum in recent weeks, led by Bitcoin (BTC), with anticipation that … Continued]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ETF Approval Priced In? Not Until BTC Sees $90K, Says One Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19075451/ETF-Approval-Priced-In-Not-Until-BTC-Sees-90K-Says-One-Analyst</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19075451/ETF-Approval-Priced-In-Not-Until-BTC-Sees-90K-Says-One-Analyst"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T14:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[X user Plan B, known as the creator of the Bitcoin Stock to Flow model, has raised a salient question about the current state of Bitcoin’s price. The tweet, directed at Eric Balchunas, senior ETF analyst at Bloomberg, suggests a misalignment between the anticipated approval odds of a spot...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Tax Haven? Switzerland Outpaces Regulatory Competition]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7491b21a31</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/crypto-tax-haven-switzerland-outpaces-regulatory-competition/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T14:49:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The regulatory struggles of crypto are evident. Despite the growing adoption of digital assets across almost every industry, there has been a significant lack of regulatory clarity. In the US, the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has relentlessly pursued restrictive regulation on crypto for the past few years. 
Although Ripple and Grayscale secured milestone victories over the SEC in October, regulators continue to scrutinize centralized exchanges and traditional institutes that support digital asset integration, and the latest legal drama involving Binance precisely proved this tendency. 
 The UK has recently seen how the Financial Conduct Authority’s (FCA) strict rules on crypto marketing have forced many growing businesses, such as Binance, to either rethink or cease their opera…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikolay Denisenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy Buys An Additional 16,130 Bitcoin For $593 Million]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7491b24fca</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/microstrategy-buys-an-additional-16130-bitcoin-for-593-million"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T14:47:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy, a leading business intelligence and software company, has continued its steadfast commitment to Bitcoin by purchasing an additional 16,130 BTC at a total cost of $593.3 million, Founder & Chairman Michael Saylor announced today. The purchase came as Bitcoin's price has been experiencing upward momentum, reaching a recent yearly high of over $38,300.
The company initially entered the Bitcoin market in August 2020, making a significant initial investment of $250 million into BTC. Since then, they have consistently added to their Bitcoin holdings, creating a treasury reserve strategy that has garnered over 174,530 bitcoin worth more than $6.59 billion at the time of writing.
“On November 30, 2023, MicroStrategy announced that, during the period between November 1, 2023 and November 29, 2023, MicroStrategy, together with its subsidiaries, acquired approximately 16,130 bitcoins for approximately $593.3 million in cash, at an average price of approximately $36,785 per bitcoin, inclusive of fees and expenses,” MicroStrategy stated. “As of November 29, 2023, MicroStrategy, together with its subsidiaries, held an aggregate of approximately 174,530 bitcoins, which were acquired at an aggregate purchase price of approximately $5.280 billion and an average purchase price of approximately $30,252 per bitcoin, inclusive of fees and expenses.”
As the fourth Bitcoin halving quickly approaches and the first spot Bitcoin ETF approval by the SEC seems imminent, MicroStrategy continues its aggressive bitcoin investment strategy with no signs of slowing down.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nik Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaramucci: Spot ETF Will Help Wall Street's Salesforce Drive Billions Into Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7491b24fb9</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/markets/scaramucci-bitcoin-spot-etf-wall-streets-salesforce-drive-billions"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T14:47:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If there's one thing people are underestimating about a Bitcoin spot ETF approval, it's the reality of Wall Street's marketing engine.
At least that was the takeaway from capital allocator Anthony Scaramucci's most recent visit to crypto industry podcast "The Scoop." 
In the interview, Scaramucci talked at length about how a Bitcoin ETF is poised to reshape the investing landscape. In particular, the founder of SkyBridge Capital, declared that an ETF "approved by the federal government" would unleash a salesforce tsunami, channeling billions into the cryptocurrency.
Scaramucci, a Wall Street veteran, underscored the strategic shift, stating, "There's this unspoken not-so-secret reality of Wall Street: products are sold, not bought." 
In his vision, the traditional sellers of ETFs would bec…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reed Macdonald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Whale Who Bought Bitcoin for 6 Thousand Dollars and Has Been Sleeping for a Long Time Awakened! BTC Worth 136 Million Dollars Moved!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19075453/The-Whale-Who-Bought-Bitcoin-for-6-Thousand-Dollars-and-Has-Been-Sleeping-for-a-Long-Time-Awakened-BTC-Worth-136-Million-Dollars-Moved</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19075453/The-Whale-Who-Bought-Bitcoin-for-6-Thousand-Dollars-and-Has-Been-Sleeping-for-a-Long-Time-Awakened-BTC-Worth-136-Million-Dollars-Moved"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T14:47:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bitcoin whale woke up after being dormant for a long time of 4 years and moved 3,623 BTC. Continue Reading: The Whale Who Bought Bitcoin for 6 Thousand Dollars and Has Been Sleeping for a Long Time Awakened! BTC Worth 136 Million Dollars Moved!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brazil set to implement a new crypto taxation policy]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19075465/Brazil-set-to-implement-a-new-crypto-taxation-policy</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19075465/Brazil-set-to-implement-a-new-crypto-taxation-policy"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T14:44:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brazil is on the verge of implementing new income tax rules that could significantly impact cryptocurrency holders. The Federal Senate of Brazil approved legislation on Nov. 29, which has already passed in the Chamber of Deputies. This impending change is part of a broader effort to regulate and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin eyes best November since 2020 as PCE fails to move BTC price]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19075435/Bitcoin-eyes-best-November-since-2020-as-PCE-fails-to-move-BTC-price</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19075435/Bitcoin-eyes-best-November-since-2020-as-PCE-fails-to-move-BTC-price"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T14:41:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin remains on track to seal its highest monthly close since May 2022, but BTC’s price is stubbornly rangebound.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy Bought $600M of BTC in November, Increased Holdings by 10%]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19075456/MicroStrategy-Bought-600M-of-BTC-in-November-Increased-Holdings-by-10</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19075456/MicroStrategy-Bought-600M-of-BTC-in-November-Increased-Holdings-by-10"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T14:41:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy is also looking to raise up to $750 million in a sale of class A common stock.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AntPool to refund the overpaid 83 BTC fee of last week]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19075402/AntPool-to-refund-the-overpaid-83-BTC-fee-of-last-week</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19075402/AntPool-to-refund-the-overpaid-83-BTC-fee-of-last-week"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T14:40:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The largest Bitcoin (BTC) mining pool, AntPool, intends to refund the 83 BTC ($3.13 million) overpaid fee. On November 23, … Continued]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unveiling the Treasures of Skink: A Crucial Quest Location in Starfield]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19075397/Unveiling-the-Treasures-of-Skink-A-Crucial-Quest-Location-in-Starfield</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19075397/Unveiling-the-Treasures-of-Skink-A-Crucial-Quest-Location-in-Starfield"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T14:38:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the vast expanse of Starfield, where mysteries unfold and quests beckon, the planet Skink emerges as a crucial destination for intrepid spacefarers. Nestled within the Cheyenne system, positioned strategically between the Narion and Kryx systems, Skink stands out as an inhospitable yet...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance’s compliance efforts bring relief to investors-Galaxy Digital CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19075398/Binances-compliance-efforts-bring-relief-to-investors-Galaxy-Digital-CEO</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19075398/Binances-compliance-efforts-bring-relief-to-investors-Galaxy-Digital-CEO"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T14:38:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent interview with Bloomberg, Mike Novogratz, the CEO of Galaxy Digital, expressed his positive outlook on Binance’s $4.3 billion settlement with the United States Department of Justice (DOJ). He believes that this high-profile settlement will have a beneficial impact on both Binance and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Antpool Offers Refund for $3 Million BTC Transaction Fee, Sets Verification Deadline for Claimant]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7491b3a3d6</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/antpool-offers-refund-for-3-million-btc-transaction-fee-sets-verification-deadline-for-claimant/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T14:38:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following a claim from an individual asserting they had lost 139 bitcoin in a hack, where 83.65 BTC was utilized as a heightened fee to expedite its mining, Antpool has disclosed its readiness to reimburse the mistakenly paid fee. Antpool specified on November 30 that the individual has a deadline of December 10, 2023, to reclaim the fee from the mining pool. 
 
Deadline Announced by Antpool for Refunding Massive Bitcoin Transaction Fee in Suspected Hack Case
 
Recently, the cryptocurrency community observed an exceptionally large transaction fee, where 83.65 BTC, valued at over $3 million, was remitted to miners. This transaction, confirmed in block 818,087, was processed by Antpool, today’s most dominant mining pool by hashrate. Following this event, an unidentified user on the social media platform X disclosed that this fee originated from their bitcoin holdings, which were allegedly compromised by hackers.
 
The user also provided a signature, verifying their claim by signing a message with the private keys of the address. On November 30, Antpool issued a statement regarding the erroneously paid fee, declaring its readiness to refund the owner of the address. “On November 23rd, some user submitted 83 BTC as a gas fee,” Antpool disclosed. “The risk control system of Antpool temporarily froze the fee when packaging the transaction.”
 

Please contact us before 00:00 (UTC+8) on December 10, 2023 and verify personal identity in the following way. After verification, Antpool will refund the fee.
 
 
Confirming the user’s identity could be crucial for Antpool, as there’s a prevailing notion that the hacker might still possess the key, and the alleged victim might actually be the perpetrator. The user is required to sign the address and forward it to Antpool’s email for verification purposes.
 
What do you think about Antpool detailing that it would refund the massive fee it mined? Share your thoughts and opinions about this subject in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized Infrastructure Provider Grove Raises $7.9M]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7491bc34a9</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/11/30/decentralized-infrastructure-provider-grove-raises-79m/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T14:34:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized infrastructure is the use of blockchain technology and token incentives to build physical networks so other projects don't need to incur the costs of buying and running their own equipment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protocol Village: Arbitrum Lands RARI's New NFT-Focused Layer-2 Chain]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7491bc349d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/11/30/protocol-latest-tech-news-crypto-blockchain/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T14:34:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest in blockchain tech upgrades, funding announcements and deals. For the period of Nov. 30-Dec. 6, with live updates throughout.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bradley Keoun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reddit refurbishes its logo as IPO rumors mount]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19075362/Reddit-refurbishes-its-logo-as-IPO-rumors-mount</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19075362/Reddit-refurbishes-its-logo-as-IPO-rumors-mount"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T14:30:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reddit, the dynamic nexus of diverse online communities, has recently undergone a substantial rebrand, coinciding with rumors swirling about a potential initial public offering (IPO). At the forefront of this visual metamorphosis is Snoo, Reddit’s iconic red and white robot mascot. The new Snoo...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pudgy Penguins CEO says praise he gets ‘is actually pretty sad’: NFT Creator]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19075392/Pudgy-Penguins-CEO-says-praise-he-gets-is-actually-pretty-sad-NFT-Creator</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19075392/Pudgy-Penguins-CEO-says-praise-he-gets-is-actually-pretty-sad-NFT-Creator"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano founder Charles Hoskinson faces accusations from XRP community]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19075361/Cardano-founder-Charles-Hoskinson-faces-accusations-from-XRP-community</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19075361/Cardano-founder-Charles-Hoskinson-faces-accusations-from-XRP-community"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T14:29:27.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano Founder Shares Surprises About Bitcoin (BTC) and Satoshi Nakamoto]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19075370/Cardano-Founder-Shares-Surprises-About-Bitcoin-BTC-and-Satoshi-Nakamoto</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19075370/Cardano-Founder-Shares-Surprises-About-Bitcoin-BTC-and-Satoshi-Nakamoto"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T14:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[November saw $343 million lost to crypto hacks and fraud cases: Immunefi]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19075343/November-saw-343-million-lost-to-crypto-hacks-and-fraud-cases-Immunefi</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19075343/November-saw-343-million-lost-to-crypto-hacks-and-fraud-cases-Immunefi"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T14:20:05.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microstrategy's Bitcoin (BTC) bullish sentiment continues with additional purchase]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19075326/Microstrategys-Bitcoin-BTC-bullish-sentiment-continues-with-additional-purchase</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19075326/Microstrategys-Bitcoin-BTC-bullish-sentiment-continues-with-additional-purchase"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T14:16:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microstrategy buys an additional 16,130 bitcoin in purchases that took place through November 2023 The company's current BTC holdings are now worth over $6 billion in the current market price]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Extinction Looms? Over 75% Of Crypto-Based Games Are Dying, Study Shows]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7491b91f40</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/75-of-crypto-based-games-are-dying-study-shows/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T14:01:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past few months, there has been a noticeable downturn in crypto-based games in the GameFi market category, which combines game theory and blockchain technology inside the decentralized finance ecosystem.
 
A recent analysis by cryptocurrency pricing tracker Coingecko found that a sizable 75% of GameFi ventures have failed. This slump highlights the difficulties that initiatives attempting to combine these cutting-edge ideas with gaming and decentralized money encounter. It also demonstrates the difficulties that exist in this confluence.
 
 
Crypto-Based Games Survival Metrics
 
Only 690 of the 2,817 games released between 2018 and 2023, according to the analysis, still have a reasonably active user base. A Web3 game is considered “failed” by CoinGecko if its 14-day moving average…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Institutional Crypto Trader Talos Taps Into Uniswap's Liquidity]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7491b91a4f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/11/30/institutional-crypto-trader-talos-taps-into-uniswaps-liquidity/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T14:01:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's the first time Talos will be routing trades through a decentralized exchange.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ubisoft-Backed Horizon Launches Sequence Builder to Make Crypto Game Dev Easier]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208034</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208034/ubisoft-backed-horizon-launches-sequence-builder-make-crypto-game-dev-easier"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Horizon Blockchain Games' Sequence development platform has launched Builder, which is designed to make adding crypto and NFTs to games easier and faster.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miner AntPool to Refund Record-Breaking $3 Million Transaction Fee]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208103</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208103/bitcoin-miner-antpool-to-refund-record-breaking-3-million-transaction-fee"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T13:56:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bitcoin user who paid a $3 million transaction fee has been invited to verify their identity and collect a refund from AntPool.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miner AntPool to Refund Record $3M BTC Transaction Fee]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7491a580d9</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/11/30/bitcoin-miner-antpool-to-refund-record-3m-btc-transaction-fee/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T13:31:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AntPool said it would verify the identity of the sender if they sign an on-chain message via another bitcoin transaction using the same message – which will prove ownership.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Mover Americas: Demand for Bitcoin Futures ETF BITO Ramps Up]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7491a580a5</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/11/30/first-mover-americas-demand-for-bitcoin-futures-etf-bito-ramps-up/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T13:31:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest price moves in bitcoin [BTC] and crypto markets in context for Nov. 30, 2023. First Mover is CoinDesk’s daily newsletter that contextualizes the latest actions in the crypto markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lyllah Ledesma, Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Renowned Economist Drops Bombshell On The US Dollar: Can Bitcoin Provide Safe Haven?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7491a1c022</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/economist-us-dollar-bitcoin/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T13:02:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Renowned Economist Peter Schiff has warned about an imminent fall in the US Dollar and the country’s economy. If his warning is anything to go by, then a case could be made for cryptocurrencies and Bitcoin in particular. 
 
US Dollar On Verge Of Historic Crash
 
In a post shared on his X (formerly Twitter), Peter Schiff stated that the US dollar is on the verge of a historic crash. He highlighted how this could affect the country’s economy as inflation, interest rates, and unemployment would soar. The economist seems to believe that the fall in the currency will be catastrophic as he says, “It’s crash and burn.”
 
 
Schiff went on to back up his point in a subsequent post. He stated that the US economy is already in recession. He noted that although the country’s GDP grew by 5.2% in Q3, th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bright Moments in Patagonia: How an NFT Artist Lured Collectors to a Remote Boulder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207902</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207902/bright-moments-patagonia-how-nft-artist-lured-collectors-remote-boulder"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T13:01:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier this month, artist Deafbeef revealed a collection of tokenized sculptures at a remote glacial boulder on a farm in rural southern Argentina. Here's how it all came together.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Benefits of Building Apps On-Chain]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7491a278a8</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/11/30/the-benefits-of-building-apps-on-chain/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T12:58:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain networks are information networks, which can be leveraged to build new types of tools and experiences, Variant's Alana Levin writes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alana Levin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LBank’s Launchpad for ACGN Protocol Wraps Up with Over 9.5 Million USDT Invested, $AIMEME Listing Ahead on LBank]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7491a2a140</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/lbanks-launchpad-for-acgn-protocol-wraps-up-with-over-9-5-million-usdt-invested-aimeme-listing-ahead-on-lbank/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T12:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. LBank recently wrapped up its third Launchpad event, this time for the ACGN Protocol ($AIMEME), and the results were remarkable. The event attracted significant attention, following in the footsteps of the successful MetaExpand and PINS Network Launchpads. A total of 95,098,311 USDT was raised by 61,005 participants, demonstrating the growing interest in this creative sector.
 
$AIMEME, the native token of the ACGN Protocol, is scheduled to be listed on LBank and will commence trading on December 1st at 06:00（UTC）, marking a new milestone for this emerging ecosystem.
 
Background and Significance
 
LBank’s decision to host the ACGN Protocol ($AIMEME) Launchpad mirrors its previous successes, such as the $PINS Launchpad, which not only raised substantial investment but also s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Operator of South Korean Crypto Exchange Upbit Sees a Nearly 40% Drop in Operating Profit]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7491ad5a85</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/report-operator-of-south-korean-crypto-exchange-upbit-sees-a-nearly-40-drop-in-operating-profit/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T12:38:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dunamu, the operator of the South Korean crypto exchange Upbit, recently said it had realized an operating profit amounting to $79 million in the third quarter of 2023. Virtual asset valuation losses contributed to the 81.6% drop in the operator’s net profit for the period. 
 
Operating Profit Down by Nearly 40%
 
In the third quarter (Q3) of 2023, Dunamu, the operator of the South Korean crypto exchange Upbit, reportedly realized an operating profit of just over $79 million (101.8 billion won). According to a Decenter report, Dunamu’s Q3 operating profit is nearly 40% lower than the $130.9 million realized in the corresponding period in 2022.
 
Similarly, Dunamu’s Q3 revenue, which stood at approximately $150 million, is 29% lower than the $211 million realized in the same period last year. Also, the crypto exchange operator’s Q3 net profit of $22.9 million is reportedly 81.6% lower than in the same period last year.
 

 
As per the report, Dunamu’s net profit for the period is lower due to so-called virtual asset valuation losses.
 
Meanwhile, the report revealed that Dunamu is now working on finding ways to mitigate the effects of the recession in the virtual assets market. An unnamed company official suggested that Dunamu is hoping to achieve this by pursuing new business opportunities.
 
“We will strive to revitalize the blockchain ecosystem and create an advanced investment environment, and do our best to provide innovative services based on Dunamu’s unique technological capabilities,” the unnamed official said.
 
What are your thoughts on this story? Let us know what you think in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Privacy vs. Regulation: The Central Bank Digital Currency Conundrum]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7491ad6707</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/privacy-vs-regulation-the-central-bank-digital-currency-conundrum/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T12:38:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As central banks globally tread into the realm of digital currencies, the  
European Central Bank (ECB) is at the center of a heated debate over the  
potential issuance of a digital euro. The European Parliament recently  
held a hearing that left lawmakers divided on the merits and risks  
associated with such a move. Similar initiatives are underway in other  
jurisdictions, including China, the UK, and Sweden, reflecting a global shift  
toward embracing digital currencies.
The ECB's Digital Euro Dilemma
Lawmakers at the European Parliament's Economic and Monetary Affairs  
Committee expressed skepticism about the necessity and implications of a  
digital euro.
The debate primarily revolves around the potential erosion of privacy and  
the perceived intrusion of the state into the mark…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Ferreira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Central Banks Aren't Sufficiently Ready for CBDC Risks: BIS Report]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7491adc03e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/11/30/central-banks-arent-sufficiently-ready-for-cbdc-risks-bis-report/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T12:35:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The introduction of central bank digital currencies could have major implications on the stability, the report said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camomile Shumba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Miami Crew Leader Sentenced to 63 Months in Prison for Crypto Fraud]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7491a8b71d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/11/30/miami-crew-leader-sentenced-to-63-months-in-prison-for-crypto-fraud/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T12:14:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In April, Esteban Cabrera Da Corte pleaded guilty to participating in a crypto scheme that defrauded U.S. banks of $4 million.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandali Handagama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Earn Bitcoin by Playing PC Shooter ‘Splitgate’—Here's How]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208050</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208050/you-can-earn-bitcoin-playing-pc-shooter-splitgate-heres-how"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T09:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Free-to-play shooter Splitgate is like Halo meets Portal, and soon you’ll be able to win Bitcoin by playing on PC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Altman Retakes Helm at OpenAI with Microsoft on the Board]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208048</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208048/sam-altman-retakes-helm-at-openai-with-microsoft-on-the-board"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T03:28:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“One of the most important things for the team that builds AGI safely is the ability to handle stressful and uncertain situations,” Altman said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Cleared to Sell $873 Million in Grayscale Bitcoin Trust Shares and Other Holdings]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208040</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208040/ftx-cleared-sell-873-million-grayscale-bitcoin-trust-shares-other-holdings"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T01:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Collapsed crypto exchange FTX can move ahead with selling some 32 million shares across multiple digital asset trusts to recover funds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Esports Giant Team Liquid Reveals Collab With NFT Game Illuvium]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208025</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208025/esports-giant-team-liquid-reveals-collab-nft-game-illuvium"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T00:49:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Team Liquid will be releasing themed NFTs for Illuvium, advise on game development, and help create the game's esports scene.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Amps Up Its AI Arsenal With an Image Generator to Take On Adobe and Stable Diffusion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208035</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208035/amazon-amps-up-its-ai-arsenal-with-an-image-generator-to-take-on-adobe-and-stable-diffusion"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T00:49:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coming on the heels of the “Q” large language model, Amazon Titan brings multimodal AI capabilities to the AWS platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The ‘Make It More’ ChatGPT Trend—And How to Play Along at Home]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208002</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208002/make-it-more-chatgpt-trend-and-how-to-play-along-at-home"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T22:23:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pushing AI image generation to the limit. Then pushing some more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stability AI in Turmoil, CEO Under Pressure as Possible Sale Looms]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207997</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207997/stability-ai-emad-mostaque-controversy-sale-acquisition"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T21:51:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stability AI, known for Stable Diffusion, is exploring a sale as controversy swirls around Emad Mostaque.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bored People on the Internet Are Using AI to Animate Memes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207987</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207987/bored-people-on-the-internet-are-using-ai-to-animate-memes"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T21:23:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Generative AI is bringing old memes to life, making them as funny (and creepy) as they can be.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PlayStation Plus: Latest Free PS5 Games to Download]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207958</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207958/playstation-plus-latest-free-ps5-games-download"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T20:46:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lego 2K Drive leads the next wave of free PlayStation 5 games for Plus subscribers. Here’s when you can grab ‘em.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Sponsorships Are Back? University of Miami Strikes Deal With Helium Mobile]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207929</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207929/crypto-sponsorships-back-university-miami-strikes-deal-helium-mobile"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T20:06:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Helium Mobile—a service built on a decentralized, crypto-powered network—is the newest sponsor of Miami Hurricanes sports teams.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another Bitcoin ETF Hopeful Enters the Race]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207898</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207898/another-bitcoin-etf-hopeful-enters-race"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T20:05:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Swiss firm Pando Asset has filed an application with the SEC to offer its Spot Bitcoin Trust to U.S. investors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Soon Play Grand Theft Auto Games on Netflix—Here's How]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207889</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207889/you-can-soon-play-grand-theft-auto-games-netflix-heres-how"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T19:06:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Streaming giant Netflix previously said a Grand Theft Auto deal was just a rumor, but three mobile games will launch soon to subscribers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Charlie Munger Meme Coin Pumps 31,000% After Bitcoin Hater's Death]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207895</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207895/charlie-munger-meme-coin-pumps-31000-bitcoin-haters-death"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T18:35:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The volatile coin has made millions on the death of famed investor Charlie Munger, who skewered the crypto industry as “contrary to the interests of civilization.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase CEO: We Asked the SEC for Feedback, All We Got Was a Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207848</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207848/coinbase-ceo-asked-sec-for-feedback-got-lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T18:26:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an exclusive interview with Decrypt, Brian Armstrong criticized U.S. regulators for treating crypto as a "jump ball" in an ongoing battle over which agency should police the market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Gets Some Shine: Ethereum Rival Rallies Again]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207861</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207861/solana-gets-some-shine-ethereum-rival-rallies-again"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T16:46:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana's gains beat other major coins and tokens with a 7% price surge on Wednesday morning.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining Could 'Mitigate' Climate Change: Cornell Study]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207824</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207824/bitcoin-mining-could-mitigate-climate-change-cornell-study"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T16:16:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The study found that wind and solar farms could generate millions of dollars in the precommercial phase before they're connected to the grid.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['District 9' Director's Shooter 'Off the Grid' Launches Mobile Game Amid Avalanche Subnet Rollout]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207849</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207849/district-9-director-avalanche-shooter-off-grid-launches-mobile-game-subnet-rollout"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T16:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an exclusive interview, Gunzilla Games CEO Vlad Korolev shares the latest plans for Off the Grid and its many crypto integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Ordinals Marketplace Bioniq Launches—On Internet Computer]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207823</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207823/bitcoin-ordinals-marketplace-bioniq-launches-internet-computer"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Backed by Polychain, Bioniq uses Internet Computer like a Bitcoin layer-2, tapping into its time and cost savings via wrapped assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pika Wows in Debut as AI Video Generator Takes Aim at Tech Giants]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207799</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207799/pika-ai-video-tool-blasts-out-of-beta"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T01:06:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A $55 million raise allows the startup to compete against giants Meta, Adobe, and Stability AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Portal Airdrop Is Coming—How to Farm the Gaming Token]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207793</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207793/portal-airdrop-coming-how-farm-gaming-token"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T00:48:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Billed as a single platform to connect a wide array of blockchain games, Portal is planning an airdrop. Here’s how to earn tokens.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Is Soaring—You Can Earn More by Playing These Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207766</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207766/solana-soaring-earn-more-playing-these-games"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T23:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to stack SOL? These Solana games let you earn tokens while you play. Here are five games to get started with.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Rat Poison’: Cantankerous Bitcoin Critic Charlie Munger Dies at 99]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207783</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207783/rat-poison-cantankerous-bitcoin-critic-charlie-munger-dies-at-99"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T23:21:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["I'm not proud of my country for allowing this crypto shit," he said earlier this year. "It's worthless, it's no good."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Kawailani Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Will Hit $100K in 2024, Predicts Standard Chartered—Again]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207767</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207767/bitcoin-will-hit-100k-in-2024-predicts-standard-chartered-again"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T22:23:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The British multinational bank has returned to its bullish stance on the biggest digital coin as more signals turn green.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All Dogs Can Go to Heaven—Later: FDA Advances Longevity Drug for Big Dogs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207748</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207748/big-dog-lifespan-canine-longevity-drug-loyal-fda"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T22:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Extending canine lifespans was just the beginning, Loyal founder Celine Halioua says.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shrapnel Game Studio Founders Say Majority Shareholder Is Staging a Coup]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207755</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207755/shrapnel-game-studio-founders-say-majority-shareholder-staging-coup"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T21:45:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Six founders at Shrapnel studio Neon Machine have filed suit against the investor alleging "severe harm," but say the game is still on track.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Launches Q: A ChatGPT AI Competitor for Businesses]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207742</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207742/amazon-q-chatbot-for-business"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T21:28:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After carving out a leadership position in cloud computing, the firm is determined to claim a significant share of the burgeoning AI market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Stock Is Soaring—What Does That Mean for Crypto?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207738</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207738/coinbase-stock-soaring-what-that-means-for-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T20:42:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase stock just hit a yearly high, outperforming Bitcoin, Ethereum, and most other related investments. Is the crypto proxy a safer bet than digital assets?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Starfield Isn't Actually Boring, Game Maker Weirdly Explains in User Review Comments]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207731</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207731/starfield-isnt-actually-boring-game-maker-weirdly-explains-user-review-comments"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T20:13:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bethesda has been responding to negative Steam reviews—mostly by telling players they should keep playing if they’re bored.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Might Be Forced to Share Your Bitcoin Trading Data With the CFTC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207736</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207736/coinbase-might-forced-share-bitcoin-trading-data-cftc"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T19:30:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company was recently served with a subpoena pertaining to crypto exchange Bybit. But Coinbase customers with no relationship to that exchange say they’re being targeted too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Turns Bullish Again Amid Dovish Fed Forecast]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207730</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207730/bitcoin-price-bullish-again-fed-dovish"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T18:59:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The biggest digital asset by market cap hit is up by more than 134% this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are NFTs Ever Coming Back?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qLmFpNKE/are-nfts-ever-coming-back</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qLmFpNKE/are-nfts-ever-coming-back"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T18:38:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this weeks episode we sit down with Cashtro from Arcade.xyz to discuss NFTs, shitcoins, what collections have held onto their floor prices, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana's Mad Lads Top Bored Apes in Daily NFT Sales as Prices Surge]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207732</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207732/solanas-mad-lads-top-bored-apes-daily-nft-sales-prices-surge"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T18:35:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lads on top: the prominent Solana NFT project leads the market in 24-hour sales volume as prices climb to yet another peak.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Token Pyth Pumps Following $77 Million Airdrop for DeFi Users]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207719</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207719/solana-token-pyth-pumps-77-million-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T17:52:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Solana-based Pyth token is up 35% over the last seven days.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum’s Vitalik Buterin: If AI Turns on Us 'Even Mars May Not Be Safe']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207692</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207692/ai-turns-mars-not-safe-ethereum-creator-vitalik-buterin"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T16:32:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI development needs to prioritize human intention for positive outcomes, not just profit maximization, says Buterin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to AI: Best AI Tools for Students]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207695</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207695/how-to-ai-best-ai-tools-for-students"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T15:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not all students are letting AI do their homework. Others are seizing upon the technology to genuinely augment their education.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano Founder Charles Hoskinson: Bitcoin Gets ‘Complete Pass’ From SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207702</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207702/cardano-founder-charles-hoskinson-bitcoin-gets-complete-pass-from-sec"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T14:51:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Cardano founder argued that Bitcoin is not decentralized, and that other cryptocurrencies are unfairly considered securities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BitMEX Founder Arthur Hayes: U.S. Treatment of CZ, Binance ‘Absurd’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207701</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207701/bitmex-founder-arthur-hayes-u-s-treatment-of-cz-binance-absurd"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T11:01:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a lengthy essay, Hayes argued that the $4.3 billion fine levied by U.S. authorities against Binance was “arbitrary.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 Things CZ Can Do in Seattle While Waiting to See If He's Going to Prison]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207657</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207657/4-things-cz-seattle-waiting-see-going-prison"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T01:58:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance founder Changpeng "CZ" Zhao got news today that he's stuck in America for the time being. So why not make the most of it?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Summit: Will Web3 Gaming Ever be Mainstream?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OvVWhGbW/web-summit-will-web3-gaming-ever-be-mainstream</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OvVWhGbW/web-summit-will-web3-gaming-ever-be-mainstream"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T19:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animoca Brands CEO Robby Yung, EndeavorXR CEO Amy Peck and Gamee co-founder CEO Bozena Rezab joined Decrypt's Stephen Graves on stage at Web Summit to talk about the future of Web3 gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Allie Eve Knox on Spankchain and the life of a Crypto Financial Dominatrix]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/16rVeg6o/allie-eve-knox-on-spankchain-and-the-life-of-a-crypto-financial-dominatrix</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/16rVeg6o/allie-eve-knox-on-spankchain-and-the-life-of-a-crypto-financial-dominatrix"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T21:20:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the first IRL episode of This Time Will Be Different!

In this week's episode, our host, Reza Jafery, is joined by Allie Eve Knox, the Spankchain Chief of Staff and FinDomme. 

They discuss
- How to sell feet pics
- If crypto is really as permissionless as it seems
- the intersections between crypto and sex work]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Questions With SCENE: Jeff Davis]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PChJu1R8/5-questions-with-scene-jeff-davis</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PChJu1R8/5-questions-with-scene-jeff-davis"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artist Jeff Davis joins 5 Questions with SCENE to answer burning questions about his artistic practice, the path that brought him to Art Blocks, and his quietly sophisticated DJ abilities.

Video shot and edited by Vincent Roazzi Jr.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Heatbit Founder Alex Busarov on the Bitcoin Miner That Heats Your Home]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DJuHqcGT/heatbit-founder-alex-busarov-on-the-bitcoin-miner-that-heats-your-home</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DJuHqcGT/heatbit-founder-alex-busarov-on-the-bitcoin-miner-that-heats-your-home"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T18:12:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt joined Heatbit founder Alex Busarov at Web Summit for a walkthrough of the firm's flagship product, a Bitcoin miner that acts as a domestic space heater—aimed at the casual user.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nym CEO Harry Halpin on Privacy, Decentralized VPNs and Tornado Cash]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/aLTtY2aq/nym-ceo-harry-halpin-on-privacy-decentralized-vpns-and-tornado-cash</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/aLTtY2aq/nym-ceo-harry-halpin-on-privacy-decentralized-vpns-and-tornado-cash"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T18:08:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The founder of privacy-preserving mixnet Nym sat down with Decrypt at Web Summit to talk about its new decentralized VPN, the Web3 privacy landscape and why "devs should be defended" in the wake of the Tornado Cash crackdown.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pat Felder - The worst is over [Macro Deep Dive Episode]]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MdcKPVo0/pat-felder-the-worst-is-over-macro-deep-dive-episode</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MdcKPVo0/pat-felder-the-worst-is-over-macro-deep-dive-episode"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T17:10:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the first Markets Edition of This Time Will Be Different! In this episode we dive into the current macroeconomic conditions around crypto and look at the data behind the price action. 


Reza sits down with Pat Felder, founder of Prismatic Capital to discuss the current macro environment, and to answer the question on everyone's mind-- is the bear market really over?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Sandbox Co-Founder Sebastien Borget: 'We're Already Integrating AI']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/HlARjhG1/the-sandbox-co-founder-sebastien-borget-were-already-integrating-ai</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/HlARjhG1/the-sandbox-co-founder-sebastien-borget-were-already-integrating-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T16:09:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt sat down with The Sandbox co-founder Sebastien Borget at Web Summit to talk about AI, the open metaverse and the creative challenges of interoperability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dacoco CEO Saro McKenna: How Alien Worlds is Creating an AI-Powered 'Lore DAO' with Kevin J Anderson]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QrQTrsjH/dacoco-ceo-saro-mckenna-how-alien-worlds-is-creating-an-ai-powered-lore-dao-with-kevin-j-anderson</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QrQTrsjH/dacoco-ceo-saro-mckenna-how-alien-worlds-is-creating-an-ai-powered-lore-dao-with-kevin-j-anderson"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T16:06:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt joined Dacoco CEO Sarojini McKenna at Web Summit 2023 to talk about Alien Worlds' new Lore DAO and its AI-powered collaboration with sci-fi author Kevin J Anderson.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avalon's Jeffrey Butler on Designing a Metaverse MMO That Lets Players Co-Create]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XDz9vsvT/avalons-jeffrey-butler-on-designing-a-metaverse-mmo-that-lets-players-co-create</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XDz9vsvT/avalons-jeffrey-butler-on-designing-a-metaverse-mmo-that-lets-players-co-create"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T00:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avalon Chief Product Officer Jeffrey Butler speaks with Decrypt reporter Jason Nelson and details his studio's new MMO game with interoperable assets—and how it will enable players to create and monetize their own content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Gen Z Is Different: OTK Chief Strategy Officer Talks Creator Economy Shift and Rise of Kick]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PieshbpH/how-gen-z-is-different-otk-chief-strategy-officer-talks-creator-economy-shift-and-rise-of-kick</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PieshbpH/how-gen-z-is-different-otk-chief-strategy-officer-talks-creator-economy-shift-and-rise-of-kick"/>
        <updated>2023-11-10T18:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One True King, an esports and gaming lifestyle brand and media company, was founded by creators like Asmongold and Mizkif. OTK's Chief Strategy Officer Zachary Diaz, who previously worked at TikTok and Twitch, shares with Decrypt's Kate Irwin about how the creator economy is changing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moisés Zamora on Videomart and Bucking the Hollywood System]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kyjQCle8/moises-zamora-on-videomart-and-bucking-the-hollywood-system</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kyjQCle8/moises-zamora-on-videomart-and-bucking-the-hollywood-system"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T17:11:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Selena: The Series" creator and co-showrunner Moisés Zamora joins Decrypt's Sander Lutz at the Film3 Summit 2023 to discuss why the Hollywood system is broken and why he founded the Videomart NFT digital film marketplace to give creators more power.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why OTK Is Making Video Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/1NCV4Fk0/why-otk-is-making-video-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/1NCV4Fk0/why-otk-is-making-video-games"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One True King (OTK) Chief Strategy Officer Zachary Diaz tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about OTK's long-term strategy and vision to become a content creator-powered media and video games company.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Questions With SCENE: LoVid]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/E8BZZBWX/5-questions-with-scene-lovid</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/E8BZZBWX/5-questions-with-scene-lovid"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T21:47:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artistic duo LoVid, aka Tali Hinkis and Kyle Lapidus, joins 5 Questions with SCENE to answer burning questions about art, lettuce, and the hellscape (in someone’s opinion) that is Miami.

Video shot and edited by Vincent Roazzi Jr.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Barney on DeFi, Privacy, and Vega]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/hgDzjboU/barney-on-defi-privacy-and-vega</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/hgDzjboU/barney-on-defi-privacy-and-vega"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T18:27:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week our host is joined by Barney the founder of Vega Protocol. 

They discuss the current state of DeFi, what's wrong with the apps being built today, whether or not privacy matters when its only applied to an L2, and most importantly-- which form of sales tax is the sexiest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Is Phantom Galaxies Releasing Two Versions of Its Game?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QtnWGSSJ/why-is-phantom-galaxies-releasing-two-versions-of-its-game</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QtnWGSSJ/why-is-phantom-galaxies-releasing-two-versions-of-its-game"/>
        <updated>2023-11-06T17:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animoca Brands-owned Blowfish Studios is building a space mech pilot game called Phantom Galaxies. Blowfish Cofounder Ben Lee tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about his plans for the game's release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sophie Maxx on NFTs, Augmented Reality, and Fashion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/VByufHjn/sophie-maxx-on-nfts-augmented-reality-and-fashion</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/VByufHjn/sophie-maxx-on-nfts-augmented-reality-and-fashion"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T23:37:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week our host is joined by Sophie Maxx (Web3Maxx) to discuss NFTs, augmented reality, the metaverse, how blockchain is sneaking into the fashion world, and more!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Questions With SCENE: Kevin Rose]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/u9LDX8Vr/5-questions-with-scene-kevin-rose</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/u9LDX8Vr/5-questions-with-scene-kevin-rose"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kevin Rose, co-founder and CEO of PROOF and co-creator of the hit Moonbirds NFT collection, joins 5 Questions with SCENE to answer some hard-hitting questions about his childhood dreams, his wife’s candy preferences, and his undying love of rap music.

Video shot and edited by Vincent Roazzi Jr.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Happened to Atari's Token? Inside Atari's Blockchain Plans]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/7OtQIdqa/what-happened-to-ataris-token-inside-ataris-blockchain-plans</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/7OtQIdqa/what-happened-to-ataris-token-inside-ataris-blockchain-plans"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T18:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin chats with Atari X director Tyler Drewitz about what happened with Atari's token plans, whether a token is coming, and what Atari games might be getting the blockchain treatment. Oh, and there's lots of Easter eggs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>