<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-10-24T19:15:54.432Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-10-24T19:15:54.432Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Game-Changer: Denmark To Introduce 1st Ever Unrealized Gains Tax]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77ba906ba6</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-game-changer-denmark-to-introduce-1st-ever-unrealized-gains-tax/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T19:14:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Benjamin Franklin, a well-known American statesman, said: “Nothing is certain in this world except death and taxes.” It’s a remark that might now hold true to crypto, as Denmark plans to impose a new taxation policy that targets the unrealized capital gains of cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin.
 
 
Denmark: Tax Reform For Crypto Assets
 
The Danish government is about to make a bold move of initiating a pioneering tax reform covering digital assets like Bitcoin.
 
It is considered as an unprecedented step as the cryptocurrency space has been subject of government regulations in many countries and the ongoing debate on implementing more government regulations and taxation on it.
 
According to the Danish government, tax authorities will start collecting a 42% tax on cryptocurrencies’ unrealized…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pennsylvania House Passes ‘Bitcoin Rights’ Bill With Bipartisan Support]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77ba906b9c</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/pennsylvania-house-passes-bitcoin-rights-bill/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T19:14:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Pennsylvania House of Representatives has made a significant move in the cryptocurrency regulation landscape in the US by passing the ‘Bitcoin Rights’ bill with “overwhelming” bipartisan support. 
 
A Landmark Move For Bitcoin Rights
 
The bill, officially known as House Bill 2481, received a decisive vote of 176 to 26, with 76 Democrats and all 100 Republicans backing the measure. 
 
The bill aims to protect the rights of individuals to self-custody their digital assets, affirm their ability to use Bitcoin for payments, and establish explicit guidelines for the taxation of Bitcoin transactions. 
 
 
After the upcoming election, the bill will advance to the Republican-led Pennsylvania Senate, and if approved, it will be sent to Governor Josh Shapiro for final approval.
 
Crafted in col…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BRICS Ends Membership For 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20087671/BRICS-Ends-Membership-For-2024</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20087671/BRICS-Ends-Membership-For-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T19:02:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The BRICS alliance has resolved to end membership for the current year, following an eventful year. However, what are the plans for Bitcoin and cryptocurrency? The BRICS alliance has agreed to terminate the block’s membership in 2024. The announcement was made during the ongoing BRICS Summit in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Base Enhances Decentralization with Upcoming Fault Proofs Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20087670/Base-Enhances-Decentralization-with-Upcoming-Fault-Proofs-Launch</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20087670/Base-Enhances-Decentralization-with-Upcoming-Fault-Proofs-Launch"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T19:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Base is set to launch permissionless fault proofs on October 30, a significant step towards decentralizing the network and reducing the control of any single entity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Goatseus Maximus (GOAT) Enters Crypto’s Top-100: Time To Buy Or Sell?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20087668/Goatseus-Maximus-GOAT-Enters-Cryptos-Top-100-Time-To-Buy-Or-Sell</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20087668/Goatseus-Maximus-GOAT-Enters-Cryptos-Top-100-Time-To-Buy-Or-Sell"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T19:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Goatseus Maximus (GOAT) has surged into the top 100 cryptocurrencies by market capitalization, currently holding the #81 position. The memecoin has experienced a remarkable 27% increase in the last 24 hours and an impressive 174% gain over the past week. With a market capitalization hovering...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polymarket's Donald Trump Whale Is French, Bets Out Of Conviction And Not To Manipulate The Market, Investigation Reveals]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20087854/Polymarkets-Donald-Trump-Whale-Is-French-Bets-Out-Of-Conviction-And-Not-To-Manipulate-The-Market-Investigation-Reveals</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20087854/Polymarkets-Donald-Trump-Whale-Is-French-Bets-Out-Of-Conviction-And-Not-To-Manipulate-The-Market-Investigation-Reveals"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T18:56:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[French trader Fredi9999 has invested heavily in Trump-related bets on Polymarket, drawing attention for his $52 million wagers and prompting additional checks by the platform. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Activist Group Says Kalshi’s Election Market Should Be Shut Due to 'Manipulative' Whales]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77ba930df9</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/10/24/activist-group-says-kalshis-election-market-should-be-shut-due-to-manipulative-whales/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T18:53:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Better Markets is using Polymarket's "French connection" as ammo against the prediction market's regulated competitor.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marc Hochstein</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Circle's Allaire: Stablecoins Could Expand by Trillions in 10 Years, Will Be Integral Part of Global Financial System]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77ba930df6</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2024/10/24/circles-allaire-stablecoins-could-expand-by-trillions-in-10-years-will-be-integral-part-of-global-financial-system/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T18:53:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While USDC has been popular in developed markets, it has seen significant growth in emerging regions among fintechs and brokers servicing businesses and households, Jeremy Allaire told CoinDesk in an interview.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Activist Group Says Kalshi’s Election Market Should Be Shut Due to 'Manipulative' Whales]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20087626/Activist-Group-Says-Kalshis-Election-Market-Should-Be-Shut-Due-to-Manipulative-Whales</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20087626/Activist-Group-Says-Kalshis-Election-Market-Should-Be-Shut-Due-to-Manipulative-Whales"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T18:51:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Better Markets is using Polymarket's "French connection" as ammo against the prediction market's regulated competitor.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Is Today’s 'Major' Telegram Game Puzzle Durov Combo]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286896</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/here-is-todays-major-telegram-puzzle-durov-combo"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T18:50:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking to complete Major’s daily Pavel Durov puzzle on Telegram? Here’s the solution updated on Wednesday, October 23.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Circle's Allaire: Stablecoins Could Expand by Trillions in 10 Years, Will Be Integral Part of Global Financial System]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20087624/Circles-Allaire-Stablecoins-Could-Expand-by-Trillions-in-10-Years-Will-Be-Integral-Part-of-Global-Financial-System</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20087624/Circles-Allaire-Stablecoins-Could-Expand-by-Trillions-in-10-Years-Will-Be-Integral-Part-of-Global-Financial-System"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T18:49:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While USDC has been popular in developed markets, it has seen significant growth in emerging regions among fintechs and brokers servicing businesses and households, Jeremy Allaire told CoinDesk in an interview.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Is Today’s 'Tomarket' Telegram Game Daily Combo]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286780</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/here-is-todays-tomarket-telegram-game-daily-combo"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T18:47:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram game Tomarket is handing out free tomatoes and bonus items ahead of the airdrop. Here’s the combo for Thursday, October 24.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Is Today’s 'Captain Tsubasa: Rivals' Telegram Game Daily Combo]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=250928</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/captain-tsubasa-rivals-telegram-game-daily-combo"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T18:45:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anime soccer game Captain Tsubasa: Rivals gives out 5 million free daily balls ahead of the TON token airdrop. Here’s the combo for Thursday, October 24.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu, Dogecoin Now Held as Long as Ether As Memecoin Holders’ Confidence Surges]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20087610/Shiba-Inu-Dogecoin-Now-Held-as-Long-as-Ether-As-Memecoin-Holders-Confidence-Surges</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20087610/Shiba-Inu-Dogecoin-Now-Held-as-Long-as-Ether-As-Memecoin-Holders-Confidence-Surges"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T18:45:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As investors grapple with the crypto market's next moves, attention is shifting away from established top-cap coins toward the burgeoning appeal of meme coins.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk’s Tesla Still Holding $772,500,000 in Bitcoin in Seven Wallets After Massive Coin Shuffle: Arkham]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20087608/Elon-Musks-Tesla-Still-Holding-772500000-in-Bitcoin-in-Seven-Wallets-After-Massive-Coin-Shuffle-Arkham</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20087608/Elon-Musks-Tesla-Still-Holding-772500000-in-Bitcoin-in-Seven-Wallets-After-Massive-Coin-Shuffle-Arkham"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T18:45:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Electric vehicle giant Tesla likely still holds $772.5 million in Bitcoin (BTC), according to the crypto deanonymizing platform Arkham. Last week, Arkham flagged a series of on-chain transactions indicating Tesla had moved its trove of 11,509 BTC for the first time in two years. However, the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Things You Need to Know Before the Banana Zone Starts w/ Kyle Reidhead]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20087667/Things-You-Need-to-Know-Before-the-Banana-Zone-Starts-w-Kyle-Reidhead</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20087667/Things-You-Need-to-Know-Before-the-Banana-Zone-Starts-w-Kyle-Reidhead"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T18:45:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This isn't your average market update – in today's episode of The Milk Road Show, Kyle Reidhead, Head Of Research for Milk Road PRO, takes us through the madness of the Banana Zone, where fortunes are made and lost in the blink of an eye. Think you're a genius investor? Everyone does in the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Named Official Partner of Canadian Football League]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77ba9cdc30</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com/cryptocurrency/coinbase-named-official-partner-of-canadian-football-league/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T18:39:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase was named official partner of the Canadian  
Football League and the 111th Grey Cup, the crypto exchange announced  
today (Thursday). As part of the deal, Coinbase will sponsor the 111th  
Grey Cup and the highly anticipated coin toss during the November event in  
Vancouver. 
Bringing Crypto Closer to CFL Fans 
According to the top crypto exchange, this partnership  
targets the growing crypto adoption in Canada, where an estimated five million  
people, about 13% of the population, are reportedly involved in the crypto  
space. The CFL's partnership deal with Coinbase reportedly  
marks the first time a major Canadian sports league has officially entered the world of cryptocurrency. 
Commenting about the partnership, Lucas Matheson, the  
CEO of Coinbase Canada, said: “The CFL is one of Canada’s most celebrated  
sports leagues, and we’re thrilled to be partnering with them. Together, we aim  
to deepen Canadians’ connection with crypto and provide them with the tools and  
opportunities to participate in the digital economy, increasing economic  
freedom across Canada in the process.”
Following the collaboration, the entities have invited  
CFL fans to take part in the crypto economy through Coinbase's promotional  
offers. Fans who make their first trade on the Coinbase app or website will reportedly  
receive $25 in Bitcoin as part of the kickoff to this partnership. 
Bitcoin Prizes
Furthermore, fans scanning QR codes will have chances  
to win Bitcoin prizes, regular season tickets, or even a grand prize of $50,000  
in Bitcoin and an all-inclusive trip to the 112th Grey Cup in 2024.
The Grey Cup will feature additional fan engagement,  
including the Twisted Tea Grey Cup Halftime Show, headlined by the Jonas  
Brothers. With over 100 years of history, the Grey Cup is one of Canada's renowned  
annual events.
 
  
 
  
This article was written by Jared Kirui at www.financemagnates.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Labs Liquidating XRP Again: How Will XRP Price React?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20087595/Ripple-Labs-Liquidating-XRP-Again-How-Will-XRP-Price-React</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20087595/Ripple-Labs-Liquidating-XRP-Again-How-Will-XRP-Price-React"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T18:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Ripple Labs-associated crypto wallet recently transferred a huge amount of XRP to an unknown wallet. This bold move has raised concerns about selling pressure in the market. Meanwhile, XRP’s price continues to drop amid a general crypto market downturn. The coin currently hovers around $0.52,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Norway Central Bank to Decide on Digital currency Recommendation]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20087586/Norway-Central-Bank-to-Decide-on-Digital-currency-Recommendation</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20087586/Norway-Central-Bank-to-Decide-on-Digital-currency-Recommendation"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T18:36:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to Deputy Central Bank Governor Pal Longva, Norway’s central bank, Norges Bank, will decide whether or not to launch a digital currency the following year. Pal Longva, the deputy central bank governor of Norway, stated in an interview with Bloomberg on October 22 that the bank is on...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ledger Crypto Hack Gets Justice After 4-Year Delay]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20087584/Ledger-Crypto-Hack-Gets-Justice-After-4-Year-Delay</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20087584/Ledger-Crypto-Hack-Gets-Justice-After-4-Year-Delay"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T18:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[French authorities finally crack down on Ledger following complaints about major crypto data hacks exposing customer details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Slow Death of Private Blockchain Tech—R3 Reportedly Explores Sale Despite Big Bank Support]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77ba9d8d0b</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/the-slow-death-of-private-blockchain-tech-r3-reportedly-explores-sale-despite-big-bank-support/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T18:33:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to a recent report, R3, the private blockchain initiative backed by several major companies—including Intel, Bank of America, and Wells Fargo—has been looking into various strategic paths, including the possibility of a sale. Sources with knowledge of the situation noted that blockchain organizations such as Ava Labs and the Solana Foundation have reportedly been […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Saylor Walks Back Bitcoin Custody Comments]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20087557/Michael-Saylor-Walks-Back-Bitcoin-Custody-Comments</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20087557/Michael-Saylor-Walks-Back-Bitcoin-Custody-Comments"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T18:31:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After facing a wave of criticism, Michael Saylor has 'clarified' his Bitcoin custody remarks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETFs Will Soon Hold 1M Tokens, Nearly as Much as Satoshi]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77ba9dd5c0</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/10/24/bitcoin-etfs-will-soon-hold-1m-tokens-nearly-as-much-as-satoshi/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T18:31:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The holdings of the U.S. spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds are about to cross over one million tokens after only ten months of trading.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain Gaming Set to Soar, Anticipated Market Cap of Over $300 Billion]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20087530/Blockchain-Gaming-Set-to-Soar-Anticipated-Market-Cap-of-Over-300-Billion</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20087530/Blockchain-Gaming-Set-to-Soar-Anticipated-Market-Cap-of-Over-300-Billion"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T18:30:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The GameFi sector is poised for significant expansion, projected to reach a market value of $301.5 billion by 2030, as reported by Nansen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pennsylvania House passes bipartisan Bitcoin bill]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20087628/Pennsylvania-House-passes-bipartisan-Bitcoin-bill</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20087628/Pennsylvania-House-passes-bipartisan-Bitcoin-bill"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T18:30:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pennsylvania House of Representatives have passed “The Bitcoin Rights Bill”, with a bipartisan majority of 176 to 26. The bill seeks regulatory clarity to the digital assets industry, including on self-custody, payments and taxation. Pennsylvania has passed “The Bitcoin Rights Bill”, a new...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Altcoin season ‘more probable’ once Bitcoin hits $80K — Hashkey Capital]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20087545/Altcoin-season-more-probable-once-Bitcoin-hits-80K-Hashkey-Capital</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20087545/Altcoin-season-more-probable-once-Bitcoin-hits-80K-Hashkey-Capital"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T18:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Analysts at Hashkey Capital say altseason could find firmer footing once Bitcoin trades above $80,000.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Listing Sends GOAT Price to New All-Time High]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20087634/Binance-Listing-Sends-GOAT-Price-to-New-All-Time-High</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20087634/Binance-Listing-Sends-GOAT-Price-to-New-All-Time-High"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T18:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Goatseus Maximus (GOAT), the AI-based meme coin trending recently, has hit a new all-time high after Binance announced that it would list the cryptocurrency. Following this development, the GOAT meme coin price climbed to $0.88. This development has sparked speculation in the market, with some...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETFs Will Soon Hold 1M Tokens, Nearly as Much as Satoshi]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20087544/Bitcoin-ETFs-Will-Soon-Hold-1M-Tokens-Nearly-as-Much-as-Satoshi</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20087544/Bitcoin-ETFs-Will-Soon-Hold-1M-Tokens-Nearly-as-Much-as-Satoshi"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T18:29:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The holdings of the U.S. spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds are about to cross over one million tokens after only ten months of trading.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy’s Michael Saylor Calls for Freedom of Choice in Bitcoin Custody Amid Backlash]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20087524/MicroStrategys-Michael-Saylor-Calls-for-Freedom-of-Choice-in-Bitcoin-Custody-Amid-Backlash</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20087524/MicroStrategys-Michael-Saylor-Calls-for-Freedom-of-Choice-in-Bitcoin-Custody-Amid-Backlash"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T18:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Saylor had previously argued that large, regulated institutions reduce the risk of Bitcoin asset seizure, unlike unregulated crypto-anarchists rejecting government oversight.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple to file Form C as SEC prepares for appeals battle over XRP sales]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20087522/Ripple-to-file-Form-C-as-SEC-prepares-for-appeals-battle-over-XRP-sales</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20087522/Ripple-to-file-Form-C-as-SEC-prepares-for-appeals-battle-over-XRP-sales"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T18:28:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple will file a Form C civil appeal to provide clarity on its arguments against the SEC's position today. The filing will detail the aspects of the court's ruling on August 7 that Ripple is challenging, particularly concerning the classification of XRP in institutional sales.Following the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Freed Binance Exec Departs Nigeria as Country Teams With US on Crypto Task Force]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=288131</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/288131/freed-binance-exec-departs-nigeria-us-task-force"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T18:26:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After eight months in Nigerian prison, Tigran Gambaryan has left the country—right as it reveals a joint crypto task force with the U.S.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy Stock Hits Highest Price Since Bitcoin Buying Spree Began]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=288096</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/288096/microstrategy-stock-highest-price-bitcoin-buying"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T18:08:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy's share price topped $230 on Thursday, marking a nearly 25-year-high and a peak since its Bitcoin strategy started in 2020.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former US Federal Agent Freed From Nigerian Prison After 8 Months]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77ba9bfa8b</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/former-us-federal-agent-freed-from-nigerian-prison-after-8-months/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T17:45:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tigran Gambaryan, a U.S. citizen and former federal agent detained in Nigeria for eight months, has been released. The charges against him, brought by the Economic and Financial Crimes Commission, were dropped. The release of the Binance executive from one of Nigeria’s notorious prisons followed intense lobbying by U.S. politicians who were urging the Biden […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Team Introduces New SHIB Burning Method Via Shibarium]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77ba841dba</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-new-shib-burn-method-shibarium/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T17:44:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The WoofSwap team, operating the decentralized exchange (DEX) on the Shibarium network, has unveiled a novel Shiba Inu token-burning mechanism through the introduction of a new token named FEED. TThe announcement was made via X, where WoofSwap detailed the intended impact of FEED.
 
The official statement read: “Feed will be a new wave of trends on Shibarium. Anyone or team can create a token based on Feed contract. Burn SHIB by minting. That’s the story.” The introduction of FEED has sparked a mix of enthusiasm and uncertainty within the SHIB community, with many users seeking clarity on its exact function and benefits.
 
New Way To Burn Shiba Inu
 
In response to the growing inquiries, Lucie, the Shiba Inu marketing lead known on X as @LucieSHIB, conducted an interview with the WoofSwap …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[As 'Sentient Memecoins' Become Latest Crypto Fad, GOAT Surges to $800M and an AI Rambles]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77ba8419d8</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/10/24/as-sentient-memecoins-become-latest-crypto-fad-goat-surges-to-800m-and-an-ai-rambles/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T17:44:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some claim a new wave of big-money tokens are backed by sentient AI bots. But that's not the reality.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[zondacrypto Adds AS Monaco to Growing Sports Portfolio]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77ba85eed1</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com/cryptocurrency/zondacrypto-adds-as-monaco-to-growing-sports-portfolio/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T17:31:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The  
cryptocurrency exchange zondacrypto revelaed today (Thursday) that AS Monaco  
has joined its roster of football team partnerships. The announcement was made  
official during the platform's event in Monte Carlo.
From Football to Crypto Traders'  
Hearts
Football  
and finance have gone hand in hand for years. First, FX/CFD brokers recognized  
this synergy, followed by cryptocurrency exchanges. zondacrypto is no  
exception. The platform has now added AS Monaco, a French Ligue 1 team  
performing well in the current Champions League season, to its growing roster  
of partner football clubs.
The announcement  
took place in the team's home city-state during an event where zondacrypto  
officially listed its previously introduced native ZND token.
The  
exchange has established strong…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Damian Chmiel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking Down Information Silos in Web3 With AI]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77ba87c892</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/opinion/2024/10/24/breaking-down-information-silos-in-web3-with-ai/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T17:19:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI-driven dashboards help aggregate data across multiple chains, giving users a more holistic view of the market, says Galxe's Charles Wayn.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Charles Wayn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SimpleFX 10th Birthday: The Decade of Online Broker]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77ba822813</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/simplefx-10th-birthday-the-decade-of-online-broker/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T17:04:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. After ten years of constant development, SimpleFX can proudly celebrate this one-of-a-kind anniversary with a unique event. This year, the platform’s users will have a chance to compete in a trading contest with a $100 000 and 5 000 SFX Coins prize pool! The plan to celebrate with the SFX platform users SimpleFX […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Retail Bitcoin Activity Hits a Low—Cryptoquant Report Explores What Is Next for Markets]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77ba83dc5f</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/retail-bitcoin-activity-hits-a-low-cryptoquant-report-explores-what-is-next-for-markets/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T16:53:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Retail bitcoin investors are slowly making a comeback, though their demand growth continues at a sluggish pace compared to historical standards. Data from Cryptoquant reveals that small-scale investors are still trailing behind their larger counterparts as 2024 unfolds. Cryptoquant Analysis: Can Retail Bitcoin Investors Keep up With the Big Players? As bitcoin (BTC) edges closer […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GOAT Meme Coin Blasts Into Top 100 Tokens Following Binance Futures Listing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=288073</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/288073/goat-blasts-top-100-binance-listing"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T16:25:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The “AI-conceived” Solana token Goatse Maximus (GOAT) is now the fastest-rising meme coin since Book of Meme (BOME).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken Set to Dive Into Blockchain Waters With Its Own Chain, ‘Ink’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77ba890022</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/kraken-set-to-dive-into-blockchain-waters-with-its-own-chain-ink/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T16:22:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken is setting its sights on launching its own blockchain next year, much like Coinbase’s Base chain, according to a report from Bloomberg’s Olga Kharif. The new network, which is focused on decentralized finance (defi), is expected to release a testnet later this year. Reportedly named “Ink,” the blockchain is slated to be ready for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Price Set To Break Out Of Long-Term Consolidation For 800% Gains, DOGE Rival Eyes 19,820% In 3 Months]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77ba8ae2a7</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-price-set-to-break-out-of-long-term-consolidation-for-800-gains-doge-rival-eyes-19820-in-3-months/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T16:11:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Dogecoin price is on the rise. The meme-inspired cryptocurrency has been a hot topic as its price has increased, and massive trading volumes have begun attracting many new crypto traders. Looking at the latest market trends, DOGE is expected to break out from its long-term period of consolidation and could quickly grow its price by 800%. 
 
Meanwhile, investors are not sleeping on WallitIQ (WLTQ) – the new DOGE rival on the market – it is also catching up to Dogecoin and is projected to grow by 19,820% in the next three months. WallitIQ (WLTQ) has launched a presale for their native token, WLTQ. Over 20,000 crypto investors had already bought the DOGE rival on the first day of the presale, with more counting. 
 
This indicates that numerous investors are more interested in this DOGE ri…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CEO Brad Garlinghouse Says Ripple Made A Mistake With The SEC, Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77ba8ae2a4</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ceo-ripple-made-a-mistake-sec/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T16:11:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent interview, Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse admitted that the payments technology company should have done better with its relations with regulators in the United States in the early days of XRP. This comment was made in relation to the legal enforcement actions Ripple has been facing in the past few years. 
 
Particularly, Garlinghouse noted that its failure to engage with regulators very early has seen Ripple and the crypto industry in general now “trying to make up for lost time to some degree.” 
 
Ripple Lawsuits Could’ve Been Avoided
 
The Ripple-SEC case, which revolves around whether XRP is considered a security, has dragged on for years and has created uncertainty not just for XRP but for the entire crypto industry. Earlier this year, the lawsuit appeared to be nearing reso…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solo Bitcoin Miner Hits the Jackpot With $222,000 Reward]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=288048</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/288048/solo-bitcoin-miner-jackpot-222k-reward"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T16:06:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's more difficult than ever to mine Bitcoin, yet individual miners occasionally persevere—and claim an enormous reward.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mech Shooter 'MetalCore' Ditches Ethereum and Immutable for Solana]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=288049</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/288049/mech-shooter-metalcore-ditches-ethereum-and-immutable-for-solana"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T16:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MetalCore originally launched on Ethereum’s Immutable zkEVM back in May, but the mech game is set to swap the chain for Solana next month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Could Trump’s 2024 Victory Send Bitcoin Soaring to $92K? This Bitwise Exec Thinks So]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77ba779558</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/could-trumps-2024-victory-send-bitcoin-soaring-to-92k-this-bitwise-exec-thinks-so/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T15:43:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitwise’s head of alpha strategies, Jeff Park, projects that a Trump win in the 2024 U.S. election could push BTC prices toward the $92,000 mark. Park isn’t alone in this prediction; a number of analysts and financial institutions are entertaining similar thoughts. Bitwise Head of Alpha Strategies Jeff Park’s Bold Bitcoin Projection If Donald Trump […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto for Advisors: Bitcoin on The Balance Sheet]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77ba7ca20d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2024/10/24/crypto-for-advisors-bitcoin-on-the-balance-sheet/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T15:14:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Historically, only crypto-native companies held bitcoin on their balance sheets. However, a significant structural shift has occurred over the past four years. Public and private companies are now embracing bitcoin, motivated by economic, geopolitical, and regulatory factors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marissa Kim, Sarah Morton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Norway Go Digital? Central Bank To Decide On CBDC Next Year]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e77ba7d3460</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/will-norway-go-digital-central-bank-to-decide-on-cbdc-next-year/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T15:10:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Next year, Norges Bank, Norway’s Central Bank, is going to make a major decision regarding the potential of establishing its own CBDC, or central bank digital currency.
 
According to Deputy Governor Pal Longva, the central bank was moving toward finalizing the recommendation, though it did not feel like the work had to be fast-tracked immediately.
 
 
Indeed, other European countries, like Switzerland, have been moving ahead on digital currency projects. Norway, on the other hand, will always take its time and move cautiously.
 
 
“We are in line with many central banks — we are studying complex issues and have much to consider before proceeding,” Longva said during an interview in Oslo. 
 
 
 

 
 
 
 
He expressed how Norway hasn’t fallen behind in the game while Switzerland, for instan…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vitalik calls out Saylor, Stocks have Worst day in Weeks, GOAT hits $870M]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/u80dcXpu/vitalik-calls-out-saylor-stocks-have-worst-day-in-weeks-goat-hits-870m</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/u80dcXpu/vitalik-calls-out-saylor-stocks-have-worst-day-in-weeks-goat-hits-870m"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T15:05:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETFs: +$192m, ETH ETFs: +$1m. SOLETH continues to hit new highs, ETH weak. Vitalik calls Saylor’s custody view ‘batshit insane’. BTC to $200k by 2025: Bernstein. BTC options point to jump to $80k post-election. Ripple misses deadline in SEC case. Denmark plans 42% tax on unrealised crypto gains. Ripple CEO debanked by Citigroup.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Exchange Kraken Launching Ethereum Layer-2 Network Ink]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=288038</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/288038/kraken-ethereum-layer-2-ink-optimism"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T14:25:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken's Ethereum layer-2 network Ink is built on Optimism's OP Stack, the same tech that powers Base, Unichain, and World Chain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Napolitano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bounces Above $67,000 as Traders Navigate a ‘Liquidity Hunt’ Post-Surge]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287980</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287980/bitcoin-bounces-back-above-67000-as-traders-navigate-liquidity-hunt-post-surge"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T02:12:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin has steadied above $67,000, with experts predicting a retest of $70,000 as the U.S. election and upcoming NFP data shape market bias.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Sinclair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tudor-Jones Bullish on BTC, Dollar keeps Rising, GOAT hits $750M]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/J2wZRRcf/tudor-jones-bullish-on-btc-dollar-keeps-rising-goat-hits-750m</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/J2wZRRcf/tudor-jones-bullish-on-btc-dollar-keeps-rising-goat-hits-750m"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T23:31:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All roads lead to inflation, own BTC: Tudor-Jones. Saylor plans to give away BTC ‘to civilisation’. India considering banning crypto for CBDC. Metaplanet raises $66m, likely to buy BTC. Peter Todd goes into hiding after Satoshi claims. SEC makes crypto examination priority in 2025. SOL again flips ETH for 24hr fees. AVAX release debit card for payments. Nigeria drops charges against Binance exec. Vitalik writes about future of The Verge for ETH. Buenos Aires builds decentralised ZK ID solution. Azura launches DeFi trading platform. Farcaster makes just $10k in October. LINK announces private transactions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple CEO Says Kamala Harris Taking 'Nuanced' Approach to Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287968</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287968/ripple-ceo-nuanced-crypto-approach-kamala-harris"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T22:30:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brad Garlinghouse painted Kamala Harris as a savvy Silicon Valley insider with a "nuanced" approach to crypto, while saying Donald Trump came out "aggressively" on the subject.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GOAT Bot's Chat With Coinbase's Brian Armstrong Triggers Price Explosion in 'Russell' Meme Coin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287950</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287950/goat-bots-chat-coinbase-ceo-triggers-price-explosion-russell-memecoin"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T21:42:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A seemingly casual exchange between Coinbase's Brian Armstrong and an online Twitter bot has sent one meme coin soaring.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP ETFs 'Inevitable' After Bitcoin and Ethereum Approvals: Ripple CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287921</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287921/xrp-etfs-inevitable-bitcoin-ethereum-ripple-ceo"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T20:54:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse believes that an XRP exchange-traded fund will get approved by the SEC following recent filings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Character AI Imposes New Safety Rules After Teen User Commits Suicide]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287925</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287925/character-ai-safety-rules-teen-user-commits-suicide"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T20:26:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A 14 year old fell in love with a Game of Thrones-themed chatbot, then shot himself, in the latest incident to plague Character AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Saalfield</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kamala Harris Whale Shakes Up Polymarket Election Odds With $2 Million Position]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287926</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287926/kamala-harris-whale-shakes-up-polymarket-election-odds-with-2-million-position"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T20:26:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A newly registered Polymarket user backed Vice President Kamala Harris with $2 million, boosting her odds in the U.S. election showdown.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Meme Coin Factory Releases Video Feature, Immediately Goes Horribly Wrong]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287919</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287919/solana-pump-fun-video-feature-goes-wrong"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T20:08:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pump.fun's new tokenized video feature was almost immediately misused to share child sexual abuse material, which has been removed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Tomarket' Reveals Airdrop Details as Telegram Game Tops 40 Million Players]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287912</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287912/tomarket-airdrop-details-telegram-game"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T18:07:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram game Tomarket has shared more airdrop criteria ahead of next week’s TOMA token launch on The Open Network (TON).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Hitting $200,000 in 2025 Is a 'Conservative' Bet: Bernstein]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287901</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287901/bitcoin-200k-next-year-conservative-bet-bernstein"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T17:13:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bullish Bernstein analysts now think Bitcoin will hit $200,000 per coin by the end of 2025—and say that's a "conservative" projection.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bringing Crypto's Global Community Together Through 'Immersive Theater']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/S3Ch0XEv/bringing-cryptos-global-community-together-through-immersive-theater</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/S3Ch0XEv/bringing-cryptos-global-community-together-through-immersive-theater"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T15:39:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HashKey Capital's Decode: Legacy experience is going on the road following its debut at Token2049. Decrypt's Liz Napolitano finds out how the immersive theater experience is helping to foster connections between crypto's diverse global community, through face-to-face interactions and problem solving.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Assassin’s Creed’ Maker Ubisoft Releases First Original NFT Game ‘Champions Tactics’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287890</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287890/ubisoft-releases-champions-tactics-nft-game"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T14:54:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ubisoft’s Champions Tactics: Grimoria Chronicles, built around NFTs on the Oasys network, is now available to play on PC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin: Michael Saylor's Bitcoin Self-Custody Comments Are 'Batshit Insane']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287881</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287881/vitalik-buterin-michael-saylors-bitcoin-self-custody-comments-are-batshit-insane"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T14:01:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum co-founder Vitalik Buterin has criticized the MicroStrategy co-founder’s recent remarks on crypto self-custody.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Stabilizes as Analysts Flag an Accumulation Period]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287869</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287869/bitcoin-price-stabilize-accumulation-period"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T13:02:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The market needs time to digest higher bond yields, "before Bitcoin can resume its upward movement," 10x Research wrote in a note.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain.com Execs Face Scrutiny for Not Filing Accounts in UK]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287861</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287861/blockchain-com-execs-face-scrutiny-for-not-filing-accounts-in-uk"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T12:35:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["We have sorted all necessary documents related to this entirely administrative matter," a Blockchain.com spokesperson said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nigeria Releases Detained Binance Exec, Drops Charges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287862</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287862/nigeria-releases-detained-binance-exec"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T11:12:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nigeria has withdrawn its charges against Tigran Gambaryan and will release him, citing his poor health.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott,Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stable Diffusion 3.5: Stability AI Redeems Itself With New Models and Expanded Features]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287807</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287807/stable-diffusion-3-5-stability-ai-redeems-itself-with-new-models-and-expanded-features"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T00:07:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After its stumble with Stable Diffusion 3 Medium, Stability AI is back on track with Stable Diffusion 3.5, offering customizable models that are uncensored, fast, and accessible for everyone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scroll Airdrop Farmers Gripe Over Ethereum Layer-2 Token Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287793</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287793/scroll-airdrop-farmers-gripe-ethereum-token-launch"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T22:29:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum layer-2 network Scroll just launched its token—but like the recent Hamster Kombat airdrop, some recipients aren't happy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk's Tesla Moved $776 Million in Bitcoin, But Is Still in Control of Wallets: Arkham]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287790</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287790/elon-musk-tesla-moved-bitcoin-still-control"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T21:52:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Electric car company Tesla moved its stash of Bitcoin last week, but data firm Arkham believes that Elon Musk's company is still holding.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic Unleashes New Claude 3.5 Sonnet: A Model Smart Enough to Take Over Your Computer]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287767</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287767/anthropic-unleashes-claude-3-5-sonnet-smart-enough-take-over-computer"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T21:20:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AI powerhouse just dropped major updates to its models, including a feature that lets its AI physically control computers, marking a shift from chat-only interactions to hands-on automation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bipartisan Hope Grows That Crypto Laws Will Pass Before Year's End]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287785</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287785/bipartisan-hope-grows-crypto-laws-pass"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T21:19:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Republicans and Democrats across the House and Senate are increasingly convinced that key pieces of crypto legislation could soon become law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop Meme Stock Craze Prompted Market 'Plumbing' Changes, Says SEC Chair Gensler]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287764</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287764/gamestop-meme-stock-market-plumbing-changes"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T20:33:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC embraced shorter settlement times after the GameStop short squeeze—but crypto already does 24/7 markets and quick trade completions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A $20 Alternative to Expensive Hearing Aids]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287714</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287714/cheap-alternative-expensive-hearing-aids"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T19:43:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quantum Senses aims to offer an affordable and durable alternative to expensive hearing aids that's made from fully recycled materials.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything You Need to Know Ahead of the 'X Empire' Telegram Game Airdrop]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287756</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287756/x-empire-telegram-game-airdrop-explainer"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T18:47:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk-themed game X Empire is launching its token on The Open Network this week. Here's what you need to know about the airdrop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SOL Outperforms, 10y Rises above 4.2%, AI Tokens Dominate flows]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zu7HXBIc/sol-outperforms-10y-rises-above-42-ai-tokens-dominate-flows</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zu7HXBIc/sol-outperforms-10y-rises-above-42-ai-tokens-dominate-flows"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T17:41:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC: 67k (-2%), ETH: 2620 (-4%), SOL: 166 (0%). Top Gainers: APT, UNI, HNT, POPCAT, RUNE, KAS. BTC drops, SOL continues to outperform. PumpFun has sold $78m of SOL fees so far. Raydium flips ETH for 24hr fees. Scroll launches at $1.2bn FDV, disappoints. Crypto only really used for drug deals: Fed’s Kashkari. VanEck adds staking to SOL ETPs in Europe. LINK announces successful results from SWIFT trial. Brevan Howard trades most crypto from UAE. Japanese parties court crypto tax cuts. XRP co-founder donates $10m to Kamala. CFTC chair says agency is ‘handcuffed’ on crypto. Transak exposes 92k customers’ data. Sky may rebrand back to MakerDAO.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SOL Breaks out, Stripe Acquires Bridge, GIGA hits $600M]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/35JgCoNO/sol-breaks-out-stripe-acquires-bridge-giga-hits-600m</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/35JgCoNO/sol-breaks-out-stripe-acquires-bridge-giga-hits-600m"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T17:30:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC briefly tops $70k as OI tops $40bn. SOL outperforms, DEX volume eclipses ETH + L2s. SOLETH has highest weekly close ever. Pension giant L&G look to test tokenisation. BTC hash rate hits ATH. Stripe acquires stablecoin company Bridge for $1.1bn. PumpFun hints at upcoming token. GOAT drops then rebounds as authenticity questioned. GIGA hits new ATH of $600m, FROG hits $250m. MEW up 15% after Upbit listing. Jaypeg called out for misleading promotions. ACK editions sell for $290k.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['All Roads Lead to Inflation' Says Billionaire Bitcoin Bull Paul Tudor Jones]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287751</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287751/billionaire-bitcoin-bull-paul-tudor-jones-inflation"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T17:29:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Billionaire investor Paul Tudor Jones is worried about U.S. federal debt—and sees inflation coming as a result. He's betting on Bitcoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Should You Play 'Dookey Dash: Unclogged'? The Bored Ape Endless Runner With Big Prizes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287740</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287740/dookey-dash-unclogged-game-review"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T16:50:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[REVIEW: Dookey Dash: Unclogged drops Bored Apes into the sewers for an endless runner with $1 million up for grabs. Here's our take.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Stubbs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stripe $1.1 Billion Bridge Deal Validates Stablecoin Growth, Says Bernstein]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287730</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287730/stripe-bridge-deal-validates-stablecoins-bernstein"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T16:32:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Stripe acquisition of Bridge for a staggering $1.1 billion has underscored the growth of stablecoins as a payment method, says Bernstein.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto CEO Loses $450K to 'Best Friend' After Connecting to His WiFi]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287425</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287425/crypto-ceo-loses-450k-wifi"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T15:37:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A ‘proximity breach’ is a rising trend, when someone exploits someone close to them to steal money—this time through a WiFi network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Huge week for BTC ETFs, Crypto now through Venmo, Memes Dominate Gainers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rLpBnnaQ/huge-week-for-btc-etfs-crypto-now-through-venmo-memes-dominate-gainers</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rLpBnnaQ/huge-week-for-btc-etfs-crypto-now-through-venmo-memes-dominate-gainers"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T19:24:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETFs see biggest inflow week since July. BlackRock ETF sees $1bn inflows in a week. Venmo can now be used to buy crypto on Moonpay. SEC’s XRP appeal doesn’t challenge security status. Worldcoin rebrands to World with new orb. EigenLayer X account compromised. FBI arrests hacker of SEC X account. SCB in Thailand adopts stablecoins for transfers. DBS in Singapore adopts ‘token services’. Trump family to get 75% of WLFL revenue. Scroll team accused of owning sybil addresses. STX Nakamoto upgrade to happen next week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Majors Fall 1 to 2%, A New Tiger takes to the Charts, Van Eck teases Big Web3 Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/a6Tm7OGW/majors-fall-1-to-2-a-new-tiger-takes-to-the-charts-van-eck-teases-big-web3-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/a6Tm7OGW/majors-fall-1-to-2-a-new-tiger-takes-to-the-charts-van-eck-teases-big-web3-gaming"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T17:42:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lucky GOAT memecoin trader turned $5,000 into $1.5M during GOAT's run to $300M. A new memecoin based on Disney Park's new baby tiger "Bakso" was a top mover on Wednesday, running to $10M (now $6M). Crypto majors fall 1-2%, memes red across board. a16z calls 2024 crypto's biggest year yet in "State of Crypto" report. Vitalik publishes part 2 of blog outlining ETH's future. Van Eck teases big bet on Parallel and web3 gaming. Huge day for digital art with 4 marquee mints seeing success.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hamster Kombat Season 2 Teaser]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/qcvjjJxN/hamster-kombat-season-2-teaser</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/qcvjjJxN/hamster-kombat-season-2-teaser"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T12:03:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here's a first look at Season 2 of Telegram tap-to-earn game Hamster Kombat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BTC hits $68K, Trump odds Continue to Rise, GOAT nears $300M]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/c88qN8eB/btc-hits-68k-trump-odds-continue-to-rise-goat-nears-300m</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/c88qN8eB/btc-hits-68k-trump-odds-continue-to-rise-goat-nears-300m"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T18:31:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC hits $68k as ETF inflows continue to soar. Open Interest at CME hits ATH, funding still low. Tesla moves $750m BTC to new wallet. Canary applies for Litcoin ETF, LTC up 8%. Grayscale asks SEC to convert altcoin fund to ETF. Kraken integrates with EigenLayer for restaking. ‘Network state’ Praxis raises $525m for new city. Trump project raises only $11m so far. a16z founders donate $2.5m to Trump PAC. TikTok accused of being crypto exchange in UK. Gotbit CEO arrested in Portugal. Perplexity AI launches finance platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ETF Inflows Soar, Kamala Courts Crypto, TURBO Nears $1BN!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zn2lboMV/etf-inflows-soar-kamala-courts-crypto-turbo-nears-1bn</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zn2lboMV/etf-inflows-soar-kamala-courts-crypto-turbo-nears-1bn"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T18:22:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETFs see $800m inflows in 2-days, huge volume. ETF inflows may be linked to Trump odds: CoinShares. Bitcoin will rival housing market as asset class: Fink. Vitalik proposes drop to 1ETH to become validator. Kamala reveals pro-crypto policies. Kamala mocked for linking crypto to race. Hyperliquid announces HYPE token coming. PUFFER airdrop claim goes live. Tether considering lending to commodities trader. Man takes $500m lost Bitcoin case to court. Google removes crypto prices from search. SUI Foundation denies $400m insider selling. UAE approves $AED stablecoin. Bitget wallet now only behind Binance for downloads.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BTC hits 2-week High, China Stocks Rally again, GOAT hits $120M]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/0V0rYhMX/btc-hits-2-week-high-china-stocks-rally-again-goat-hits-120m</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/0V0rYhMX/btc-hits-2-week-high-china-stocks-rally-again-goat-hits-120m"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T14:09:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC hits 2-week high as China stocks rise. SUI breaks into the top 15 coins. $1.3bn ETH might be sold from PlusToken scam. S. Korea may approve BTC & ETH ETFs this month. Australia launches first ETH ETF. Samara to buy BTC with $33m bond. Altcoins to see $500m unlocks this week. Vitalik writes blog on the future of ETH. Grayscale reveals 35 altcoins considered for funds. Ethena proposes SOL for USDe collateral. Only one Binance launchpad coin up this year. AVAX summit begins this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Todd ‘revealed’ as Satoshi, Google may be Broken-up, Murad’s Wallets Doxxed]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pLw8b2d2/todd-revealed-as-satoshi-google-may-be-broken-up-murads-wallets-doxxed</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pLw8b2d2/todd-revealed-as-satoshi-google-may-be-broken-up-murads-wallets-doxxed"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T07:29:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC will be range bound until election: Bernstein. TAO & memecoins dominate mindshare. Peter Todd ‘revealed’ as Satoshi by HBO. US government able to sell $4.4bn Silk Road BTC. Ireland unable to access $378m seized BTC. SOL could do 5x if Trump wins: StanChart. Coinbase integrates Taproot addresses for BTC. Canary Capital applies for XRP ETF. S. Korea to regulate stablecoin transfers. CryptoCom files countersuit against SEC. Babylon fills cap with 22k BTC. Scroll airdrop coming Oct 22nd. USDC goes live on SUI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Falls Ahead of CPI, Stripe Reinstates Crypto, Fed Charges Market-makers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/aYgFvZqj/crypto-falls-ahead-of-cpi-stripe-reinstates-crypto-fed-charges-market-makers</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/aYgFvZqj/crypto-falls-ahead-of-cpi-stripe-reinstates-crypto-fed-charges-market-makers"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T07:29:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Majors drop despite stocks hitting ATHs. Stripe reinstates crypto payments. Crypto settlements near $20bn in 2024. S. Korea to review ban on BTC ETFs. US charges market makers for market manipulation. FBI created their own coin to ensnare targets. Vitalik ‘outside pick’ for Nobel Prize. Trump family token to built on Aave stack. $16m OP tokens allocated to superchain users. Wisdomtree debuts debit card for on-chain fund. 47% of hedge funds have crypto exposure. Argentina overtakes Brazil for crypto inflows. Tucker interviews Ryan Salame over FTX.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bounces from $59K, Tesla unveils Robotaxis, Memecoins Outperform]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cyJj6tWj/bitcoin-bounces-from-59k-tesla-unveils-robotaxis-memecoins-outperform</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cyJj6tWj/bitcoin-bounces-from-59k-tesla-unveils-robotaxis-memecoins-outperform"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T07:29:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC briefly dips under $59k, $160m liquidations. Mt Gox extends repayment plan by 1 year. Uniswap plans L2 for DeFi. SEC sues crypto trading firm Cumberland. Binomial sues SEC over futures trading. SEC’s Uyeda criticises agency’s policy. Justin Sun named prime minister of Liberland. MicroStrategy wants to become BTC bank. Binance pre-market trading goes live. Nearly 50% of US investors want crypto ETFs. Whale phished for $35m crypto. Ethena invests $46m in RWA funds. Trump’s crypto project aims to raise $300m.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentraland Desktop Client Preview]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qqzvDcTC/decentraland-desktop-client-preview</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qqzvDcTC/decentraland-desktop-client-preview"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T15:53:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum metaverse game Decentraland has shared an exclusive look at the visual and performance upgrades coming via its new desktop client.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Trader Murad Mahmudov talks about the Supercycle and how he chooses Meme Coins.]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Hj3nDp7G/crypto-trader-murad-mahmudov-talks-about-the-supercycle-and-how-he-chooses-meme-coins</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Hj3nDp7G/crypto-trader-murad-mahmudov-talks-about-the-supercycle-and-how-he-chooses-meme-coins"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T21:47:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Trader Murad Mahmudov talks about the Supercycle and how he chooses Meme Coins. Crypto stable, had sold off after China stocks fall. Crypto adopted faster than other tech: BlackRock. Crypto adoption to hit 8% of world population. CryptoCom recieves Wells notice from SEC. HBO documentary on Satoshi airs tonight. FTX bankruptcy plan approved by judge. Scroll airdrop may be imminent. Jupiter goes live on mobile iOS. Phantom rolls out support for Base. AAVE launches GHO on Base. Gensler may be replaced by Robinhood CLO. 87% of new token launches on SOL. National Bank of Bahrain creates BTC fund. BedRock DeFi allows BTC staking on ARB.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Memecoins take off, funding stays low, China stocks keep on rising!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/703mAYhV/memecoins-take-off-funding-stays-low-china-stocks-keep-on-rising</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/703mAYhV/memecoins-take-off-funding-stays-low-china-stocks-keep-on-rising"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T08:27:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR EP213. Memecoins take off, funding stays low, China stocks keep on rising!
Many altcoins & memecoins soar despite stable BTC. Funding rates continue to be low or negative. Crypto funds saw $147m of outflows last week. BTC remains best performing major assets this year. SUI breaks into the top 20 coins again. TAO leads top 100 away from memes, sifu shorts. $100m bridge to SOL over the last 7 days. Metaplanet buys $6.7m more BTC. ETH proposal aims to improve throughput 50%. EIGEN, OP, APT lead token unlocks this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Walrus Protocol Unlocks New Applications for Decentralized Data Storage]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kwEYLYWj/how-walrus-protocol-unlocks-new-applications-for-decentralized-data-storage</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kwEYLYWj/how-walrus-protocol-unlocks-new-applications-for-decentralized-data-storage"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T11:19:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mysten Labs Chief Scientist George Danezis joined Decrypt to talk about its new decentralized storage protocol Walrus, which promises to unlock new applications such as AI and social media, thanks to its novel Red Stuff data encoding algorithm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Coinbase Sees Crypto as a Bipartisan, 'Purple' Political Issue]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/YR2YmmwR/why-coinbase-sees-crypto-as-a-bipartisan-purple-political-issue</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/YR2YmmwR/why-coinbase-sees-crypto-as-a-bipartisan-purple-political-issue"/>
        <updated>2024-10-05T22:18:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase VP of Corporate and Business Development, Shan Aggarwal, joined Decrypt's Sander Lutz and Liz Napolitano at Messari Mainnet 2024 to discuss the exchange's efforts to grow mainstream crypto adoption—and how the changing political conversation around digital assets is rapidly playing a major role in that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Is Playing Offense—Not Just Defense—Against Crypto Crime, Says Head of Financial Investigations]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DiJ8D2Qc/binance-is-playing-offensenot-just-defenseagainst-crypto-crime-says-head-of-financial-investigations</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DiJ8D2Qc/binance-is-playing-offensenot-just-defenseagainst-crypto-crime-says-head-of-financial-investigations"/>
        <updated>2024-10-05T01:58:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nils Anderson Röed, the exchange’s global head of financial investigations, sat down with Decrypt’s Sander Lutz at Messari Mainnet 2024 to discuss how Binance is proactively dismantling criminal networks around the world, the strategy with which the crypto exchange is approaching sensitive conflicts in the Middle East, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>