<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-05-13T05:13:17.167Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-05-13T05:13:17.167Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance to Withdraw From Canadian Market Due to Regulatory Climate]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750be9b664</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/binance-to-withdraw-from-canadian-market-due-to-regulatory-climate/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-13T04:46:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance, the world’s largest cryptocurrency exchange by trading volume, announced on Friday that it is “proactively withdrawing from the Canadian market.” The company thanked the regulators who worked with them and said that the Canadian market was “small.”
 
Binance Bows Out of Canada Due to Regulatory Guidance
 
The cryptocurrency exchange Binance has decided to withdraw from the Canadian market. The company noted that it was the home country of its founder and cited regulatory guidance as the reason for its decision. Binance claims that the new regulatory climate in Canada makes it less feasible for its digital currency business to operate in the country.
 
“Unfortunately, today we are announcing that Binance will be joining other prominent crypto businesses in proactively withdrawing f…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance announces new feature to bolster trading as BNB continues to record losses]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328804/Binance-announces-new-feature-to-bolster-trading-as-BNB-continues-to-record-losses</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328804/Binance-announces-new-feature-to-bolster-trading-as-BNB-continues-to-record-losses"/>
        <updated>2023-05-13T04:30:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance announced the launch of Trading Bots, signaling a shift away from traditional trading strategies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vietnamese Residents Accused of $1.5 Million Crypto Theft and Kidnapping to Face Justice (Report)]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328794/Vietnamese-Residents-Accused-of-15-Million-Crypto-Theft-and-Kidnapping-to-Face-Justice-Report</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328794/Vietnamese-Residents-Accused-of-15-Million-Crypto-Theft-and-Kidnapping-to-Face-Justice-Report"/>
        <updated>2023-05-13T04:15:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two former police officers and 14 other Vietnamese supposedly kidnapped an individual and stole $1.5 worth of bitcoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nifty News: Assassin’s Creed unveils ‘smart collectibles’, MechaFightClub winds down and more ….]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328773/Nifty-News-Assassins-Creed-unveils-smart-collectibles-MechaFightClub-winds-down-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328773/Nifty-News-Assassins-Creed-unveils-smart-collectibles-MechaFightClub-winds-down-and-more"/>
        <updated>2023-05-13T03:35:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NFT game MechaFightClub is shutting down due to the regulatory uncertainty in the U.S., while Yuga Lab’s new CEO has snapped up a BAYC NFT well over the floor price.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s how Dogecoin reacted to Elon Musk’s declaration to drop the Twitter mantle]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328772/Heres-how-Dogecoin-reacted-to-Elon-Musks-declaration-to-drop-the-Twitter-mantle</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328772/Heres-how-Dogecoin-reacted-to-Elon-Musks-declaration-to-drop-the-Twitter-mantle"/>
        <updated>2023-05-13T03:30:54.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Over 440,000 Ethereum Added to Liquid Staking Derivatives in Two Weeks]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750bd0eec0</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/over-440000-ethereum-added-to-liquid-staking-derivatives-in-two-weeks/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-13T03:13:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In less than two weeks, the total value locked (TVL) in liquid staking derivatives has increased by 441,110 ether, worth roughly $793 million. While Lido Finance dominates the market with 74.35% of the TVL, competing liquid staking protocols Rocket Pool and Frax Ether have recorded double-digit gains of 34% to 42% in the past 30 days.
 
Number of Ethereum Locked in Liquid Staking Derivatives Nears 9 Million
 
Liquid staking protocols continue to grow, with the top decentralized finance (defi) protocols recording an additional 441,110 ethereum (ETH). As of May 12, 2023, the total value locked (TVL) in liquid staking derivatives (LSDs) stands at 8,872,715 ether, equivalent to $16.101 billion. This marks a significant increase from the 8,431,605 ethereum locked in liquid staking protocols on …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How does Polygon [MATIC] fare amidst emerging L2 solutions? Assessing…]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328744/How-does-Polygon-MATIC-fare-amidst-emerging-L2-solutions-Assessing</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328744/How-does-Polygon-MATIC-fare-amidst-emerging-L2-solutions-Assessing"/>
        <updated>2023-05-13T02:30:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon's dominance gets threatened by other L2 protocols and their upcoming airdrops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leave My Bitcoin Miners Alone!#bitcoin #crypto #shorts]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328737/Leave-My-Bitcoin-Miners-Alonebitcoin-crypto-shorts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328737/Leave-My-Bitcoin-Miners-Alonebitcoin-crypto-shorts"/>
        <updated>2023-05-13T02:19:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[► SUBSCRIBE - https://bit.ly/3QbgqTQ► LEAVE A LIKE 👍► COMMENT 👉]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Making Waves in Dubai: Gov’t Media Office Hails It as Enterprise Blockchain Leader]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328734/Ripple-Making-Waves-in-Dubai-Govt-Media-Office-Hails-It-as-Enterprise-Blockchain-Leader</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328734/Ripple-Making-Waves-in-Dubai-Govt-Media-Office-Hails-It-as-Enterprise-Blockchain-Leader"/>
        <updated>2023-05-13T02:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk’s NFT rocket launch. What has he done to Milady?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328729/Elon-Musks-NFT-rocket-launch-What-has-he-done-to-Milady</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328729/Elon-Musks-NFT-rocket-launch-What-has-he-done-to-Milady"/>
        <updated>2023-05-13T02:09:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NFTs were ready for takeoff this week and Elon Musk's tweet blasted it off.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IMF Warns of ‘Very Serious Repercussions’ if US Defaults on Debt Obligations]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750bdfac1a</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/imf-warns-of-very-serious-repercussions-if-us-defaults-on-debt-obligations/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-13T01:40:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The International Monetary Fund (IMF) has warned of “very serious repercussions” to both the U.S. and the global economy if the U.S. defaults on its debt obligations, which could be as soon as June 1. “We are calling on all of the parties to come together, reach consensus, and resolve the matter as quickly as possible,” said the IMF’s director of communications.
 
IMF Warns About U.S. Debt Default
 
The International Monetary Fund (IMF) has warned that the U.S. defaulting on its debt obligations would have “very serious repercussions” on both the American and global economies.
 
IMF Director of Communications Julie Kozack was asked at a press briefing on Thursday about “the knock-on effects” on the global economy, particularly for emerging markets, of “the debt ceiling crisis that is happe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Last Time THIS Happened BTC Dumped 50% #shorts]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328701/Last-Time-THIS-Happened-BTC-Dumped-50-shorts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328701/Last-Time-THIS-Happened-BTC-Dumped-50-shorts"/>
        <updated>2023-05-13T01:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last Time THIS Happened BTC Dumped 50%●▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬Ongoing Offers▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬●💵ALTCOIN BUZZ + BINANCEGet Up To $600* On Sign Up + Win a Share of $1,000 Become a Top Trader and win a share of $1,000!✅5 traders with the highest trading volume will share $750✅ 5 lucky draw winners will get $50 each✅Just...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Despite Arbitrum’s subdued performance, there are takers for ARB and here’s why]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328682/Despite-Arbitrums-subdued-performance-there-are-takers-for-ARB-and-heres-why</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328682/Despite-Arbitrums-subdued-performance-there-are-takers-for-ARB-and-heres-why"/>
        <updated>2023-05-13T00:30:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Although the hype around the token has submerged, growth in holder count suggests that there was belief in long-term price action.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Governor Ron DeSantis Signs Bill Prohibiting Use of Central Bank Digital Currencies in Florida]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750bc6967d</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/governor-ron-desantis-signs-bill-prohibiting-use-of-central-bank-digital-currencies-in-florida/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-13T00:08:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Friday Florida’s governor Ron DeSantis signed legislation that bans the use of a central bank digital currency (CBDC) in the state. Following the bill SB 7054 being signed into law, Florida’s Uniform Commercial Code (UCC) now explicitly forbids the use of a federally adopted CBDC as money.
 
Florida Puts the Brakes on CBDCs
 
The Sunshine State has officially outlawed the use of a central bank digital currency (CBDC) following the approval of SB 7054 or HB 7049 by the Florida House of Representatives and Senate. Governor Ron DeSantis put pen to paper and signed the bill, cementing the ban on Friday. The signing ceremony, which took place in Fort Myers, was attended by Wilton Simpson, the state’s 13th commissioner of agriculture, and Kathleen Passidomo, president of the Southwest Florida…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More Than 700 US Banks Facing ‘Significant Safety and Soundness Risk’ Due to Massive Unrealized Losses: Federal Reserve]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328668/More-Than-700-US-Banks-Facing-Significant-Safety-and-Soundness-Risk-Due-to-Massive-Unrealized-Losses-Federal-Reserve</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328668/More-Than-700-US-Banks-Facing-Significant-Safety-and-Soundness-Risk-Due-to-Massive-Unrealized-Losses-Federal-Reserve"/>
        <updated>2023-05-13T00:04:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Newly released data from the Federal Reserve shows more than 700 American banks are facing “significant safety and soundness risk” due to massive unrealized losses on their balance sheets. According to the Fed, more than 700 banks have self-reported unrealized losses that exceed 50% of their...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tron Founder Justin Sun Announces Intention To Enter Memecoin Market As High-Profile Dogecoin Competitor Dips]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328663/Tron-Founder-Justin-Sun-Announces-Intention-To-Enter-Memecoin-Market-As-High-Profile-Dogecoin-Competitor-Dips</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328663/Tron-Founder-Justin-Sun-Announces-Intention-To-Enter-Memecoin-Market-As-High-Profile-Dogecoin-Competitor-Dips"/>
        <updated>2023-05-13T00:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quadriga CX Bankruptcy Claimants to Get 13% on the Dollar]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750bc072f5</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/05/12/quadriga-cx-bankruptcy-claimants-to-get-13-on-the-dollar/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T23:45:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The interim distribution to users will account for 87% of the funds the collapsed exchange’s Trustee is currently holding.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bakkt delists majority of tokens from recently acquired Apex Crypto platform]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328658/Bakkt-delists-majority-of-tokens-from-recently-acquired-Apex-Crypto-platform</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328658/Bakkt-delists-majority-of-tokens-from-recently-acquired-Apex-Crypto-platform"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T23:43:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The delisting included major tokens used in DeFi; the company said it was following “up-to-date regulatory guidance.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Senators Introduce Bill Requiring Reports On El Salvador’s Bitcoin Adoption]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750bc14a5b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/el-salvador-bitcoin-news/bill-requiring-reports-on-el-salvadors-bitcoin-adoption-introduced"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T23:34:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A group of United States senators have introduced a bill requiring reports on the adoption of bitcoin as legal tender in El Salvador. 
The "Accountability for Cryptocurrency in El Salvador Act," introduced by Senator James Risch, Senator Bob Menendez, and Senator Bill Cassidy, requires the Secretary of State, in coordination with other relevant Federal departments and agencies, to submit a report on the adoption of bitcoin as legal tender in El Salvador. The report must include an assessment of the regulatory framework in El Salvador and the potential impact of Bitcoin adoption on macroeconomic stability, democratic governance, and the flow of remittances from the United States to El Salvador.
The bill also calls for a plan to mitigate any potential risks to the United States financial system posed by the adoption of a cryptocurrency as legal tender in El Salvador and any other country that uses the U.S. dollar as legal tender. According to the bill, the plan should be submitted to the appropriate committees of Congress no later than 90 days after the report required by subsection (a).
The Bitcoin Law, passed by the Salvadoran government in June 2021, gives Bitcoin legal tender status in the country. The move was criticized by some experts, who argued that it could lead to instability in the country's economy. Others, however, saw the move as a potential catalyst for broader adoption of bitcoin in the region. Despite the controversy surrounding the move, El Salvador has remained committed to its Bitcoin adoption plans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BtcCasey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quadriga CX Bankruptcy Claimants to Get 13% on the Dollar]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328642/Quadriga-CX-Bankruptcy-Claimants-to-Get-13-on-the-Dollar</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328642/Quadriga-CX-Bankruptcy-Claimants-to-Get-13-on-the-Dollar"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T23:22:21.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Musician RAC's NFT Fan Pass Is 'About Belonging to Something']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139981</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139981/musician-racs-nft-fan-pass-about-belonging-something"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T22:52:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain pioneer RAC tells Decrypt about launching the CULT Pass orb, which evolves depending on the contents of your wallet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ali Shutler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Musician RAC's NFT Fan Pass Is 'About Belonging to Something']]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328621/Musician-RACs-NFT-Fan-Pass-Is-About-Belonging-to-Something</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328621/Musician-RACs-NFT-Fan-Pass-Is-About-Belonging-to-Something"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T22:52:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain pioneer RAC tells Decrypt about launching the CULT Pass orb, which evolves depending on the contents of your wallet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sleeping Bitcoin Wallet Awakens: $3.7M Worth of BTC Suddenly Moves After Close to 12 Years of Dormancy]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750bce07a5</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/sleeping-bitcoin-wallet-awakens-3-7m-worth-of-btc-suddenly-moves-after-close-to-12-years-of-dormancy/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T22:37:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On May 11, 2023, a long-inactive bitcoin wallet sprang to life and transferred a substantial 139.7 bitcoin worth $3.7 million. The address, established on June 19, 2011, has contributed to the year’s total of 1,125.37 bitcoin moved from dormant 2010 and 2011 wallets.
 
139.7 Bitcoin Worth $3.7 Million Suddenly Moves From Idle Wallet
 
A vintage wallet created on June 19, 2011, suddenly relocated 139.7 BTC, equivalent to $3.7 million at the time of transfer, on Thursday, May 11, 2023. Btcparser.com flagged this activity, which was confirmed at block height 789,291 at 8:14 p.m. (UTC). Shortly before that date — April 24 — the last 2011 bitcoin transfer from a dormant wallet took place and involved shifting 400 BTC at block height 786,801. The wallet that received the 139.7 bitcoin still hold…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bakkt to delist two-thirds of supported tokens]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328606/Bakkt-to-delist-two-thirds-of-supported-tokens</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328606/Bakkt-to-delist-two-thirds-of-supported-tokens"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T22:35:29.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Wars: Google’s Improved Bard Is Ready to Take On OpenAI’s ChatGPT]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139953</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139953/google-bard-openai-chatgpt-ai-wars"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T22:34:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We all love ChatGPT, but Bard has everything that makes us drool—for free.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Wars: Google’s Improved Bard Is Ready to Take On OpenAI’s ChatGPT]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328607/AI-Wars-Googles-Improved-Bard-Is-Ready-to-Take-On-OpenAIs-ChatGPT</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328607/AI-Wars-Googles-Improved-Bard-Is-Ready-to-Take-On-OpenAIs-ChatGPT"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T22:34:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We all love ChatGPT, but Bard has everything that makes us drool—for free.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Award-Winning Green Web3 Start-up Ecoterra Raises $3.5 Million as Investors Swoop In Ahead of 10% Price Rise]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328605/Award-Winning-Green-Web3-Start-up-Ecoterra-Raises-35-Million-as-Investors-Swoop-In-Ahead-of-10-Price-Rise</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328605/Award-Winning-Green-Web3-Start-up-Ecoterra-Raises-35-Million-as-Investors-Swoop-In-Ahead-of-10-Price-Rise"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T22:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Award-winning green web3 start-up ecoterra’s presale continues to fly, with sales of its native $ECOTERRA token having now surpassed $3.5 million as investors swoop in ahead of a 10% token price rise. Ecoterra is building an all-in-one $ECOTERRA-powered web3 ecosystem, designed to encourage...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Analyst Says Memecoins Serve Founders, Not Communities as $PEPE Gains Traction]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328604/Crypto-Analyst-Says-Memecoins-Serve-Founders-Not-Communities-as-PEPE-Gains-Traction</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328604/Crypto-Analyst-Says-Memecoins-Serve-Founders-Not-Communities-as-PEPE-Gains-Traction"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T22:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Crypto to Buy Now 12 May – Bitget Token, Stellar, Cosmos]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328586/Best-Crypto-to-Buy-Now-12-May-Bitget-Token-Stellar-Cosmos</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328586/Best-Crypto-to-Buy-Now-12-May-Bitget-Token-Stellar-Cosmos"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T22:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Network Suffers Finality Issues—Here’s What That Means]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139961</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139961/ethereum-network-suffers-finality-issues-heres-what-that-means"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T22:03:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum has suffered a potentially serious technical issue for the second straight day, prompting confusion among crypto users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Elon Musk's Pick for New Twitter CEO a Dogecoin Maxi Too?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139948</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139948/elon-musk-pick-new-twitter-ceo-dogecoin-maxi-too"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T21:47:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We decipher what little is known about the crypto views of Linda Yaccarino, Twitter's incoming CEO, who follows meme coin personalities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bakkt Mass Delists Tokens Including Aave, Avalanche, Compound, Filecoin, MakerDAO and Uniswap]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750bcb0086</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/05/12/bakkt-mass-delists-tokens-including-aave-avalanche-compound-filecoin-makerdao-and-uniswap/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T21:43:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intercontinental Exchange-owned Bakkt discontinued its consumer-facing app in February as it shifts away from retail]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[As Bitcoin Scales, We Need Better Custodial Solutions]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750bb44cd3</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/05/12/as-bitcoin-scales-we-need-better-custodial-solutions/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T21:30:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If Bitcoin is going to scale through layer 2s, then we need more options and more clarity around the trade-offs between the different ways to use the cryptocurrency.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Kaloudis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken’s Top Lawyer Says Signs of Progress in U.S. Congress Put SEC in Legal Bind]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750bb6a119</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/05/12/krakens-top-lawyer-says-signs-of-progress-in-us-congress-put-sec-in-legal-bind/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T21:07:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) continues to rain enforcement fire onto the crypto industry, Kraken’s chief legal officer, Marco Santori, says a specific legal doctrine could undermine the regulator’s authority.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lido Community Weighing On-Chain Vote to Deploy Version 2 on Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750bb6a1f7</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/05/12/lido-community-weighing-on-chain-vote-to-deploy-version-2-on-ethereum/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T21:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If the governance vote passes, the latest iteration of Lido will come to the Ethereum blockchain, Lido’s biggest market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sage D. Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do Kwon to Be Released on €400,000 Bail, Pleads Not Guilty in Montenegro]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750bb6a9a2</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/do-kwon-to-be-released-on-e400000-bail-pleads-not-guilty-in-montenegro/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T21:06:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform founder Do Kwon will be released from jail but placed under police surveillance at a local residence, a Montenegrin court has decided. The trial against him and another Korean, on charges of travelling on false documents, opened on Thursday with both pleading not guilty.
 
Court Grants Bail Request for Do Kwon, Puts Him Under House Detention
 
A first instance court in Podgorica has agreed to release the founder and former chief executive of failed blockchain firm Terraform Labs, Do Kwon, and another South Korean citizen on bail, local and foreign media reported. They are charged with attempting to use forged personal documents in the small Balkan nation.
 
Do Kwon, or Kwon Do-Hyung as is his full name, was arrested by Montenegrin authorities on March 23 while trying to board a f…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lubomir Tassev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Surfing Tourists Are Flocking to El Salvador—What’s the Big Deal?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139944</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139944/bitcoin-surfing-tourists-are-flocking-to-el-salvador-whats-the-big-deal"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T20:59:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Murders have dropped massively in the Central American country, attracting lots of tourism. Thank its Bitcoin-loving president for the turnaround.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Assassin's Creed 'Smart Collectibles' Pair NFTs With 3D-Printed Physical Items]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139938</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139938/assassins-creed-smart-collectibles-nfts-3d-printed"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T20:53:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ubisoft’s collab with Integral Reality Labs lets NFT holders customize a physical collectible based on the smash game franchise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[House Democrats Consider New Stablecoin Bill Proposal: Source]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750bb1e07d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/05/12/house-democrats-consider-new-stablecoin-bill-proposal-source/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T20:35:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[House Democrats on the Financial Services Committee are considering a new version of proposed stablecoin bill weeks after Republicans on the committee introduced their own discussion draft.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De, Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Announces Exit from Canada, Citing Regulatory Tensions]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750bb1e072</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/05/12/binance-announces-exit-from-canada-citing-regulatory-tensions/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T20:35:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The world’s largest crypto exchange by volume said new guidance related to stablecoins and investor limits prompted the exit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tracy Wang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miner Riot Sues Peer Rhodium Enterprises for Alleged $26M in Unpaid Fees]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750bb1e06e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/05/12/bitcoin-miner-riot-sues-peer-rhodium-enterprises-for-alleged-26m-in-unpaid-fees/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T20:35:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Participation in demand response programs in Texas are at the core of a disagreement between the two mining firms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliza Gkritsi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are We Witnessing A NFT Capitulation? Market Sees Biggest Drop Of 2023]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750bb39282</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/are-we-witnessing-nfts-capitulation/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T20:19:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cryptocurrency market has faced a challenging week, with meme tokens and NFTs taking a significant hit in value. According to Satoshi Club, many tokens have lost 10% or more of their value in just seven days, with the PEPE token dropping by a staggering 44%. This has led some to question whether this is the beginning of an NFT capitulation.
 
 
NFTs Take A Beating As Meme Tokens Plummet
 
Over the last 30 days, only two out of the top 10 NFT collections appreciated, with the average return being 16% in ETH and 23% in dollars (USD). Many collections have hit new lows, causing concern among investors.
 
 
Furthermore,  According to Satoshi Club, daily NFT trading volumes hit their lowest point since 2021, with volumes across all exchanges dropping by approximately 80% from a year ago. Th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PEPE Sees Heavy Futures Liquidations As Price Crashes 24%]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750bb39279</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/pepe-heavy-futures-liquidations-price-crashes-24/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T20:19:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data shows PEPE has observed many future liquidations in the last 24 hours as the memecoin’s price has taken a 24% hit.
 
PEPE Has Registered Total Futures Liquidations Of More Than $13 Million
 
The “liquidation” of a futures market contract happens when a derivative exchange has to forcibly close said contract because the holder has accumulated losses equal to a specific percentage of the margin or the initial collateral (this percentage can differ from platform to platform).
 
A couple of things can significantly raise the risk of a contract being liquidated. The first one is the volatility of the asset the contract is for. Cryptocurrencies generally have quite volatile prices, and memecoins like PEPE are especially known to display some wild volatility, so the risk of getting liquidate…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hououin Kyouma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Staking Platform Agility Soared After Ethereum’s Shapella Upgrade, but It’s Suffered Ever Since]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750bbf218f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/05/12/staking-platform-agility-soared-after-ethereums-shapella-upgrade-but-its-suffered-ever-since/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T19:46:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key metrics like total value locked (TVL) and the price of its AGI token have tumbled recently, following their post-Shapella runup.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sage D. Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Resumes Finalizing Blocks after Second Performance Hiccup in 24 Hours]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750bbf2177</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/05/12/ethereum-resumes-finalizing-blocks-after-second-performance-hiccup-in-24-hours/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T19:46:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Finality refers to the guarantee that a block cannot be altered and removed from the Ethereum blockchain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sage D. Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Musk Hires New CEO for Twitter, ‘She Will Be Starting in 6 Weeks’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750bbf809f</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/musk-hires-new-ceo-for-twitter-she-will-be-starting-in-6-weeks/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T19:43:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Billionaire investor Elon Musk will be stepping down as chief executive of Twitter and taking on other roles in the company. The owner of the microblogging platform revealed he has hired a new CEO, media executive Linda Yaccarino, who should be at the helm of the social media giant in less than two months’ time.
 
Elon Musk to Leave CEO Post at Twitter and Become Company’s CTO
 
Entrepreneur Elon Musk announced he has found someone to replace him as chief executive officer (CEO) of Twitter, making good on a promise to the social network’s users. In a tweet on Thursday, he also said he is staying with the company but in other executive roles.
 
 
Excited to announce that I’ve hired a new CEO for X/Twitter. She will be starting in ~6 weeks!
 
My role will transition to being exec chair & CTO…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lubomir Tassev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Florida Governor Ron DeSantis Bans CBDCs in the State]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139919</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139919/florida-governor-ron-desantis-bans-cbdcs"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T19:36:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DeSantis first introduced legislation in March that sought to ban the use of "Big Brother's digital dollar" in the state of Florida.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meme Coins Meet Table Tennis: FLOKI Lands World Championship Sponsorship]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139914</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139914/floki-table-tennis-world-championship-sponsorship"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T19:28:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The meme coin, inspired by Elon Musk's pet Shiba Inu, will appear in ads at the championship in South Africa this month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MechaFightClub NFT Game 'Paused Indefinitely' Due to US 'Regulatory Limbo']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139910</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139910/a16z-backed-mechafightclub-shutters-game-regulatory-limbo"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T17:58:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Irreverent Labs received $40M in funding, but is now scrapping its cock-fighting Solana game MechaFightClub and offering to buy back NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MetaCannes Ushers in Film3's Next Wave of Cinema at Cannes Film Festival]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139889</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139889/metacannes-ushers-in-film3s-next-wave-of-cinema-at-cannes-film-festival"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T16:31:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Web3 film festival will showcase Film3’s potential to transform the industry, with livestreamed talks and screenings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Names NBCUniversal’s Linda Yaccarino New Twitter CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139905</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139905/elon-musk-names-nbcuniversals-linda-yaccarino-new-twitter-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T16:24:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Musk says Yaccarino will start in six weeks as he segues to “focus on product design and new technology” at the social media giant.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LG Files Patent for TV That Lets Users Trade NFTs From Their Couches]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139899</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139899/lg-patents-tv-that-can-trade-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T16:14:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LG television would permit purchases through a user’s cryptocurrency wallet connected to the TV set, according to the patent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The State Of Web3 Gaming On Hedera]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/7TTEckkZ/the-state-of-web3-gaming-on-hedera</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/7TTEckkZ/the-state-of-web3-gaming-on-hedera"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T14:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hedera VP Alex Russman tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about Hedera's Web3 gaming ecosystem and shares a game he's particularly excited about.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Liquidity on Binance Has More Than Halved Since February: Kaiko]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139877</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139877/bitcoin-liquidity-binance-has-more-than-halved-since-february-kaiko"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T13:57:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Low liquidity and volumes on Binance have led to a serious uptick in volatility in the price action for Bitcoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly,Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform CEO Do Kwon to Be Released on Bail in Montenegro]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139873</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139873/terraform-ceo-do-kwon-be-released-bail-montenegro"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T13:09:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Basic Court in Montenegro has agreed to a $436,000 bail for Terraform Labs’ co-founder and CEO Do Kwon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former FTX Exec Cooperating in Lawsuit Against Celebrity Promoters]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139866</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139866/former-ftx-exec-cooperating-lawsuit-against-celebrity-promoters"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T10:48:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FTX's former compliance chief shared evidence in support of a lawsuit alleging that celebrities promoted the now-bankrupt crypto exchange.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CZ Looking to Offload Some of Majority Stake in Binance US: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139867</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139867/cz-looking-to-offload-majority-stake-binance-us-report"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T10:18:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao is reportedly looking to hand over some of his majority stake in Binance.US to appease American regulators.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Own a Share of a Famed Andy Warhol Print for Just $20—Kinda]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139850</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139850/you-can-own-share-famed-andy-warhol-print-just-23-kinda"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T10:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New fractionalized art platform Freeport is offering Ethereum-based tokenized shares of original Warhol screen prints.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Hits Two-Month Low Amid Dollar Strength, Cooling Ordinals Activity]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139861</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139861/bitcoin-hits-two-month-low-dollar-strength-cooling-ordinals-activity"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T09:45:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin took a hit this morning amid rising economic uncertainty around the U.S. debt limit crisis and a slowdown in Ordinals hype.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Chamber of Commerce Slams SEC, Backs Coinbase in Legal Fight]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139843</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139843/chamber-commerce-slams-sec-coinbase-lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T22:53:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A heavyweight in the business world, the organization says the SEC's "regulatory chaos is by design, not happenstance."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your Crypto Mining Chips Are No Good for AI—Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139825</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139825/crypto-mining-chips-ai-heres-why"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T21:07:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mining and AI have different tastes when it comes to GPUs, and crypto miners can’t satisfy them both.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Is Hot—But Meta Is Still ‘Really Interested in the Metaverse,’ Exec Claims]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139826</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139826/ai-is-hot-but-meta-is-still-really-interested-in-the-metaverse-exec-claims"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T21:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meta’s short-term focus has shifted towards AI, but an exec says that such tools will actually help its metaverse vision come to life.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Cohen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Heavy Metal Band Avenged Sevenfold Keeps Betting on NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139832</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139832/avenged-sevenfold-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T20:59:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avenged Sevenfold frontman M. Shadows appeared on Decrypt’s gm podcast to discuss why he thinks NFTs give fans a better experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Mirandus is Innovating Video Game Audio]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kLHZIUsl/how-mirandus-is-innovating-video-game-audio</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kLHZIUsl/how-mirandus-is-innovating-video-game-audio"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T20:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mirandus' Lead Developer and Gala Games Cofounder Michael McCarthy tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the game's thoughtful approach to audio design and the technologies being built to support the MMORPG's immersive world.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IRS Trains Ukraine Law Enforcement to Track and Trace Russia's Cryptocurrency Moves]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139812</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139812/irs-chainalysis-train-urkaine-law-enforcement"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T17:58:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["We resist the aggressor state not only on the battlefield, but also on the economic front," said the head of Ukraine's Economic Security Bureau.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘We Screwed Up’: Coinbase Apologizes for Pepe Comments as #DeleteCoinbase Trends]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139805</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139805/we-screwed-up-coinbase-apologizes-for-pepe-comments-as-deletecoinbase-trends"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T17:14:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The move comes after the hashtag trended on Twitter, as PEPE holders bristled over Coinbase's description of Pepe's past alt-right history.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Labs Opening 25,000-Square-Foot Office Space in NYC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139795</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139795/solana-labs-opens-nyc-coworking-space"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T16:47:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite shuttering stores earlier this year, the company behind the 10th biggest cryptocurrency is opening co-working space.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Silvergate Lays Off 230 Workers as Crypto-Friendly Bank Continues Wind Down]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139791</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139791/silvergate-lays-off-230-as-it-continues-wind-down"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T15:28:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The banked shuttered in March after its deposits were rocked in the wake of FTX’s collapse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do Gamers Hate NFTs?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/X0FtIw0j/do-gamers-hate-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/X0FtIw0j/do-gamers-hate-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin asks the InfiniGods developers Damon Gura and Owen O’Donoghue about gamers and NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking Boundaries: YuYu's Personal Journey as a Queer Artist in the NFT World]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139737</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139737/breaking-boundaries-yuyu-personal-journey-queer-artist-nft-world"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T15:03:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[YuYu’s first NFT-powered exhibit “GAG” merges a variety of artforms—including traditional art and photography—all on the blockchain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gaming Dominates On-Chain Transactions in April as Arbitrum Users Surge]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139695</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139695/gaming-dominates-on-chain-transactions-in-april-as-arbitrum-users-surge"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T15:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The meme token craze might be impacting Web3 gaming activity, DappRadar suggests, but Arbitrum users are up and Sui is gaining steam.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miners Earning $40M Daily Revenue as Ordinals Debate Splits Devs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139679</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139679/bitcoin-miners-earning-40m-daily-revenue-as-ordinals-debate-splits-devs"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T14:51:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Miners have struggled as of late, but the Ordinals craze is creating a windfall for a fortunate few.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin and Ethereum Down 3%, Top Altcoins Fall as Market Sees Red]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139747</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139747/bitcoin-and-ethereum-down-3-percent"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T14:45:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now that Bitcoin fees have subsided, delayed selling has dragged down BTC, ETH, and altcoin prices a day after the U.S. CPI report.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Artizen Fund Raises $2.2 Million to Create NFT Cultural Artifacts]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139682</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139682/artizen-fund-raises-2-2-million-to-create-nft-cultural-artifacts"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The platform leverages tokenization and gamification to crowdfund niche projects in the arts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Texas Lawmakers Vote to Include Use of Digital Currencies in State's Bill of Rights]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139729</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139729/texas-lawmakers-vote-include-use-digital-currencies-states-bill-rights"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T12:55:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The people of Texas may soon be guaranteed the right to use cryptocurrencies if lawmakers enshrine it into the state’s Bill of Rights.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Crypto Rules ‘Will Bite’ Firms That Market to Consumers, Says Financial Regulator]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139730</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139730/new-crypto-rules-will-bite-firms-marketing-consumers-says-financial-regulator"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T12:35:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Financial Conduct Authority said the UK is looking to protect consumers with upcoming crypto regulatory framework changes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Crypto Bros Are Certainly a Problem': Ripple Managing Director]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139724</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139724/crypto-bros-are-certainly-problem-ripple-managing-director"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T09:54:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solving the long-standing issue of diversity in the crypto industry demands more than just “one magic bullet,” says Ripple’s Sendi Young.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Serves Bitcoin Mining Firm Marathon Digital With Subpoena, Again]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139722</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139722/sec-serves-bitcoin-mining-firm-marathon-digital-subpoena-again"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T09:17:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marathon Digital revealed the company has received a new subpoena from the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CleanSpark Eyes Expansion Plans Ahead of Bitcoin Halving]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139713</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139713/cleanspark-eyes-expansion-plans-ahead-bitcoin-halving"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T08:14:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CleanSpark assured investors during its Q2 earnings call that that it is both growing rapidly and focusing on efficiency.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Krantz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why DeFi Cybersecurity Can Never Sleep]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139573</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139573/why-defi-cybersecurity-can-never-sleep"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T22:41:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["You can't know if the report is that serious hack, or if it's just spam," said Immunefi CEO Mitchell Amador.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonah Elkowitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Barbie and Boss Beauties Make Joint Bid to Bring More Women into Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139666</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139666/barbie-boss-beauties-digital-collectibles-nfts-women-web3"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T21:50:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The two brands have created a crossover NFT collection featuring a variety of rarity levels and real-world perks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can New York AG’s Crypto Proposal Offer Investors Greater Protection?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139659</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139659/new-york-crypto-crpto-act-law-regulation-investor-protection"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T21:06:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CRPTO Act focuses on transparency and conflicts of interest in an already crypto-savvy state.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: Avenged Sevenfold's M. Shadows on Deathbats, Fandom, and AI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JEgr9COw/gm-avenged-sevenfolds-m-shadows-on-deathbats-fandom-and-ai</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JEgr9COw/gm-avenged-sevenfolds-m-shadows-on-deathbats-fandom-and-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T20:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avenged Sevenfold lead singer Matt Sanders, aka M. Shadows, is rehearsing for the band's upcoming tour. He's also figuring out how to upend what it means to be a music fan. The band launched a Deathbats Club NFT collection in 2021. That is to say: They were early. The lead singer said it was timed to give fans a chance to get comfortable with Web3 technology ahead of the group's 2023 tour, when the NFT holders can use their Deathbats for early access to tickets. M. Shadows also talked to hosts Andrew Hayward and Stephen Graves about AI and bringing Web3 into gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Mojo Melee's Lore with Creator Mike Levine and Art Director Eric Campanella]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BfIB2H5e/inside-mojo-melees-lore-with-creator-mike-levine-and-art-director-eric-campanella</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BfIB2H5e/inside-mojo-melees-lore-with-creator-mike-levine-and-art-director-eric-campanella"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T22:29:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the Game Developers' Conference, Mojo Melee Creator Mike Levine and Art Director Eric Campanella tell Decrypt's Kate Irwin about their autobattler game and its unique characters, which are also NFTs on Polygon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why 'Blair Witch' Exec Producer Kevin Foxe Is '1,000% In' on Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZXj16C8r/why-blair-witch-exec-producer-kevin-foxe-is-1-000-in-on-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZXj16C8r/why-blair-witch-exec-producer-kevin-foxe-is-1-000-in-on-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T23:02:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["The Blair Witch Project" Executive Producer Kevin Foxe wants to avoid corporate overlords and enlighten fans of the dark "Mandala" graphic novel with a video game adaptation and NFTs across multiple blockchains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gala Games Co-Founder on the Aesthetic of Mirandus]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/1bQV1R6l/gala-games-co-founder-on-the-aesthetic-of-mirandus</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/1bQV1R6l/gala-games-co-founder-on-the-aesthetic-of-mirandus"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T14:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["When assets are overdone, they just feel a little dirty. It's not pretty to look at," shared Mirandus' Lead Developer and Gala Games co-founder Michael McCarthy in an interview with Decrypt's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Games GM: Play-to-Earn Games Are DeFi Products, Not Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yp7btQtl/solana-games-gm-play-to-earn-games-are-defi-products-not-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yp7btQtl/solana-games-gm-play-to-earn-games-are-defi-products-not-games"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T16:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Games' General Manager Johnny Lee offers a hot take on the first generation of Web3 gaming with Decrypt's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brycent's Advice For Gaming Content Creators]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/o19nZCeN/brycents-advice-for-gaming-content-creators</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/o19nZCeN/brycents-advice-for-gaming-content-creators"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T20:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XSET's Brycent shares his advice for Web3 content creators with Decrypt's Kate Irwin, including which social media platform is best for posting content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Behind the Scenes of Jeremy Cowart's 'Auras' NFT Event]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/C0ZeidQg/behind-the-scenes-of-jeremy-cowarts-auras-nft-event</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/C0ZeidQg/behind-the-scenes-of-jeremy-cowarts-auras-nft-event"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T22:54:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A look at the preparation behind "Auras," an event in which photographer Jeremy Cowart produced and starred in 10,000 photo-based NFTs, captured in less than 30 minutes before a live audience. Credit: Brett Carlsen for Decrypt]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jeremy Cowart Discusses 'Auras' Event, Live-Shooting 10,000 Photo NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/E3ViHsPd/jeremy-cowart-discusses-auras-event-live-shooting-10-000-photo-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/E3ViHsPd/jeremy-cowart-discusses-auras-event-live-shooting-10-000-photo-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T18:32:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jeremy Cowart speaks with Decrypt's Sander Lutz in Nashville ahead of the "Auras" event, in which the noted photographer live-shot 10,000 unique photo-based NFTs in less than 30 minutes. The NFTs will be released through OpenSea on May 9. Video credit: Brett Carlsen for Decrypt]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azra Games CEO on Putting Fun Before Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/03W3KZjM/azra-games-ceo-on-putting-fun-before-web3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/03W3KZjM/azra-games-ceo-on-putting-fun-before-web3"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T14:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["The Web3 interfaces cannot be on the foreground of the player's initial experience," says Azra Games CEO Mark Otero.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: Meet Immunefi's White Hat Whisperer]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/2vTAgpTC/gm-meet-immunefis-white-hat-whisperer</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/2vTAgpTC/gm-meet-immunefis-white-hat-whisperer"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T17:30:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Web3 bug bounty platform Immunefi launched two years ago, CEO and founder Mitchell Amador says the bug bounties weren't great and adoption was slow. But the tides started to turn because even if exploiting a smart contract nets a bigger payday than a bounty, it comes with a huge drawback. "There's a ton of risk when you engage in this, you know, wantonly criminal behavior and steal $200 million from someone else," he said. "There's no way someone's not going to come looking."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gala Games Co-Founder on Why Mirandus Will Not Have NPCs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5pey6epR/gala-games-co-founder-on-why-mirandus-will-not-have-npcs</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5pey6epR/gala-games-co-founder-on-why-mirandus-will-not-have-npcs"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T17:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lead Mirandus Developer and Gala Games Cofounder Michael McCarthy tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the Web3 MMORPG Mirandus and what its world will be like.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFC Lisbon Founder John Karp Heralds 'Level 2' Content for 2023 Event]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cYaJ25qv/nfc-lisbon-founder-john-karp-heralds-level-2-content-for-2023-event</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cYaJ25qv/nfc-lisbon-founder-john-karp-heralds-level-2-content-for-2023-event"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T09:44:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No panels, no problem. This year's NFC Lisbon from June 7 to June 9 boasts a variety of alternative formats, catering to a decentralized (and sometimes pseudonymous) NFT community. The event also plans to take a closer look into one of the faster-growing niches in NFTs: Photography and what founder John Karp calls "level 2" content. Not to be missed, as NFC Lisbon's media partner, Decrypt will be on-site for all three days. Come say hi!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Does Magic Eden Vet Web3 Games?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ogci0VQ6/how-does-magic-eden-vet-web3-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ogci0VQ6/how-does-magic-eden-vet-web3-games"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Magic Eden Chief Gaming Officer Chris Akhavan tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about how the NFT marketplace vets potential Web3 games for its platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interview: Kevin Rose on the 'Weird Dynamic' of Building an NFT Project]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rb2MhkWH/interview-kevin-rose-on-the-weird-dynamic-of-building-an-nft-project</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rb2MhkWH/interview-kevin-rose-on-the-weird-dynamic-of-building-an-nft-project"/>
        <updated>2023-04-30T18:49:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Proof co-founder and CEO Kevin Rose chats with Decrypt Culture Editor Andrew Hayward during NFT NYC 2023 to discuss his startup's reaffirmed focus on digital art and collectors, the challenges of building in the NFT market, and what he's learned in the last year since the buzzy Moonbirds drop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How MMORPG Mirandus is Managing its Web3 Elements]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XETXOt0k/how-mmorpg-mirandus-is-managing-its-web3-elements</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XETXOt0k/how-mmorpg-mirandus-is-managing-its-web3-elements"/>
        <updated>2023-04-29T16:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gala Games Cofounder Michael McCarthy says an "unbelievable" amount of Mirandus conversations are about its approach to Web3 and crypto transactions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Azra Games's Creative Process?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zyYFJkg0/what-is-azra-gamess-creative-process</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zyYFJkg0/what-is-azra-gamess-creative-process"/>
        <updated>2023-04-28T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azra Games CEO Mark Otero tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about Azra's creative process to game development and storytelling.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aurory Is 'Pokemon Meets The Matrix,' Says Executive Producer]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/AotiTeMz/aurory-is-pokemon-meets-the-matrix-says-executive-producer</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/AotiTeMz/aurory-is-pokemon-meets-the-matrix-says-executive-producer"/>
        <updated>2023-04-27T20:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Aurory Web3 game's Executive Producer Jonathan Campeau tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin at the 2023 Game Developer's Conference about the game and what it's like to play.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>