<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-05-30T17:11:34.001Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-05-30T17:11:34.001Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Market Anticipation Builds As Optimism Plans To Unlock $587M Worth Of OP Tokens]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7500aaa810</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/market-anticipation-builds-as-optimism-plans-unlock/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T17:06:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Optimism developers plan to unlock 386 million OP tokens with a value of over $587 million. This token unlock event will occur on May 31, 2023, marking the end of the initial vesting period. 
 
 
The event will increase the circulating supply of OP tokens by over 100%. Analysts opine that the upcoming unlock event might affect OP’s price negatively.
 
OP Price Might Dip As Early Investors Cash In
 
Token unlocks in the crypto market are scheduled events that release early investors’ locked tokens after freezing them for a specific period. 
 
Crypto communities use token locks to avoid large asset sales in low liquidity periods. Selling during these periods could have an impact on the price of the token. 
 
But these events increase the number of tokens in circulation, creating an imbalance…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Dambel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mercedes Benz Web3 Arm To Release NFT Collection With Digital Art Community Fingerprints DAO]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7500abf761</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/web3/2023/05/30/mercedes-benz-web3-arm-to-release-nft-collection-with-digital-art-community-fingerprints-dao/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T16:57:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Titled “Maschine,” the generative art collection was created by Dutch artist Harm van den Dorpel and draws inspiration from automotive concepts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cam Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trader Who Accurately Called 2023 Crypto Rally Predicts Massive Litecoin (LTC) Surge – Here’s His Forecast]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18463872/Trader-Who-Accurately-Called-2023-Crypto-Rally-Predicts-Massive-Litecoin-LTC-Surge-Heres-His-Forecast</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18463872/Trader-Who-Accurately-Called-2023-Crypto-Rally-Predicts-Massive-Litecoin-LTC-Surge-Heres-His-Forecast"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T16:55:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A trader who skillfully rode this year’s crypto turnaround is updating his outlook on the peer-to-peer payments network Litecoin (LTC). Pseudonymous crypto strategist DonAlt tells his 486,900 Twitter followers that he believes that the time is ticking for Litecoin to make a move. According to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Lead Shytoshi Kusama Says That There's "Many" Great Things in the Works]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18463860/Shiba-Inu-Lead-Shytoshi-Kusama-Says-That-Theres-Many-Great-Things-in-the-Works</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18463860/Shiba-Inu-Lead-Shytoshi-Kusama-Says-That-Theres-Many-Great-Things-in-the-Works"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T16:48:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu's project lead Shytoshi Kusama sparked excitement in the cryptocurrency community on Tuesday after hinting at substantial developments for the meme coin]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Controversial Stablecoin Issuer Tether Plans to Start Mining Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142830</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142830/controversial-stablecoin-issuer-tether-plans-to-start-mining-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T16:37:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoin issuers have accrued huge amounts of Bitcoin in the past—but it hasn't always gone to plan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Connor Sephton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Controversial Stablecoin Issuer Tether Plans to Start Mining Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18463856/Controversial-Stablecoin-Issuer-Tether-Plans-to-Start-Mining-Bitcoin</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18463856/Controversial-Stablecoin-Issuer-Tether-Plans-to-Start-Mining-Bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T16:37:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoin issuers have accrued huge amounts of Bitcoin in the past—but it hasn't always gone to plan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Case Passed to Third Circut Court of Appeals: ‘The facts are not in dispute’]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18463830/FTX-Case-Passed-to-Third-Circut-Court-of-Appeals-The-facts-are-not-in-dispute</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18463830/FTX-Case-Passed-to-Third-Circut-Court-of-Appeals-The-facts-are-not-in-dispute"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T16:36:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Delaware District Judge Colm F. Connolly has approved to pass the case involving FTX to the U.S. Third Circuit Court of Appeals, leading the way for an independent investigators appointment, according to the memorandum opinion.The move has gained the backing of the government and bipartisan...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Bitcoin Standard Author Saifedean Ammous Joins El Salvador’s National Bitcoin Office As Economic Advisor]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750097200d</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/el-salvador-bitcoin-news/saifedean-ammous-joins-el-salvadors-bitcoin-office-as-economic-advisor"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T16:35:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dr. Saifedean Ammous, prominent economist and author of "The Bitcoin Standard," is poised to take on a new role as an Economic Advisor to El Salvador's Bitcoin Office. This appointment comes after El Salvador made history by becoming the first country to adopt bitcoin as legal tender in September 2021.
“Having Saifedean Ammous on team El Salvador is fantastic,” Max Keiser, Senior Bitcoin Advisor to the country said in a statement to Bitcoin Magazine. “Ammous brilliantly captured the role of Bitcoin as, ‘The alternative to Central Banking’ in his now classic, ‘The Bitcoin Standard’ as well as the philosophy of Bitcoin including popularizing the idea of 'time preference' as a life-hack. This news makes me very happy.”
Ammous, known for his expertise in Bitcoin and monetary economics, is expected to provide valuable guidance and insights to the Bitcoin Office as it navigates the implementation and integration of Bitcoin into the country's economy. His extensive knowledge and research on the subject have earned him recognition within the community and beyond.
The Bitcoin Law, proposed by El Salvador's President Nayib Bukele and approved by the Legislative Assembly, has set the stage for a new era in the country's financial landscape. With Ammous joining as an Economic Advisor, El Salvador aims to leverage his expertise to maximize the benefits and address potential challenges associated with adopting bitcoin as legal tender.
The Bitcoin Office, established to oversee the implementation of the Bitcoin Law, will likely benefit from Ammous' insights on monetary policy, sound money principles and the potential economic implications of embracing a decentralized digital currency. His appointment signals El Salvador's commitment to incorporating expert opinions into their strategy and decision-making process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BtcCasey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BRC-721E Standard to Bridge Gap between Ethereum NFTs and Bitcoin Ordinals]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18463826/BRC-721E-Standard-to-Bridge-Gap-between-Ethereum-NFTs-and-Bitcoin-Ordinals</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18463826/BRC-721E-Standard-to-Bridge-Gap-between-Ethereum-NFTs-and-Bitcoin-Ordinals"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T16:35:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinspeaker BRC-721E Standard to Bridge Gap between Ethereum NFTs and Bitcoin Ordinals As the NFT landscape continues to evolve, the integration of Ethereum and Bitcoin ecosystems through the BRC-721E standard paves the way for further innovation and expansion that can even attract more...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Market Anticipation Builds As Optimism Plans To Unlock $587M Worth Of OP Tokens]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18463821/Market-Anticipation-Builds-As-Optimism-Plans-To-Unlock-587M-Worth-Of-OP-Tokens</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18463821/Market-Anticipation-Builds-As-Optimism-Plans-To-Unlock-587M-Worth-Of-OP-Tokens"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T16:30:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Optimism developers plan to unlock 386 million OP tokens with a value of over $587 million. This token unlock event will occur on May 31, 2023, marking the end of the initial vesting period. Related Reading: BREAKING: Bitcoin Mining Industry Spared From 30% Tax In US Debt Ceiling Deal The event...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You can now bridge Ethereum NFTs to Bitcoin — but you can’t get them back]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18463838/You-can-now-bridge-Ethereum-NFTs-to-Bitcoin-but-you-cant-get-them-back</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18463838/You-can-now-bridge-Ethereum-NFTs-to-Bitcoin-but-you-cant-get-them-back"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T16:30:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new tool lets Ethereum NFTs be transferred to the Bitcoin blockchain. , However, it’s a one-way bridge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Set for Comeback Amid Anticipated DXY Reversal, Says Glassnode Co-Founder]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18463840/Bitcoin-Set-for-Comeback-Amid-Anticipated-DXY-Reversal-Says-Glassnode-Co-Founder</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18463840/Bitcoin-Set-for-Comeback-Amid-Anticipated-DXY-Reversal-Says-Glassnode-Co-Founder"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T16:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In face of several market headwinds, Bitcoin may be poised for significant rally, according to Glassnode co-founder Yann Allemann]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shibburn Spurs 1516% as SHIB Community Burns 6.3B in a Week]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18463791/Shibburn-Spurs-1516-as-SHIB-Community-Burns-63B-in-a-Week</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18463791/Shibburn-Spurs-1516-as-SHIB-Community-Burns-63B-in-a-Week"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T16:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s getting boiling hot for Shiba Inu with the yearly burn record shattered twice in one month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Launchpad XYZ the Best Crypto App for Newcomers? Here's How to Find the Next Meme Coin to Explode]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18463790/Is-Launchpad-XYZ-the-Best-Crypto-App-for-Newcomers-Heres-How-to-Find-the-Next-Meme-Coin-to-Explode</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18463790/Is-Launchpad-XYZ-the-Best-Crypto-App-for-Newcomers-Heres-How-to-Find-the-Next-Meme-Coin-to-Explode"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T16:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 can be very daunting for beginners. There are so many strange concepts, and so much jargon. Non-crypto natives need to wrap their heads around the concept of blockchains, wallets, gas fees, the difference between cryptocurrencies and crypto tokens (of the ERC-20 and BEP-20 ilk), as well as...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance in Talks To Let Traders Keep Collateral at a Bank: Bloomberg]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18463757/Binance-in-Talks-To-Let-Traders-Keep-Collateral-at-a-Bank-Bloomberg</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18463757/Binance-in-Talks-To-Let-Traders-Keep-Collateral-at-a-Bank-Bloomberg"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T16:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance, the world’s largest crypto exchange, is in the midst of discussing a proposal to let some of its institutional clients keep their trading collateral at a bank, instead of with the crypto platform, according to Bloomberg News. ... Read More: Binance in Talks To Let Traders Keep...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Ordinals Threaten Ethereum NFTs with New BRC-721E Standard]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18463792/Bitcoin-Ordinals-Threaten-Ethereum-NFTs-with-New-BRC-721E-Standard</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18463792/Bitcoin-Ordinals-Threaten-Ethereum-NFTs-with-New-BRC-721E-Standard"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T16:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Ordinals, with the BRC-721E standard, are stirring the NFT market, posing a challenge to Ethereum's dominance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Rising: Russia To Create Framework For Establishment Of Crypto Exchanges]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750093bf40</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/russias-evolving-crypto-exchange-landscape/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T16:04:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Russia’s crypto landscape has taken a notable shift as the government has abandoned its plans to establish a centralized national digital currency exchange. Instead, the focus has now shifted towards the regulation of multiple crypto trading platforms within the country. 
 
This strategic change aims to provide a structured framework for the creation and management of these platforms, as reported by local news agency Izvestia on May 29.
 
Colin Wu, renowned for his coverage of blockchain-related news as Wu Blockchain, took to Twitter to break the story. In his tweet, he shared a translated version of a report from a Russian news outlet.
 
 
Russian lawmakers have said they will no longer move forward with plans to create a state-level cryptocurrency trading platform. Focus on developing ru…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pro-XRP Lawyer Alleges Lack of Approval by SEC Ethics Office For Hinman’s Speech]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750093bf37</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/pro-xrp-lawyer-alleges-lack-of-approval-sec-ethics/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T16:04:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Attorney John Deaton, known for his pro-XRP stance, has disclosed that the SEC’s Ethics Office did not approve William Hinman’s controversial speech.
 
The former director of SEC’s Corporation Finance, Hinman, made remarks in 2018 classifying Bitcoin and Ethereum as non-securities but failing to mention XRP.
 
 
Deaton recently shared a document that shed light on the various departments at the SEC that received drafts of Hinman’s speech.
 
Surprisingly, the Ethics Office was notably absent from the list of recipients, raising questions about the official approval process for the speech.
 
SEC’s Ethics Office Approval Could Have Helped Ripple, Deaton
 
Expressing his views on social media, Deaton asserted that if the SEC Ethics Office approved Hinman’s speech, it would have been made publi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Dambel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mercedes Benz Web3 Arm To Release NFT Collection With Digital Art Community Fingerprints DAO]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18463753/Mercedes-Benz-Web3-Arm-To-Release-NFT-Collection-With-Digital-Art-Community-Fingerprints-DAO</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18463753/Mercedes-Benz-Web3-Arm-To-Release-NFT-Collection-With-Digital-Art-Community-Fingerprints-DAO"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T16:02:14.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Examiner Appointment Referred to Court of Appeals by District Judge]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75009c71a4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/05/30/ftx-examiner-appointment-referred-to-court-of-appeals-by-district-judge/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T16:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. government is pushing to have an independent inquiry into the crypto exchange despite concerns over cost]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack Schickler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized exchange PancakeSwap moves into GameFi]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18463755/Decentralized-exchange-PancakeSwap-moves-into-GameFi</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18463755/Decentralized-exchange-PancakeSwap-moves-into-GameFi"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T16:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The DEX has partnered with BNB GameFi protocol Mobox to create a blockchain tower defense game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fantom Blockchain to Return 15% of Gas Fees to Boost Network Usage – Here's What You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18463758/Fantom-Blockchain-to-Return-15-of-Gas-Fees-to-Boost-Network-Usage-Heres-What-You-Need-to-Know</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18463758/Fantom-Blockchain-to-Return-15-of-Gas-Fees-to-Boost-Network-Usage-Heres-What-You-Need-to-Know"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Fantom (FTM) blockchain has introduced a new initiative called the "dApp Gas Monetization Program," aiming to reward projects that utilize its network and contribute to increased gas fee usage. The new program, which recently received community support through a governance vote, seeks to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Litecoin (LTC) Reaches Major Milestone as This Metric's Value Spikes]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18463762/Litecoin-LTC-Reaches-Major-Milestone-as-This-Metrics-Value-Spikes</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18463762/Litecoin-LTC-Reaches-Major-Milestone-as-This-Metrics-Value-Spikes"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T15:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacker Robs Tornado Cash, Launders Loot Through the Same Service]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18463733/Hacker-Robs-Tornado-Cash-Launders-Loot-Through-the-Same-Service</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18463733/Hacker-Robs-Tornado-Cash-Launders-Loot-Through-the-Same-Service"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T15:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a surprising turn of events, the hacker responsible for the Tornado Cash heist has unexpectedly handed back control of the protocol to the team.  Adding to the irony, the criminal utilized the very same service to launder the funds stolen during the attack. Tornado Cash, which has long been...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Transfer Your Ethereum NFTs to Bitcoin With New Token Standard]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18463723/Transfer-Your-Ethereum-NFTs-to-Bitcoin-With-New-Token-Standard</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18463723/Transfer-Your-Ethereum-NFTs-to-Bitcoin-With-New-Token-Standard"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T15:53:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Users can send their favorite digital collectibles straight to Bitcoin from Ethereum by initiating a bridging contract acting as a single on-chain inscription request]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether invests in energy production in Uruguay to mine bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18463719/Tether-invests-in-energy-production-in-Uruguay-to-mine-bitcoin</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18463719/Tether-invests-in-energy-production-in-Uruguay-to-mine-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T15:49:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tether is following in the footsteps of Bitfinex operator iFinex, which has previously invested in bitcoin mining efforts led by Blockstream.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nansen cuts staff 30% amid ‘brutal’ year for crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18463839/Nansen-cuts-staff-30-amid-brutal-year-for-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18463839/Nansen-cuts-staff-30-amid-brutal-year-for-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T15:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why InfiniGods Laughs at 'AAA' Web3 Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/WzdrzXOY/why-infinigods-laughs-at-aaa-web3-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/WzdrzXOY/why-infinigods-laughs-at-aaa-web3-games"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The InfiniGods founders share their approach to game development and offer a critique of games that call themselves "AAA."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biggest Movers: XRP Hits 6-Week High, SOL Collides With Key Resistance Level]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75009fd048</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/biggest-movers-xrp-hits-6-week-high-sol-collides-with-key-resistance-level/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T15:38:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XRP rallied to a six-week high in today’s session, as the token extended a recent bull run to a sixth day. Prices have risen by as much as 10% in that period, with the latest surge sending the cryptocurrency above $0.50. Solana was also higher, hitting a multi-week high of its own.
 
XRP
 
XRP, formerly known as ripple, was one of the biggest movers in cryptocurrency markets on Tuesday, as it rose above $0.50.
 
XRP/USD raced to a peak of $0.5049 earlier in today’s session, after starting the week trading at a low of $0.4779.
 
As a result of this surge, the token moved to its strongest point since April 19, when it hit a high of $0.5390.
 
 
Today’s rally has also led to the 14-day relative strength index (RSI) hitting its highest reading since March 31.
 
At the time of writing, the index is tracking at 67.55, which is marginally below a ceiling of 68.00.
 
In the event this upcoming ceiling is broken, there is a reasonable chance that XRP moves closer to March’s high.
 
 
Solana (SOL)
 
Solana (SOL) was also in the green, as it moved close to a key resistance level of $21.50.
 
After trading at a low of $20.30 during Monday’s session, SOL/USD bulls took the token to a high of $21.37 today.
 
This surge saw SOL hit its highest level since May 8, when the token was trading above $21.80.
 
 
Following recent gains, solana is now trading 7% higher than at the same point last week, with today’s rally sending the RSI to a ceiling at 55.00.
 
As of writing, the index is hovering marginally below this point, which has resulted in a drop from today’s peak.
 
Bulls will firstly need to overcome the ceiling at 55.00, and should they achieve this, SOL will likely move above $22.00.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
Do you expect a breakout in the coming days? Let us know your thoughts in the comments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Umbrel Announces New Umbrel Home Plug-And-Play Server]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75009fd3d6</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/umbrel-announces-new-umbrel-home-plug-and-play-server"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T15:38:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Umbrel, the company behind umbrelOS, has introduced a new home server solution called Umbrel Home with the intent of providing users control over their data, privacy and digital lives, according to a press release sent to Bitcoin Magazine. Priced at $699, Umbrel Home is aimed at making self-hosting accessible to everyone. By leveraging umbrelOS, users can eliminate the need for third-party cloud services by utilizing a wide range of self-hosted apps available in the Umbrel App Store including a Bitcoin/Lightning node, Nextcloud, Plex and Home Assistant.
 
         
         
         
         
    
According to the press release, Umbrel Home offers accelerated performance, featuring a 2.9GHz Quad-Core Intel CPU, 2TB NVMe SSD, 16GB dual-channel RAM, and an active cooling system while consuming just 10 watts of power. This compact home server outperforms a Raspberry Pi 4-based solution in terms of CPU performance, SSD read and write speeds, RAM and memory bandwidth the release states.
Mayank Chhabra, Umbrel's Co-founder and CEO, highlighted the company's vision for Umbrel Home, saying that "Building a plug-and-play home server that was specifically engineered for umbrelOS has been our dream since day one. With the recent challenges in Raspberry Pi pricing and supply chain, we knew it was time to bring our vision to life, set a new benchmark in self-hosting, and make it accessible to users of all skill levels."
With privacy and data ownership concerns on the rise, self-hosting presents a modern solution that allows users to take ownership of their data, storage, access and sharing. In addition, Umbrel Home’s zero-configuration and one-click app installations from the Umbrel App Store make it easy to build a customized ecosystem tailored to individual needs.
Pre-orders for Umbrel Home are now available on umbrel.com, with shipping set to begin in June 2023. With its exceptional performance, user-friendly features and affordability, Umbrel Home aims to make self-hosting accessible to a global audience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BtcCasey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Plight of Hyped-Blockchain Canto Demonstrates Dreary DeFi Outlook]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7500851aba</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/05/30/the-plight-of-hyped-blockchain-canto-demonstrates-dreary-defi-outlook/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T15:05:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Layer 1 blockchain Canto has experienced a 35% slump in total value locked (TVL) over the past month as liquidity continues to dry up across the decentralized finance (DeFi) sector.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Make it Fast, Make it Friendly: Jerome de Tychey Unpacks Key Themes at This Year's EthCC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yNyunUz4/make-it-fast-make-it-friendly-jerome-de-tychey-unpacks-key-themes-at-this-years-ethcc</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yNyunUz4/make-it-fast-make-it-friendly-jerome-de-tychey-unpacks-key-themes-at-this-years-ethcc"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T15:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After six years running, EthCC is back, this time in Paris from July 17 to July 20. Decrypt sat down with the brains behind one of Ethereum’s longest-running events Jerome de Tychey to get an inside look into what’s on the agenda this year, several unannounced guests, and the rollout of at least one “secret” DeFi project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ordinals Inscriptions on Bitcoin Surpass 10 Million, Fueling NFT and Token Boom]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750081ce43</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ordinals-inscriptions-on-bitcoin-surpass-10-million-fueling-nft-and-token-boom/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T14:35:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Monday, May 28, 2023, a pivotal landmark was reached as the aggregate quantity of Ordinal inscriptions minted on the Bitcoin blockchain exceeded 10 million in under half a year. Since Ordinal inscriptions’ inception, bitcoin miners have garnered roughly 1,596 bitcoins, valued at $44.37 million.
 
10 Million Ordinal Inscriptions and Counting
 
This week witnessed the total Ordinal inscriptions surpassing the 10 million mark; as of this writing, 10,142,233 inscriptions have been issued. Moreover, the BRC20 token economy consisting of 24,677 registered BRC20 tokens boasts a combined value of $433 million. Bitcoin inscriptions have carved out a niche in the realm of non-fungible token (NFT) markets and currently stand as the second-largest blockchain in terms of NFT sales.
 
Data from the p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoin Issuer Tether Invests in Sustainable Bitcoin Mining in Uruguay]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75008cab96</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/05/30/stablecoin-issuer-tether-invests-in-sustainable-bitcoin-mining-in-uruguay/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T14:17:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tether announced this month to invest a part of its net realized profits in BTC purchases and infrastructure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin (DOGE) Volatility Set To Ignite – Good Or Bad For The Meme Coin?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75008edf5b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-volatility-set-to-ignite/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T14:03:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin (DOGE) is currently experiencing an unprecedented period of stability. However, according to a technical analysis indicator known as Bollinger Bandwidth, this tranquil phase may soon come to an end, paving the way for a significant and potentially explosive price swing in the foreseeable future. 
 
Such a volatility explosion in the price of Dogecoin could have far-reaching consequences for traders and investors. It could ignite a new wave of interest, drawing in fresh capital and pushing the cryptocurrency to new heights. 
 
 
Alternatively, a sharp downturn could trigger a cascade of sell-offs, causing the price to plummet and leading to substantial losses for those caught on the wrong side of the trade.
 

 
 
Understanding Dogecoin’s Impending Volatility
 
The Bollinger bandwi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KilroyPunk NFT Drop Mashes Up Iconic Meme With a CryptoPunk]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142778</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142778/kilroypunk-nft-drop-mashes-up-iconic-meme-cryptopunk"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T13:30:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Holograph unveils a collab between artist Eric Elms and the pseudonymous foobar—a multichain, open edition KilroyPunk NFT that spans eras.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Technical Analysis: BTC Back Above $28,000, as ‘Death Cross’ Approaches]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750074bd08</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-ethereum-technical-analysis-btc-back-above-28000-as-death-cross-approaches/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T13:27:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin was once again trading above $28,000 on Tuesday, as the 10-day and 25-day moving averages neared a death cross. The two trend lines have moved closer to one another, with an upwards bullish crossover somewhat imminent. Ethereum was also marginally higher today.
 
Bitcoin
 
Bitcoin (BTC) jumped back above $28,000 on Tuesday, with a possible death cross signaling upcoming bullish momentum.
 
BTC/USD hit a peak of $28,044.76 today, following a low at $27,563.88 earlier in the session.
 
Today’s move led to bitcoin remaining close to a three-week high at $28,473, which was marginally below a ceiling at $28,500.
 
 
Looking at the chart, Tuesday’s rebound comes as the relative strength index (RSI) remained above a floor at 53.00
 
At the time of writing, the index is now tracking at 54.29, with a ceiling of 57.00 still a possible target for current bulls.
 
As the session has progressed, earlier gains have somewhat slipped, as market uncertainty remains high.
 
 
Ethereum
 
Ethereum (ETH) was relatively more stable during today’s session, remaining above $1,900 for the majority of the day.
 
Following a low of $1,879.08 on Tuesday, ETH/USD raced to an intraday high of $1,916.57, as the session matured.
 
Similar to BTC, this move saw ethereum continue to track close to its strongest point since May 8.
 
 
An upwards crossover of the 10-day (red) and 25-day (blue) moving averages has already occurred, which could likely entice further bulls to reenter the market.
 
In the event this happens, a ceiling at $1,930 will be one of the last points of resistance preventing a move above $2,000.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
Could we see ethereum & bitcoin make significant gains in June? Leave your thoughts in the comments below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining Difficulty’s Record Setting Streak Shows No Signs of Stopping]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7500754b93</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/05/30/bitcoin-mining-difficultys-record-setting-streak-shows-no-signs-of-stopping/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T13:23:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The difficulty of mining bitcoin is poised to set a new all-time high this week as miners continue to deploy new mining machines to cash in on recent spike in revenue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliza Gkritsi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Exchange bitFlyer Aligns Itself With FATF 'Travel Rule' With New Restrictions]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7500754b87</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/05/30/crypto-exchange-bitflyer-aligns-itself-with-fatf-travel-rule-with-new-restrictions/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T13:23:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company is only allowing crypto and transfers to platforms that comply with Coinbase-led Travel Rule Universal Solution Technology (TRUST).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandali Handagama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia Overtakes Meta, Tesla by Market Cap as Firm Captures AI Hype]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142805</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142805/nvidia-overtakes-meta-tesla-market-cap-firm-captures-ai-hype"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T12:57:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Nvidia edges towards the trillion-dollar club on the back of AI, it’s now more valuable than some of the market’s biggest names.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gabe Nikias</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Mover Americas: Bitcoin on Track for First Monthly Loss of the Year]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75007e5d6f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/05/30/first-mover-americas-bitcoin-on-track-for-first-monthly-loss-of-the-year/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T12:24:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest price moves in bitcoin (BTC) and crypto markets in context for May 30, 2023. First Mover is CoinDesk’s daily newsletter that contextualizes the latest actions in the crypto markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lyllah Ledesma, Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[India's RBI Intends to Push G-20 to Focus on Crypto's Macro Risks]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75007f3d8c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/05/30/indias-rbi-intends-to-push-g-20-to-focus-on-cryptos-macro-risks/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T12:19:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[India's central bank is trying to expand the global narrative around cryptocurrencies beyond "financial stability and integrity to macro-financial and cross-sectoral implications and risks of crypto-assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amitoj Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain-Based Render Network's Token Tracks Tech Stocks as Broader Crypto Market Decouples]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75007f3d73</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/05/30/render-networks-rndr-token-tracks-tech-stocks-as-broader-crypto-market-decouples/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T12:19:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RNDR has been a good high beta Nasdaq play in recent weeks, one portfolio manager noted.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Sharks & Whales Have Bought 93,000 BTC Since April Top: Santiment]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750079ec52</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-sharks-whales-bought-93000-btc-april-top/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T12:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data from Santiment shows that Bitcoin sharks and whales have gone on a 93,000 BTC buying spree since the local top back in April.
 
Bitcoin Sharks & Whales Have Accumulated Since The April Top
 
According to data from the on-chain analytics firm Santiment, these holders have become a bit more cautious in the last few weeks. The relevant indicator here is the “Supply Distribution,” which measures the total amount of Bitcoin that each wallet group in the market is holding right now.
 
The addresses are divided into wallet groups based on the total number of coins that they are carrying in their balances currently. The 1-10 coins cohort, for example, includes all investors that are holding at least 1 and at most 10 BTC.
 
In the context of the current discussion, there are two inves…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hououin Kyouma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bali Government Cracks Down on Crypto Payments by Foreign Tourists]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7500659638</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bali-government-cracks-down-on-crypto-payments-by-foreign-tourists/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T11:36:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The government of Bali, Indonesia, is cracking down on the use of cryptocurrency as a means of payment by foreign tourists. “Strict actions range from deportation, administrative sanctions, criminal penalties, closure of business premises, and other tough sanctions,” said the governor of Bali.
 
Strict Penalties Imposed for Foreign Tourists Using Crypto in Bali, Warns Governor
 
The Bali provincial government is cracking down on the use of cryptocurrency as a means of payment by foreign tourists in hotels, restaurants, shopping centers, and various other establishments, according to a report from the Antara Indonesian News Agency.
 
Bali Governor Wayan Koster said at the Bali tourism development press conference Sunday:
 

Foreign tourists who behave inappropriately, do activities that are…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USDC Backing Maker’s Stablecoin DAI Plummets to 23%]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142801</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142801/usdc-backing-makers-stablecoin-dai-plummets"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T11:20:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The decentralized stablecoin DAI is undergoing a massive shift as MakerDAO reduces USDC exposure and opts for U.S. Treasury bills.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Trades at 18% Discount on Binance Australia as Exchange Cuts On-Ramp]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142799</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142799/bitcoin-discount-emerges-binance-australia-as-exchange-cuts-ramp-services"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T09:19:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Australia's impending on-ramp service suspension has triggered a steep fall in Bitcoin's value in Australian Dollars.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russia Drops Plans for State-Run Crypto Exchange]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142784</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142784/russia-drops-plans-for-state-run-crypto-exchange"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T22:24:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After sending mixed signals, the government may be more willing to work with the cryptocurrency industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 Can Help Marginalized Communities Share Their Stories: Jordan Bayne]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142763</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142763/web3-can-help-marginalized-communities-share-their-stories-jordan-bayne"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T19:43:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The award-winning filmmaker says blockchain tech provides a powerful way for artists to connect with audiences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PancakeSwap Launches Tower Defense Game—With CAKE Token Rewards]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142762</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142762/you-can-earn-cake-crypto-by-playing-pancake-protectors"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T19:23:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pancake Protectors enlists the CAKE token to lure new users to Web3 gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet the Crypto Rich Who Want to Live Forever: Inside Vitalik's Zuzalu]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142530</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142530/meet-crypto-rich-who-want-live-forever-inside-vitaliks-zuzalu"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T17:19:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zuzalu attendees tell Decrypt about the secretive two-month gathering of tech leaders in a Montenegrin seaside town, which ended last week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scientists Develop New Antibiotic To Kill Superbug Using AI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142739</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142739/scientists-develop-new-antibiotic-to-kill-superbug-using-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T16:07:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Machine learning enabled scientists to rapidly screen thousands of molecules to find a new antibacterial compound.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unioverse Game Preview: Hands-on With the Cinematic Proving Grounds]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/t68sovuN/unioverse-game-preview-hands-on-with-the-cinematic-proving-grounds</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/t68sovuN/unioverse-game-preview-hands-on-with-the-cinematic-proving-grounds"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Unioverse is a multimedia sci-fi franchise with plans to facilitate user-generated content. Decrypt reporter and GG producer Kate Irwin checked out the Unioverse as Reyu, an alien character, and navigated the Proving Grounds with him. In the Proving Grounds, you'll fight an array of different drone-like flying robots (some have tentacles!!) as you navigate the puzzle-like dystopian environment. Alien meets Portal, anyone?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Square Enix to Ubisoft: The Biggest Publishers Building NFT Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142527</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142527/from-square-enix-to-ubisoft-the-biggest-publishers-building-nft-games"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T14:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The makers of Final Fantasy and Assassin's Creed, respectively, are leading the charge for traditional game publishers building in Web3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Debt Ceiling Deal Blocks 30% Bitcoin Mining Tax: Congressman]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142711</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142711/us-debt-ceiling-deal-blocks-30-bitcoin-mining-tax-congressman"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T11:01:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The proposed Digital Asset Mining Energy tax has reportedly been taken off the table, according to U.S. Congressman Warren Davidson.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bali Tells Tourists: Don’t Pay With Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142720</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142720/bali-tells-tourists-dont-pay-with-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T10:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Local authorities have warned that tourists who attempt to use crypto as a means of payment will be "dealt with firmly."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alys Key</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Touches $28,000 as U.S. Debt Ceiling Deal Heads to Congress]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142712</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142712/bitcoin-touches-28000-as-u-s-debt-ceiling-deal-heads-to-congress"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T10:14:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stock market indices rose to new yearly highs, while cryptocurrencies saw positive gains as risk-on sentiments returned.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Americans May Not Love Crypto, But These Top Brands Are Into It]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142698</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142698/americans-may-not-love-crypto-but-these-top-brands-are-into-it"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T04:28:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chick-Fil-A, Toyota, Pfizer and Samsung are among the Top 100 brands to explore the cryptocurrency space.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin and Ethereum Rise as U.S. Lawmakers Scramble to Dodge Historic Debt Default]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142689</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142689/bitcoin-ethereum-rise-avoid-debt-ceiling-default"/>
        <updated>2023-05-28T22:47:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The potential compromise comes as America’s “X-date” approaches quickly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 May Flip ‘Content Consumption on its Head,’ but Still Needs Traditional Media: MyCo Co-Founder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142687</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142687/web3-may-flip-content-consumption-on-its-head-but-still-needs-traditional-media-myco-co-founder"/>
        <updated>2023-05-28T20:57:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The streaming platform’s content lead said Web3 is still far from mainstream—and yields a unique opportunity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week on Crypto Twitter: Shaq Served with Two Crypto Lawsuits on Same Day]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142671</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142671/this-week-on-crypto-twitter-shaq-served-two-crypto-lawsuits-fake-ai-news"/>
        <updated>2023-05-28T19:44:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some viral fake news in the form of an AI-generated explosion at the Pentagon briefly tanked Bitcoin’s price on Monday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Earn Bitcoin by Playing Mobile Solitaire Games—Here's How Much]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142635</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142635/you-can-earn-bitcoin-by-playing-mobile-solitaire-games-heres-how-much"/>
        <updated>2023-05-27T22:10:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[REVIEW: These iPhone and Android solitaire games reward you with real Bitcoin. We picked the best of the bunch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Bitcoin and Ethereum See Fourth Flat Week as TRON and Tether Surge]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142627</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142627/this-week-in-coins-bitcoin-ethereum-fourth-flat-week-tron-tether-surge"/>
        <updated>2023-05-27T18:51:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Republican presidential hopeful Ron DeSantis touched on cryptocurrencies in his Twitter Space with Elon Musk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Social Tokens Finally Click? Stealcam Is Betting on It]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142543</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142543/will-social-tokens-finally-click-stealcam-friendtech"/>
        <updated>2023-05-27T13:22:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Steal to reveal" platform Stealcam is rebranding and shifting gears. Can Friend.tech finally crack the social token model for creators?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When DAOs Self-Execute—What Could Go Wrong?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142499</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142499/when-daos-self-execute-what-could-go-wrong"/>
        <updated>2023-05-27T12:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Self-executing DAO proposals are the pinnacle of autonomy for decentralized communities. Still, the feature comes with a lot of baggage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former EverQuest Lead: Games Must Be Co-Created With Players]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142554</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142554/former-everquest-lead-games-must-co-created-players"/>
        <updated>2023-05-26T22:14:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avalon's Jeffrey Butler says that the future of gaming, including the metaverse, will require players to co-create and be rewarded for it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not Just Nvidia: These Are the Other Big Winners in the AI Chip Biz]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142568</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142568/nvidia-big-winners-ai-chip-biz-tech-stocks"/>
        <updated>2023-05-26T21:44:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[COVID-19 was hell for tech stock and chip manufacturers. But AI has now flipped the script. Here are the companies benefiting the most so far.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JP Morgan Files Patent for ChatGPT Finance Clone, IndexGPT]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142577</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142577/jp-morgan-files-patent-for-chatgpt-finance-clone-indexgpt"/>
        <updated>2023-05-26T21:04:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bot would give financial advice on securities, investments, and monetary affairs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EverQuest Producer Jeffrey Butler on How Ready Player One Led Him to Web3 Project Avalon]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/fdmq9t7l/everquest-producer-jeffrey-butler-on-how-ready-player-one-led-him-to-web3-project-avalon</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/fdmq9t7l/everquest-producer-jeffrey-butler-on-how-ready-player-one-led-him-to-web3-project-avalon"/>
        <updated>2023-05-26T21:02:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jeffrey Butler started his game development career producing EverQuest. Now, he's Avalon's Chief Product Officer. Butler told Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how he wants to create a customizable world where users can create their own worlds and in-game content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There's Now a Dollar-Backed Stablecoin on Bitcoin Using Ordinals Protocol]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142548</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142548/usd-backed-stablecoin-on-bitcoin-using-ordinals-protocol"/>
        <updated>2023-05-26T20:16:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stably debuted Stably USD in 2019. It's got a $7 million market capitalization across 11 blockchains, according to its April attestation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grand Theft Auto 6 Crypto Rumors Are Swirling Again—Here’s What’s Going On]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142533</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142533/grand-theft-auto-6-crypto-rumors-swirling-again-heres-whats-going-on"/>
        <updated>2023-05-26T18:07:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rumors suggest that Rockstar Games' anticipated Grand Theft Auto 6 will feature cryptocurrency. Is there any truth to the claims?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Esports Orgs Should Become More Like Tech Companies: Community Gaming CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/t27ac1ik/esports-orgs-should-become-more-like-tech-companies-community-gaming-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/t27ac1ik/esports-orgs-should-become-more-like-tech-companies-community-gaming-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-05-26T16:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Community Gaming CEO and 3XP conference organizer Chris Gonsalves believes crypto and tech could rejuvenate and reinvent the esports industry. In an interview, he tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin why he thinks esports organizations should shake up their approach.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[European Securities Regulator Raises Concerns Over Crypto Products Ahead of MiCA Rollout]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142518</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142518/esma-raises-concerns-unregulated-crypto-products-mica-rollout"/>
        <updated>2023-05-26T13:44:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite the adoption of MiCA, ESMA said today firms must still label crypto offerings as unregulated until the framework is implemented.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Expects to Launch New Thai Crypto Exchange in Q4 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142511</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142511/binance-expectslaunch-new-thai-crypto-exchange-q4-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-05-26T13:21:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After landing a crypto operator's license in Thailand today, Binance Gulf is expected to open its doors at the end of this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum, Bitcoin Balances on Exchanges Edges Toward 5-Year Low]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142507</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142507/ethereum-bitcoin-balances-exchanges-edges-5-year-lows"/>
        <updated>2023-05-26T13:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The collapse of FTX, the rise in self-custody interest, and Ethereum’s latest upgrade appear to be fueling the latest exchange exodus.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Exchange Gemini Turns to Ireland for European Headquarters]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142500</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142500/crypto-exchange-gemini-turns-ireland-european-headquarters"/>
        <updated>2023-05-26T09:58:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amid increasing regulatory pressure in the U.S., the Winklevoss twins see the Emerald Isle as an “entry point” into the rest of Europe.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Hold Ground as $3.5 Billion in Options Expire]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142493</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142493/bitcoin-ethereum-hold-ground-3-5b-options-expiry-event"/>
        <updated>2023-05-26T09:17:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With billions in Bitcoin and Ethereum options expiring today, analysts expected the worst.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's the Environmental Impact of Generative AI Tools?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142483</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142483/whats-environmental-impact-generative-ai-tools"/>
        <updated>2023-05-26T02:36:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Will ChatGPT and other generative AI tools make an outsized impact on the planet? Maybe—but there's reason for optimism, too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ordinals Is Drawing Former Ethereum Devs to Build on Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142439</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142439/ordinals-draws-ethereum-devs-to-build-on-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-05-26T01:19:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The buzzy Bitcoin protocol is attracting talent from across the Web3 ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ubisoft's Rabbids Invade Reddit as Free NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142438</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142438/ubisoft-rabbids-invade-reddit-free-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T23:40:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reddit released a limited quantity of free Rabbids avatar NFTs and users are scooping them up, with multiple varieties already depleted.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mojo Melee Game Preview: Hands-on With the Casual Web3 Auto Battler]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LtI7u3W0/mojo-melee-game-preview-hands-on-with-the-casual-web3-auto-battler</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LtI7u3W0/mojo-melee-game-preview-hands-on-with-the-casual-web3-auto-battler"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T23:02:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mojo Melee is an auto battler game that offers Polygon NFTs. Decrypt contributor Ryan S. Gladwin playtested the game in beta and offers his thoughts on the gameplay experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No Virginia, Ron DeSantis's Campaign Didn't Alter His Video With AI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142455</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142455/no-virginia-ron-desantiss-campaign-didnt-alter-his-video-with-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T22:56:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[They used good old-fashioned digital editing tools instead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mojo Melee Puts a Casual Spin on Teamfight Tactics-Style Auto Battlers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142432</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142432/mojo-melee-puts-casual-spin-teamfight-tactics-style-auto-battlers"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T22:46:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PREVIEW: The NFT-infused Mojo Melee is simple in its beta state, but that makes it a good introduction to a complex genre.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Governments Need to 'Move Faster' on AI Rules, Says Microsoft President]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142430</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142430/governments-need-move-faster-ai-rules-says-microsoft-president"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T21:37:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft President Brad Smith is the latest tech leader to call for government AI regulation, but says companies have a role too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How 3XP Plans to Reshape Crypto's Reputation Among Gamers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/dJRkJI2l/how-3xp-plans-to-reshape-cryptos-reputation-among-gamers</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/dJRkJI2l/how-3xp-plans-to-reshape-cryptos-reputation-among-gamers"/>
        <updated>2023-05-24T14:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Community Gaming CEO and 3XP organizer Chris Gonsalves tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the first 3XP video game conference, which aims to bring together fans of crypto-enabled video games, influencers, game developers, blockchain firms, and gamers under one roof in Pasadena, California from June 8-9, 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mark Otero Shares Why a16z Invested in Azra Games' Approach to Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/auPCxWfY/mark-otero-shares-why-a16z-invested-in-azra-games-approach-to-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/auPCxWfY/mark-otero-shares-why-a16z-invested-in-azra-games-approach-to-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-05-23T17:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is Azra Games' approach to NFTs in gaming? Azra Games CEO Mark Otero shares his vision and why he believes his approach was a key reason Azra received investment from venture capital firms like Andreessen Horowitz (a16z).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Funding Web3 Film Calladita With Traditional Systems 'Wasn't Working', Says Director Miguel Faus]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yJ4pf6MZ/funding-web3-film-calladita-with-traditional-systems-wasnt-working-says-director-miguel-faus</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yJ4pf6MZ/funding-web3-film-calladita-with-traditional-systems-wasnt-working-says-director-miguel-faus"/>
        <updated>2023-05-23T17:35:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spanish Film Director Miguel Faus talks with Decrypt about how he financed his movie “Calladita” with NFTs. In his view, Web3 and blockchain allow creators to get around some of the key difficulties present in the traditional movie industry, specifically finding funding.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Web3 Offers Something Hollywood Does Not': Film3 Pioneer, Filmmaker Jordan Bayne]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JBxcmUQf/web3-offers-something-hollywood-does-not-film3-pioneer-filmmaker-jordan-bayne</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JBxcmUQf/web3-offers-something-hollywood-does-not-film3-pioneer-filmmaker-jordan-bayne"/>
        <updated>2023-05-23T16:57:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Film3 pioneer, Metacannes and The Squad founder, Jordan Bayne discusses the advantages that crypto offers to filmmakers, notably owning their work's IP throughout the entire creation, production, and distribution processes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Film3 Offers 'a Whole Bunch of Independent Filmmakers' Hope, Says First Flights Co-founder Nick Sadler]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/NfeY8QGu/film3-offers-a-whole-bunch-of-independent-filmmakers-hope-says-first-flights-co-founder-nick-sadler</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/NfeY8QGu/film3-offers-a-whole-bunch-of-independent-filmmakers-hope-says-first-flights-co-founder-nick-sadler"/>
        <updated>2023-05-23T16:56:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[First Flights co-founder Nick Sadler sat down with Decrypt at this year's MetaCannes festival to discuss how Web3 can support independent filmmakers by leveraging its unique blockchain-powered crowdfunding platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Film3 Movement 'Doesn't Need Competitors, it Needs Collaborators': Bingeable CEO, Founder Stephen Murray]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/nv8Knuvw/the-film3-movement-doesnt-need-competitors-it-needs-collaborators-bingeable-ceo-founder-stephen-murray</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/nv8Knuvw/the-film3-movement-doesnt-need-competitors-it-needs-collaborators-bingeable-ceo-founder-stephen-murray"/>
        <updated>2023-05-23T16:52:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Founder and CEO of Bingeable Stephen Murray unpacks how creators and filmmakers can lower the barriers for audiences to connect with their work. "Within two clicks on hearing about the movie, you're watching it," he told Decrypt at this year's MetaCannes festival.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt Learn: Defining The Web3 Stack]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/33Mc05zz/decrypt-learn-defining-the-web3-stack</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/33Mc05zz/decrypt-learn-defining-the-web3-stack"/>
        <updated>2023-05-23T12:55:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this video, part of Infura’s Web3 Dev Series, you’ll learn how to define the web3 stack in order to build full stack decentralized applications. Author: Clarissa Watson, Senior Writer at ConsenSys.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Web3 Creates a Tighter Bond' Between Audiences, Creators: MyCo CCO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OthLPXDN/web3-creates-a-tighter-bond-between-audiences-creators-myco-cco</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OthLPXDN/web3-creates-a-tighter-bond-between-audiences-creators-myco-cco"/>
        <updated>2023-05-23T08:07:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MyCo’s streaming platform CCO Phil McKenzie talks with Decrypt about the Film3 movement and the Metacannes festival he helped to organize occurring alongside the Festival de Cannes. He explains how Web3 can help creators to find funding and create new ways to interact with the audience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Immutable's Chris Clay: Crypto Can Solve the 'Dreaded Rollback' in MMORPGs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Dg9am6Ro/immutables-chris-clay-crypto-can-solve-the-dreaded-rollback-in-mmorpgs</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Dg9am6Ro/immutables-chris-clay-crypto-can-solve-the-dreaded-rollback-in-mmorpgs"/>
        <updated>2023-05-22T15:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Immutable VP and Gods Unchained Game Director Chris Clay tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about how Immutable is actually immutable—and how that changes everything for both developers and players.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gary Vee Discusses the Rise and Impact of AI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/E2erJr3t/gary-vee-discusses-the-rise-and-impact-of-ai</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/E2erJr3t/gary-vee-discusses-the-rise-and-impact-of-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-05-20T16:46:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During VeeCon 2023, entrepreneur spoke with Decrypt's Andrew Hayward about the rise of AI tools, what excites him about the technology, and what kind of impact he thinks it will have on creators and business.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gary Vee Discusses VeeCon 2023's Broader Shift Beyond Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/FqIm7PfV/gary-vee-discusses-veecon-2023s-broader-shift-beyond-web3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/FqIm7PfV/gary-vee-discusses-veecon-2023s-broader-shift-beyond-web3"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T20:25:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VeeCon is back in 2023, moving from Minneapolis to Indianapolis, and creator and entrepreneur Gary Vaynerchuk joined Decrypt's Andrew Hayward to discuss his aim to make it the "coolest business conference in the world." And that means expanding the focus beyond NFTs and Web3 to include AI and other tech innovations, along with broader business and pop culture content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gary Vee on the NFT Market and Why 'NFTs Are Stuffed Animals']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Sij5GHus/gary-vee-on-the-nft-market-and-why-nfts-are-stuffed-animals</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Sij5GHus/gary-vee-on-the-nft-market-and-why-nfts-are-stuffed-animals"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T20:25:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gary Vaynerchuk called the NFT market decline back in 2021, but the owner of CryptoPunks and other valuable tokenized assets still believes that a sustainable market will eventually form. He joins Decrypt's Andrew Hayward amid VeeCon 2023 to discuss why he thinks the NFT space will be comparable to collectible sports cards, art, and even stuffed animals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Immutable's Chris Clay Learned in 23 Years of Game Development]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/lpOWjBfU/what-immutables-chris-clay-learned-in-23-years-of-game-development</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/lpOWjBfU/what-immutables-chris-clay-learned-in-23-years-of-game-development"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T20:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Immutable VP & Gods Unchained Game Director Chris Clay tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about what it's like to work in the game industry for decades and why he's not giving up on NFT games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Azra Games CEO Mark Otero is Not a Fan of "Play-to-Earn" Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/F08xddFc/why-azra-games-ceo-mark-otero-is-not-a-fan-of-play-to-earn-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/F08xddFc/why-azra-games-ceo-mark-otero-is-not-a-fan-of-play-to-earn-games"/>
        <updated>2023-05-18T16:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Each game is a miracle," says Azra Games CEO Mark Otero. In this clip, he shares his thoughts on "play-to-earn" games and gamer motivation with Decrypt's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>