<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-12-17T08:17:40.067Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-12-17T08:17:40.067Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analyst Who Caught Crypto Rally Earlier This Year Unveils Roadmap for Bitcoin Surge to $110,000 – Here’s His Timeline]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19114755/Analyst-Who-Caught-Crypto-Rally-Earlier-This-Year-Unveils-Roadmap-for-Bitcoin-Surge-to-110000-Heres-His-Timeline</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19114755/Analyst-Who-Caught-Crypto-Rally-Earlier-This-Year-Unveils-Roadmap-for-Bitcoin-Surge-to-110000-Heres-His-Timeline"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T08:04:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A top analyst who accurately called Bitcoin’s (BTC) 2022 price floor is laying out a price path for the crypto king to hit a new all-time high of $110,000. In a new strategy session, pseudonymous analyst DonAlt tells his 55,400 YouTube subscribers that he sees Bitcoin igniting a parabolic ascent...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Bitcoin NFTs Break Network? Analyst Warns of Stress, Hash War]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19114743/Will-Bitcoin-NFTs-Break-Network-Analyst-Warns-of-Stress-Hash-War</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19114743/Will-Bitcoin-NFTs-Break-Network-Analyst-Warns-of-Stress-Hash-War"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T07:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent tweet, a renowned Bitcoin analyst with X username “MDB” shared a mixed perspective on the growing trend of Bitcoin ordinal inscriptions, otherwise called NFTs, arguing potential stress test and hash war. According to MDB, Bitcoin ordinals, which grant users the ability to store extra...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VanEck CEO Managing $76 Billion Predicts All-Time High Date for Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19114739/VanEck-CEO-Managing-76-Billion-Predicts-All-Time-High-Date-for-Bitcoin-BTC-Price</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19114739/VanEck-CEO-Managing-76-Billion-Predicts-All-Time-High-Date-for-Bitcoin-BTC-Price"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T07:44:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VanEck CEO Jan van Eck made important evaluations about Bitcoin in the TV program he attended. Continue Reading: VanEck CEO Managing $76 Billion Predicts All-Time High Date for Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These Are the Cardano (ADA) Price Predictions to Watch in 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19114736/These-Are-the-Cardano-ADA-Price-Predictions-to-Watch-in-2024</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19114736/These-Are-the-Cardano-ADA-Price-Predictions-to-Watch-in-2024"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T07:43:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some analysts believe ADA could surpass the $10 level shortly after the BTC Halving in 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mapping Ethereum’s prediction as whales rally to save prices]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19114728/Mapping-Ethereums-prediction-as-whales-rally-to-save-prices</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19114728/Mapping-Ethereums-prediction-as-whales-rally-to-save-prices"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T07:30:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even as Ethereum’s price witnesses a drop, whales accumulate over 100,000 ETH.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spot Bitcoin ETFs Approval Window Opens in Less Than 20 Days]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19114723/Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-Approval-Window-Opens-in-Less-Than-20-Days</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19114723/Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-Approval-Window-Opens-in-Less-Than-20-Days"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T07:12:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The window for the approval of spot Bitcoin ETFs will open in less than 20 days, and the cryptocurrency influencer, Crypto Rover, has posted a list of the pending ETF filings with their respective details. In a recent post on X (formerly Twitter), the renowned influencer shared a tabulated...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Lawmakers Slam SEC and Chair Gensler for Refusing to Provide Clear Regulation for Crypto Industry]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748e2ad769</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/us-lawmakers-slam-sec-and-chair-gensler-for-refusing-to-provide-clear-regulation-for-crypto-industry/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T07:04:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. lawmakers have slammed the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and its chairman Gary Gensler for refusing to provide clear crypto regulation. “SEC Chair Gary Gensler’s continued refusal to provide clarity for the digital asset ecosystem is shameful,” one congressman said. “The SEC’s policy to provide less clarity to the marketplace instead of more is designed to create chaos and it will corrupt our great capital markets,” another opined.
 
Lawmakers Concerned About SEC’s Refusal to Provide Clarity for Crypto Ecosystem
 
U.S. Representatives Patrick McHenry (R-NC) and Tom Emmer criticized the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and its Chairman Gary Gensler on Friday after the SEC denied Coinbase’s petition for clear crypto regulation.
 
Following Gensler’s statement in …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tap Protocol Secures $4.2M Funding for Bitcoin OrdFi Innovation]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19114697/Tap-Protocol-Secures-42M-Funding-for-Bitcoin-OrdFi-Innovation</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19114697/Tap-Protocol-Secures-42M-Funding-for-Bitcoin-OrdFi-Innovation"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T06:41:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tap Protocol, a key innovator in the Bitcoin network, has completed a $4.2 million funding round, led by Sora Ventures. The significant financial boost positions Tap Protocol for substantial growth in the Bitcoin ecosystem. The funding round attracted an impressive array of venture capital firms...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Unplugged – Insights on AI and Demographics at Italian Summit]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19114698/Elon-Musk-Unplugged-Insights-on-AI-and-Demographics-at-Italian-Summit</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19114698/Elon-Musk-Unplugged-Insights-on-AI-and-Demographics-at-Italian-Summit"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T06:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the weekend, Tesla’s enigmatic CEO, Elon Musk, took center stage at the Italian “Atreju” political conference, where he engaged in a thought-provoking interview with il Giornale deputy editor Nicola Porro. Musk, known for his pioneering role in technology and his unfiltered insights, delved...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yield Guild Games and Ubisoft Forge a New Era in Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19114677/Yield-Guild-Games-and-Ubisoft-Forge-a-New-Era-in-Gaming</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19114677/Yield-Guild-Games-and-Ubisoft-Forge-a-New-Era-in-Gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T05:57:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yield Guild Games, a key player in the realm of digital gaming, has announced a strategic partnership with Ubisoft, a titan in the gaming world. The collaboration is centered around Ubisoft’s innovative venture into the blockchain gaming sphere with Champions Tactics, a player-versus-player...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Surge in Highly Pathogenic Avian Influenza Cases Hits South Korean Poultry Farms]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19114674/Surge-in-Highly-Pathogenic-Avian-Influenza-Cases-Hits-South-Korean-Poultry-Farms</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19114674/Surge-in-Highly-Pathogenic-Avian-Influenza-Cases-Hits-South-Korean-Poultry-Farms"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T05:48:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amid mounting concerns over the increasing spread of highly pathogenic avian influenza (AI) in South Korea, the poultry industry faces a serious challenge. The number of confirmed cases of H5 AI infection in poultry farms has surged to 20, prompting swift action from authorities to curb the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Evolution of AI in Fighter Jets: Shaping the Future of Aerial Combat]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19114672/The-Evolution-of-AI-in-Fighter-Jets-Shaping-the-Future-of-Aerial-Combat</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19114672/The-Evolution-of-AI-in-Fighter-Jets-Shaping-the-Future-of-Aerial-Combat"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T05:34:28.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Venom Foundation Announces Operational Wind-Down in ADGM]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19114667/Venom-Foundation-Announces-Operational-Wind-Down-in-ADGM</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19114667/Venom-Foundation-Announces-Operational-Wind-Down-in-ADGM"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T05:29:47.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Goldman Sachs: Don’t Expect Immediate BTC Spike After Spot Bitcoin ETF Approvals]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748e13b24c</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/goldman-sachs-dont-expect-immediate-btc-spike-after-spot-bitcoin-etf-approvals/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T05:05:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Global investment bank Goldman Sachs has advised investors against anticipating a sudden and immediate surge in the price of bitcoin upon the approval of spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). Nonetheless, Goldman Sachs highlighted that the “ability to actually transact a product that people are familiar with and can provide scale” is “very positive.”
 
Goldman on Spot Bitcoin ETF Hype
 
Global investment bank Goldman Sachs does not anticipate an immediate surge in BTC prices following the approval of spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), Mathew McDermott, head of the digital asset unit at Goldman Sachs, told Reuters this week.
 
While emphasizing that he does not expect the a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evernode (EVERS) Reschedules Mainnet Launch for January 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19114649/Evernode-EVERS-Reschedules-Mainnet-Launch-for-January-2024</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19114649/Evernode-EVERS-Reschedules-Mainnet-Launch-for-January-2024"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T04:50:04.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US DOJ Charges 4 Individuals for Laundering Over $80M From Crypto Investment Scams]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19114644/US-DOJ-Charges-4-Individuals-for-Laundering-Over-80M-From-Crypto-Investment-Scams</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19114644/US-DOJ-Charges-4-Individuals-for-Laundering-Over-80M-From-Crypto-Investment-Scams"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T04:38:38.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How RAND and Billionaires Influenced Biden’s AI Executive Order – Report Claims]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19114640/How-RAND-and-Billionaires-Influenced-Bidens-AI-Executive-Order-Report-Claims</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19114640/How-RAND-and-Billionaires-Influenced-Bidens-AI-Executive-Order-Report-Claims"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T04:20:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an unprecedented disclosure, a recent report suggests that the RAND Corporation, a well-known nonprofit think tank, has wielded considerable influence in shaping President Joe Biden’s recent AI executive order. This disclosure comes from an AI researcher familiar with the situation, claiming...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Revolutionizing Oil Exploration – AI Digital Twinning Tech Set to Transform E&P Operations]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19114632/Revolutionizing-Oil-Exploration-AI-Digital-Twinning-Tech-Set-to-Transform-EP-Operations</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19114632/Revolutionizing-Oil-Exploration-AI-Digital-Twinning-Tech-Set-to-Transform-EP-Operations"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T03:41:17.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ice-T Envisions Endless Acting Stint with AI Technology]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19114611/Ice-T-Envisions-Endless-Acting-Stint-with-AI-Technology</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19114611/Ice-T-Envisions-Endless-Acting-Stint-with-AI-Technology"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T03:19:36.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Denies Coinbase’s Petition for Clear Crypto Regulation — Exchange Responds by Taking the Regulator to Court]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748e1b6c0c</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/sec-denies-coinbases-petition-for-clear-crypto-regulation-exchange-responds-by-taking-the-regulator-to-court/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T03:08:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has rejected cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase’s petition for regulatory clarity in the crypto industry. SEC Chairman Gary Gensler backs his agency’s decision to deny Coinbase’s petition. In response, Coinbase has pursued legal action against the securities regulator to challenge this decision.
 
Coinbase Challenging SEC’s Decision in Court
 
The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has denied Coinbase Global’s Petition for Rulemaking. The crypto exchange filed the petition in July last year, seeking regulatory clarity, including “potential rules to identify which digital assets are securities.” With no response from the SEC for 18 months, the crypto exchange escalated the matter to court, prompting the agency to respond with the de…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Councilwoman-Elect Susan Zhuang Acknowledges AI-Generated Responses in Communication with Constituents and Media]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19114601/Councilwoman-Elect-Susan-Zhuang-Acknowledges-AI-Generated-Responses-in-Communication-with-Constituents-and-Media</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19114601/Councilwoman-Elect-Susan-Zhuang-Acknowledges-AI-Generated-Responses-in-Communication-with-Constituents-and-Media"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T02:57:16.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano: Can a high development activity really help ADA]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19114596/Cardano-Can-a-high-development-activity-really-help-ADA</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19114596/Cardano-Can-a-high-development-activity-really-help-ADA"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T02:30:45.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blackrock Meets With SEC 4 Times to Discuss Spot Bitcoin ETF Application]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748e036825</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/blackrock-meets-with-sec-4-times-to-discuss-spot-bitcoin-etf-application/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T01:06:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blackrock, the world’s largest asset manager, has met with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) for the fourth time recently to discuss its spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) application. SEC Chairman Gary Gensler said this week that the securities regulator is “taking a new look” at spot bitcoin ETF filings.
 
Blackrock Holds Another Meeting With SEC
 
The expectation of the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) approving spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) has intensified this week as several spot bitcoin ETF issuers engage in discussions with the securities regulator regarding their applications. Notably, Blackrock, the world’s largest asset manager, has held its fourth recent meeting with the SEC concerning its spot bitcoin ETF proposal.
 
According to a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$2,300,000,000 Cash Handout Coming to Residents in This US State, if Governor Has His Way: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19114563/2300000000-Cash-Handout-Coming-to-Residents-in-This-US-State-if-Governor-Has-His-Way-Report</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19114563/2300000000-Cash-Handout-Coming-to-Residents-in-This-US-State-if-Governor-Has-His-Way-Report"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T01:04:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the largest oil-producing states in the US is reportedly planning to give away billions of dollars as a measure to help people keep up with inflation. Alaska Governor Mike Dunleavy recently revealed a budget plan for next year that would allocate $2.3 billion to the state’s Permanent Fund...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Safemoon Files for Chapter 7 Bankruptcy Protection Amid Securities and Wire Fraud Charges]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748e0996c0</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/safemoon-files-for-chapter-7-bankruptcy-protection-amid-securities-and-wire-fraud-charges/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T23:37:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the latest development, Safemoon, a crypto company, voluntarily initiated Chapter 7 bankruptcy proceedings in the District of Utah, as stated in their bankruptcy documentation. This action comes on the heels of the company’s founders facing indictment for securities fraud, wire fraud, and money laundering by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission and Department of Justice last month.
 
Safemoon US Files Chapter 7; SFM Token Plummets
 
On December 14, 2023, Safemoon US, LLC, the entity behind the safemoon.com website, lodged a Chapter 7 bankruptcy petition in Utah. This type of bankruptcy, often referred to as “liquidation,” necessitates selling the debtor’s nonexempt assets to settle debts with creditors.
 
For a business such as Safemoon, Chapter 7 bankruptcy signifies halting all…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto App Shakepay Reveals Data Breach Affecting a ‘Small Number’ of Customers]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748ff02c80</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/crypto-app-shakepay-reveals-data-breach-affecting-a-small-number-of-customers/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T22:06:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent announcement, Shakepay, the Canadian crypto app, disclosed a data breach involving unauthorized access to personal information of a select group of its customers. The breach, detected on Dec. 13, 2023, compromised data but did not affect any bank accounts, crypto wallets, or customer credentials.
 
Shakepay Addresses Data Breach Concerns, Offers Free Credit Monitoring to Impacted Users
 
The breach at Shakepay, which offers commission-free services for trading bitcoin (BTC) and ethereum (ETH), was identified following unusual activity on an employee’s work device. Shakepay’s security team quickly responded, deauthenticating and removing the compromised device from their network. This action was part of the company’s incident response protocol, aimed at minimizing the impact of …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Team Member Addresses Questions Of When Massive $1.2 Million In SHIB Will Be Burned]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748ff042cd</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-team-1-2-million-burned/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T22:05:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A member of the Shiba Inu (SHIB) team has come out to provide an update to the community following a ‘failed promise’. This comes as the team has come under fire for failing to carry out certain transactions that could have been bullish for SHIB’s price.
 
Shiba Inu Team Addresses Burns Delay
 
In a post on his X (formerly Twitter) platform, Digarch shared an update on the SHIB burns from the Shibarium development team. The post contained a screenshotted Telegram message from DaVinci, who highlighted the fact that the burn didn’t take place as scheduled. He further mentioned that there was no exact timing for when these burns will now take place. 
 
 
Many in the Shiba Inu community, however, seemed displeased with the update. One X user alluded to the poor communication from the team. The…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Transaction Fees Soar to $40, Sparking Debate and Push for L2 Solutions Amid Mempool Backlog]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748fff1d71</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-transaction-fees-soar-to-40-sparking-debate-and-push-for-l2-solutions-amid-mempool-backlog/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T20:36:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Saturday, Dec. 16, 2023, Bitcoin’s transaction fees spike to a high of $40 per transaction at 1:48 p.m. Eastern Time. The jump in onchain fees surpassed the high reached on May 8, 2023, when the average transfer cost topped $31 per transfer.
 
Skyrocketing Bitcoin Fees Surpass $40
 
Bitcoin transaction fees are climbing and at the time of writing, a high-priority transaction tapped $40 just before 2 p.m. on Saturday, Dec. 16. Miners have been raking in the fees and an example of this is the fact that block height 821,485 came with 7.314 BTC in fees, which is over the size of the 6.25 BTC block subsidy. Presently, the hash price per petahash per second (PH/s) is coasting along at $108 per PH/s per day.
 
The recent spike in Bitcoin’s transaction fees to $40 each significantly surpasses t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Spot ETF: Why SEC Boss Gary Gensler Is Taking A ‘New Look’ At Applications]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748fe6d08e</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-spot-etf-sec-new-look/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T19:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent interview with CNBC, the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Chair Gary Gensler mentioned that the Commission is taking a “new look” at the pending Spot Bitcoin ETF applications. His comment suggests that the SEC may be looking to do things the right way now despite any reservations Gensler or the Commission might have about the crypto industry. 
 
Gensler’s Comment Suggests That SEC’s Hands Are Tied
 
Gensler stated that the SEC was taking a “new look” at these Spot Bitcoin ETF applications because of the court’s decision in the Grayscale case. He alluded to the fact that the Commission had, in the past, rejected similar applications but has had to reconsider its stance following the court’s intervention. 
 
 
The Court in the Grayscale case had adopted the asset manager’…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Echoes of 2013: Bitcoin Mining Concentration Reaches Decade-High Levels]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748fe6e754</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/echoes-of-2013-bitcoin-mining-concentration-reaches-decade-high-levels/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T19:04:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the past 72 hours, Antpool has dominated 26.48% of Bitcoin’s overall hashrate, closely followed by Foundry USA at 24.95%. Together, these two mining pools wield 51.43% of the prevailing 502 exahash per second (EH/s) total hashrate. This level of concentration in bitcoin mining pools has been unprecedented since 2013, reminiscent of the era when Ghash and Btc Guild were the leading forces in hashrate dominance.
 
Bitcoin Mining Power Shift: A Return to Dominance by Few Players
 
Years back, the focus among bitcoin advocates was heavily on the centralization of bitcoin (BTC) mining pools, a topic that sparked considerable debate. Nowadays, though some voices still raise concerns over miner centralization, these issues have largely faded into background noise.
 
For example, in the last th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFT Sales Soar to Over $500M; Bitcoin Leads With Unprecedented Growth]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748fea0828</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/nft-sales-soar-to-over-500m-bitcoin-leads-with-unprecedented-growth/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T17:04:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sales of non-fungible tokens (NFTs) have surged by 52.81% over the past week, reaching a total of $503.35 million. Bitcoin has emerged as the frontrunner in this week’s NFT market, generating $276.79 million in sales, surpassing Ethereum’s $99.67 million, which previously held the top spot.
 
Bitcoin Once Again Outperforms Ethereum in Thriving NFT Market
 
The total NFT sales this week, amounting to $503.35 million, saw Bitcoin accounting for more than half of this figure, with its $276.79 million representing 54.98% of the week’s total. This period also marked a significant rise in market activity, with a 199.44% increase in buyers and a 193.20% surge in sellers of NFTs, according to cryptoslam.io stats.
 
Bitcoin’s performance in NFT sales was notably strong, with a 122.16% increase comp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano Community Member Cautions ADA Holders Against This Serious Scam]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748fd07126</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/cardano-community-member-cautions-ada-holders-against-this-serious-scam/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T16:02:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Cardano community has remained vigilant after a member issued a crucial warning, cautioning members about a crypto scam attack targeting ADA holders. 
 
 
Cardano Issues Scam Warning Alerts
 
In its official X (formerly Twitter) account, the Cardano Community recently released a high-risk warning, alerting community members about an ongoing crypto scam attack operated using a malicious Berry Pool scam event. The scam alert was published on December 14 and is aimed at increasing awareness on the dangers of these malicious crypto attacks. 
 
 
Warning: Scam Alert 
 
We want to bring to your attention that some Berry Pool delegators have received an NFT promising additional ada rewards through a deceptive/fake rewards event.
 
Please be cautious as the associated website has been identifi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Difficulty Set for Upturn Amid Escalating Hashrate and Soaring Miner Fees]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748fde55d9</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-difficulty-set-for-upturn-amid-escalating-hashrate-and-soaring-miner-fees/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T15:07:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After the last adjustment that resulted in a slight 0.96% reduction, the upcoming difficulty retarget on Dec. 23, 2023 is anticipated to bring about an increase, eclipsing the previous decline, as the hashrate regains its upward trajectory. The seven-day average hashrate reached a low of 473 exahash per second (EH/s) on December 11, and has since ascended to 487 EH/s.
 
Bitcoin’s Total Hashrate Regains Upward Momentum Alongside Hash Price Rise
 
Barring any major shifts in the coming week, Bitcoin’s difficulty is poised for an upswing. Projections based on current data suggest an increase ranging from 1.64% to 4.5% on Dec. 23. According to data from Luxor’s hashrateindex.com, the hashrate is currently coasting along at 487 EH/s following a temporary dip last week. Presently, block generati…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These Are The Best Cryptos To Buy Before Christmas – AVAX, ETH, XRP, SOL, BTC]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748fdbf127</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/these-cryptos-are-the-best-to-buy-before-christmas/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T14:08:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The majority of the biggest cryptocurrencies have recently experienced strong momentum, but investors in cryptocurrencies are still waiting for more regulatory changes.
 
Crypto bulls think the erratic market is headed for new highs and are hopeful that more institutional investors will start embracing cryptocurrencies as a result of clearer regulations.
 
We have selected these cryptos below that we believe have what it takes to face the challenges of the market and tally significant price gains before December 25.
 
 
Top 5 Cryptos Seen Climbing Before Christmas
 
AVAX
 
Out of the top 10 projects, Avalanche (AVAX) is the cryptocurrency with the best performance right now. The token has increased by more than 116% over the past month, over 82% over the last 14 days, and over 50% over the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Biggest Games Coming Out in 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210052</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210052/biggest-games-coming-out-nintendo-playstation-xbox-pc"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From Final Fantasy VII Rebirth to Star Wars Outlaws and plenty in between, these are our most anticipated games of 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Difficult Adjustment]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748fc27840</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/the-difficult-adjustment"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T13:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article is featured in Bitcoin Magazine’s “The Primary Issue”. Click here to get your Annual Bitcoin Magazine Subscription.
Click here to download a PDF of this article.
Well, here we are. Block 800,000. None of us reading this will ever see another Bitcoin block height starting with a 7. We’re less than a year from another halving, awaiting systemic implications from federal regulation and institutional adoption, standing at the precipice of an American primary election into which Bitcoin has irrevocably inserted itself. 
Welcome to the big leagues. Bitcoin is being recognized as the most powerful brand in the world, and everyone wants a piece of that sweet, orange action. The individuals, companies, and leaders that have rallied behind Satoshi’s code have become too influential to i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Goodwin,Alex Bergeron</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lesotho’s Entire Payment System Reportedly Goes Offline After Cyberattack]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748fc275a8</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/lesothos-entire-payment-system-reportedly-goes-offline-after-cyberattack/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T13:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Central Bank of Lesotho recently confirmed that its payment system was attacked by unknown cybercriminals. The bank also acknowledged that the resulting downtime is making it “impossible for all local banks to honor inter-bank transactions in the country.”
 
No Financial Loss Suffered
 
The Central Bank of Lesotho (CBL) has stated that the cyber security incident on December 11, which reportedly knocked out the country’s entire payments system, did not result in “any financial or other loss.” However, the bank has “suspended some of its systems to prevent further infiltration from the attackers.”
 
While the central bank has not shared details about the severity of the attack, one South African media outlet suggested that interbank and international payments routed through the country had gone offline. Another outlet suggested that the incident posed a threat to the stability of Lesotho’s financial system and the local currency’s exchange rate versus the South African rand.
 
In a statement issued a day after the attack, the Lesotho central bank said it has since initiated an investigation into the incident and is working to restore normalcy.
 
“Consequently, some payments may be delayed while the Bank works on getting the systems back to normalcy,” the CBL said.
 

 
Meanwhile, in another statement issued on Dec. 13, the CBL, together with the Lesotho Bankers Association, confirmed that the downtime is making it “impossible for all local banks to honor inter-bank transactions in the country.”
 
The two institutions have since agreed to undertake so-called business continuity processes and measures which are expected to help facilitate transactions between banks while work to restore normal service is underway.
 
Register your email here to get a weekly update on African news sent to your inbox:
 
 
What are your thoughts on this story? Let us know what you think in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security Engineer Pleads Guilty To $12 Million Crypto Exchange Hack]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748fcaab99</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-security-engineer-guilty-of-12m-hack/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T11:34:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An unidentified decentralized crypto exchange and Nirvana Financial, a decentralized financial yield protocol, were both compromised in a hacking incident, which a software engineer admitted to.
 
A maximum five-year prison term awaits him for wire fraud and money laundering charges. According to the US Attorney’s Office, this was the first smart contract hacking case to result in a conviction.
 
Shakeeb Ahmed has agreed to turn over $12.3 million, including $5.6 million in unlawfully obtained cryptocurrencies, as part of his guilty plea.
 
 
Exploiting Smart Contracts: Ahmed’s Crypto Heist
 
This appeal is a result of his role in taking advantage of flaws in Nirvana Finance’s and another anonymous decentralized digital currency exchange’s smart contracts.
 
Ahmed hacked two decentralized …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Circle CEO Says Investors Should Have Exposure to Bitcoin in Complex Geopolitical Environment]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748fb53216</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/circle-ceo-says-investors-should-have-exposure-to-bitcoin-in-complex-geopolitical-environment/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T11:09:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Circle CEO Jeremy Allaire says in a complex geopolitical environment, bitcoin is an asset that investors should have some exposure to. He emphasized that “digital commodities are here to stay,” noting that bitcoin is the largest digital commodity asset. The executive also believes that stablecoins will be “explosive in terms of its growth in the coming years.”
 
‘Digital Commodities Are Here to Stay’
 
The CEO of crypto firm Circle, Jeremy Allaire, shared his bitcoin outlook in an interview with CNBC earlier this week. “Digital commodities are here to stay,” the executive began, emphasizing that “Bitcoin is the largest digital commodity asset.” He opined:
 

In a complex geopolitical environment, a complex macroeconomic environment, this is an asset that you should have some exposure to.
 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Instant Settlement: The Construction Industry]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748fb364a6</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/technical/instant-settlement-the-construction-industry"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T10:03:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As I delve deeper into the realm of Bitcoin and the Lightning Network, I am consistently struck by the potential benefits it holds for humanity. The realization of how inefficient and broken our societal structures are due to the limitations of fiat currency becomes increasingly apparent to everyone. While the spotlight often shines on the monetary aspects of Bitcoin, my exploration into the Lightning Network, spurred by my work at Breez and our company's visionary goals, has unveiled an aspect that remains largely unspoken. This hidden gem promises significant benefits for humanity, yet it requires the careful alignment of various building blocks before its full potential can be realized.
I will try to illustrate individual pieces of the vision that I have for changing human behavior thro…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ivan Makedonski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Bonk Continues Surge With Solana Hype, Bitcoin Dips]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210009</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210009/this-week-in-coins-bonk-continues-surge-with-solana-hype-bitcoin-dips"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T10:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin and other major coins and tokens are down. But new meme coin BONK is still rallying.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The ‘Bitcoin Bull Cycle Is Underway,’ Analyst Confirms With These 3 Indicators]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748fbd8f8b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/the-bitcoin-bull-cycle-is-underway-analyst-confirms/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T09:40:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the cryptocurrency space, the Bitcoin bull cycle is one of the most anticipated seasons, as several investors patiently hope for the premier cryptocurrency to climb to unprecedented heights again. With the current market climate on a positive shift, many crypto enthusiasts believe that Bitcoin might be on the verge of a bull run that could drive the coin’s price to levels higher than its current all-time high.
 
Interestingly, a pseudonymous crypto enthusiast and analyst have offered their hypothesis on the possibility of a bull run for the number one cryptocurrency.
 
These Three Indicators Signal An Incoming Bull Run
 
In a recent report, a CryptoQuant analyst with the pseudonym Tarekonchain assessed three major on-chain indicators and their correlation with the current market conditi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Opeyemi Sule</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Voice Generating Startup Resemble AI Promises to Restore Old Audio]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210063</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210063/resemble-ai-voice-enhance-recordings"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T01:34:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An AI startup has built a tool that it says can make low-fidelity speech recordings sound like new.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not That Grok: Musician Grimes and OpenAI Launch Plush Toy with AI Inside]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210024</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210024/grok-ai-twitter-toy-elon-musk-grimes-trademark"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T22:36:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk’s ex partners with Curio to launch a line of AI-powered toys designed to cut back on screen time and enhance interaction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jupiter Airdrop Set for January With a Billion JUP for Solana DeFi Users]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210017</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210017/jupiter-airdrop-set-january-billion-jup-solana-defi-users"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T22:10:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Half of the 10 billion JUP supply will ultimately go to the Jupiter community, with 10% landing in Solana wallets during the first airdrop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Weighs Demand for Saga Phones After Sellout Amid BONK Boom]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210036</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210036/solana-weighs-demand-saga-phones-after-sellout-amid-bonk-boom"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T21:51:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Saga is sold out in the U.S. and EU supplies are nearly tapped out. Solana Labs told Decrypt how it’s assessing next moves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Tech Giant Alibaba Unveils New AI Video Tool]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210018</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210018/alibaba-ai-text-to-video-generative-cloud"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T21:07:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alibaba says its I2VGen-XL model can handle “visualization, sampling, training, inference, join training using images and videos, acceleration, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitch Walks Back Changes After Surge in Nudity: 'We Went Too Far']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209998</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209998/twitch-walks-back-changes-after-surge-nudity-went-too-far"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T19:37:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, Twitch announced it would allow artistic nudity. Now, it’s blocked again, in part because of concerns around AI realism.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Plans to Challenge SEC Denial of Crypto Rulemaking Petition]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209997</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209997/coinbase-plans-challenge-sec-denial-crypto-rulemaking"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T18:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC today denied crypto exchange Coinbase's petition to clarify new crypto rules for the digital assets industry. Coinbase isn't taking "no" for an answer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Scaler Arbitrum Suffers Outage—And Inscriptions Are to Blame]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209996</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209996/ethereum-scaler-arbitrum-suffers-outage-inscriptions-blame"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T18:12:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arbitrum and other chains have recently been bombarded by users making "inscriptions" as on Bitcoin, even though such networks support NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gary Gensler: SEC 'Taking a New Look' at Bitcoin ETF Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209964</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209964/gary-gensler-sec-taking-new-look-bitcoin-etf-applications"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T16:06:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC chair stated that the regulator is reviewing spot Bitcoin ETF applications in light of a recent court ruling.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BONK Spikes 101% Amid Solana Saga Sales Frenzy to Claim Airdrop]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209966</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209966/bonk-spikes-101-amid-solana-saga-sales-frenzy-to-claim-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T15:40:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana-based meme coin BONK has continued to soar in value and hit new all-time highs—and the Saga smartphone is an unexpected beneficiary.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SocialFi Startup Reach Aims to Improve Crypto Twitter With Anti-Bot Protocol]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209903</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209903/socialfi-reach-crypto-twitter-anti-bot-protocol-token"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T15:01:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest addition to the "point" meta seeks to address the challenges of Crypto Twitter with the support of Seedphrase, Pranksy, Gmoney, and Zeneca.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SafeMoon Files for Bankruptcy, SFM Token Crashes 50% to All-Time Low]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209951</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209951/safemoon-files-for-bankruptcy-sfm-token-crashes-50-to-all-time-low"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T10:08:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Chapter 7 bankruptcy filing comes after SafeMoon's founders were indicted by the DOJ for a "multi-million dollar international fraud scheme."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Casio Drops Virtual G-Shock Watches as Ethereum NFTs—With Exclusive Perks]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209939</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209939/casio-drops-virtual-g-shock-watches-ethereum-nfts-exclusive-perks"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T03:02:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The G-Shock watch brand debuts a pair of fantastical digital designs on Ethereum, with a variety of special benefits for holders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vatican Says AI Is the ‘Highest-Stakes Gamble of Our Future’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209925</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209925/pope-declares-ai-the-highest-stakes-gamble-of-our-future"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T00:46:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pope Francis urged global leaders to work together to adopt a binding international treaty that regulates AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grindr Dating App Adds an AI ‘Wingman’ to Help Users Find Love]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209919</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209919/grindr-dating-app-adds-an-ai-wingman-to-help-users-find-love"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T00:18:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“If you’re not first to market with something in AI, you’re going to miss out," says Grindr CEO George Arison.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Devs Got a BONK Airdrop Worth $300 Last Christmas—It's Now Worth $500,000]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209906</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209906/solana-devs-bonk-airdrop-worth-300-last-christmas-now-worth-500000"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T23:01:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers in LamportDAO received a gift of billions of BONK last year. It helped some pay rent—and others get crypto-rich (maybe).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Instagram Adds Generative AI That Swaps Image Backgrounds]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209868</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209868/instagram-adds-generative-ai-that-swaps-image-backgrounds"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T21:59:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The green screen-like Backdrop feature lets users replace their messy kitchens with lush tropical forests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Native Bitcoin Staking on Ethereum and Solana Could Soon Be a Reality]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209867</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209867/native-bitcoin-staking-ethereum-solana-soon-reality-babylon"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T21:24:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto startup Babylon says it's developed a way to stake Bitcoin on any proof-of-stake blockchain. Here's how it works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana DeFi Hacker Pleads Guilty in First-Ever Smart Contract Fraud Conviction]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209859</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209859/solana-defi-hacker-pleads-guilty-smart-contract-fraud-conviction"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T21:01:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's the "first ever conviction for such a hack,” according to the DOJ. The hacker will be sentenced in March.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Did Michael Cohen Let AI Write His Legal Briefs?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209869</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209869/did-michael-cohen-let-ai-write-his-legal-briefs"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T20:53:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cohen's attorneys must prove the existence of cases they cited as speculation swirls around potential AI-generated content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emerge 2023 Project of the Year: OpenAI ChatGPT 3.5]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209784</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209784/emerge-2023-project-of-the-year-openai-chatgpt"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T19:37:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In barely over a year, ChatGPT rocketed from obscure, largely academic roots to the embodiment of a global revolution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Kawailani Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana's BONK Becomes 69th Largest Coin as Market Cap Tops $1 Billion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209850</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209850/solanas-bonk-69th-largest-coin-market-cap-tops-1-billion"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T18:55:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BONK continues its recent boom with a 64% surge on the day, landing in the meme-friendly #69 spot on CoinGecko’s market ranking.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Farcana Raises $10 Million for NFT Esports Shooter That Pays Out Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209817</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209817/farcana-raiases-10-million-nft-esports-shooter-pays-out-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T18:36:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Exclusive: The sci-fi, team-based hero shooter Farcana is still in early development. Now, it has a fresh round of capital to tap into.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a Single Phishing Link Unleashed Chaos on Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209838</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209838/single-phishing-link-unleashed-chaos-on-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T18:14:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ledger has confirmed the attack began because “a former Ledger employee fell victim to a phishing attack.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin and Ethereum Rebound From Wallet Hack Wobble]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209814</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209814/bitcoin-ethereum-rebound-after-wallet-hack-wobble"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T17:40:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin had briefly dipped, but it and the rest of the market has bounced back.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nintendo Switch 2 Preview: Everything You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197793</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197793/nintendo-switch-2-rumors-leaks-latest-news"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T16:46:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATE: Will the Nintendo Switch 2 get Grand Theft Auto 6? Technical experts weigh in on whether the hardware can even handle GTA 6.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fetch AI, SingularityNET Team Up to Squash AI Hallucinations]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209790</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209790/fetch-ai-singularitynet-team-up-to-squash-ai-hallucinations"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The two companies aim to use decentralized technology to make AI more dependable and intelligent, reducing inaccurate or irrelevant outputs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Stop Using Dapps': Ledger Library 'Compromised' With Wallet Drainer]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209804</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209804/ledger-library-compromised-with-wallet-drainer"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T13:47:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ledger has warned users not to connect to any dapps after a malicious version of its Connect Kit was identified.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JP Morgan: Ethereum to Outperform Bitcoin in 2024, Halving ‘Priced In’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209786</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209786/jp-morgan-ethereum-to-outperform-bitcoin-in-2024-halving-priced-in"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T11:53:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bank’s 2024 crypto outlook is cautious, with Bitcoin overbought amid “excessive optimism” over a spot Bitcoin ETF approval.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Axie Infinity NFTs Can Soon Evolve Like Pokémon—Here's How]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209166</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209166/axie-infinity-nfts-can-soon-evolve-like-pokemon-heres-how"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T07:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Exclusive: You can finally power-up your Axies and give them a new look with upgraded parts, but it'll take money, materials, and time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2023 Will Be the ‘Last Year You’ll Know A Song Was Written by a Human’: Queen Guitarist]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209761</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209761/2023-will-be-the-last-year-youll-know-a-song-was-written-by-a-human-queen-guitarist"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T01:16:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Legendary guitarist and astrophysicist Brian May reflects on AI's current and future impact on the music industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI Joins Rolling Stone Publisher to Merge AI With Journalism]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209754</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209754/openai-joins-rolling-stone-publisher-to-merge-ai-with-journalism"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T00:08:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Readers get better summaries, and LLMs get more training data—could AI enhance journalism while disrupting it?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Lords of Light' NFT Game Studio Raini Reveals New Owners, RST Token on Beam]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209730</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209730/lords-light-nft-game-studio-raini-reveals-new-owners-launches-rst-token-beam"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T23:29:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Raini Studios is now part of a joint venture, and the firms have already begun development on a new unannounced combat game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Meme Coin BONK Hits Another All-Time High Ahead of Coinbase Listing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209745</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209745/solana-meme-coin-bonk-hits-another-all-time-high-ahead-of-coinbase-listing"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T23:10:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BONK bounces back, jumping 21% on the day after top exchange Coinbase said it would list the Solana token on Thursday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating peaceful money & taking over your local government w/ Joseph Schiarizzi]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zb0VG27G/creating-peaceful-money-taking-over-your-local-government-w-joseph-schiarizzi</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zb0VG27G/creating-peaceful-money-taking-over-your-local-government-w-joseph-schiarizzi"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T23:23:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week our host Reza Jafery is joined by Joseph Schiarizzi, founder of OpenDollar and prolific solidity developer. 


We discuss: 
- Onchain beer
- Taking over your local government
- His Emmy and 3 patents?!?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INTERVIEW: Ember Sword CEO Says NFT Games Are More 'Transparent']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/M9OHCVpA/interview-ember-sword-ceo-says-nft-games-are-more-transparent</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/M9OHCVpA/interview-ember-sword-ceo-says-nft-games-are-more-transparent"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T21:58:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ember Sword CEO Mark Laursen shares why some big game studios "irk" him—and why he got into game development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Director Jordan Bayne on the State of Film3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZLoEDkL9/director-jordan-bayne-on-the-state-of-film3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZLoEDkL9/director-jordan-bayne-on-the-state-of-film3"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T00:11:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the 2023 Film3 Summit, Jordan Bayne—director and founder of The Squad—spoke with Decrypt's Sander Lutz about how the Film3 world has progressed over the last year and what decentralized technologies can offer to creators that want to buck the Hollywood system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Questions With SCENE: Phil Mohun]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TwOjXfOR/5-questions-with-scene-phil-mohun</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TwOjXfOR/5-questions-with-scene-phil-mohun"/>
        <updated>2023-12-01T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bright Moments co-founder Phil Mohun joins 5 Questions With SCENE to recount some favorite moments from the road, including negotiating with Patagonian gauchos, falling in love with Tokyo, and gaining a newfound appreciation for shrooms chocolate bars.

Shot and edited by Vincent Roazzi Jr.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are NFTs Ever Coming Back?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qLmFpNKE/are-nfts-ever-coming-back</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qLmFpNKE/are-nfts-ever-coming-back"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T18:38:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this weeks episode we sit down with Cashtro from Arcade.xyz to discuss NFTs, shitcoins, what collections have held onto their floor prices, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Summit: Will Web3 Gaming Ever be Mainstream?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OvVWhGbW/web-summit-will-web3-gaming-ever-be-mainstream</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OvVWhGbW/web-summit-will-web3-gaming-ever-be-mainstream"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T19:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animoca Brands CEO Robby Yung, EndeavorXR CEO Amy Peck and Gamee co-founder CEO Bozena Rezab joined Decrypt's Stephen Graves on stage at Web Summit to talk about the future of Web3 gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Allie Eve Knox on Spankchain and the life of a Crypto Financial Dominatrix]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/16rVeg6o/allie-eve-knox-on-spankchain-and-the-life-of-a-crypto-financial-dominatrix</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/16rVeg6o/allie-eve-knox-on-spankchain-and-the-life-of-a-crypto-financial-dominatrix"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T21:20:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the first IRL episode of This Time Will Be Different!

In this week's episode, our host, Reza Jafery, is joined by Allie Eve Knox, the Spankchain Chief of Staff and FinDomme. 

They discuss
- How to sell feet pics
- If crypto is really as permissionless as it seems
- the intersections between crypto and sex work]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Questions With SCENE: Jeff Davis]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PChJu1R8/5-questions-with-scene-jeff-davis</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PChJu1R8/5-questions-with-scene-jeff-davis"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artist Jeff Davis joins 5 Questions with SCENE to answer burning questions about his artistic practice, the path that brought him to Art Blocks, and his quietly sophisticated DJ abilities.

Video shot and edited by Vincent Roazzi Jr.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>