<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-04-24T14:15:29.686Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-04-24T14:15:29.686Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trading of Hong Kong Spot Bitcoin and Ethereum ETFs Starts April 30]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74307d50b6</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/trading-of-hong-kong-spot-bitcoin-and-ethereum-etfs-starts-april-30/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T14:14:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Per the Securities and Futures Commission (SFC) of Hong Kong, the region’s newly authorized spot bitcoin and ethereum exchange-traded funds (ETFs) are set to commence trading on Tuesday, April 30, 2024. Anticipation Builds for the Rollout of Bitcoin and Ethereum ETFs in Hong Kong Recently, the SFC of Hong Kong announced its approval for several […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some Square Users Can Now Convert Their Dollars to Bitcoin Via Cash App]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74307d533c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2024/04/24/some-square-users-can-now-convert-their-dollars-to-bitcoin-via-cash-app/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T14:14:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Conversions will charge a flat 1% fee to automatically convert a portion of merchant revenues into BTC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Kuhn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Block Enables Millions of Square Sellers to Convert Sales to Bitcoin With Cash App]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74307e3391</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/block-enables-millions-of-square-sellers-to-convert-sales-to-bitcoin-with-cash-app"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T14:09:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Block, a global technology company focusing on financial services, has announced the launch of Bitcoin Conversions, a feature that allows millions of Square sellers to convert a percentage of their daily sales to Bitcoin using Cash App, according to a press release sent to Bitcoin Magazine.
 
                         
                         
                         
                     
                    
This collaboration between Square and Cash App empowers eligible Square sellers in the U.S. to allocate between 1-10% of their daily sales from their Square seller account to be automatically transferred to their personal Cash App account. The funds will then be used to purchase bitcoin at the end of each day, and sellers will have full control over their bitcoin holdings, including the ability to hold, send, sell, and manage their BTC as they see fit. A transparent, flat 1% fee applies to each conversion made from daily sales to Bitcoin.
Block stated that it believes that Bitcoin is a tool for economic empowerment, enabling global participation in a digital monetary system. Direct feedback from Square sellers indicates a strong interest in Bitcoin for various use cases, including long-term savings and diversification of business holdings.
This initiative is part of Block's broader strategy to integrate Bitcoin into various ecosystems, providing new avenues for individuals, developers, and now, sellers, to engage with Bitcoin. The collaboration builds on previous integrations between Square and Cash App, offering additional value and efficiencies for participants across Block's ecosystem.
Bitcoin Conversions is available to eligible sole proprietors or single member LLCs in the U.S., with a gradual rollout planned for all eligible sellers in the coming months (excluding New York State-based sellers).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nik Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unchained Is Helping Users Secure 90,000 BTC And Counting in Self Custody]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74307e3369</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/unchained-is-helping-users-secure-90000-btc-and-counting-in-self-custody"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T14:09:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Company Name: Unchained
Founders: Joe Kelly and Dhruv Bansal
Date Founded: October 2016
Location of Headquarters: Austin, TX
Amount of Bitcoin in Treasury: Not disclosed
Number of Employees: 107
Website: https://unchained.com/
Public or Private? Private
Joe Kelly and Dhruv Bansal started Unchained with one main objective: to provide financial services to people like themselves — long-term bitcoin holders. Since 2017, when Unchained launched its first product, a lending desk that allowed customers to borrow US dollars against their bitcoin, the company has developed into a full-on financial services company for Bitcoiners who value holding their private keys.
Unchained now offers a suite of services and products, including multsig vaults for both individuals and businesses, a bitcoin tradin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Frank Corva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2,000 Bitcoin ATMs installed in 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19432734/2000-Bitcoin-ATMs-installed-in-2024</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19432734/2000-Bitcoin-ATMs-installed-in-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T14:08:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While the metric finds itself in the news only infrequently, it probably does not come as a surprise that the … Continue reading]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Price Prediction as Meme Coins Bounce Back – Can SHIB Overtake Ethereum?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19432732/Shiba-Inu-Price-Prediction-as-Meme-Coins-Bounce-Back-Can-SHIB-Overtake-Ethereum</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19432732/Shiba-Inu-Price-Prediction-as-Meme-Coins-Bounce-Back-Can-SHIB-Overtake-Ethereum"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T14:06:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SHIB has risen by 1.5% in the past 24 hours, with the Shiba Inu price reaching $0.00002713 on a day when the crypto market as a whole has gained by 1%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s Behind the Hedera Hashraph HBAR Rally: Black Rock MMF Token Hosted by Archax]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19432725/Whats-Behind-the-Hedera-Hashraph-HBAR-Rally-Black-Rock-MMF-Token-Hosted-by-Archax</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19432725/Whats-Behind-the-Hedera-Hashraph-HBAR-Rally-Black-Rock-MMF-Token-Hosted-by-Archax"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T14:04:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hedera (HBAR), the token behind Hedera Hashgraph, held a spectacular rally at the start of the new week. HBAR peaked at $0.18, its highest price for the past two years, doubling its price overnight. Investors in HBAR saw rumors that the Hedera blockchain carried one of BlackRock’s tokenized...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Renzo Restaked ETH Suffers a Brief Crash on Uniswap]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74307f7c3f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/04/24/renzo-restaked-eth-suffers-a-brief-crash-on-uniswap/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T14:01:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The sell-off was likely catalyzed by users looking to reclaim their ETH in low liquidity conditions and large liquidations of ezETH-collateralized positions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Custody Firm Fireblocks Now Offers DeFi Threat Detection for Institutions]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74307f7c1b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2024/04/24/crypto-custody-firm-fireblocks-offers-defi-threat-detection-for-institutions/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T14:01:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The products check decentralized applications across 40+ blockchains via WalletConnect, Fireblocks’ browser extension, and MetaMask Institutional.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Payments App Strike Launches for European Customers]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74307f7c04</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2024/04/24/bitcoin-payments-app-strike-launches-for-european-customers/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T14:01:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Strike, the payments application using the Bitcoin blockchain, has launched in Europe, allowing customers to buy, sell and withdraw bitcoin {{BTC}} in the region, it announced Wednesday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DePin Crypto The 100X Opportunity Most Will Miss]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19432735/DePin-Crypto-The-100X-Opportunity-Most-Will-Miss</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19432735/DePin-Crypto-The-100X-Opportunity-Most-Will-Miss"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T14:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DePIN the 100x opportunity that many will miss🔥 GET MY FREE NEWSLETTER 👉 https://cryptolark.co/WEALTH_MASTERY💎 BITGET 👉 $30,000 IN BONUSES ►► https://cryptolark.co/BITGET30K 💸 BYBIT $30,030 BONUS & FEE DISCOUNT 👉 https://cryptolark.co/BYBIT💡💡💡 ESSENTIAL CRYPTO KNOWLEDGE 💡💡💡🔥 GET MY FREE...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analyst Predicts DXY Retreat to 102-103: Could Bitcoin Hit $90,000?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19432712/Analyst-Predicts-DXY-Retreat-to-102-103-Could-Bitcoin-Hit-90000</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19432712/Analyst-Predicts-DXY-Retreat-to-102-103-Could-Bitcoin-Hit-90000"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The recent events in the financial markets have revealed the possibility that the DXY dollar index can inversely affect the price of Bitcoin, hence, these conditions are likely to create very interesting occurrences for both currency and digital currency markets. The DXY index, now facing...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some Square Users Can Now Convert Their Dollars to Bitcoin Via Cash App]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19432742/Some-Square-Users-Can-Now-Convert-Their-Dollars-to-Bitcoin-Via-Cash-App</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19432742/Some-Square-Users-Can-Now-Convert-Their-Dollars-to-Bitcoin-Via-Cash-App"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Conversions will charge a flat 1% fee to automatically convert a portion of merchant revenues into BTC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Magic Runes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IGWg0R64/magic-runes</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IGWg0R64/magic-runes"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T13:59:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC stables at $66k, liquidations in narrow range. BTC funding again turns negative in bullish sign. ETFs net inflow after Grayscale moves to lower fees. BTC demand 5x vs supply post-halving: Bitfinex. SOL congestion issue now largely solved. Two SEC lawyers resign after ‘gross abuse of power’. Ripple fights to lower $2bn SEC fine. SAFE trades at $2.8bn FDV after OKX lists. MANEKI hits $150m on first day, China memes pump. Memecoins are ‘black hole you can’t ignore’. DeGods up 20%, may switch back to SOL. Magic Eden launches Runes platform ahead of time.  Louis Vuitton gifts Pharrell jacket to NFT holders. Melania Trump launches necklace with SOL NFTs. Hoodie Punk trades for $620K.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Magic Runes]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19432733/Magic-Runes</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19432733/Magic-Runes"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T13:59:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC stables at $66k, liquidations in narrow range. BTC funding again turns negative in bullish sign. ETFs net inflow after Grayscale moves to lower fees. BTC demand 5x vs supply post-halving: Bitfinex. SOL congestion issue now largely solved. Two SEC lawyers resign after ‘gross abuse of power’....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock’s Bitcoin ETF achieves record inflows, ranks in U.S. top 10 ETFs]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19432707/BlackRocks-Bitcoin-ETF-achieves-record-inflows-ranks-in-US-top-10-ETFs</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19432707/BlackRocks-Bitcoin-ETF-achieves-record-inflows-ranks-in-US-top-10-ETFs"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T13:59:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock’s Bitcoin ETF, IBIT, has achieved a significant milestone since its launch in January 2024, securing a spot among the … Continue reading]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin Leads the Charge in Digital Identity and Privacy]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19432691/Worldcoin-Leads-the-Charge-in-Digital-Identity-and-Privacy</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19432691/Worldcoin-Leads-the-Charge-in-Digital-Identity-and-Privacy"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T13:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin, led by well-known figures like Sam Altman and Alex Blania, is on a mission to change the vision of how we think about digital identities and privacy in the world of cryptocurrency.The Worldcoin project, guided by Sam Altman and Alex Blania, is on a mission to build stronger...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock, Grayscale Amend Ethereum ETF Applications After SEC Delays]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=227817</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/227817/blackrock-grayscale-amend-ethereum-etf-applications-after-sec-delays"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T13:57:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The flurry of filings follows the SEC's announcement yesterday that it would delay its decision on multiple spot Ethereum ETF proposals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance to Delist Six Trading Pairs: Details]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19432686/Binance-to-Delist-Six-Trading-Pairs-Details</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19432686/Binance-to-Delist-Six-Trading-Pairs-Details"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T13:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance to remove and cease trading on six spot trading pairs on April 26]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hedge Funds Are Embracing Memecoins in the Hope of Achieving Spectacular Returns: Bloomberg Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19432687/Hedge-Funds-Are-Embracing-Memecoins-in-the-Hope-of-Achieving-Spectacular-Returns-Bloomberg-Report</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19432687/Hedge-Funds-Are-Embracing-Memecoins-in-the-Hope-of-Achieving-Spectacular-Returns-Bloomberg-Report"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T13:49:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent article, Bloomberg News highlighted a growing trend in the hedge fund world: the increasing interest in memecoins. According to the report, the allure of these highly speculative tokens has become irresistible for some hedge funds as they seek to capitalize on the potential for quick...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Injective unveils largest tokenomics upgrade with INJ 3.0 release]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19432679/Injective-unveils-largest-tokenomics-upgrade-with-INJ-30-release</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19432679/Injective-unveils-largest-tokenomics-upgrade-with-INJ-30-release"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T13:47:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Injective has activated the INJ 3.0 update, designed to inject long-term value and support the growth of the Injective ecosystem. The latest version's key focus is a substantial reduction in the supply of Injective's native token, INJ, which the team said is the largest tokenomics...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strike's Expansion into Europe Accelerates Bitcoin Adoption]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74307a1bfc</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//fintech/payments/strike-expansion-into-europe-accelerates-bitcoin-adoption/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T13:46:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Strike, a payments application utilizing the Bitcoin  
blockchain, has launched its services in Europe, enabling customers in the  
region to engage in buying, selling, and withdrawing bitcoin (BTC). The  
announcement was made today (Wednesday).
Expanding Operations Across Continents
Having recently expanded its operations to Africa, Strike  
has already established its presence in Asia, the Caribbean, and Latin America.  
However, availability may vary by country, and interested customers are  
encouraged to check their local iOS or Android app stores for accessibility, as  
some regions may be excluded from the expansion.
“As the third-largest economy globally … Europe presents  
vast opportunities for bitcoin adoption,” Strike said in a press release.  
“We’ve seen the demand and heard…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tareq Sikder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Renzo’s ezETH depegs to $688 following end of airdrop farming window]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19432683/Renzos-ezETH-depegs-to-688-following-end-of-airdrop-farming-window</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19432683/Renzos-ezETH-depegs-to-688-following-end-of-airdrop-farming-window"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T13:44:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite the temporary price depeg, a trader made nearly $400,000 in profit due to the unfortunate incident.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The #1 Bitcoin Indicator You Need To Watch To Predict Price]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19432661/The-1-Bitcoin-Indicator-You-Need-To-Watch-To-Predict-Price</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19432661/The-1-Bitcoin-Indicator-You-Need-To-Watch-To-Predict-Price"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T13:43:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#bitcoin #crypto #cryptocurrencies Consider dropping a like if you enjoyed the video! 👍Check out our partner, AngelBlock: https://angelblock.io/Check out our partner, iTrustCapital: https://www.itrustcapital.com/datadashSign up for the DashReport 💹➡️ http://nicholasmerten.com/dashreport/00:00 -...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["$150k Bitcoin by End of 2024" | EP 976]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19432680/150k-Bitcoin-by-End-of-2024-EP-976</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19432680/150k-Bitcoin-by-End-of-2024-EP-976"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T13:36:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Analyst from Standard Chartered bank says that Bitcoin can still reach $150,000 by year-end╔═╦╗╔╦╗╔═╦═╦╦╦╦╗╔═╗║╚╣║║║╚╣╚╣╔╣╔╣║╚╣═╣ ╠╗║╚╝║║╠╗║╚╣║║║║║═╣╚═╩══╩═╩═╩═╩╝╚╩═╩═╝✓ SUBSCRIBE TO SIMPLY BITCOIN - https://bit.ly/3QbgqTQ✓ LEAVE A LIKE & COMMENT LEAD SPONSOR► Bitcoin Well:...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Fund Snobs Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19432685/This-Fund-Snobs-Bitcoin</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19432685/This-Fund-Snobs-Bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T13:30:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[🔥 GET MY FREE NEWSLETTER 👉 https://cryptolark.co/WEALTH_MASTERY💎 BITGET 👉 $30,000 IN BONUSES ►► https://cryptolark.co/BITGET30K 💸 BYBIT $30,030 BONUS & FEE DISCOUNT 👉 https://cryptolark.co/BYBIT💡💡💡 ESSENTIAL CRYPTO KNOWLEDGE 💡💡💡🔥 GET MY FREE NEWSLETTER 👉 https://cryptolark.co/WEALTHMASTERY💎...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do Kwon, Terraform Labs Face $5B Penalty After LUNA Fiasco]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19432606/Do-Kwon-Terraform-Labs-Face-5B-Penalty-After-LUNA-Fiasco</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19432606/Do-Kwon-Terraform-Labs-Face-5B-Penalty-After-LUNA-Fiasco"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has moved to request billions of dollars in disgorgement and civil penalties from Do Kwon and Terraform Labs, the team behind the ill-fated Terra Luna and UST tokens. In a recent filing in the U.S. District Court for the Southern...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unchained Is Helping Users Secure 90,000 BTC And Counting in Self Custody]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19432642/Unchained-Is-Helping-Users-Secure-90000-BTC-And-Counting-in-Self-Custody</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19432642/Unchained-Is-Helping-Users-Secure-90000-BTC-And-Counting-in-Self-Custody"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T13:26:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Kelly, CEO and co-founder of Bitcoin financial services platform Unchained, is determined to give users a true Bitcoin experience, while still meeting them where they’re at.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NBA playoffs to feature Coinbase’s new $15 million campaign]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19432588/NBA-playoffs-to-feature-Coinbases-new-15-million-campaign</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19432588/NBA-playoffs-to-feature-Coinbases-new-15-million-campaign"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T13:25:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase is allegedly launching a nationwide mega ad campaign. The company will use $15 million for the TV ads that will air during the NBA playoffs, which are expected to kick off on Wednesday. Coinbase ads highlight banking flaws with Pizza The campaign consists of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apology Letter from Binance Former CEO CZ to the Court Judge!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19432583/Apology-Letter-from-Binance-Former-CEO-CZ-to-the-Court-Judge</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19432583/Apology-Letter-from-Binance-Former-CEO-CZ-to-the-Court-Judge"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T13:20:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CZ, the founder of the world's largest cryptocurrency exchange, wrote a letter to the court judge. There was a lot of support for CZ. Continue Reading: Apology Letter from Binance Former CEO CZ to the Court Judge!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XOCIETY brings AAA gaming to Web3 with Sui]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=227864</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/227864/xociety-brings-aaa-gaming-to-web3-with-sui"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T13:15:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Palo Alto, CA, April 24th, 2024, GamingWire Web3 Gaming is evolving, and in a significant move, XOCIETY, one of Web3’s most anticipated games, is partnering with Mysten Labs, the original contributor to Sui, an innovative Layer 1 and smart contract platform. XOCIETY and Mysten Labs will work together to revolutionize gaming in the Web3 space.  […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>gamingwire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Contributor Issues Critical Alert On Memecoins]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7430604f5b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-contributor-alert-on-memecoins/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T13:12:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a nuanced critique published on X, a prominent Dogecoin contributor known as @Mishaboar has issued a significant warning concerning the trading of meme coins, especially those that secure listings on cryptocurrency exchanges almost immediately after their release. The contributor, who is a key figure within the Dogecoin community, used his platform to outline the potential pitfalls that unsuspecting investors might face.
 
The Risks Of Memecoins
 
@Mishaboar expressed deep concerns regarding the current trend in the crypto markets where meme coins quickly achieve market capitalizations in the millions or even billions of dollars, facilitated by almost instantaneous listings on major exchanges. He stated, “There is an explosion in tokens that go up to crazy market caps, with instant list…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Prosecutors Recommend 3-Year Prison Sentence for Binance's Changpeng Zhao: Report]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7430613be5</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/us-prosecutors-recommend-3-year-prison-sentence-for-binances-changpeng-zhao-report/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T13:06:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US prosecutors have proposed a 36-month prison sentence for Binance's former CEO, Changpeng Zhao. According to a report by  
CNBC, the prosecutors argued that such a sentence, which is double the advisory  
guidelines, reflects the seriousness of the charges against Zhao.
The recommendation, outlined in a sentencing  
memorandum filed with the Western District Court of Washington, highlights the  
severity of the accusations against Zhao, who stepped down from his position  
last November following a plea deal with the US Department of Justice.
US Prosecutors' Charges Against Zhao
US prosecutors said a 36-month custodial sentence  
is necessary to underscore the seriousness of the charges against Zhao, which  
include failure to implement anti-money laundering measures as mandated  
by the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a Conservative German Bank Offering Crypto Makes Sense]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e743062afcb</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2024/04/24/how-a-conservative-german-bank-offering-crypto-makes-sense/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T12:58:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Germany is a relatively conservative financial market, and landesbank are among its most conservative institutions. So what is the country’s largest landesbank doing launching crypto services? Noelle Acheson explains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Noelle Acheson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Mover Americas: Hedera's HBAR Soars on Exaggerated BackRock Link]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74306dc5c7</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/04/24/first-mover-americas-hederas-hbar-soars-on-exaggerated-backrock-link/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T12:40:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest price moves in bitcoin (BTC) and crypto markets in context for April 24, 2024. First Mover is CoinDesk’s daily newsletter that contextualizes the latest actions in the crypto markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lyllah Ledesma, Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dubai-Based CoinW Unveils Rebranding and Prop Trading Product]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7430684892</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/dubai-based-coinw-unveils-rebranding-and-prop-trading-product/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T12:25:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CoinW Exchange, a notable presence within the digital asset  
trading domain, is undergoing changes as it observes its sixth-year  
anniversary. Situated in Dubai, the exchange has revealed an exhaustive  
rebranding effort alongside the debut of its Proprietary Trading (Prop Trading)  
product. 
Introducing Prop Trading for Profit Opportunities
Having cemented its position within the digital assets  
trading industry, CoinW Exchange is now set to enter a fresh phase of  
development. A centrepiece of its transformation is the launch of the Prop  
Trading product, an offering aimed at providing traders with expanded avenues  
for profit optimization. This new product is set to play a role in CoinW  
Exchange's strategic outlook for the future according to the firm.
According to Sonic, Dire…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tareq Sikder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong Bitcoin ETFs to Trade on 30th April: HashKey Capital]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7430544b0b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/hong-kong-bitcoin-etfs-to-trade-30th-april"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T12:02:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong's Securities and Futures Commission recently approved Bitcoin Spot ETFs for several major asset managers, paving the way for the city to become a leading hub for such products. 
The approval comes after months of anticipation and marks a significant milestone for the Bitcoin industry in Asia.

JUST IN: 🇭🇰 Hong Kong spot #Bitcoin ETFs will begin trading on April 30: HashKey Capital
Asia is ready 🚀 pic.twitter.com/TDfNZTqPQU
— Bitcoin Magazine (@BitcoinMagazine) April 24, 2024
 
 
 
HashKey Capital, a local asset management firm, confirmed that its Bitcoin ETF will start trading next Tuesday. In a statement, a spokesman for the firm acknowledged the launch date, making it one of the first companies to offer a spot Bitcoin ETF in Hong Kong.
OSL, a digital asset platform that acts as a sub-custodian and infrastructure service provider for two major fund managers, has also indicated that spot bitcoin products aim to launch as early as late April. This news further solidifies Hong Kong's position as a frontrunner in the race to offer investors access to Bitcoin through traditional financial instruments.
Elsewhere, some of China's top asset managers are in the final leg of preparations for the spot Bitcoin ETFs to begin trading potentially by the end of April. 
This development is expected to attract significant interest from investors within and outside Hong Kong.
 
                         
                         
                        Click the image to learn more. 
                     
                    
According to predictions by Singapore-based crypto services provider Matrixport and Markus Thielen, founder of 10x Research, Hong Kong Spot Bitcoin ETFs could bring in and unlock up to $25 billion in new demand. 
This influx of capital could have a profound impact on Bitcoin and further legitimize it as an asset class.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vivek Sen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tevaera Secures $5M Funding to Redefine Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=227828</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/227828/tevaera-secures-5m-funding-to-redefine-gaming"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T12:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Participating investors include Hashkey Capital, Fenbushi Capital, Matter Labs, Draper Dragon, Faculty Group and Crypto.com Capital.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>gamingwire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Prosecutors Seek 36-Month Sentence for Binance’s Changpeng Zhao Over Legal Violations]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e743055cff1</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/us-prosecutors-seek-36-month-sentence-for-binances-changpeng-zhao-over-legal-violations/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T11:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Federal prosecutors have recommended a 36-month prison sentence for Changpeng Zhao (CZ), the cryptocurrency exchange Binance’s former CEO, for U.S. law violations. Prosecutors contend Zhao’s deliberate non-compliance facilitated massive unlawful transactions, impacting national security and financial systems. CZ’s Legal Woes Deepen With Proposed Three-Year Prison Term Changpeng Zhao, referred to as “CZ” and the brain […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Founder Changpeng Zhao Apologizes Ahead of Sentencing, 161 Others Send Letters of Support]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e743056a266</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/04/24/binance-founder-changpeng-zhao-apologizes-ahead-of-sentencing-161-others-send-letters-of-support/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T11:48:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance's founder and former chief executive, Changpeng "CZ" Zhao has apologised for his "poor  decisions" and accepted "full responsibility" for his actions, in a letter to the judge overseeing his case.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amitoj Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong Spot Bitcoin and Ethereum ETFs to Begin Trading April 30]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=227818</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/227818/hong-kong-spot-bitcoin-and-ethereum-etfs-to-begin-trading-april-30"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T11:37:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trading for Hong Kong’s spot crypto ETFs will begin April 30, after the securities regulator formally signed off on their approval.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thai SEC Instructed to Share Information on Unauthorized Digital Asset Platforms With Government]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e743051563d</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/thai-sec-instructed-to-share-information-on-unauthorized-digital-asset-platforms-with-government/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T11:32:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Thai Securities and Exchange Commission has been instructed to share information on unauthorized digital asset service providers with the Ministry of Digital Economy and Society. The regulator warned investors using such platforms of the risks they face which include the possibility of being scammed or involved in money laundering. Enhancing Efficiency in Law Enforcement […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s Borderless Power: IMF Recognizes Positive Impact On Global Finance]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e743051755d</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-imf-sees-positive-impact-on-global-finance/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T11:31:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amidst economic turmoil and stringent regulations, citizens in countries like Argentina and Venezuela have turned to Bitcoin as a lifeline. The International Monetary Fund (IMF) examines how individuals in these nations are leveraging Bitcoin to manage their finances, bypassing capital controls through off-blockchain transactions.
 
 
This trend underscores the resilience and adaptability of cryptocurrencies in providing financial autonomy to individuals in challenging economic environments.
 
The IMF has released a groundbreaking report titled “A Primer on Bitcoin Cross-Border Flows,” shedding light on the increasing relevance of the world’s most popular cryptocurrency in facilitating international financial exchanges.
 

 
 
Understanding The Dynamics Of Bitcoin Transactions
 
The report…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Number of Stablecoin Holders Nears 100M Mark, Data Show]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7430534090</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/04/24/number-of-stablecoin-holders-nears-100m-mark-data-show/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T11:20:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The number of addresses holding stablecoins has risen 15% this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Memereum Presale: New Wave of Crypto Opportunities Offering Investors Access to DeFi Innovation]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74305d1acf</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/memereum-presale-new-wave-of-crypto-opportunities-offering-investors-access-to-defi-innovation/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T11:09:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. Monaco, April 24, 2024 – Memereum, a promising project on the BNB Smart Chain, is delighted to announce the launch of its presale. It invites investors to join the movement towards financial empowerment and innovation. With a suite of special financial products and services, Memereum is going to participate in the future advancement […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Xai? The Rising Ethereum Layer-3 Gaming Network on Arbitrum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=227667</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-xai-the-rising-ethereum-layer-3-gaming-network-on-arbitrum"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T11:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Xai is an Arbitrum-based layer-3 gaming network for Ethereum, powered by the XAI token after a sizable airdrop. Here's what you need to know.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Department of Justice Seeks 3-Year Jail Sentence for Former Binance CEO CZ]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=227779</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/227779/us-department-of-justice-seeks-3-year-jail-sentence-for-former-binance-ceo-cz"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T09:22:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Citing Changpeng Zhao's "willful violation of U.S. law," the DoJ recommended a harsher-than-expected for the former Binance CEO.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Assistant Users Could Develop An ‘Emotional Attachment’ to Them, Google Warns]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=227754</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/227754/ai-assistant-users-could-develop-an-emotional-attachment-to-them-google-warns"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T23:40:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With great power comes great responsibility, and one of the largest providers of AI assistants says they are becoming quite powerful.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Are Bitcoin Rune Names So Weird? There's a Method to the Madness]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=227748</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/227748/bitcoin-rune-name-rules-long-weird"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T23:21:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite quirky and long labels, there are already several thousand etchings in the wake of the Bitcoin halving.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google, Meta, OpenAI Unite With Other Industry Giants Against AI Child Abuse Imagery]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=227731</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/227731/aig-csam-google-meta-openai-fight-ai-child-sexual-abuse-material"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T22:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A coalition of high-powered players pledges to prioritize child safety in all phases of AI development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Space Nation Online' Preview: Ethereum Game's Promising Beta Plagued by Server Issues]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=227668</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/227668/space-nation-online-preview-ethereum-game-beta-server-issues"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T21:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The voice acting and graphics shine in Space Nation Online's test, but server hitches tied to airdrop demand keep popping up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IRS Set to Kill Pseudonymity in Crypto? Tax Form Proposal Raises Alarms]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=227730</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/227730/irs-kill-pseudonymity-crypto-tax-form-proposal-raises-alarms"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T21:15:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A draft of an IRS form appears to indicate that the agency will require self-custodial wallet addresses from DeFi users filing taxes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Luxury Watches, Designer Shoes Will Soon Trade Like NFTs: Arianee CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/CSNQG2md/luxury-watches-designer-shoes-will-soon-trade-like-nfts-arianee-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/CSNQG2md/luxury-watches-designer-shoes-will-soon-trade-like-nfts-arianee-ceo"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arianee CEO Pierre-Nicolas Hurstel sat down with Rug Radio founder Farokh and Decrypt’s Sander Lutz at NFT Paris to discuss everything from the future of on-chain luxury to the secret hack to finding the best restaurants in France.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Proposal to Restore Satoshi Code Gets a '420' Update]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=227723</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/227723/bitcoin-proposal-restore-satoshi-code-420-update"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T20:25:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OP_CAT, which could enable advanced functionality on Bitcoin, was introduced as BIP-420 by Taproot Wizards co-founder Udi Wertheimer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Venezuela Turns to Tether to Skirt US Oil Sanctions: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=227690</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/227690/venezuela-turns-to-tether-to-skirt-us-oil-sanctions-report"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T18:48:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amid election turmoil, state-run oil firm PDVSA is using USDT. But Tether vows to follow the law and block transactions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano Founder Charles Hoskinson's Studio Releases First Game—But It's on GalaChain]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=227709</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/227709/cardano-founder-charles-hoskinson-game-galachain"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T18:35:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RFLXT, the Charles Hoskinson-backed firm, is releasing Voyager: Ascension via Gala today—but has Cardano gaming in its sights, too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Punts on Ethereum ETF Proposals From Grayscale and Franklin Templeton]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=227705</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/227705/sec-punts-ethereum-etf-proposals-grayscale-franklin-templeton"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T18:10:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC has again delayed on giving a decision on spot Ethereum ETF proposals from both Grayscale and Franklin Templeton.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Lobbyists Sue SEC Over 'Dealer' Rule That Could Threaten DeFi]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=227701</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/227701/crypto-lobbyists-sue-sec-dealer-rule-threaten-defi"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T17:52:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The suit is the latest in a series of proactive, offensive legal moves from the crypto industry against the federal regulator.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biggest Crypto Gaming Tokens Launched in 2024—So Far]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=219999</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/219999/biggest-crypto-gaming-tokens-launched-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T17:22:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATED: The KARRAT token tied to battle royale game My Pet Hooligan enters the gaming tokens list, but does it shake up the standings?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock Bitcoin ETF Is Halfway to Setting a New Record]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=227681</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/227681/blackrock-bitcoin-etf-is-halfway-to-setting-a-new-record"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T14:35:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite most Bitcoin ETFs seeing outflows recently, BlackRock’s spot Bitcoin ETF has seen impressive inflows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GuildFi Rebrands to Zentry, Launching a 'Game of Games' to Reward Players]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=227622</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/227622/guildfi-rebrands-zentry-game-of-games-reward-players"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T12:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zentry’s “superlayer” will benefit players across crypto and Web2 games alike, along with social media and real-world activities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward,Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Two DePIN Projects Are Dominating the Top 100 With Double-Digit Gains]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=227653</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/227653/why-two-depin-projects-are-dominating-the-top-100-with-double-digit-gains"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T11:16:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DePIN projects Akash Network and Zebec Network have seen their AKT and ZBC tokens score massive double-digit gains in the past day.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PayPal Wants to Give Green Bitcoin Miners Extra BTC Rewards]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=227656</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/227656/paypal-wants-to-give-green-bitcoin-miners-extra-btc-rewards"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T11:09:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The research paper aims to incentivize miners to use verified low-carbon energy sources, by rewarding them with additional Bitcoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Centralized Exchanges Are Already Listing Bitcoin Runes—Which Ones Will Be Next?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=227613</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/227613/centralized-exchanges-listing-bitcoin-runes-which-ones-next"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T00:18:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Runes tokens are already trading via Gate.io, as other big exchanges potentially test the waters. Will widespread adoption follow?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward,Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robert F. Kennedy Jr. Vows to Put the US Budget on Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=227594</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/227594/robert-f-kennedy-jr-vows-to-put-the-us-budget-on-blockchain"/>
        <updated>2024-04-22T21:20:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The independent candidate for U.S. president cited outrageous Pentagon spending as a reason to adopt fully transparent technology.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apecoin Rebounds 4.6% Amid NFT Launchpad and DEX Proposal]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=227581</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/227581/apecoin-price-up-4-percent-nft-launchpad-dex-proposals"/>
        <updated>2024-04-22T21:08:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following a 66% drop in the last year and declining Bored Ape Yacht Club NFT prices, the community pins its hopes on new proposals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale's Bitcoin ‘Mini-Me’ Trust Will Undercut Fellow ETFs With Lowest Fees]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=227562</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/227562/grayscale-mini-bitcoin-trust-lowest-etf-fees"/>
        <updated>2024-04-22T19:11:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Responding to massive outflows, Grayscale’s updated entry is aggressively competitive, a new SEC filing shows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Will Auction Off the Rest of Its Locked Solana Tokens]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=227483</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/227483/ftx-solana-sol-auction"/>
        <updated>2024-04-22T18:44:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bankrupt crypto exchange FTX will auction off the rest of its locked Solana tokens in the hopes of getting a better price.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Draws $12 Million Raise for New Blockchain and TREAT Token]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=227561</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/227561/shib-treat-token-shiba-inu-shibarium-meme-coin"/>
        <updated>2024-04-22T18:26:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TREAT will be the “final non-stable token” for the forthcoming privacy-focused blockchain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Runes Launch on Magic Eden in Attempt to 'Streamline' BTC Token Trading]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=227551</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/227551/bitcoin-runes-magic-eden-attempt-streamline-btc-token-trading"/>
        <updated>2024-04-22T18:18:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just three days after Bitcoin's Runes protocol launched, Magic Eden has rolled out support for the tokens. Here's what to expect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erika Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Meme Coin Pepe Surges 16% on Coinbase Perpetual Futures Listing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=227538</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/227538/ethereum-meme-coin-pepe-surges-16-percent-coinbase-futures"/>
        <updated>2024-04-22T17:48:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto markets are relatively calm after the buzzy Bitcoin halving hype, but Ethereum meme coin Pepe is blasting off after Coinbase news.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notcoin's Co-Creator Explains the Game's Token Delay—And When to Expect NOT Now]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/7Zx33xo5/notcoins-co-creator-explains-the-games-token-delayand-when-to-expect-not-now</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/7Zx33xo5/notcoins-co-creator-explains-the-games-token-delayand-when-to-expect-not-now"/>
        <updated>2024-04-22T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Notcoin co-creator Sasha Plotvinov spoke with Decrypt's Sander Lutz at Token 2049 Dubai to discuss why the NOT token launch was pushed back from the original 4/20 target, when to expect the listing, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TON’s Justin Hyun Breaks Down The Importance of USDT Coming to Telegram]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ODQI6ACA/tons-justin-hyun-breaks-down-the-importance-of-usdt-coming-to-telegram</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ODQI6ACA/tons-justin-hyun-breaks-down-the-importance-of-usdt-coming-to-telegram"/>
        <updated>2024-04-19T10:14:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Token 2049 in Dubai, The Open Network’s director of investments sat down with Decrypt’s Sander Lutz to discuss what he sees as the game-changing integration of USDT onto TON, and his plans for getting Telegram’s 900 million users to start using crypto in the immediate future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Influencer Ansem Explains His Meme Coin Thesis and Why He’s Bullish on Bitcoin Runes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/u9DHFoK0/crypto-influencer-ansem-explains-his-meme-coin-thesis-and-why-hes-bullish-on-bitcoin-runes</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/u9DHFoK0/crypto-influencer-ansem-explains-his-meme-coin-thesis-and-why-hes-bullish-on-bitcoin-runes"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T21:56:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ansem, the crypto trader who's amassed a sizable following on the back of meme coin Dogwifhat (WIF) and other calls, chats with Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz at Token 2049 Dubai about his meme coin thesis, why he's bullish on Bitcoin Runes, and what he sees ahead for the crypto markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Sander Lutz Braves the Dubai Floods for a Crypto Conference]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/mtjVHGa3/decrypts-sander-lutz-braves-the-dubai-floods-for-a-crypto-conference</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/mtjVHGa3/decrypts-sander-lutz-braves-the-dubai-floods-for-a-crypto-conference"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T21:33:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz reports from Dubai amid a historic storm that flooded the famed city, trudging through the streets to complete his essential task: Attending the Token 2049 crypto conference.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gold Beats Its All Time High]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/6ULgUKVk/gold-beats-its-all-time-high</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/6ULgUKVk/gold-beats-its-all-time-high"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T09:53:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) maintains its trend of reaching higher lows amidst choppy market conditions. Exchange-traded funds (ETFs) witness another influx of $125 million. There's anticipation of Hong Kong approving ETFs for both Bitcoin and Ethereum (ETH) come Monday. Notable institutional investor BlackRock shows interest in Bitcoin. Recent filings reveal increased Bitcoin purchases by banks. A Bitcoin-friendly political party secures victory in the South Korean election. Analyst Kang predicts Bitcoin could surge to $80-100k by May. Meanwhile, Ethereum sees accumulation by stablecoin whales on the rise. A new Ethereum Improvement Proposal (EIP) aims to streamline signing requests. Solana (SOL) experiences a resurgence in activity, reaching yearly highs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NASA’s Next Deep Space Mission Won’t Use Artificial Intelligence]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/0WGP33Rp/nasas-next-deep-space-mission-wont-use-artificial-intelligence</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/0WGP33Rp/nasas-next-deep-space-mission-wont-use-artificial-intelligence"/>
        <updated>2024-04-13T18:42:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Thursday, Decrypt Media visited NASA's Jet Propulsion Laboratory in Pasadena, CA to meet with the Engineering team behind the Europa Clipper before its launch to Jupiter's Europa moon in October.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Do A Little with Weesh]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LnaOT9bF/we-do-a-little-with-weesh</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LnaOT9bF/we-do-a-little-with-weesh"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T07:46:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week’s episode, we did a little something different. We took the man who is usually behind the camera and put him in front of it. We sat down with our producer Weesh to dive into how in fell in love with art and became a collector, how he met Andy and fun childhood memories together, his biggest wins in crypto, and so much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside VanEck’s Crypto Takeover of the New York Stock Exchange]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9YAY4wGD/inside-vanecks-crypto-takeover-of-the-new-york-stock-exchange</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9YAY4wGD/inside-vanecks-crypto-takeover-of-the-new-york-stock-exchange"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T14:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worlds collide as Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz heads to the floor of the NYSE to witness a special closing bell ceremony hosted by VanEck in honor of Web3. Featuring Choose Rich Nick, VanEck Head of Web3 Matt Bartlett, and more!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wormhole Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9SNiIVfU/wormhole-wednesday</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9SNiIVfU/wormhole-wednesday"/>
        <updated>2024-04-07T17:42:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC hits $64.5K then rebounds, SOL outperforms. Government sends $2B BTC to Coinbase to sell. Funding rates stay low after sweep lower. ETFs see small inflow, Ark outflow more than GBTC. Wormhole W launches at $15B FDV. BTC ‘inflection point’ if it follows rates or gold. Gold & BTC very correlated for the last year. Expect slower ETF volume this month: Bloomberg. BTC 2x and 3x levered ETFs launch yesterday. BTC ETFs now half the size of gold.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Dogs, Now Cats]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/2KrbCFNp/first-dogs-now-cats</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/2KrbCFNp/first-dogs-now-cats"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T14:06:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC falls another 6% amid $400m liquidations. ETF outflows and dollar strength blamed for move. Funding completely reset to lows in move. BTC lower high leaves market in ‘no trade zone’. This cycle acting ‘nothing like previous cycle’. ETH unlikely to be classed a security: Coinbase CFO. Crypto VC funding up 53% in MarchAnsem’s cat coin sees more volume than NFT market. Most memecoins down 10-20% given move in majors. MEW up 10% after HTX lists, airdrop to Saga phones. MEME to launch memecoin chain, NFTs rise. Pixelmon releases trailer for Anime series.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Do A Little With Spencer Gordon-Sand]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/jSsgl6SQ/we-do-a-little-with-spencer-gordon-sand</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/jSsgl6SQ/we-do-a-little-with-spencer-gordon-sand"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T17:11:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week’s episode, we sit down with Spencer Gordon Sand, the mastermind behind Spencer Ventures. Before launching Spencer Ventures, Spencer was a competitive fencer, Magic the gathering player, and startup enjoyooor. 

We dive into Spencer’s investment thesis behind NFTs and how his fund invests, finding and buying distressed assets in a bear market , point farming optimization, a peak behind the 3AC liquidation and dickbutt buys, and so much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Get Your Foot In Ihe Door And Building During Bear Markets]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/d8FYP5tO/how-to-get-your-foot-in-ihe-door-and-building-during-bear-markets</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/d8FYP5tO/how-to-get-your-foot-in-ihe-door-and-building-during-bear-markets"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T11:37:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week’s episode, we sit down with Intern and Tunez from the Monad team. Prior to Monad, Tunez was working with Delphi Digital and Intern was working at CMS Holdings. They’re two of my oldest friends from crypto twitter.

We get into why they joined the Monad team, alpha for finding jobs in the space, biggest lessons from previous cycles, and so much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SBF Sentencing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZmRslhIl/sbf-sentencing</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZmRslhIl/sbf-sentencing"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T11:29:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC: 70.7k (+1%), ETH: 3585 (0%), SOL: 186 (-1%). Top 100 gainers: DOGE, GT, BCH, RBN. Crypto mixed, BTC-beta & memes outperform. SEC case vs Coinbase set to go to trial. DeFi win as case dismissed vs Coinbase wallet. ETFs see $244m inflows led by Ark. BlackRock ETF fastest growing in history: Fink. ETH ETF possible even if its a security: Fink. ETH spot ETF by May chances only 20%: GSR. SBF sentencing today, faces 50 years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The $63 Million Exploit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/l2sy2ZQY/the-63-million-exploit</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/l2sy2ZQY/the-63-million-exploit"/>
        <updated>2024-03-28T16:42:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC consolidates around $70k, funding still low. ETFs see $418m inflow as GBTC outflow tiny. BTC set to have record 7th-straight green month. AI coins soar, FET hits ATH amid merger rumour. FET, OCEAN, AGIX token proposed at $7.5bn FDV. DoJ charges KuCoin over money laundering. KuCoin sees $800m outflows after charges. CFTC names ETH & LTC commodities in charges. HK set to allow ‘in-kind’ style ETFs. HSBC launches tokenised gold fund. Fidelity files S1 form for ETH ETF. Short sellers bet $11bn crypto rally won’t last. More customer USDC balances to be stored on Base.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BTC Is Back On Top]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/1t8j4uWb/btc-is-back-on-top</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/1t8j4uWb/btc-is-back-on-top"/>
        <updated>2024-03-28T16:16:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC breaks $70K as $175M of shorts liquidated. ETFs see net inflow despite high GBTC outflows. Gold miner set to buy $1.7B BTC. UK to list crypto ETNs in May. ETH ETF may still be approved: Grayscale. Grayscale ETH discount falls to 22%. ETH ETF has no positive signs: Bloomberg. Coinbase pumps 10%, Ark continue to sell shares. Coinbase Int. record trading volumes in March. FTX to sell majority of Anthropic stake for $884M. Trader makes $20m profit in MEW rally. Puppets hit ATH, lead move higher in Ordinals. Azuki flips MAYC market cap in bounce. Magic Eden makes $15m in 30d trading revenue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Base On Top]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OGLEeanX/base-on-top</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OGLEeanX/base-on-top"/>
        <updated>2024-03-28T15:05:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Majors continue to rally as ETF sentiment improves. Genesis have likely sold half their GBTC position. BlackRock could flip GBTC holdings in 3 weeks. BTC short squeeze would liquidate $6.6bn by $75k. Lack of on-chain activity indicates ‘limited selling’. BTC crucial to the financial system: BlackRock. Resurging interest in crypto assets: Goldman Sachs. Crypto summer has started: Raoul Pal. Base outpaces SOL & ETH for trading volumes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>