<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-01-26T04:19:01.051Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-01-26T04:19:01.051Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South African Regulator Expects to Determine Fate of 50 Crypto License Applications in ‘Coming Weeks’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f6488deb</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/south-african-regulator-expects-to-determine-fate-of-50-crypto-license-applications-in-coming-weeks/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T04:11:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The head of enforcement at South Africa’s financial industry watchdog said on Jan. 24 that he expects the organization to decide the fate of 50 crypto firms’ license applicants in the coming weeks. The watchdog stated that from the more than 100 entities that applied for a license, 20 have since withdrawn from their respective applications.
 
The Cost of Obtaining a License
 
An official with the Financial Sector Conduct Authority (FSCA), South Africa’s financial industry watchdog, announced on Jan.24 that the organization expects to determine the fate of some 50 crypto firms’ license applications in the coming weeks. Gerhard van Deventer, the head of enforcement at the FSCA, revealed that out of the 90-plus applicants, 20 have since withdrawn.
 
As reported by Bitcoin.com News in late 202…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arthur Hayes Reveals Two Altcoin Picks, Warns Bitcoin Has Further To Drop – Here’s His Outlook]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19204946/Arthur-Hayes-Reveals-Two-Altcoin-Picks-Warns-Bitcoin-Has-Further-To-Drop-Heres-His-Outlook</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19204946/Arthur-Hayes-Reveals-Two-Altcoin-Picks-Warns-Bitcoin-Has-Further-To-Drop-Heres-His-Outlook"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T04:08:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BitMEX co-founder Arthur Hayes says he thinks Bitcoin (BTC) will continue to drop in price, and that he’s prepared to load up on specific altcoins if it does. In a new analysis, Hayes notes that a 30% correction is due for the crypto king from its 2024 high of around $48,000, which it reached after […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US SEC Initiates Proceedings On Grayscale’s Spot Ethereum ETF, Extends Decision Deadline]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f648f8f6</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/sec-initiates-grayscales-spot-ethereum-etf-decision/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T04:07:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a significant development for the cryptocurrency market, the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has initiated proceedings on Grayscale Investments’ application for a spot Ethereum ETF and extended the decision deadline. 
 
Review Period For Grayscale’s Ethereum ETF
 
Grayscale’s application, filed with the SEC on October 10, 2023, sought approval for listing and trading shares of the Grayscale Ether Trust on the New York Stock Exchange (NYSE) Arca under the Commodity-Based Trust Shares rule. 
 
The proposed rule change was published for public comment in the Federal Register on October 27. In response, the SEC provided an extended period to approve, disapprove, or institute proceedings on the proposed rule change, similar to the Commission’s steps before approving th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vivek Ramaswamy Says He Explained Harms Of CBDC To Donald Trump: 'I Give Him A Lot Of Credit For Being Intellectually Open']]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19204927/Vivek-Ramaswamy-Says-He-Explained-Harms-Of-CBDC-To-Donald-Trump-I-Give-Him-A-Lot-Of-Credit-For-Being-Intellectually-Open</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19204927/Vivek-Ramaswamy-Says-He-Explained-Harms-Of-CBDC-To-Donald-Trump-I-Give-Him-A-Lot-Of-Credit-For-Being-Intellectually-Open"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T03:38:20.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin And Nasdaq 100 Correlation Weakens: Is BTC Decoupling?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f636e6ce</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-nasdaq-100-correlation-weakens/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T03:07:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On January 25, market data provider Kaiko revealed that the 60-day correlation between Bitcoin (BTC) and the Nasdaq 100 has averaged close to zero since June 2023. This suggests that the two asset classes have become less correlated in recent months, potentially showing that their prices are increasingly decoupling.
 

 
Bitcoin Decoupling with Nasdaq 100?
 
Historically, Bitcoin has been highly correlated with traditional asset classes, particularly the Nasdaq 100, due to its association with risk-on sentiment and speculative trading. However, this recent divergence could signal a shift in their relationships.
 
Several factors could be behind this decoupling. The rise of institutional investors in the crypto market has led to a more diverse set of participants and a broader range of inve…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dalmas Ngetich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Eyes Recovery But Can BTC Bulls Regain Strength?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19204896/Bitcoin-Price-Eyes-Recovery-But-Can-BTC-Bulls-Regain-Strength</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19204896/Bitcoin-Price-Eyes-Recovery-But-Can-BTC-Bulls-Regain-Strength"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T03:01:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin price is aiming for an upside break above the $40,500 resistance. BTC bulls could face heavy resistance near $40,850 and $41,350. Bitcoin price is attempting a recovery wave from the $38,500 support zone. The price is trading just above $40,000 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Cardano Could Be The Next Big Crypto Winner: An Influencer’s Perspective]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19204870/Why-Cardano-Could-Be-The-Next-Big-Crypto-Winner-An-Influencers-Perspective</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19204870/Why-Cardano-Could-Be-The-Next-Big-Crypto-Winner-An-Influencers-Perspective"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T03:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent video from the crypto-based YouTube channel Cheeky Crypto, the host underscores Cardano’s (ADA) approach, which separates it from its contenders, particularly its reliance on “academic rigor” and “research-driven development.” Dropping out his reasons for being bullish on Cardano,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin And Nasdaq 100 Correlation Weakens: Is BTC Decoupling?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19204883/Bitcoin-And-Nasdaq-100-Correlation-Weakens-Is-BTC-Decoupling</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19204883/Bitcoin-And-Nasdaq-100-Correlation-Weakens-Is-BTC-Decoupling"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T03:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Whales and Sharks Actively Selling as Price Dips, On-Chain Analysis Shows]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19204889/Bitcoin-Whales-and-Sharks-Actively-Selling-as-Price-Dips-On-Chain-Analysis-Shows</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19204889/Bitcoin-Whales-and-Sharks-Actively-Selling-as-Price-Dips-On-Chain-Analysis-Shows"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T03:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JPMorgan says GBTC sell-off ‘behind us’ as ETFs post record net outflow]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19204864/JPMorgan-says-GBTC-sell-off-behind-us-as-ETFs-post-record-net-outflow</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19204864/JPMorgan-says-GBTC-sell-off-behind-us-as-ETFs-post-record-net-outflow"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T02:41:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Analysts from JPMorgan believe the majority of “profit taking” from Grayscale’s Bitcoin Trust is now likely over, while U.S. Bitcoin funds have just recorded their biggest day of net outflows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Bitmex Chief Expects Bitcoin to Bottom Out Between $30,000 and $35,000]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f631858f</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/former-bitmex-chief-expects-bitcoin-to-bottom-out-between-30000-and-35000/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T02:40:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Bitmex CEO Arthur Hayes has predicted that bitcoin will find a support level between $30,000 and $35,000. He contends that the ongoing bitcoin selloff is not due to outflows from Grayscale’s bitcoin trust (GBTC). “That argument is bogus,” he claimed, adding that bitcoin’s price movement is “anticipating the Bank Term Funding Program (BTFP) will not be renewed.”
 
Ex-Bitmex Chief’s Bitcoin Price Prediction
 
Arthur Hayes, co-founder and former CEO of crypto exchange Bitmex, has shared his bitcoin price prediction, explaining that he believes the cryptocurrency will form support between $30,000 and $35,000. In a blog post published Tuesday, Hayes detailed:
 

I think bitcoin will find a local bottom between $30,000 and $35,000.
 
Referring to his statement earlier this month that he e…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Curve drops 28% in 2024 despite surging TVL: What’s going on?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19204856/Curve-drops-28-in-2024-despite-surging-TVL-Whats-going-on</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19204856/Curve-drops-28-in-2024-despite-surging-TVL-Whats-going-on"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T02:30:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Curve’s TVL has maintained its upward trajectory in 2024 despite a 28% price drop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Giant CoinShares Slashes Bitcoin ETP Management Fees]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19204855/Crypto-Giant-CoinShares-Slashes-Bitcoin-ETP-Management-Fees</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19204855/Crypto-Giant-CoinShares-Slashes-Bitcoin-ETP-Management-Fees"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T02:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF: Was It A Massive Disaster?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19204747/Bitcoin-ETF-Was-It-A-Massive-Disaster</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19204747/Bitcoin-ETF-Was-It-A-Massive-Disaster"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T02:19:07.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla Holds Steady On Bitcoin: Q4 Earnings Reveal Unchanged Crypto Stance]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f63cb5bf</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/tesla-holds-steady-on-bitcoin-q4-earnings-crypto/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T02:08:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the latest financial disclosures from Tesla Inc., the Elon Musk-helmed electric vehicle giant, there’s a notable absence of any Bitcoin transaction activities. This silence in their 2023 Q4 report suggests that Tesla has maintained its position in the crypto space, holding onto its Bitcoin.
 
Notably, Tesla’s decision not to buy or sell Bitcoin during the fourth quarter of last year coincides with the uptrend experienced by the crypto market.
 
 
Musk’s Tesla Holds Steady On Bitcoin
 
Tesla, recognized for its “forward-thinking” approach to technology and investment, holds 9,720 BTC. By not reporting BTC-related transactions, the company signals its continued confidence in Bitcoin as an investment.
 
This steadiness is noteworthy, considering the market’s volatility over the past months…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla Holds Steady On Bitcoin: Q4 Earnings Reveal Unchanged Crypto Stance]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19204837/Tesla-Holds-Steady-On-Bitcoin-Q4-Earnings-Reveal-Unchanged-Crypto-Stance</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19204837/Tesla-Holds-Steady-On-Bitcoin-Q4-Earnings-Reveal-Unchanged-Crypto-Stance"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T02:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Prediction Platform Users See Trump as Likely 2024 Presidential Election Winner]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19204838/Crypto-Prediction-Platform-Users-See-Trump-as-Likely-2024-Presidential-Election-Winner</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19204838/Crypto-Prediction-Platform-Users-See-Trump-as-Likely-2024-Presidential-Election-Winner"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T02:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Money Laundering Crypto Lawyer Sentenced to 10 Years Behind Bars]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19204881/Money-Laundering-Crypto-Lawyer-Sentenced-to-10-Years-Behind-Bars</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19204881/Money-Laundering-Crypto-Lawyer-Sentenced-to-10-Years-Behind-Bars"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T01:56:19.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[88% of Top Media Houses Now Block AI Bots Amid Content Use Concerns]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19204815/88-of-Top-Media-Houses-Now-Block-AI-Bots-Amid-Content-Use-Concerns</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19204815/88-of-Top-Media-Houses-Now-Block-AI-Bots-Amid-Content-Use-Concerns"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T01:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[11 Bitcoin miners may not mine profitably post halving: Cantor Fitzgerald]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19204809/11-Bitcoin-miners-may-not-mine-profitably-post-halving-Cantor-Fitzgerald</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19204809/11-Bitcoin-miners-may-not-mine-profitably-post-halving-Cantor-Fitzgerald"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T01:36:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bitcoin halving could spell a great deal of pain for Bitcoin miners if the price of BTC fails to surge, though hedging strategies could mitigate this risk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China’s Bitcoin Ban Backfires: $86B Crypto Volume Soars Amid Stock Slump]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f63a7e26</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/china-bitcoin-ban-backfires-86b-crypto-volume-soars/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T01:09:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[China’s cryptocurrency trading and mining ban hasn’t deterred local investors from flocking to the crypto market. In defiance of the ban, these investors turn to digital assets to escape the economic downturn plaguing traditional investments, such as stocks and real estate. 
 
According to a Reuters report, Chinese individuals are finding “creative” ways to participate in the crypto market, leveraging grey-market dealers, overseas bank accounts, and Hong Kong’s endorsement of digital assets.
 
Chinese Investors Defy Regulations
 
A perfect example of the new ways Chinese investors invest in crypto is Dylan Run, an executive in the financial sector based in Shanghai, who began to diversify his investments into cryptocurrencies at the beginning of 2023. 
 
Recognizing the declining Chinese e…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla Maintains Bitcoin Holdings — $184M in Digital Assets Shown on Balance Sheet]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f63a77e1</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/tesla-maintains-bitcoin-holdings-184m-in-digital-assets-shown-on-balance-sheet/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T01:08:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk’s electric car company, Tesla, has maintained its bitcoin holdings. The company’s balance sheet for Q4 2023 shows net digital assets of $184 million. Musk is convinced that in the long term, Tesla will be the most valuable company in the world. The billionaire recently disclosed that another of his companies, Spacex, also owns “a bunch of bitcoin.”
 
Tesla’s Bitcoin Holdings Stand at $184 Million
 
Tesla, Elon Musk’s electric car company, released its fourth quarter 2023 earnings on Wednesday, showing net digital assets of $184 million on its balance sheet. Tesla has held this amount of digital assets since the fourth quarter of 2022.
 
 
Tesla previously explained that its digital assets were made up almost entirely of bitcoin (BTC), noting that while the company accepts the mem…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US National Debt Surges $98,000,000,000 in January As Lawmakers Warn America Is ‘Rapidly Approaching the Crisis Point’]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19204775/US-National-Debt-Surges-98000000000-in-January-As-Lawmakers-Warn-America-Is-Rapidly-Approaching-the-Crisis-Point</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19204775/US-National-Debt-Surges-98000000000-in-January-As-Lawmakers-Warn-America-Is-Rapidly-Approaching-the-Crisis-Point"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T01:04:14.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China’s Bitcoin Ban Backfires: $86B Crypto Volume Soars Amid Stock Slump]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19204777/Chinas-Bitcoin-Ban-Backfires-86B-Crypto-Volume-Soars-Amid-Stock-Slump</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19204777/Chinas-Bitcoin-Ban-Backfires-86B-Crypto-Volume-Soars-Amid-Stock-Slump"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T01:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[YOU Are A SLAVE to The MONEY PRINTER!! #bitcoin #crypto #shorts]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19204774/YOU-Are-A-SLAVE-to-The-MONEY-PRINTER-bitcoin-crypto-shorts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19204774/YOU-Are-A-SLAVE-to-The-MONEY-PRINTER-bitcoin-crypto-shorts"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T01:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Let me issue and control a nation’s money and I care not who writes the laws.” - Mayer Amschel Rothschild (Allegedly*)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Analyst Who Called 2018 Market Bottom Forecasts No More Dips for DOGE Rival $WIF, Predicts Surge Beyond $1]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19204780/Crypto-Analyst-Who-Called-2018-Market-Bottom-Forecasts-No-More-Dips-for-DOGE-Rival-WIF-Predicts-Surge-Beyond-1</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19204780/Crypto-Analyst-Who-Called-2018-Market-Bottom-Forecasts-No-More-Dips-for-DOGE-Rival-WIF-Predicts-Surge-Beyond-1"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T01:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A top cryptocurrency strategist that has gained a large following on social media after accurately calling bitcoin’s 2018 bear market bottom above $3,000 has recently suggested that the price of meme-inspired cryptocurrency Dogwifhat ($WIF) has bottomed out. According to an update the analyst...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Judge says FTX investigation should move faster]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19204781/Judge-says-FTX-investigation-should-move-faster</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19204781/Judge-says-FTX-investigation-should-move-faster"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T00:52:15.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK Supreme Court Refuses Craig Wright Appeal]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f62535e7</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/01/26/uk-supreme-court-refuses-craig-wright-appeal/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T00:41:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In July it was ruled that Wright was only entitled to just 1 GBP in compensation for a libel claim against bitcoin podcaster Peter McCormack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camomile Shumba, Elizabeth Napolitano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum’s Long-Awaited Upgrade Gets Closer As Devs Set Final Timeline]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=214328</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/214328/ethereum-upgrade-dencun-sepolia-holesky-timeline"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T00:26:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The next two updates should be completed in February, setting the stage for the final upgrade to go live.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IOTA Plots Ethereum Alignment and Traders Are Suddenly Bullish]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=214348</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/214348/iota-plots-ethereum-alignment-and-traders-are-suddenly-bullish"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T23:58:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is IOTA the phoenix of crypto? As the second best performing token of the day, hardcore fans likely hope it is.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Swiss Regulator Grants Approval Enabling Retail Users to Trade Tokenized Securities and Digital Assets]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f623be9c</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/swiss-regulator-grants-approval-enabling-retail-users-to-trade-tokenized-securities-and-digital-assets/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T23:39:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Swiss financial markets regulator has granted the digital asset infrastructure firm Taurus the approval which allows its retail users to “create an account and trade digital assets and tokenized securities.” Besides receiving the FINMA approval, Taurus said it will be admitting new tokenized assets from Swiss companies that have selected TDX as their preferred venue. 
 
Secure and Compliant Trading
 
The Swiss Financial Market Supervisory Authority (FINMA) has given Taurus, a digital asset infrastructure provider, the green light to open its financial services and TDX marketplace to retail users. The approval allows Taurus’ clients “to create an account and trade digital assets and tokenized securities.”
 
According to a statement released on Jan. 23, the approval means that Taurus’ re…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche Foundation Unveils $100 Million Fund To Buy Meme Coins, But There’s A Catch]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f623f0da</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/avalanche-foundation-meme-coins/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T23:37:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Avalanche Foundation, a non-profit organization actively supporting the Avalanche community, has announced a $100 million support fund dedicated to facilitating the deployment of meme coins within the community. However, the organization has revealed strict guidelines and criteria that developers must adhere to before their meme coins would be considered eligible for support. 
 
Avalanche Foundation Makes Big Move Into Memecoins
 
In a recent January 23 blog post, the Avalanche Foundation outlined its goals and vision for the Avalanche community through the use of meme coins. The organization expressed its commitment to completely embracing the community’s core principles, which are culture, creativity, and camaraderie. 
 
 
The foundation revealed that it recognises these specific ele…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celo, Shopping for Blockchain Partner, Turns to the Delicate Issue of Money]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f62df484</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2024/01/25/celo-shopping-for-blockchain-partner-turns-to-the-delicate-issue-of-money/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T23:17:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A standalone blockchain, Celo is looking to migrate to become a layer-2 network atop Ethereum. The months-long selection process has started to look like "The Bachelorette," with teams behind the Arbitrum, Optimism, Polygon and zkSync networks all vying to win the technology mandate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bradley Keoun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche Announces Eligibility Criteria for Meme Coin Purchasing Program]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f62a0e9a</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/avalanche-announces-eligibility-criteria-for-meme-coin-purchasing-program/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T22:39:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Avalanche Foundation, a non-profit organization seeking to support the avalanche ecosystem, has announced the rules covering its already active meme coin purchasing program. The institution has defined the holder count, concentration, liquidity, liquidity providers, lifespan, and market cap requirements that these projects need to fulfill to get selected and informed more projects are being considered on an ongoing basis.
Avalanche Announces Meme Coin Purchasing Framework
The Avalanche Foundation, a non-profit entity that supports initiatives on the Avalanche ecosystem, has announced the requirements to invest in meme coins using the $100 million Culture Catalyst fund launched in 2022. The foundation had previously reported on the purchase of these tokens but had not specified the cond…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Farm the Drift Protocol Airdrop on Solana]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=214157</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/214157/how-farm-drift-protocol-airdrop-solana"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T22:23:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Drift Protocol, the largest perpetual swap futures exchange on Solana, just launched a points program ahead of an airdrop. Here's what you need to know.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX-Linked Billionaire Joe Lewis Pleads Guilty To 19 Fraud Charges In The US]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f615a51a</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ftx-linked-billionaire-joe-lewis-pleads-guilty/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T22:08:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a significant development, billionaire Joe Lewis, formerly associated with bankrupt crypto exchange FTX and known for owning a Premier League football club, has pleaded guilty to 19 fraud charges related to insider trading in the United States. 
 
Lewis, who had sold over $76 million worth of property in the Bahamas to Sam Bankman-Fried, the founder of FTX, acknowledged his involvement in a scheme to benefit friends and associates. 
 
Securities Fraud Scandal
 
According to a Reuters report, under the agreement with the US Attorney’s office in Manhattan, Lewis, 86, pleaded guilty to one count of conspiracy to commit securities fraud and two counts of securities fraud. 
 
However, his lawyer, David Zornow, stated that Lewis retains the right to appeal if the judge imposes a prison senten…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Cuts 1,900 Xbox and Activision Staff Amid Gaming Industry Crisis]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=214331</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/214331/microsoft-cuts-1900-xbox-activision-staff-amid-gaming-industry-crisis"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T22:06:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nearly 6,000 game industry employees have lost their jobs already in 2024, with Microsoft now responsible for nearly one-third of the cuts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Topps Navigates Web3 Hurdles: Shifts to Fortress Amid Regulatory Challenges in NFT Expansion]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f611249c</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/topps-navigates-web3-hurdles-shifts-to-fortress-amid-regulatory-challenges-in-nft-expansion/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T21:39:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week the collectibles and candy company Topps communicated with its customers regarding its non-fungible token (NFT) initiatives. The company acknowledged encountering challenges with a payment service provider in January 2023, leading to a transition to a new provider, Fortress, in September. Nevertheless, regulatory constraints have resulted in the unavailability of custodial wallets for collectors in New York and Texas.
 
Topps Partners With Fortress, Faces State Regulatory Hurdles in NFT Journey
 
Topps has acknowledged that the past year presented numerous obstacles for the Web3 community, stating that its own NFT program was “not excluded” from these difficulties. Back in January 2023, Bitcoin.com News covered the story of Wyre altering its withdrawal procedure, a development th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF Flows Show Negative Trend For First Time Since Launch]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f6135664</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/01/25/bitcoin-etf-flows-show-negative-trend-for-first-time-since-launch/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T21:21:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The group of recently launched spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) are seeing combined negative flows for the first time since they opened for trade on Jan. 11 as money moving into funds like BlackRock's IBIT and Fidelity's FBTC has failed to keep pace with the exits from Grayscale’s GBTC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rollups Are Coming to Bitcoin Through ‘Superlayer’ Protocol BitcoinOS]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=214329</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/214329/bitcoin-rollups-bitcoinos-superlayer-sovryn-protocol"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T21:12:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Backed by the DeFi project Sovryn, the framework is nearly trustless and has built-in anti-fraud features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ETH ETFs Are Inevitable — But When?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f61fdba6</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2024/01/25/eth-etfs-are-inevitable-but-when/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T20:43:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the SEC delays applications from Grayscale and BlackRock, Daniel Kuhn looks at how soon regulators might approve these investment products.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Kuhn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Lender Abra to Return Assets to Texas Investors]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f61844bf</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/crypto-lender-abra-to-return-assets-to-texas-investors/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T20:40:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following regulatory scrutiny, crypto lender Abra has agreed to a settlement. The settlement, which focuses on Abra’s alleged unregistered securities offerings, will see the company returning assets to Texan investors.
 
Abra Agrees to Refund Texas Investors in Settlement Over Crypto Offerings
 
The Texas State Securities Board (TSSB) has reached a settlement in principle with crypto lender Abra, following allegations of unregistered securities offerings. As per the agreement, Abra will return assets to Texan investors, with an opportunity for other U.S. clients to reclaim their investments.
 
Securities Commissioner Travis J. Iles announced the settlement, highlighting the resolution of concerns regarding Abra’s interest-bearing cryptocurrency products, Abra Boost and Abra Earn. The enfor…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Sencil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Praised By Reddit Co-Founder, Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f61984da</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-btc-praised-by-reddit-co-founder-heres-why/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T20:30:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reddit Co-Founder Alexis Ohanian was a guest on The Late Show with Stephen Colbert on January 24, where he explained the reason that made Bitcoin “empowering” to many and the opportunities it holds for its owners.
 
 
A Empowering Asset For People Around The World?
 
In the interview with late-night host Stephen Colbert, Alexis Ohanian was questioned about blockchain and cryptocurrencies. When asked to explain why he chose crypto instead of fiat money, he replied that Bitcoin and digital assets are “a fuel for a potential new internet” and an opportunity for people to safely have a store of value without the need to be “backed by a single country.”
 
The entrepreneur explains to the audience that, although it might seem silly to some, there is a “very real need” for these types of assets, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rubmar Garcia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk's Tesla Still Holds $387 Million in Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=214314</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/214314/elon-musk-tesla-holds-387-million-in-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T20:10:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company paper-handed its BTC during COVID-19, but then diamond handed the rest as it now focuses on AI and robotics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Punts on Yet Another Spot Ethereum ETF]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=214301</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/214301/sec-punts-yet-another-spot-ethereum-etf"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T19:45:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission has pushed back a decision on Grayscale's spot Ethereum ETF conversion proposal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Swan Bitcoin Unveils Stealth Mining Operations, Eyes 8 EH/s Goal by 2024 Amid Industry Expansion]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f6000efd</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/swan-bitcoin-unveils-stealth-mining-operations-eyes-8-eh-s-goal-by-2024-amid-industry-expansion/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T19:39:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Los Angeles-based firm Swan Bitcoin recently revealed its covert bitcoin mining operations, initiated in the summer of 2023. The company shared on Thursday its anticipation of achieving 8 exahash per second (EH/s) by March 2024. Up to this point, Swan’s mining subsidiary has successfully mined 750 bitcoin.
 
Swan Mining Breaks Cover, Sets Sights on Hashpower Expansion
 

 
Swan Bitcoin, specializing in bitcoin-centric financial services, recently emerged from stealth mode with its BTC mining subsidiary, Swan Mining. Swan reports that its mining activities currently boast 4 EH/s of hashpower, with plans to expand this capacity by March 2024. “The unit has purchased and taken delivery of mining equipment that will bring its total capacity to more than 8 exahash, expecting full deployment…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[To Meme, Or Not To Meme: The CAT]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f6008dd8</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/technical/to-meme-or-not-to-meme-the-cat"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T19:35:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is it really surprising, given that cats have essentially dominated the internet for the last two decades, that cat memes have finally taken over the Bitcoin space as well in the last few weeks? Cats are the most viral meme on the internet, so it's not shocking in the least bit that the Taproot Wizards have leaned into it, reinforced by the trolling Luke over his “dietary choices.” 
The question has to be asked though, are meme campaigns really how we want to go about deciding and discussing consensus changes to a protocol as valuable as Bitcoin? I’ve seen numerous music videos, campaigns to go out in the world and “educate” people on OP_CAT, and the whole “Quest” system that Taproot Wizards has launched taking place…but the reality is the vast majority of this content that I have seen has…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shinobi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Will Sell $117 Million in Bitcoin Seized From Silk Road Drug Trafficker]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=214309</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/214309/us-sell-117-million-bitcoin-seized-silk-road-drug-trafficker"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T19:09:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The United States plans to sell a substantial stash of Bitcoin forfeited by a convicted Silk Road drug trafficker from Maryland.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Pixels’ Game Gives Out NFTs, Ronin Tokens Ahead of Airdrop]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=214304</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/214304/pixels-game-gives-out-nfts-ronin-tokens-ahead-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T18:40:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The PIXEL token airdrop is nearly here—but until then, the Pixels team is keeping the buzz alive with giveaways and challenges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Britcoin' CBDC Not Ready Yet, Says Bank of England]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=214295</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/214295/britcoin-cbdc-not-ready-yet-says-bank-england"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T18:19:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[British policy makers are still undecided on a digital pound—dubbed "Britcoin"—following a central bank digital currency (CBDC) consultation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WEN Token? Over a Million Wallets Eligible for Solana Meme Coin Airdrop]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=214282</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/214282/wen-token-over-million-wallets-eligible-solana-meme-coin-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T18:06:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jupiter’s launchpad will debut WEN on Friday, before next week’s JUP airdrop. Here’s who is eligible to claim the Solana meme coin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AltLayer Airdrop Puts $100 Million Into the Wallets of Ethereum Users]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=214245</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/214245/altlayer-airdrop-puts-103-million-into-wallets-ethereum-users"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T17:05:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Another day, another airdrop. About half a million Ethereum wallets can claim the AltLayer (ALT) token now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Steadies on Strong GDP Report in U.S.]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=214210</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/214210/bitcoin-steadies-on-strong-gdp-report-in-u-s"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T15:31:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin remained steady on news that the U.S. economy grew more than expected during Q4, even if it did slow down from the previous quarter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10n8 Little Dragon Raises $1.5 Million in 72-Hour Fundraise]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213877</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213877/10n8-little-dragon-raises-1-5-million-in-72-hour-fundraise"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T15:29:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The gamified Bitcoin DeFi accelerator aims to be a “viral utility token,” building a DeFi and gaming ecosystem on Bitcoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Developer Refutes ‘Eternal You’ Documentary, Calls Foul on Its Depiction of His Chatbot]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=214163</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/214163/ai-developer-refutes-eternal-you-documentary-calls-depiction-of-his-chatbot-misleading"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jason Rohrer says the interactions with his AI model, based on a deceased person, were taken out of context in a new film screened at Sundance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Judge Blocks CZ Travel to UAE, Despite Offer to Use $4.5B Binance Equity as Security]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=214169</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/214169/judge-blocks-cz-travel-to-uae-despite-offer-to-use-4-5b-binance-equity-as-security"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T12:08:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Binance founder had requested to travel to the UAE to be present for the “hospitalization and surgery” of an unnamed individual.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All the Donald Trump, Joe Biden and U.S. Election-Themed Crypto Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=214170</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/214170/biggest-donald-trump-joe-biden-us-election-crypto-projects"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T12:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From meme coins to NFTs, here are all the biggest and zaniest crypto projects tied to U.S. elections.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telecom Giant Telefónica Launches Solana-Powered Helium Mobile Hotspots]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=214160</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/214160/telecom-giant-telefonica-launches-solana-powered-helium-mobile-hotspots"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T23:54:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nova Labs has teamed with Telefónica to deploy the wireless hotspots, which are incentivized with crypto tokens on Solana, in Mexico.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETFs Are Pulling in Billions—But Crypto Stocks Are Taking a Beating]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=214144</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/214144/bitcoin-etfs-pulling-billions-crypto-stocks-taking-beating"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T23:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin-related stocks like Coinbase and MicroStrategy are down as the price of the biggest cryptocurrency takes a heavy hit this month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gala Games Shuns Creator for Talking Too Much About Token Prices]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=214129</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/214129/gala-games-shuns-creator-talking-too-much-about-token-prices"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T22:02:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gala Games supports content creators, but doesn't want them focused on token prices and ROI. Can "moonboy" talk pose a real legal threat?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Delays Decision on BlackRock's Spot Ethereum ETF Application]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=214137</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/214137/sec-delays-decision-blackrock-ethereum-spot-etf-application"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T21:45:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC has delayed its decision on the long-awaited investment vehicle.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump’s Ethereum Wallet Holds $1.1M in MAGA Meme Coin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=214133</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/214133/donald-trump-ethereum-wallet-million-maga-meme-coin"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T21:39:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trump sold ETH last month, but he didn’t dump TRUMP. Now the Ethereum-based meme coin has skyrocketed in value.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Billionaire Arthur Hayes Says Bitcoin Could Fall to $30,000 in 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=214128</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/214128/crypto-billionaire-arthur-hayes-says-bitcoin-could-fall-to-30000-in-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T21:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The exCEO of Bitmex thinks that a series of wars and the need to finance them are among reasons to expect a steep crypto price correction before the next bull run.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Self-Described Bitcoin Inventor Craig Wright Offers to Settle IP Case]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=214116</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/214116/self-described-bitcoin-inventor-craig-wright-offers-to-settle-ip-case"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T19:16:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wright proposes a settlement in the dispute over Bitcoin’s creation, offering concessions to COPA ahead of the February 5 trial.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trash-Fueled BTC Mining w/ Chris Bennet]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/uLy5Y1E7/trash-fueled-btc-mining-w-chris-bennet</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/uLy5Y1E7/trash-fueled-btc-mining-w-chris-bennet"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T19:09:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reza is joined by Chris Bennet from Spacestation Investments.

They discuss:
- Mining BTC with energy generated from landfills
- How to increase deal-flow
- Running an agency vs running a fund]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Is Poised for Another Run—If Fed Cuts Rates: Analysts]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=214110</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/214110/bitcoin-is-poised-for-another-run-if-fed-cuts-rates-analysts"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T19:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin and Ethereum draw more investor interest amid ETF launches and eased monetary policies. Is crypto set to rise again?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Lender Nexo Sues Bulgaria for $3 Billion After Beating 'Politically Motivated' Investigation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=214108</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/214108/crypto-lender-nexo-sues-bulgaria-3-billion-beating-politically-motivated-investigation"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T18:32:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nexo claims that it would have closed an $8 billion raise if not for Bulgaria's office raid trashing the company's reputation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Biggest Nintendo Games Still Coming Before the Switch 2]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206987</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206987/biggest-nintendo-games-still-coming-before-switch-2"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T16:54:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATED: The Nintendo Switch 2 is reportedly on the horizon, but original Switch owners will have promising games ahead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bounces as Grayscale Slows Down Sales]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=214075</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/214075/bitcoin-bounces-grayscale-slows-down-sales"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T16:38:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin has jumped above $40,000 again after taking a big hit at the start of the week. Can we thank Grayscale for the reprieve?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gaming Tokens Rebound as Ronin and Beam Post Double-Digit Gains]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=214084</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/214084/gaming-tokens-rebound-ronin-beam-post-double-digit-gains"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T16:11:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ronin continues its recent rise amid Pixels game hype, while Beam and Immutable are bouncing back after a rough few weeks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Coinbase Earn Makes Staking Simple—and Secure]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211808</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211808/how-coinbase-earn-makes-staking-simple-and-secure"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase's staking program aims to be a “one-stop shop” for crypto staking, the firm's staking product lead told Decrypt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC's Hester Peirce: Bitcoin ETF 'Lesson Will Certainly Stick']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=214039</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/214039/secs-hester-peirce-bitcoin-etf-lesson-will-certainly-stick"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T13:27:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC Commissioner doubled down on remarks criticizing the regulator's handling of spot Bitcoin ETF approvals, in a recent interview.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Palworld' Roadmap Revealed—Huge Upgrades Are Coming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=214049</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/214049/palworld-roadmap-revealed-huge-upgrades-coming"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T12:54:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The "Pokémon with guns" game is an enormous hit. Here's a look at the bug fixes and new modes and features coming to Palworld.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Meme Coin Dogwifhat Soars 30% on Bitget Listing, SOL and BONK See Gains]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=214038</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/214038/solana-meme-coin-dogwifhat-soars-30-on-bitget-listing-sol-and-bonk-see-gains"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T12:11:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana meme coin Dogwifhat (WIF) soared as trading began on crypto exchange Bitget early Wednesday morning.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Target Crypto Email Lists, Send Phishing Attacks Netting Over $700,000]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=214033</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/214033/hackers-target-crypto-email-lists-send-phishing-attacks-steal-700000"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T02:23:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The MailerLite email marketing service says an employee was phished and allowed internal access to its systems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are Mt. Gox Creditor Gears Turning? Rumors Rattle Bitcoin Market]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213987</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213987/mt-gox-repayment-reports-bitcoin-crash"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T01:40:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin fell after reports emerged saying Mt. Gox has started to repay its creditors—dragging the rest of the cryptocurrency market with it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Palworld Isn’t a Crypto Game—But It Is a Vampire Attack on Pokémon]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213978</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213978/palworld-isnt-crypto-game-but-vampire-attack-pokemon"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T00:14:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's "Pokémon with guns" and it's the hottest thing in gaming right now. Why Palworld is the video game equivalent of a crypto vampire attack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is a Crypto Token Itself a Security? SEC Can't Make Up Its Mind]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213990</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213990/crypto-token-itself-security-sec-cant-make-up-mind-coinbase-binance"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T23:56:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apparent contradictions in the SEC’s arguments in the Coinbase and Binance lawsuits expose mounting legal troubles for the regulator, experts say.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jupiter Launching Solana Meme Coin With An Airdrop Even Bigger Than JUP]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213983</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213983/jupiter-solana-meme-coin-airdrop-bigger-than-jup"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T23:31:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Waiting for the Jupiter airdrop? Jupiter’s launchpad will deploy a Solana meme coin to even more wallets this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Watch Your Mouth, Anon: 'Call of Duty' AI Tool Punishes Millions of Toxic Players]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213971</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213971/watch-your-mouth-anon-call-of-duty-ai-tool-punishes-millions-of-toxic-players"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T23:02:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over 2 million accounts have faced enforcement for disruptive chat since the launch of the AI-powered ToxMod tool for Call of Duty.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Preview of Agoria's 'Le Code d’Orsay']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PK7ynKMB/preview-of-agorias-le-code-dorsay</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PK7ynKMB/preview-of-agorias-le-code-dorsay"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A first look at "Sigma Lumina," a sculpture by artist and musician Agoria in collaboration with Johan Lescure. It features in "Le Code d’Orsay," the first NFT exhibition at the Musée d’Orsay.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are you the one being farmed? w/ Frisson]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/i3sesrao/are-you-the-one-being-farmed-w-frisson</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/i3sesrao/are-you-the-one-being-farmed-w-frisson"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T18:38:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reza is joined by Frisson from Tallyx.xyz

They reflect on:
- building in the bear market
- the points system meta
- will zoomers care about decentralization]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Look Touch Own': OONA Discusses Her Performance Art Exhibition]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/79jpGlCe/look-touch-own-oona-discusses-her-performance-art-exhibition</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/79jpGlCe/look-touch-own-oona-discusses-her-performance-art-exhibition"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T16:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Conceptual artist OONA joins moderator Raina Marie to discuss "Look Touch Own," her performance art exhibition featuring her own former breast implants, which have been tokenized. This conversation was recorded at Rug Radio's R Haus event at Art Basel Miami in December 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Genius Marketing by Genius Marketers: How Crypto Builders Can Reach the Masses]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/YiQgzWJW/genius-marketing-by-genius-marketers-how-crypto-builders-can-reach-the-masses</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/YiQgzWJW/genius-marketing-by-genius-marketers-how-crypto-builders-can-reach-the-masses"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rug Radio founder Farokh Sarmad moderates a conversation between 9dcc founder and CEO Gmoney and Serotonin founder and CEO Amanda Cassatt about the challenges and opportunities in Web3 marketing and how they're navigating the ever-evolving space. Recorded at Rug Radio's R Haus event at Art Basel Miami in December 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generative Art Across Mediums: Artists Discuss the Evolving Space]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/GK3aN0zo/generative-art-across-mediums-artists-discuss-the-evolving-space</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/GK3aN0zo/generative-art-across-mediums-artists-discuss-the-evolving-space"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T02:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this panel discussion from Rug Radio's R Haus at Art Basel Miami 2023, Sofia Garcia, Ismail Tazi, Emily Edelman, and Aleksandra Art discuss the expanding generative art space—and why "generative" doesn't necessarily have to mean digital.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The AI Coin to Rule Them All with Mike Grantis]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rkYpU8TJ/the-ai-coin-to-rule-them-all-with-mike-grantis</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rkYpU8TJ/the-ai-coin-to-rule-them-all-with-mike-grantis"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T18:46:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reza is joined by Mike Grantis from Contango Digital to discuss
- The AI coin to rule them all
- The Solana Ecosystem 
- What's next for Solana airdrops]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conversation With Snowfro: Bringing 'Chromie Squiggle' #8107 to the Physical Space]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/DcrU04gG/conversation-with-snowfro-bringing-chromie-squiggle-8107-to-the-physical-space</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/DcrU04gG/conversation-with-snowfro-bringing-chromie-squiggle-8107-to-the-physical-space"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Art Blocks founder and CEO and "Chromie Squiggle" project creator Erick "snowfro" Calderon spoke with Benny Redbeard Gross at Rug Radio's R Haus event at Art Basel 2023, to discuss how and why "Chromie Squiggle" NFT #8107 was given a special edition print run in collaboration with Avant Arte.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don't Underestimate Mobile Gaming: Qualcomm's Matthew Grossman]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/34Oil4Qu/dont-underestimate-mobile-gaming-qualcomms-matthew-grossman</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/34Oil4Qu/dont-underestimate-mobile-gaming-qualcomms-matthew-grossman"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Qualcomm product marketing manager Matthew Grossman tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin why mobile esports is exploding in popularity around the world—and dispels some of the misconceptions around mobile gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF: This Is the 'Calm Before the Storm', Says ETF Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/VOX04ytt/bitcoin-etf-this-is-the-calm-before-the-storm-says-etf-analyst</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/VOX04ytt/bitcoin-etf-this-is-the-calm-before-the-storm-says-etf-analyst"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T20:20:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bloomberg Senior ETF Analyst Eric Balchunas joins Farokh Sarmad, Michael Anderson, and Ovie Faruq on the FOMO Hour to share the latest intel on the looming approval for a spot Bitcoin ETF, what might happen when the very different worlds of TradFi and crypto collide, and his insights on “Genslish,” the unique and strategic language of SEC chair Gary Gensler.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Losing 1500 BTC on Mt Gox and the Problem with Women in Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/EfNuNu8a/losing-1500-btc-on-mt-gox-and-the-problem-with-women-in-web3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/EfNuNu8a/losing-1500-btc-on-mt-gox-and-the-problem-with-women-in-web3"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T19:02:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week our host is joined by Brooke Lacey! 

They discuss:  
- Making and losing generational wealth
- Trauma Bond
- Women in Web3
- The Problem with WAGMI]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ESL Faceit Group Exploring Blockchain 'Opportunistically,' Says Exec]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/yvrs4lBx/esl-faceit-group-exploring-blockchain-opportunistically-says-exec</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/yvrs4lBx/esl-faceit-group-exploring-blockchain-opportunistically-says-exec"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T02:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Braithwaite—ESL Faceit Group's VP of Game Ecosystems, Mobile, and Snapdragon Pro Series—shares the esports firm's approach to blockchain technology with GG's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>