<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-10-17T09:20:04.964Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-10-17T09:20:04.964Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Flashing Bullish Signal That Previously Triggered Huge Run, Says Crypto Analyst – Here’s His Outlook]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20033491/Bitcoin-Flashing-Bullish-Signal-That-Previously-Triggered-Huge-Run-Says-Crypto-Analyst-Heres-His-Outlook</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20033491/Bitcoin-Flashing-Bullish-Signal-That-Previously-Triggered-Huge-Run-Says-Crypto-Analyst-Heres-His-Outlook"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T09:15:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Analyst and trader Kevin Svenson is leaning bullish on Bitcoin (BTC) amid a rally that has seen Bitcoin go up by nearly 15% over the past six days. Svenson tells his 80,000 YouTube subscribers in a new video that the Relative Strength Index (RSI) indicator, a momentum oscillator used for...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin open interest hit another all-time high adding 32,440 BTC in 7 days]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20033466/Bitcoin-open-interest-hit-another-all-time-high-adding-32440-BTC-in-7-days</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20033466/Bitcoin-open-interest-hit-another-all-time-high-adding-32440-BTC-in-7-days"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T09:09:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s open interest has reached another all-time high, with CME’s notional open interest closing at 179,745 BTC, according to Vetle Lunde, Head of Research at K33 Research. Open interest has grown by 32,440 BTC since Oct. 10, representing a 40% weekly growth in exposure driven by active...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s WLFI Presale Raises $12M, 4% of $300M Goal]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20033296/Trumps-WLFI-Presale-Raises-12M-4-of-300M-Goal</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20033296/Trumps-WLFI-Presale-Raises-12M-4-of-300M-Goal"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T09:04:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This initiative raised $12 million in just 30 hours. That’s just 4% of its $300 million goal. The project, closely tied to Trump and his family, launched its initial token sale early Tuesday. While they’ve made a dent, the $12 million is far from the $300 million target they’re hoping to hit....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum’s Vitalik Buterin Shares Roadmap for L2 Scalability for 100K TPS]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20033266/Ethereums-Vitalik-Buterin-Shares-Roadmap-for-L2-Scalability-for-100K-TPS</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20033266/Ethereums-Vitalik-Buterin-Shares-Roadmap-for-L2-Scalability-for-100K-TPS"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T09:03:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinspeaker Ethereum’s Vitalik Buterin Shares Roadmap for L2 Scalability for 100K TPS Vitalik Buterin outlined Ethereum’s scalability roadmap, known as "Surge," aiming for 100,000 transactions per second (TPS) across the mainnet and Layer-2 (L2) blockchains. Ethereum’s Vitalik Buterin Shares...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There’s A Proposal To Decentralize Cardano Physical Infrastructure: Will ADA Prices Push Higher?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7447c6195e</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/decentralize-cardano-physical-infrastructure/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T09:02:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano is one of the largest blockchains and among the first to use the proof-of-stake consensus algorithm. While the network has been slipping away from the top 10, it remains one of the most decentralized platforms. Pooltool data shows that Cardano has over 2,800 stake pools (or validators) when writing on October 16. 
 
 
To maintain this level of decentralization, stake pool operators must run nodes and maintain a high uptime, over 99%, to avoid penalties. This is often achieved using centralized cloud service providers like Google, Amazon, and others.
 
Developer Proposes To Decentralize Computing Resource Using Physical Infrastructure
 
A proposal now aims to decentralize the physical computing infrastructure, ensuring that stake pool operators don’t spend cash on centralized soluti…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dalmas Ngetich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cosmos Faces Security Concerns Over Inherited Malicious Code]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20033175/Cosmos-Faces-Security-Concerns-Over-Inherited-Malicious-Code</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20033175/Cosmos-Faces-Security-Concerns-Over-Inherited-Malicious-Code"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T09:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cosmos (ATOM) is at risk due to potentially harmful code inherited from North Korean hackers disguised as developers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu’s 14,575% hike – Good news for SHIB’s price or should traders beware?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20033262/Shiba-Inus-14575-hike-Good-news-for-SHIBs-price-or-should-traders-beware</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20033262/Shiba-Inus-14575-hike-Good-news-for-SHIBs-price-or-should-traders-beware"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T09:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SHIB’s burn rate surge and growing network activity are good signs, but is that all?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What size stimulus will be enough to jumpstart China’s economy?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20033157/What-size-stimulus-will-be-enough-to-jumpstart-Chinas-economy</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20033157/What-size-stimulus-will-be-enough-to-jumpstart-Chinas-economy"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T09:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[China's government threw some serious money at the economy, leading to a brief surge in the stock market. The CSI 300 index in Shanghai and Shenzhen jumped by 25%, and Hong Kong’s Hang Seng shot up by 21% in just two weeks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 New Crypto Jobs You Can Apply for Now – Oct17th]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20033142/8-New-Crypto-Jobs-You-Can-Apply-for-Now-Oct17th</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20033142/8-New-Crypto-Jobs-You-Can-Apply-for-Now-Oct17th"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T08:53:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptopolitan Job Posting Newsletter brings you top job picks in Crypto and Blockchain. Stay updated on the latest job openings and advance your career in Web3. Protocol Tester · Remote · Full-time https://ethereum.foundation WHO WE ARE: The Ethereum Foundation (EF) is a global non-profit...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Tax Is The Next Major Nut To Crack, Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20033143/Crypto-Tax-Is-The-Next-Major-Nut-To-Crack-Heres-Why</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20033143/Crypto-Tax-Is-The-Next-Major-Nut-To-Crack-Heres-Why"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T08:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite uncertainty in crypto tax concerns, digital currencies continue to capture the attention of investors, traditional organizations, and governments. While crypto trading has gained traction as a legal tender in countries like El Salvador, others have recorded slow adoption. In most...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These 2 Meme Coins Chart Biggest Daily Gains as Bitcoin (BTC) Maintains $67K (Market Watch)]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20033134/These-2-Meme-Coins-Chart-Biggest-Daily-Gains-as-Bitcoin-BTC-Maintains-67K-Market-Watch</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20033134/These-2-Meme-Coins-Chart-Biggest-Daily-Gains-as-Bitcoin-BTC-Maintains-67K-Market-Watch"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T08:48:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The two memes in question are NEIRO and BONK.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Defies Election Jitters, Analyst Sees King Crypto Scaling $70K Milestone Again 'In The Coming Weeks']]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20033297/Bitcoin-Defies-Election-Jitters-Analyst-Sees-King-Crypto-Scaling-70K-Milestone-Again-In-The-Coming-Weeks</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20033297/Bitcoin-Defies-Election-Jitters-Analyst-Sees-King-Crypto-Scaling-70K-Milestone-Again-In-The-Coming-Weeks"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T08:47:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (CRYPTO: BTC) has once again captured the spotlight after a notable rally this week so far, defying election jitters, with analysts forecasting a potential rise to $70,000 in the near future. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Record Crypto Activity in 2024, Led by Solana’s 100M Active Addresses: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20033120/Record-Crypto-Activity-in-2024-Led-by-Solanas-100M-Active-Addresses-Report</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20033120/Record-Crypto-Activity-in-2024-Led-by-Solanas-100M-Active-Addresses-Report"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T08:42:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The “2024 State of Crypto” report from a16z Crypto, the cryptocurrency-focused arm of the venture capital firm Andreessen Horowitz (a16z), presents an in-depth look at the significant advancements in the cryptocurrency space, revealing an industry that has not only grown but also evolved in key...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Moves 42 Million RLUSD in 48 Hours—Is a Major Launch Around the Corner?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20033101/Ripple-Moves-42-Million-RLUSD-in-48-HoursIs-a-Major-Launch-Around-the-Corner</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20033101/Ripple-Moves-42-Million-RLUSD-in-48-HoursIs-a-Major-Launch-Around-the-Corner"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T08:39:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple recently transferred 42 million RLUSD stablecoins within 48 hours, intensifying community excitement around the stablecoin’s potential launch. According to Ripple Stablecoin Tracker on X, Ripple minted and moved large RLUSD batches, with the largest transfer alone reaching 18 million...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ireland Catching Up with EU Deadline: Urgently Drafting Crypto Laws]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7447c1428e</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com/cryptocurrency/ireland-catching-up-with-eu-deadline-urgently-drafting-crypto-laws/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T08:38:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Irish lawmakers are urgently preparing legislation covering digital assets and crypto firms ahead of the broader European Union’s anti-money laundering and terror financing laws, set to be enacted on 30 December 2024.
According to a report by the Irish Examiner, Ireland’s Finance Minister, Jack Chambers, has already asked the cabinet to draft this urgent law, as the country needs to update its regulations before the European bloc's deadline.
EU Moves Ahead with Crypto Laws
The 27-country European bloc’s Anti-Money Laundering and Countering the Financing of Terrorism Act covers crypto transactions. However, it differs from the Markets in Crypto-Assets Regulation (MiCA), which partially came into effect earlier this year, with its remaining provisions set to be enforced by the end of 2024.
W…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arnab Shome</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nishad Singh’s defense pushes for no jail time, citing ‘limited’ role in FTX case]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20033082/Nishad-Singhs-defense-pushes-for-no-jail-time-citing-limited-role-in-FTX-case</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20033082/Nishad-Singhs-defense-pushes-for-no-jail-time-citing-limited-role-in-FTX-case"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T08:33:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Attorneys for Nishad Singh, a former FTX executive, said his circumstances are 'extraordinary in every way that matters to sentencing.']]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russia’s Digital Currency Measures Fail to Satisfy FATF, Blacklist Possible]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7447c202ea</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/russias-digital-currency-measures-fail-to-satisfy-fatf-blacklist-possible/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T08:32:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Russia’s financial regulator maintains that its anti-money laundering system, including strengthened virtual currency regulations, remains effective even if the country faces potential blacklisting by the Financial Action Task Force (FATF). The agency highlighted new federal laws addressing previous concerns and stressed that no significant deficiencies exist that would justify Russia’s inclusion on the FATF blacklist, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Future of Ethereum: Vitalik Buterin Unveils Ambitious Goals for ETH 2.0]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20033070/Future-of-Ethereum-Vitalik-Buterin-Unveils-Ambitious-Goals-for-ETH-20</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20033070/Future-of-Ethereum-Vitalik-Buterin-Unveils-Ambitious-Goals-for-ETH-20"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T08:30:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin reveals goals for the future of Ethereum, focusing on the Ethereum 2.0 upgrade and "The Surge" to improve scalability and efficiency. 
The post Future of Ethereum: Vitalik Buterin Unveils Ambitious Goals for ETH 2.0 first appeared on Ecoinimist.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tech Titans Set to Battle for $4 Trillion Valuation as U.S. Stock Market Soars]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20033069/Tech-Titans-Set-to-Battle-for-4-Trillion-Valuation-as-US-Stock-Market-Soars</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20033069/Tech-Titans-Set-to-Battle-for-4-Trillion-Valuation-as-US-Stock-Market-Soars"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T08:30:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. stock market has shown remarkable resilience in 2024, with the S&P 500 rising by 22.76% year-to-date, even amid rising concerns about various risks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BREAKING: Things Are About To GET INTENSE For Bitcoin And Altcoins, I HOPE EVERYONE IS READY]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20033104/BREAKING-Things-Are-About-To-GET-INTENSE-For-Bitcoin-And-Altcoins-I-HOPE-EVERYONE-IS-READY</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20033104/BREAKING-Things-Are-About-To-GET-INTENSE-For-Bitcoin-And-Altcoins-I-HOPE-EVERYONE-IS-READY"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T08:30:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OH BOY, things are about to heat up for Bitcoin and cryptocurrencies. I honestly can't believe that we finally made it.--------------------------------------------------------Keep Your Crypto Wealth SAFE With A Ledger...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano: What ADA needs to break out of the ‘neutral’ zone]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20033074/Cardano-What-ADA-needs-to-break-out-of-the-neutral-zone</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20033074/Cardano-What-ADA-needs-to-break-out-of-the-neutral-zone"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T08:30:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ADA is on the verge of a breakout, but RSI places it in the neutral territory. Can market sentiment and volume push ADA higher?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Promoter Flees With Investor’s Money, Gets 20 Years Jail Term]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20033068/Crypto-Promoter-Flees-With-Investors-Money-Gets-20-Years-Jail-Term</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20033068/Crypto-Promoter-Flees-With-Investors-Money-Gets-20-Years-Jail-Term"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T08:30:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the Forcount Ponzi scandal, U.S. courts sentenced cryptocurrency marketer Juan Tacuri to 20 years in prison for his role in a fraudulent scheme masquerading as a crypto mining venture. This scam targeted thousands of investors, particularly in Hispanic communities across the United States....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s Presidential Win Could Ignite Bitcoin Bull Run Hints Prediction Market]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20033036/Trumps-Presidential-Win-Could-Ignite-Bitcoin-Bull-Run-Hints-Prediction-Market</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20033036/Trumps-Presidential-Win-Could-Ignite-Bitcoin-Bull-Run-Hints-Prediction-Market"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T08:28:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin is on fire! After last week’s surge, the crypto bulls are eyeing the all-time highs of March, with prices jumping 11% to over $67,800. This Bitcoin rally is turning heads and sparking excitement among investors, many of whom think it points to a big win for pro-crypto Republican...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kalshi Research Finds 'Widespread Evidence' of Strong Republican Momentum in U.S. Elections]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7447c33d9c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/10/17/kalshi-research-finds-widespread-evidence-of-strong-republican-momentum-in-us-elections/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T08:23:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A note from Kalshi's market research team suggests the prediction market - polls gap can be explained by Harris' sliding popularity with key demographics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong Police Take Down $46 Million Romance Crypto Scam—Here’s How]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7447ce64df</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/hong-kong-police-take-down-million-romance-crypto/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T08:02:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong authorities have dismantled a HK$360 million ($46.3 million) cryptocurrency-based romance fraud scheme in a significant crackdown on fraud operations.
 
This scheme, which targeted individuals over a year, reportedly lured victims into investing in cryptocurrencies under the guise of online romantic relationships.
 
 
Detailing The Scheme And The Seizure
 
The operation, codenamed “Secret Word,” culminated in the arrest of 27 suspects who allegedly masterminded the fraud and swindled unsuspecting individuals from Hong Kong and other countries, including India, Singapore, and Malaysia.
 
The Hong Kong police deployed over 100 officers to investigate and conduct an onsite raid, seizing over HK$200,000 ($25,742) in cash, luxury watches, and other valuables.
 
Among the items confisc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sui Foundation Denies $400 Million Token Sales Claims]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7447c98d3d</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/sui-foundation-denies-400-million-token-sales-claims/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T07:35:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Sui Foundation has denied allegations that its employees or insiders from Mysten Labs sold $400 million worth of SUI tokens. The foundation also rejected claims that insiders were involved in preemptive selling or violating token lockup agreements. Sui Insiders Dumping on Retail Investors Allegations The Sui Foundation has dismissed claims that its employees or […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Retail Investors Returning To The Market – Metrics Show Increasing Demand]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7447b5b1a0</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-retail-investors-returning-to-the-market-metrics-show-increasing-demand/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T07:02:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin has surged past the $67,000 mark and is testing key supply levels to determine its next target. As election day approaches, the crypto market is experiencing heightened volatility, fueling expectations of a potential Bitcoin rally. 
 
Key data from CryptoQuant reveals that retail investors are returning to the market, marking a resurgence in demand that could signal the beginning of a broader rally. As the price continues to climb, this renewed interest from retail participants is seen as a bullish indicator, adding momentum to Bitcoin’s rise.
 
 
The cryptocurrency has also benefited from a strong buy wall on exchanges, further supporting the price and dampening selling pressure. As Bitcoin holds above crucial support levels, market sentiment remains optimistic, suggesting that fu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Villafuerte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Asian Private Wealth Managers Embrace Crypto, Some Foresee Bitcoin at $100K By Year-End]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7447b77c8c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/10/17/asian-private-wealth-managers-embrace-crypto-some-foresee-bitcoin-at-100k-by-year-end/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T06:45:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Asian Private Wealth Managers Embrace Crypto, Some Foresee Bitcoin at $100 By Year-End]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gold Arrives on 'Digital Gold' as Bitcoin Gets Tokenized Version of the Metal]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7447b77c87</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2024/10/17/gold-arrives-on-digital-gold-as-bitcoin-gets-tokenized-version-of-the-metal/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T06:45:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin is often referred to as "digital gold," but now it is possible to mint and trade physical gold on the Bitcoin blockchain via the Ordinals protocol.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Sends Crypto Promoter to Prison for 20 Years in Multi-Million Dollar Ponzi Scheme]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7447b0969a</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/us-sends-crypto-promoter-to-prison-for-20-years-in-multi-million-dollar-ponzi-scheme/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T06:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A cryptocurrency promoter was sentenced to 20 years in prison for running a Ponzi scheme that defrauded thousands of investors, particularly in Spanish-speaking U.S. communities. The scheme, disguised as a crypto mining operation, promised guaranteed returns but left victims unable to withdraw funds while promoters pocketed millions. The fraudster was ordered to forfeit over $3.6 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Demand Surges in Bullish Catalyst That May Drive BTC Price to $70K]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7447b1dff1</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/10/17/bitcoin-demand-surges-in-bullish-catalyst-that-may-drive-btc-price-to-70k/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T06:23:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Technical indicators point to a price surge, and Polymarket bettors have their money on BTC passing $70K this month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa, Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin Lays Out Grand Vision for Ethereum Layer 2's With ‘The Surge’ Roadmap]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286826</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286826/vitalik-buterin-lays-out-grand-vision-ethereum-layer-2s-the-surge-roadmap"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T06:09:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While Buterin didn’t give an exact date for when The Surge would be fully implemented, he did call for sustained progress for Ethereum.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vismaya V</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nishad Singh’s Lawyers Ask Judge to Spare Him Prison, Say He Is an 'Uncommonly Selfless Individual']]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7447bc2e30</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/10/17/nishad-singhs-lawyers-ask-judge-to-spare-him-prison-say-he-is-an-uncommonly-selfless-individual/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T06:04:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lawyers say that his early cooperation was critical to bringing cases against Sam Bankman-Fried and Ryan Salame.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Callan Quinn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Jumps 10% Just As 106,600 Holders Give Up On DOGE]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7447bc5b8a</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-jumps-10-just-as-106600-holders-doge/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T06:02:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin has just witnessed a rally of around 10% after on-chain data signaled a mass exodus of holders from the DOGE network.
 
Dogecoin Has Seen A Jump Of Almost 12% Over The Past Day
 
This week has brought bullish winds in the cryptocurrency sector as a whole, but among the top coins, one asset in particular has stood out: Dogecoin. The meme-based token has managed to surpass the $0.127 level after registering an uplift of nearly 12% during the last 24 hours.
 

 
 
For perspective, Bitcoin (BTC) is up around 4% in the same window, while Shiba Inu (SHIB), DOGE’s rival-coin, is up about 5%. The asset has also performed well in terms of weekly returns, with only Bitcoin Cash (BCH) with its 12% returns coming close to DOGE’s 14% profits.
 
 
The DOGE market cap has now grown to $18.5 bill…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Euroclear Enters Asia with Stake in Singapore’s Blockchain Infrastructure Firm Marketnode]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286823</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286823/euroclear-enters-asia-stake-singapores-blockchain-infrastructure-firm-marketnode"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T05:34:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Euroclear has made its first Asian investment, acquiring a stake in blockchain-focused Marketnode, backed by Temasek, SGX Group, and HSBC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Sinclair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hermetica Raises $1.7M in Seed Round to Fuel Stablecoin Expansion]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7447bf2c5d</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/hermetica-raises-1-7m-in-seed-round-to-fuel-stablecoin-expansion/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T05:33:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hermetica, the creator of USDH, a Bitcoin-backed, yield-bearing synthetic dollar, has secured $1.7 million in seed funding. The round, led by UTXO Management, will accelerate the development of USDH, a stablecoin that operates on Bitcoin’s layer one (L1) and layer two (L2) networks. USDH Gains Momentum as Hermetica Raises $1.7 Million in Seed Funding According […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[October Crypto Shock: Phishing Scams Drain $41 Million From Victims]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7447ba9f9b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/phishing-scams-drain-over-41-million-from-victims/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T05:03:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A whopping $41 million has been lost in October so far due to the increasing influx of phishing attacks. Most of the phishing operations within the crypto space usually involve engaging users in signing actions through their crypto wallets, to approve contracts or linking permissions.
 
 
Making false tokens that look like real wallet tokens is one typical phishing method used to pilfer cryptocurrencies from victims’ wallets. Particularly harmful is permit phishing since it lets several highly valuable tokens be transferred simultaneously.
 
 
 3 hours ago, another victim lost $1.57M after signing a “permit” phishing signature. pic.twitter.com/wDGZIMdJ7N
 
— Scam Sniffer | Web3 Anti-Scam (@realScamSniffer) October 15, 2024
 

 
Phishing: Hackers Getting Smarter
 
An example is a wallet bre…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Set to Rise Beyond $70,000 in 'Coming Weeks,' Experts Say]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286814</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286814/bitcoin-rise-beyond-70000-coming-weeks-experts-say"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T04:45:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin's upward momentum remains robust, with market experts forecasting a rise beyond its March all-time high.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Second 2011 Bitcoin Wallet Moves $10M This Week—Could the Transfers Be Linked?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7447a5a4f4</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/a-second-2011-bitcoin-wallet-moves-10m-this-week-could-the-transfers-be-linked/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T04:33:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Wednesday, as bitcoin soared to an intraday peak of $68,388 per coin, a wallet from 2011 suddenly sprang to life after lying dormant for over 13 years, spending 150 BTC, valued at $10.17 million. This latest awakening follows the movement of 100 BTC from a similar 2011 address just two days earlier. Bitcoin Wallet […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Makes Grayscale’s List Of Potential Crypto Products, Is A DOGE ETF Coming?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7447a25258</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-grayscale-doge-etf/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T04:03:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto asset management giant Grayscale has recently announced its consideration of expanding its offerings to include products based on the popular meme cryptocurrency, Dogecoin. In a recent blog post, Grayscale highlighted that Dogecoin has caught the company’s attention as a potential asset for future investment products. As the king of meme coins, a Dogecoin-based crypto product would be a turning point for the entire meme coin niche. 
 
Dogecoin Product To Hit The Market Soon?
 
This extensive portfolio includes top-tier digital assets such as Bitcoin, the number one cryptocurrency by market cap, alongside a variety of innovative and emerging tokens like Filecoin (FIL), Bittensor (TAO), and Decentraland (MANA), to name a few. 
 
 
Grayscale’s involvement in such a wide spectrum of cry…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$7.5 Million In Bitcoin, ETH, XRP Powers Trump’s Latest Campaign Efforts]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7447a25253</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/7-5-million-bitcoin-eth-xrp-trump-campaign/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T04:03:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A political action committee supporting former President Donald Trump has raised approximately $7.5 million in crypto donations since early June, according to a recent filing with the Federal Election Commission. The Trump 47 joint fundraising committee received contributions in Bitcoin, Ether, XRP, as well as stablecoins Tether and USD Coin.
 
The latest filing, submitted on Tuesday, covers donations from July 1 through September 30 and includes cumulative contributions. This huge amount of crypto donations confirms the previous data, which confirmed that the industry is betting heavily on Trump, with the US election only three weeks away.
 
Bitcoin And Crypto Donations Bolster Trump Campaign
 
Trump, who previously expressed skepticism toward Bitcoin and cryptocurrencies during his presi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BRICS Bank Offers Zimbabwe Escape From IMF Debt Traps, Says Professor]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7447acf5c5</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/brics-bank-offers-zimbabwe-escape-from-imf-debt-traps-says-professor/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T03:32:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Zimbabwean professor has highlighted the BRICS New Development Bank (NDB) as a crucial alternative to the International Monetary Fund (IMF), offering better financial terms to developing nations. He emphasized the NDB’s role in helping countries like Zimbabwe escape debt cycles and discussed the introduction of Zimbabwe Gold (ZiG), a currency backed by mineral wealth, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Italy Targets Bitcoin With Capital Gains Tax Hike as EU Prepares for MiCA Regulations]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7447a998a1</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/italy-targets-bitcoin-with-capital-gains-tax-hike-as-eu-prepares-for-mica-regulations/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T02:34:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Italy plans to raise its capital gains tax on bitcoin to 42%, up from 26%, as part of efforts to fund election promises and curb the fiscal deficit. The government cites growing bitcoin adoption as a key factor. This comes as the European Union prepares to implement its Markets in Crypto-Assets Regulation (MiCA), aiming to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood Targets Seasoned Traders With Bitcoin Futures, New Desktop Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286802</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286802/robinhood-targets-seasoned-traders-with-bitcoin-futures-new-desktop-platform"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T00:04:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood told Decrypt on Wednesday its futures offerings via its trading app is expected in the “coming months.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Sinclair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miners Gain Record Hash Rate as JP Morgan Gives Nod to Sector Ahead of US Election]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286786</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286786/bitcoin-miners-gain-record-hash-rate-jp-morgan-gives-nod-sector-us-election"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T23:07:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The combined hash rate of U.S.-publicly listed bitcoin miners now accounts for a record 28.9% of the network, J.P. Morgan said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Meta Is Helping AI Models 'Think' Clearly Before Answering]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286731</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286731/meta-helping-ai-models-think"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T22:12:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meta researchers introduced TPO, a technique that teaches an AI model to essentially "think" about an answer before responding.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Weather Agency Turns to AI for More Accurate and Faster Hurricane Forecasts]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286788</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286788/us-weather-agency-turns-to-ai-for-more-accurate-and-faster-hurricane-forecasts"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T22:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The agency, which has been utilizing machine learning for years, is now leaning heavily on neural networks to boost prediction accuracy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Is Today’s 'Tomarket' Telegram Game Daily Combo]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286780</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/here-is-todays-tomarket-telegram-game-daily-combo"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T21:39:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram game Tomarket is handing out free tomatoes and bonus items ahead of the airdrop. Here’s the combo for Wednesday, October 16.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Hits Miami, But XRP Army Appears MIA]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286730</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286730/ripple-miami-xrp-army"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T21:22:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Labs’ eighth annual Ripple Swell event featured panels and accoutrements intended for a white-collar crowd.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Realm of Historia Making History ‘Accessible’ With First NFT Collection]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286629</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286629/realm-of-historia-making-history-accessible-with-first-nft-collection"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T21:13:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cultural heritage preservation platform has launched its first NFT collection, focused on Armenia’s ancient Carahunge site.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Radiant Capital Exploited for $50 Million Across BNB Chain, Arbitrum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286728</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286728/radiant-capital-exploited-50-million"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T20:58:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Radiant confirmed that its lending markets were facing an "issue" Wednesday, urging users to revoke permissions to smart contracts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Napolitano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prada Reveals Futuristic Spacesuit for NASA's Next Moon Landing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286653</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286653/prada-spacesuit-nasa-moon-landing"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T20:09:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AxEMU suit combines Prada’s material expertise and Axiom’s tech for NASA's return to the lunar surface.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Limits, Technical Hitches Combine for Lackluster Trump Token Sale]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286650</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286650/lackluster-trump-token-sale"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T19:54:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Donald Trump-backed World Liberty Financial has only sold through 4% of its allotted tokens so far. What happened?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Trader Turns $5K Into $1.5 Million With Lucky Bet on GOAT Meme Coin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286672</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286672/goat-trader-turns-5k-into-1-5-million"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T19:37:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greatest of all trades? A Solana meme coin trader hit the jackpot with GOAT, a token based on an AI chatbot's musings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BTC hits $68K, Trump odds Continue to Rise, GOAT nears $300M]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/c88qN8eB/btc-hits-68k-trump-odds-continue-to-rise-goat-nears-300m</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/c88qN8eB/btc-hits-68k-trump-odds-continue-to-rise-goat-nears-300m"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T18:31:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC hits $68k as ETF inflows continue to soar. Open Interest at CME hits ATH, funding still low. Tesla moves $750m BTC to new wallet. Canary applies for Litcoin ETF, LTC up 8%. Grayscale asks SEC to convert altcoin fund to ETF. Kraken integrates with EigenLayer for restaking. ‘Network state’ Praxis raises $525m for new city. Trump project raises only $11m so far. a16z founders donate $2.5m to Trump PAC. TikTok accused of being crypto exchange in UK. Gotbit CEO arrested in Portugal. Perplexity AI launches finance platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Florida Man Sentenced to 20 Years in Prison Over Crypto Ponzi Scheme]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286647</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286647/florida-man-20-years-prison-ponzi"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T17:37:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Juan Tacuri was sentenced to 20 years in prison on Tuesday following what prosecutors described as an elaborate crypto Ponzi scheme.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Italy Reveals 62% Increase in Bitcoin Capital Gains Tax]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286630</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286630/italy-increase-bitcoin-capital-gains-tax"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T17:18:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Italian government has proposed a capital gains tax jump on Bitcoin and other crypto assets, rising from 26% to 42%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Pumps Following Elon Musk 'D.O.G.E.' Tweet]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286595</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286595/dogecoin-pumps-elon-musk-tweet"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T16:29:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin is the biggest gainer in the top 40 coins this week, and the reason appears to be a familiar one: Elon Musk tweets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developers Linked to North Korea Helped Develop Cosmos Staking Module, Says Co-Founder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286539</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286539/developers-linked-to-north-korea-helped-develop-cosmos-staking-module-says-co-founder"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T15:46:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Cosmos co-founder attributed the oversight to "gross negligence" by validator hosting firm Iqlusion and its leader, Zaki Manian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Is Today’s 'Captain Tsubasa: Rivals' Telegram Game Daily Combo]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=250928</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/captain-tsubasa-rivals-telegram-game-daily-combo"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T15:12:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anime soccer game Captain Tsubasa: Rivals gives out 5 million free daily balls ahead of the TON token airdrop. Here’s the combo for Wednesday, October 16.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Are Today’s ‘X Empire’ Elon Musk Game Daily Combo and Rebus Solution]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241078</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/todays-musk-empire-stock-exchange-daily-combo"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T15:10:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking for the X Empire daily combo and rebus solution for Wednesday, October 16? Here are the latest boosts for the Telegram game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK Political Parties Ignoring Crypto Is ‘Disservice’ to Constituents, Says Ex-Tory MP]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286540</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286540/uk-parties-disservice-crypto-ex-tory-mp"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T15:04:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dr. Lisa Cameron, former chair of the UK Crypto Parliamentary Group, said parties need to address crypto in the next election campaign.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tales Reveals Gaming AI: Enables Users to Build &amp; Play Any Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286607</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286607/tales-reveals-gaming-ai-enables-users-to-build-play-any-game"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T15:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Palo Alto, California, 16th October 2024, GamingWire]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GamingWire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ireland To Draft ‘Urgent’ New Crypto Rules Ahead of EU Money Laundering Crackdown]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286587</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286587/ireland-to-draft-urgent-new-crypto-rules-ahead-of-eu-money-laundering-crackdown"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T13:30:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The EU's Anti-Money Laundering and Countering the Financing of Terrorism Act comes into play on December 30th 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will McCurdy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Will 'Rise Stupendously' as Middle East Conflict Intensifies, Says Arthur Hayes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286547</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286547/bitcoin-rise-stupendously-geopolitical-tensions-arthur-hayes"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T13:02:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Bitcoin and crypto will rise as energy prices spike higher," Hayes wrote, if the conflict in the Middle East causes energy prices to rise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Accuses SEC of 'Erroneous Denials' in Delayed FOIA Request]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286536</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286536/coinbase-sec-erroneous-denials-foia"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T12:47:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase’s latest motion escalates tensions with the SEC that have been building over the past year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vismaya V</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Off the Grid' Hex Guide: How to Extract the Most Hexes in the Battle Royale Shooter]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286413</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/off-the-grid-game-hex-guide"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T11:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trying to rack up the most hex extractions in Off the Grid to unlock weapons and skins? Here are five tips to boost your game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Stubbs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Faces Correction Risk as Open Interest Surges Amid Low Trading Volume]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286520</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286520/bitcoin-price-faces-correction-risk-as-open-interest-surges-amid-low-trading-volume"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T10:56:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["The market is becoming fragile, and any loss of momentum could trigger a swift correction," an analyst from CEX.io told Decrypt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Every Blockchain Project Will ‘Have a Telegram Complement,’ Animoca CEO Says]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286096</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286096/web3-project-telegram-animoca-ceo"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T10:18:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animoca Brands CEO, Robby Yung, says that Telegram gaming is ‘representative’ of mass adoption and other projects will get onboard.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Warren Says Political Rival Deaton Will 'Fight for Crypto' if Elected to Replace Her in the Senate]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286517</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286517/warren-says-deaton-will-fight-for-crypto-if-elected-to-replace-her-in-senate"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T06:01:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“I wish Senator Warren attacked inflation the way she attacks crypto,” John Keaton said during in the debate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vismaya V</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Bot Pumps Meme Coin 7,000% Following $50,000 Gift from Billionaire Marc Andreessen]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286478</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286478/ai-bot-pumps-meme-coin-7000-following-50000-gift-from-billionaire-marc-andreessen"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T02:22:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The sudden surge of meme coins like GOAT underscores a broader trend where digital memes are fueling speculative financial bets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken Launches Restaking on Ethereum-Based Protocol EigenLayer]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286494</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286494/kraken-launches-restaking-on-ethereum-based-protocol-eigenlayer"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T01:17:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken is letting non-U.S. customers directly restake their ETH on Eigen Layer amid booming growth in the sector.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Napolitano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Salvadorans May Like Bukele But They Aren’t Using Bitcoin, Survey Finds]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286463</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286463/salvadorans-like-bukele-but-arent-using-bitcoin-survey-says"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T22:54:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new University report shows that not many people are using the orange coin to buy things in El Salvador.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Ending Direct Crypto Paycheck Feature, New Wallet Integration In the Works]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286470</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286470/coinbase-ending-direct-crypto-paycheck-feature-new-wallet-integration-in-the-works"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T22:46:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase customers using the paycheck direct deposit feature have spoken out on social media about the unexpected change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erika Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized eSIMs Promise Anonymous Global Connectivity]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286455</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286455/decentralized-esims-anonymous-global-connectivity"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T22:12:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Liquify’s Boundless new eSIM service offers private 5G access to international travelers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk's Tesla Just Moved $765 Million in Bitcoin to Unknown Wallets]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286456</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286456/elon-musk-tesla-moves-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T21:50:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla has moved the bulk of its Bitcoin to new wallets, though there's no immediate suggestion that Elon Musk's car company is selling.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ETF Inflows Soar, Kamala Courts Crypto, TURBO Nears $1BN!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zn2lboMV/etf-inflows-soar-kamala-courts-crypto-turbo-nears-1bn</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zn2lboMV/etf-inflows-soar-kamala-courts-crypto-turbo-nears-1bn"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T18:22:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETFs see $800m inflows in 2-days, huge volume. ETF inflows may be linked to Trump odds: CoinShares. Bitcoin will rival housing market as asset class: Fink. Vitalik proposes drop to 1ETH to become validator. Kamala reveals pro-crypto policies. Kamala mocked for linking crypto to race. Hyperliquid announces HYPE token coming. PUFFER airdrop claim goes live. Tether considering lending to commodities trader. Man takes $500m lost Bitcoin case to court. Google removes crypto prices from search. SUI Foundation denies $400m insider selling. UAE approves $AED stablecoin. Bitget wallet now only behind Binance for downloads.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BTC hits 2-week High, China Stocks Rally again, GOAT hits $120M]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/0V0rYhMX/btc-hits-2-week-high-china-stocks-rally-again-goat-hits-120m</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/0V0rYhMX/btc-hits-2-week-high-china-stocks-rally-again-goat-hits-120m"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T14:09:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC hits 2-week high as China stocks rise. SUI breaks into the top 15 coins. $1.3bn ETH might be sold from PlusToken scam. S. Korea may approve BTC & ETH ETFs this month. Australia launches first ETH ETF. Samara to buy BTC with $33m bond. Altcoins to see $500m unlocks this week. Vitalik writes blog on the future of ETH. Grayscale reveals 35 altcoins considered for funds. Ethena proposes SOL for USDe collateral. Only one Binance launchpad coin up this year. AVAX summit begins this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Todd ‘revealed’ as Satoshi, Google may be Broken-up, Murad’s Wallets Doxxed]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pLw8b2d2/todd-revealed-as-satoshi-google-may-be-broken-up-murads-wallets-doxxed</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pLw8b2d2/todd-revealed-as-satoshi-google-may-be-broken-up-murads-wallets-doxxed"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T07:29:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC will be range bound until election: Bernstein. TAO & memecoins dominate mindshare. Peter Todd ‘revealed’ as Satoshi by HBO. US government able to sell $4.4bn Silk Road BTC. Ireland unable to access $378m seized BTC. SOL could do 5x if Trump wins: StanChart. Coinbase integrates Taproot addresses for BTC. Canary Capital applies for XRP ETF. S. Korea to regulate stablecoin transfers. CryptoCom files countersuit against SEC. Babylon fills cap with 22k BTC. Scroll airdrop coming Oct 22nd. USDC goes live on SUI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Falls Ahead of CPI, Stripe Reinstates Crypto, Fed Charges Market-makers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/aYgFvZqj/crypto-falls-ahead-of-cpi-stripe-reinstates-crypto-fed-charges-market-makers</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/aYgFvZqj/crypto-falls-ahead-of-cpi-stripe-reinstates-crypto-fed-charges-market-makers"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T07:29:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Majors drop despite stocks hitting ATHs. Stripe reinstates crypto payments. Crypto settlements near $20bn in 2024. S. Korea to review ban on BTC ETFs. US charges market makers for market manipulation. FBI created their own coin to ensnare targets. Vitalik ‘outside pick’ for Nobel Prize. Trump family token to built on Aave stack. $16m OP tokens allocated to superchain users. Wisdomtree debuts debit card for on-chain fund. 47% of hedge funds have crypto exposure. Argentina overtakes Brazil for crypto inflows. Tucker interviews Ryan Salame over FTX.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bounces from $59K, Tesla unveils Robotaxis, Memecoins Outperform]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cyJj6tWj/bitcoin-bounces-from-59k-tesla-unveils-robotaxis-memecoins-outperform</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cyJj6tWj/bitcoin-bounces-from-59k-tesla-unveils-robotaxis-memecoins-outperform"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T07:29:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC briefly dips under $59k, $160m liquidations. Mt Gox extends repayment plan by 1 year. Uniswap plans L2 for DeFi. SEC sues crypto trading firm Cumberland. Binomial sues SEC over futures trading. SEC’s Uyeda criticises agency’s policy. Justin Sun named prime minister of Liberland. MicroStrategy wants to become BTC bank. Binance pre-market trading goes live. Nearly 50% of US investors want crypto ETFs. Whale phished for $35m crypto. Ethena invests $46m in RWA funds. Trump’s crypto project aims to raise $300m.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentraland Desktop Client Preview]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qqzvDcTC/decentraland-desktop-client-preview</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qqzvDcTC/decentraland-desktop-client-preview"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T15:53:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum metaverse game Decentraland has shared an exclusive look at the visual and performance upgrades coming via its new desktop client.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Trader Murad Mahmudov talks about the Supercycle and how he chooses Meme Coins.]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Hj3nDp7G/crypto-trader-murad-mahmudov-talks-about-the-supercycle-and-how-he-chooses-meme-coins</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Hj3nDp7G/crypto-trader-murad-mahmudov-talks-about-the-supercycle-and-how-he-chooses-meme-coins"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T21:47:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Trader Murad Mahmudov talks about the Supercycle and how he chooses Meme Coins. Crypto stable, had sold off after China stocks fall. Crypto adopted faster than other tech: BlackRock. Crypto adoption to hit 8% of world population. CryptoCom recieves Wells notice from SEC. HBO documentary on Satoshi airs tonight. FTX bankruptcy plan approved by judge. Scroll airdrop may be imminent. Jupiter goes live on mobile iOS. Phantom rolls out support for Base. AAVE launches GHO on Base. Gensler may be replaced by Robinhood CLO. 87% of new token launches on SOL. National Bank of Bahrain creates BTC fund. BedRock DeFi allows BTC staking on ARB.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Memecoins take off, funding stays low, China stocks keep on rising!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/703mAYhV/memecoins-take-off-funding-stays-low-china-stocks-keep-on-rising</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/703mAYhV/memecoins-take-off-funding-stays-low-china-stocks-keep-on-rising"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T08:27:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR EP213. Memecoins take off, funding stays low, China stocks keep on rising!
Many altcoins & memecoins soar despite stable BTC. Funding rates continue to be low or negative. Crypto funds saw $147m of outflows last week. BTC remains best performing major assets this year. SUI breaks into the top 20 coins again. TAO leads top 100 away from memes, sifu shorts. $100m bridge to SOL over the last 7 days. Metaplanet buys $6.7m more BTC. ETH proposal aims to improve throughput 50%. EIGEN, OP, APT lead token unlocks this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Walrus Protocol Unlocks New Applications for Decentralized Data Storage]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kwEYLYWj/how-walrus-protocol-unlocks-new-applications-for-decentralized-data-storage</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kwEYLYWj/how-walrus-protocol-unlocks-new-applications-for-decentralized-data-storage"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T11:19:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mysten Labs Chief Scientist George Danezis joined Decrypt to talk about its new decentralized storage protocol Walrus, which promises to unlock new applications such as AI and social media, thanks to its novel Red Stuff data encoding algorithm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Coinbase Sees Crypto as a Bipartisan, 'Purple' Political Issue]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/YR2YmmwR/why-coinbase-sees-crypto-as-a-bipartisan-purple-political-issue</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/YR2YmmwR/why-coinbase-sees-crypto-as-a-bipartisan-purple-political-issue"/>
        <updated>2024-10-05T22:18:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase VP of Corporate and Business Development, Shan Aggarwal, joined Decrypt's Sander Lutz and Liz Napolitano at Messari Mainnet 2024 to discuss the exchange's efforts to grow mainstream crypto adoption—and how the changing political conversation around digital assets is rapidly playing a major role in that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Is Playing Offense—Not Just Defense—Against Crypto Crime, Says Head of Financial Investigations]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DiJ8D2Qc/binance-is-playing-offensenot-just-defenseagainst-crypto-crime-says-head-of-financial-investigations</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DiJ8D2Qc/binance-is-playing-offensenot-just-defenseagainst-crypto-crime-says-head-of-financial-investigations"/>
        <updated>2024-10-05T01:58:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nils Anderson Röed, the exchange’s global head of financial investigations, sat down with Decrypt’s Sander Lutz at Messari Mainnet 2024 to discuss how Binance is proactively dismantling criminal networks around the world, the strategy with which the crypto exchange is approaching sensitive conflicts in the Middle East, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 212 - SEEDPHRASE TALKS ART!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PJfaJNkZ/fomo-hour-212-seedphrase-talks-art</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PJfaJNkZ/fomo-hour-212-seedphrase-talks-art"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T19:29:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Payrolls Higher than expected, Bitcoin reacts hard. Crypto sank early in the week as Middle East tensions spooked markets. Powell signals two more rate cuts this year. SUI leads L1s again, nears YTD high despite large unlock. Majority of FTX repayments still months away. EIGEN becomes non-transferable, hits $6bn FDV. SEC to appeal Ripple securities law ruling. Visa launches tokenization platform for banks. SWIFT plans digital asset trial in 2025. ByBit launched trading of global stock indices. SPX, GIGA & FWOG hit ATHs, most memes fall. XCOPY to release 250 piece collection on Shape. HBO documentary claims to have identified Satoshi.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Altcoins bleed, ByBit launches stock index trading, POCHITA soars]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kYjAt3nt/altcoins-bleed-bybit-launches-stock-index-trading-pochita-soars</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kYjAt3nt/altcoins-bleed-bybit-launches-stock-index-trading-pochita-soars"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T21:11:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Altcoins sink, BTC dominance nears cycle high. BTC in ‘three blind mice’ downtrend. Tron revenue hits record $577m in Q3. ByBit to launch trading of major stock indices. Franklin Templeton launch fund on APT. SWIFT banks to trial digital assets in 2025. Aerodrome hits $1bn TVL on Base. Cronje calls out Aerodrome for copyright. ETH ICO wallet sells $47m. SEC files appeal against Ripple ruling. EIGEN falls 20% on staking rewards FUD. FTX to auction off WLD position. Half of US voters think crypto ‘important’. North Korea ‘infiltrating’ crypto industry. Snowden challenged over SOL centralisation view. Top SEC official on crypto set to depart.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DACOM Summit: Fastex CLO Vardan Khachatryan on Crypto Compliance]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LGGnxkb6/dacom-summit-fastex-clo-vardan-khachatryan-on-crypto-compliance</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LGGnxkb6/dacom-summit-fastex-clo-vardan-khachatryan-on-crypto-compliance"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T14:32:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fastex Chief Legal Officer Vardan Khachatryan joined Rug Radio creator Mlow at DACOM Summit to discuss how the crypto exchange is advancing compliance, and the regulatory challenges that lie ahead for the sector.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 210 - MIDDLE EAST TENSIONS RISE]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Bcj37IF2/fomo-hour-210-middle-east-tensions-rise</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Bcj37IF2/fomo-hour-210-middle-east-tensions-rise"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T17:14:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto drops as Middle East tensions flare. $500m liquidations in drop. BTC ETFs see largest outflows in a month. Fidelity ETH ETF sees 2nd highest outflow ever. SUI hits 6-month highs, bridge goes live on mainnet. Hashdex set to launch XRP ETF. Wormhole leads altcoin gains after Upbit lists. BTC miners hit record low profits in September Crypto hackers stole $750m in Q3. Telegram has been disclosing IPs since 2018.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Arbitrum is Simplifying Web3 for Web2 Adopters]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Mm9OGAoG/how-arbitrum-is-simplifying-web3-for-web2-adopters</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Mm9OGAoG/how-arbitrum-is-simplifying-web3-for-web2-adopters"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T14:19:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arbitrum's Head of Korea, John Park, joined Rug Radio creator Pukerainbow at ArbiVerse to talk about the Ethereum layer-2's strategy in Asia, hackathons, and bringing enterprise clients to its ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rep. Tom Emmer Is Confident Crypto Laws Are Coming Soon—No Matter Who Wins the Election]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qWDybFgM/rep-tom-emmer-is-confident-crypto-laws-are-coming-soonno-matter-who-wins-the-election</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qWDybFgM/rep-tom-emmer-is-confident-crypto-laws-are-coming-soonno-matter-who-wins-the-election"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T20:37:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Republican Majority Whip Tom Emmer sat down with Decrypt’s Sander Lutz and Liz Napolitano to discuss the state of crypto legislation, Kamala Harris, Fairshake, and more at Messari Mainnet 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 209 - LET UPTOBER BEGIN!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DdOpex2X/fomo-hour-209-let-uptober-begin</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DdOpex2X/fomo-hour-209-let-uptober-begin"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T19:23:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETFs see inflows for 8 straight days. SUI enters top 20, $110m of unlocks today. SOL weekly DEX volume flips ETH. Firedancer sees very fast TPS on Testnet. ETH gas up 500% in 2 weeks. EIGEN opens at $7bn FDV. FTX creditors vote in favour of restructuring plan. Dell to sell another $1.2bn Dell stock. Metaplanet buys another 107 BTC.Grayscale opens decentralised AI fund to investors. Robinhood allows crypto transfer in EU. Pollak to head Coinbase Wallet & join exec team. Gemini to close in Canada. Japan considers lower cap gains tax on crypto. Ohio bill would make it legal to pay taxes in crypto. Trump project opens whitelist to non-US users. CZ pledges to invest in blockchain companies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance CEO Richard Teng Talks Progress on Exchange's Global Regulatory Goals]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DNhZEWGn/binance-ceo-richard-teng-talks-progress-on-exchanges-global-regulatory-goals</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DNhZEWGn/binance-ceo-richard-teng-talks-progress-on-exchanges-global-regulatory-goals"/>
        <updated>2024-09-28T22:11:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt Reporters Sander Lutz and Liz Napolitano spoke with Binance CEO Richard Teng about the crypto exchange's progress on establishing a global headquarters, improving its relationships with regulators, and expanding its global presence in the wake of founder Changpeng "CZ" Zhao's jailing in the U.S.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>