<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-08-30T07:13:14.057Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-08-30T07:13:14.057Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EOS Token Receives Trading Approval in Japan]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754b7043b7</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/08/30/eos-token-receives-trading-approval-in-japan/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T07:03:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Under the Payment Services Act, the JVCEA and FSA, two financial bodies, closely monitor and regulate crypto-asset providers, requiring a thorough pre-screening process for new tokens.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Launches Crypto Transfer Service in Nine Latin American Countries]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18868146/Binance-Launches-Crypto-Transfer-Service-in-Nine-Latin-American-Countries</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18868146/Binance-Launches-Crypto-Transfer-Service-in-Nine-Latin-American-Countries"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T06:57:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance has launched a new cryptocurrency transfer service called Send Cash, enabling users in nine countries in Latin America to transfer crypto via Binance Pay. The recent statement notes that it aims to solve “specific challenges” that citizens in the region face. Binance Aims To Increase...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Exodus in the US? Robinhood and Jump Trading End Partnership]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754b711c31</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/crypto-exodus-in-the-us-robinhood-and-jump-trading-end-partnership/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T06:55:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood Markets (Nasdaq: HOOD), a popular American commission-free broker, has quietly ended its partnership with Chicago-based Jump Trading, a big name in the traditional finance industry, for facilitating crypto transactions, Coindesk reported, citing “a person familiar with the matter.”  

On-chain data shows that the two companies stopped doing business together in July. However, there is no official confirmation as neither the companies confirmed the end of the partnership.  

Robinhood and Jump Trading End Crypto Partnership  

Jump Trade was the first company that supported Robinhood’s crypto trades when the broker entered the cryptocurrency markets in 2018. Jump Trading was an early mover in crypto and has been active in digital assets since at least 2017, earlier than most tradi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arnab Shome</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Open Interest Declines, Lowest Since Terra Collapse]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18868155/Bitcoin-Open-Interest-Declines-Lowest-Since-Terra-Collapse</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18868155/Bitcoin-Open-Interest-Declines-Lowest-Since-Terra-Collapse"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T06:55:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain analytical firm Kaiko reported that Bitcoin Open Interest has declined to levels last seen during the Terra-Luna collapse in May last year. Kaiko says the decline started on August 17 after the largest cryptocurrency in the world had one of its worst sell-offs yet. The report has...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EOS Network's Token Receives Trading Approval in Japan, EOS Surges Nearly 10%]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18868148/EOS-Networks-Token-Receives-Trading-Approval-in-Japan-EOS-Surges-Nearly-10</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18868148/EOS-Networks-Token-Receives-Trading-Approval-in-Japan-EOS-Surges-Nearly-10"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T06:49:27.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Nigerian Central Bank Sued for Dollarizing Economy]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754b7296ca</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/report-nigerian-central-bank-sued-for-dollarizing-economy/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T06:39:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a lawsuit filed by a Nigerian human rights activist, the country’s central bank is accused of failing to stop the dollarization of the economy. According to the activist, the central bank’s unwillingness to stop economic agents from demanding U.S. dollars for domestic transactions has “resulted in the constant devaluation, depreciation and unending plunge of the naira.”
 
Nigeria’s Foreign Exchange Woes
 
A Nigerian lawyer and human activist, Femi Falana, is suing the Central Bank of Nigeria (CBN) for allegedly dollarizing the economy. In his suit filed with a Lagos High Court, Falana also alleged that the CBN’s failure to perform its statutory obligations had “resulted in the constant devaluation, depreciation and unending plunge of the naira.”
 
As has been reported by Bitcoin.com New…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Exchanges Saw Inflows of 30K Bitcoin Prior to Grayscale's SEC Victory]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754b7332f0</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/08/30/crypto-exchanges-saw-inflows-of-30k-bitcoin-prior-to-grayscales-sec-victory/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T06:33:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The exchange supply of bitcoin increased significantly just prior to Grayscale's win over the SEC, according to analytics firm Santiment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Exchange Binance Announces This Altcoin Will Support Mainnet Integration!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18868122/Bitcoin-Exchange-Binance-Announces-This-Altcoin-Will-Support-Mainnet-Integration</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18868122/Bitcoin-Exchange-Binance-Announces-This-Altcoin-Will-Support-Mainnet-Integration"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T06:33:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency exchange Binance has announced that this altcoin will support the upcoming Mainnet Integration. Continue Reading: Bitcoin Exchange Binance Announces This Altcoin Will Support Mainnet Integration!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Bitcoin’s [BTC] recovery here to stay? This data indicates that…]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18868106/Is-Bitcoins-BTC-recovery-here-to-stay-This-data-indicates-that</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18868106/Is-Bitcoins-BTC-recovery-here-to-stay-This-data-indicates-that"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T06:30:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin was seen climbing the price chart as of 29 August with maximum support from investors and indicators. However, traders may still need to stay alert given its drastic price change over a short course.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Fails to Take Out Last Summer’s Highs Despite Grayscale’s Court Win]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18868120/Bitcoin-Fails-to-Take-Out-Last-Summers-Highs-Despite-Grayscales-Court-Win</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18868120/Bitcoin-Fails-to-Take-Out-Last-Summers-Highs-Despite-Grayscales-Court-Win"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T06:20:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin keeps struggling despite the industry’s major legal wins]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale’s Roadmap To A Bitcoin Spot ETF Following SEC Triumph]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754b7cd7c9</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/grayscales-roadmap-bitcoin-spot-etf-sec/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T06:16:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a seismic shift for the Bitcoin industry, the DC Circuit court has ruled in favor of Grayscale Investments yesterday, effectively vacating the US Securities and Exchange Commission’s (SEC) previous denial of Grayscale’s Bitcoin spot ETF proposal. The decision has set the stage for a new chapter in the long-standing saga of Bitcoin spot ETFs, with experts speculating on various timelines and outcomes.
 
Timeline Expectations For A Bitcoin Spot ETF
 
Jake Chervinsky, Chief Policy Officer at Blockchain Association, described the ruling as “massive,” emphasizing that it’s extremely rare for a federal circuit court to find an agency like the SEC in violation of the Administrative Procedure Act (APA). Chervinsky stated, “The DC Circuit soundly rejected the SEC’s view that Grayscale’s ETF prop…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Senator Davidson Resparks Calls to Fire Gary Gensler After Second Legal Loss]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18868147/US-Senator-Davidson-Resparks-Calls-to-Fire-Gary-Gensler-After-Second-Legal-Loss</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18868147/US-Senator-Davidson-Resparks-Calls-to-Fire-Gary-Gensler-After-Second-Legal-Loss"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T06:15:35.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Exchanges Saw Inflows of 30K Bitcoin Prior to Grayscale's SEC Victory]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18868094/Crypto-Exchanges-Saw-Inflows-of-30K-Bitcoin-Prior-to-Grayscales-SEC-Victory</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18868094/Crypto-Exchanges-Saw-Inflows-of-30K-Bitcoin-Prior-to-Grayscales-SEC-Victory"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T06:13:06.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EOS secures regulatory approval in Japan, will trade against yen]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18868080/EOS-secures-regulatory-approval-in-Japan-will-trade-against-yen</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18868080/EOS-secures-regulatory-approval-in-Japan-will-trade-against-yen"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T06:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale’s Roadmap To A Bitcoin Spot ETF Following SEC Triumph]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18868062/Grayscales-Roadmap-To-A-Bitcoin-Spot-ETF-Following-SEC-Triumph</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18868062/Grayscales-Roadmap-To-A-Bitcoin-Spot-ETF-Following-SEC-Triumph"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T05:55:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a seismic shift for the Bitcoin industry, the DC Circuit court has ruled in favor of Grayscale Investments yesterday, effectively vacating the US Securities and Exchange Commission’s (SEC) previous denial of Grayscale’s Bitcoin spot ETF proposal. The decision has set the stage for a new...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Shorts Worth $120M Liquidated In Single Day After Bitcoin, Ethereum Spike As Court Rules In Favor Of Grayscale Over SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18868061/Crypto-Shorts-Worth-120M-Liquidated-In-Single-Day-After-Bitcoin-Ethereum-Spike-As-Court-Rules-In-Favor-Of-Grayscale-Over-SEC</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18868061/Crypto-Shorts-Worth-120M-Liquidated-In-Single-Day-After-Bitcoin-Ethereum-Spike-As-Court-Rules-In-Favor-Of-Grayscale-Over-SEC"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T05:35:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cryptocurrency market experienced the liquidation of crypto shorts worth a staggering $120 million within a span of 24 hours. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong grants SEBA Bank in-principle approval for crypto trading]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18868043/Hong-Kong-grants-SEBA-Bank-in-principle-approval-for-crypto-trading</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18868043/Hong-Kong-grants-SEBA-Bank-in-principle-approval-for-crypto-trading"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T05:32:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Hong Kong branch of SEBA Bank has received an in-principle approval from regulators to provide virtual asset trading services in the jurisdiction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB) Perpetuals Go Live on BitMEX]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18868056/Shiba-Inu-SHIB-Perpetuals-Go-Live-on-BitMEX</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18868056/Shiba-Inu-SHIB-Perpetuals-Go-Live-on-BitMEX"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T05:31:53.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s A Go! Twitter (X) Gets License To Enable Crypto Payments]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754b7a42f1</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/twitter-gets-license-to-enable-crypto-payments/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T05:17:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Striving to evolve X (formerly Twitter) into a multifaceted community platform replete with diverse functionalities, the Elon Musk-led company has successfully secured the necessary authorization to function as a payment hub in the United States.
 
This action follows Grayscale’s victory on August 29 over the US Securities and Exchange Commission. Additionally, it follows the social network’s January 2022 approval of the use of NFTs as profile images.
 
As indicated by records on the Nationwide Multistate Licensing System (NMLS), X has obtained a Currency Transmitter License (CTL) on August 28th from the state of Rhode Island.
 
 
 BREAKING: Twitter (X) receives a license to add crypto payments; May bring crypto sending and receiving capabilities to millions of users worldwide. pic.twitter…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[British MPs call on government to scrap AI exemptions that hurt artists]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18868031/British-MPs-call-on-government-to-scrap-AI-exemptions-that-hurt-artists</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18868031/British-MPs-call-on-government-to-scrap-AI-exemptions-that-hurt-artists"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T05:14:49.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEBA Bank Granted Conditional Approval for Hong Kong Crypto Services]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18868034/SEBA-Bank-Granted-Conditional-Approval-for-Hong-Kong-Crypto-Services</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18868034/SEBA-Bank-Granted-Conditional-Approval-for-Hong-Kong-Crypto-Services"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T04:52:38.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Mulls Leaving Russia, Limits Options for Russian Users]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754b65b38a</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/binance-mulls-leaving-russia-limits-options-for-russian-users/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T04:39:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto exchange Binance considers exiting Russia amid increased scrutiny over its services for users in the sanctioned nation. The news of the potential move comes after the exchange delisted several sanctioned Russian banks from its peer-to-peer (P2P) platform and restricted fiat payment options for Russian traders.
 
Full Russia Exit Is on the Table, Binance Representative Says
 
The world’s leading exchange for digital assets, , is currently reevaluating its Russian business, the Wall Street Journal reported. The process includes the possibility of a full withdrawal from what was an important market for the crypto giant. A spokesperson for the company told the publication:
 

All options are on the table, including a full exit.
 
The statement comes after a WSJ article suggested last we…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lubomir Tassev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Candidate Who Said He'd Get Paid In Bitcoin If Elected President Bows Out: Francis Suarez Calls It Quits]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18868003/The-Candidate-Who-Said-Hed-Get-Paid-In-Bitcoin-If-Elected-President-Bows-Out-Francis-Suarez-Calls-It-Quits</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18868003/The-Candidate-Who-Said-Hed-Get-Paid-In-Bitcoin-If-Elected-President-Bows-Out-Francis-Suarez-Calls-It-Quits"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T04:30:47.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ETH bulls rally: Grayscale’s legal win boosts open interest, sentiment]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18867990/ETH-bulls-rally-Grayscales-legal-win-boosts-open-interest-sentiment</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18867990/ETH-bulls-rally-Grayscales-legal-win-boosts-open-interest-sentiment"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T04:30:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH, like most cryptocurrencies, set out on a bullish journey post Grayscale's win against the SEC. A rise in open interest added to the bullish narrative.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s A Go! Twitter (X) Gets License To Enable Crypto Payments]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18867991/Its-A-Go-Twitter-X-Gets-License-To-Enable-Crypto-Payments</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18867991/Its-A-Go-Twitter-X-Gets-License-To-Enable-Crypto-Payments"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T04:25:26.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance launches crypto-to-bank account payment product in Latin America]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18867976/Binance-launches-crypto-to-bank-account-payment-product-in-Latin-America</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18867976/Binance-launches-crypto-to-bank-account-payment-product-in-Latin-America"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T04:23:33.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Surges in market volatility pinned to autumn months]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18867950/Surges-in-market-volatility-pinned-to-autumn-months</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18867950/Surges-in-market-volatility-pinned-to-autumn-months"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T04:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Files Sealed Motion In Binance Case: Unveiling A ‘Rare’ Legal Maneuver]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754b6cbf25</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/sec-files-sealed-motion-binance-case-legal-maneuver/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T03:17:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a surprising turn of events, the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has filed a sealed motion in its ongoing litigation against Binance, the world’s largest cryptocurrency exchange. 
 
This rare legal maneuver, which aims to file documents under seal, has drawn attention and speculation within the legal and cryptocurrency communities. Former SEC official John Reed Stark has provided insights into this “unprecedented” development, shedding light on potential reasons behind the SEC’s decision.
 
Intrigue Surrounds Sealed Motion In Binance Lawsuit
 
The filing, submitted on August 28th, includes a motion and 37 accompanying submissions, such as exhibits, a proposed order, and a declaration by SEC trial attorney Jennifer Farer. 
 
 
Usually, the SEC’s motions and enforce…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu’s Shibarium Returns to Full Operation After Navigating Bridge Issues]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754b688c66</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/shiba-inus-shibarium-returns-to-full-operation-after-navigating-bridge-issues/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T02:31:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Shiba Inu development team has announced that Shibarium is now fully functional after recent challenges where funds became inaccessible in the bridge. Shiba Inu’s Shytoshi Kusama thanked Sandeep Nailwal, the co-founder of Polygon Labs, who stepped in with crucial resources to address the issue. 
 
Shibarium Back Online After Resolving Bridge Glitch, Team Thanks Polygon Co-Founder
 
Two weeks prior, Shibarium had faced difficulties with over $2 million in cryptocurrency deposits trapped in its bridge. However, on August 28, an update was shared via a blog post confirming that Shibarium’s layer two (L2) was back in action.
 
It highlighted that Sandeep Nailwal and the Polygon team were instrumental in resolving the situation. “Quickly after the incident began, I called Sandeep from Polyg…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Spikes, Whales Swiftly Scoop 8,000 ETH: More Gains Incoming?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754b6977e7</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-spikes-whales-scoops-8000-eth/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T02:19:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Immediately after Ethereum spiked on August 29, a whale bought 8,000 ETH at $1,709, spending 13.66 million USDC. ETH prices continue to rise, trading at around $1,740 when writing. 
 
The coin may post even more gains in the sessions following a shift in trader sentiment after a favorable appellate court ruling in the case pitting Grayscale, the issuer of several trusts, including the Bitcoin Trust, versus the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).
 
The Grayscale Catalyst
 
The United States District of Columbia Court of Appeals faulted the SEC for not allowing Grayscale to convert the billions worth of over-the-counter (OTC) Bitcoin Trust to a Bitcoin spot Exchange-Traded Fund (ETF). The SEC has already approved a Bitcoin Futures ETF that doesn’t track the price of Bitco…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dalmas Ngetich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitch Chat Hivemind Played World of Warcraft—And Just Maxed Out a Character]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154155</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154155/twitch-chat-hivemind-played-world-warcraft-maxed-out-character"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T01:11:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A streamer let his chat clumsily control a World of Warcraft character with text commands—and they got to level 70. Here's how it went down.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ben Armstrong Calls Allegations by BitBoy Crypto Network ‘Diabolical,’ Levels Own Claims Against Company]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154196</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154196/ben-armstrong-bitboy-calls-allegations-diabolical-makes-own-claims"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T01:09:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Armstrong says the accusations leveled against him are defamatory and “100% false”—and makes provocative counterclaims of his own.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC’s ‘Secret’ Filing in Binance Case Could Relate to Criminal Investigation, Says Former SEC Official]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754b511f27</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/secs-secret-filing-in-binance-case-could-relate-to-criminal-investigation-says-former-sec-official/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T00:39:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission’s former head of Internet enforcement suspects that the SEC’s “secret” filing in the Binance case is a “rare” tactic that could relate to the Department of Justice’s criminal investigation against the crypto exchange. He stressed that the securities regulator’s “seal-seeking filing is unusual, odd, and uncommon,” emphasizing that the move “cannot be overstated.”
 
SEC Takes ‘Rare’ Move in Binance Case
 
Former U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) official John Reed Stark shared his perspective Tuesday regarding what he called a “secret” SEC filing in its litigation against cryptocurrency exchange Binance in a lengthy post on social media platform X. Stark is currently president of cybersecurity firm John Reed Stark Consulting. He founded…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tornado Cash Indictments May Prove to Be Just a Localized Storm After All]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754b517d78</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/08/30/tornado-cash-indictments-may-prove-to-be-just-a-localized-storm-after-all/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T00:34:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Tornado Cash indictments could be another tipping point for crypto. How the case plays out could define how the federal government can deal with decentralized trading platforms if they’re seen as broad precedents. But the case may be much more straightforward than initial reactions suggested.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC In Turmoil: Internal Rebellion Erupts Over NFT Showdown, Regulators At War?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754b529280</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/internal-rebellion-over-nft-showdown-regulators-war/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T00:19:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent development, two prominent commissioners at the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), Mark Uyeda and Hester Peirce, have expressed their dissent against the agency’s enforcement action on Non-Fungible Tokens (NFT). 
 
As reported by Bitcoinist on Monday, the SEC had initiated legal proceedings against media and entertainment company Impact Theory, which resulted in a cease-and-desist order and a substantial financial penalty of over $6.1 million.
 
Commissioners Uyeda and Peirce, known for their support of innovation within the crypto industry, voiced their disagreement with the SEC’s classification of certain NFT sales as securities. 
 
They emphasized their concerns about applying the Howey analysis, a legal framework used to determine whether an investment contract ex…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Genesis Global And DCG Strike Crucial Deal With Creditors: 90% Recovery Imminent?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754b5f6b2d</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/genesis-and-dcg-strike-crucial-deal-with-creditors/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T23:20:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest update for the financial complications faced by Genesis Global, a notable name in the crypto lending space, and its parent company, Digital Currency Group (DCG), shows that both entities seem to have navigated their way out of the murky waters, striking an agreement with their creditors.
 
The Path To Recovery For Creditors
 
As revealed through recent court filings, the agreement marks a turning point that could ensure stakeholders have a fair shot at recovering their investments. Genesis Global and Digital Currency Group’s recent announcement signals hope for numerous creditors.
 
 
According to the documents filed in the U.S. bankruptcy court in the Southern District Of New York, unsecured creditors stand to recover a substantial portion of their claims. 
 
The projected reco…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UniLend Finance Empowers Community Governance with the Launch of UFTG Token]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754b58a9a4</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/unilend-finance-empowers-community-governance-with-the-launch-of-uftg-token/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T23:06:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. UniLend Finance, a leading decentralized finance (DeFi) protocol is thrilled to announce the launch of its new wrapped governance token, UFTG (UniLend Finance Governance Token) as the revolutionary protocol approaches closer to Governance launch on 4th September.
 
This groundbreaking token signifies UniLend’s commitment to community-driven decision-making and plays a pivotal role in making a decentralized future. However, it’s crucial to clarify that UFTG is a wrapped version of UFT; we are not releasing or transitioning to a new token.
 
UFTG: A Gateway to Empowering Governance Participation 
 
UFTG is the governance token that wraps native UFT tokens, enabling users to actively participate in UniLend governance processes. With a seamless 1:1 swap mechanism between UFT and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Policy 'Weaknesses' in UK Put Artists at Risk, MPs Warn]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154174</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154174/ai-policy-weaknesses-in-uk-put-artists-at-risk-mps-warn"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T23:02:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[British lawmakers say Rishi Sunak's government must heed the concerns of musicians, authors and artists over the future of their livelihoods.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Connor Sephton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale’s Victory Ignites a GBTC Trading Frenzy as Investors Bet on Narrowing Discount to Bitcoin Price]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754b5998e0</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/08/29/grayscales-victory-ignites-a-gbtc-trading-frenzy-as-investors-bet-on-narrowing-discount-to-bitcoin-price/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T22:55:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC must review its rejection to convert the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust into an exchange-traded fund, the appeals court ruled Tuesday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI-Generated Books on Amazon Could Give Deadly Advice]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154187</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154187/ai-generated-books-on-amazon-could-give-deadly-advice"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T22:54:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If people blindly follow AI guides into the forest, it's not going to end well.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Congress Members Clash on the Potential Effect of Proposed Tax Rules on the Crypto Industry]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754b5b54e6</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/us-congress-members-clash-on-the-potential-effect-of-proposed-tax-rules-on-the-crypto-industry/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T22:35:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Members of the U.S. Congress have expressed concerns about the possible problems that implementing the newly proposed crypto tax reporting requirements could create in the entire industry. Patrick McHenry, Cynthia Lummis, and others reacted differently to the potential effects of these proposals on decentralized finance platforms and stablecoins.
U.S. Congress Members Concerned Over New Tax Obligations for Defi Exchanges and Stablecoins
Several U.S. Congress members have expressed concerns over the newly proposed crypto-related tax reporting rule revealed recently by the U.S. Treasury Department and the Internal Revenue Service (IRS) and its possible effect on several elements of the cryptocurrency industry.
In a recent post on social media, Wyoming Senator Cynthia Lummis stated that while…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US DOJ Opposes Sam Bankman-Fried’s Claims on Potential Evidence]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754b5bfb6d</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/us-doj-opposes-sam-bankman-frieds-claims-on-potential-evidence/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T22:28:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US  
Department of Justice (DOJ) has responded to claims by FTX Founder Sam  
Bankman-Fried’s lawyers that prosecutors are dumping “millions of pages” of  
discovery materials or potential evidence on the embattled crypto entrepreneur  
less than six weeks before his criminal trial. In a letter sent on Friday to Judge Lewis  
Kaplan, who is presiding over the case, Bankman’s legal team had claimed that  
prosecutors produced “an additional 4 million pages of discovery” without plans  
to make them available for the former FTX CEO's review.
DOJ Slams  
Bankman-Fried’s Claims
In another  
letter sent yesterday (Monday), the lawyers further claimed that US prosecutors  
also produced another 3.7 million pages of discovery. They noted that producing  
these materials while Bankman-Fried is…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Solomon Oladipupo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC’s Grayscale Court Rout Puts Agency in Will-They, Won’t-They Role Starring Gensler]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754b448b64</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/08/29/secs-grayscale-court-rout-puts-agency-in-will-they-wont-they-role-starring-gensler/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T22:22:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto industry’s campaign to set up exchange-traded funds (ETFs) has now pushed the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission against a wall with Grayscale Investments’ consequential court win, but it’s still up to the agency to decide whether to retreat or keep fighting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Directs Belgian Users To Polish Arm Following Regulatory Clampdown]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754b4490b9</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/binance-directs-belgian-users-to-polish-arm/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T22:21:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prominent cryptocurrency exchange Binance has devised a strategy to save its Belgian market following a suspension order by Belgium’s financial market regulator in June.
 
The world’s largest exchange was ordered to cease its operations in Belgium because it offered crypto services from countries outside the European Economic Area (EEA). 
 
 
Binance Moves To Retain Belgium Market
 
According to a blog post on Monday, August 28, Binance redirects all its Belgian users to its Polish branch. The exchange claims this move allows it to meet regulatory compliance and maintain its customers in Western Europe. 
 
Binance is a registered virtual assets service provider (VASP) in Poland, an EEA member state. Therefore, all Belgian crypto exchange customers can regain access to its trading platform …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Semilore Faleti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Did the SEC Just Declare War on NFTs?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154153</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154153/did-sec-declare-war-nfts-legal-analysis"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T21:50:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Legal analysts dissect the agency’s first-ever enforcement action against an NFT sale—and what it means for the future of the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's Good for Grayscale and Bitcoin ETFs Could Be Great for Coinbase]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154156</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154156/whats-good-for-grayscale-and-bitcoin-etfs-could-be-great-for-coinbase"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T20:45:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Coinbase has a significant role to play as the custodian of choice, ensuring protection of client assets,” Coinbase CLO Paul Grewal told Decrypt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Stock Soars 15% Following Grayscale’s Bitcoin ETF Win Against SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154152</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154152/coinbase-stock-soars-following-grayscale-bitcoin-etf-win-against-sec"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T20:27:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Investors have reasoned what's good for Bitcoin ETF applicants could be great for Coinbase and its bottom line.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Gets a Boost—But It's a Week After Bearish Investors Pulled $149M From BTC Funds]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154151</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154151/bitcoin-gets-a-boost-but-its-a-week-after-bearish-investors-pulled-149m-from-btc-funds"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T20:15:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Total withdrawals stood at $168 million last week, the worst 1-week change for crypto funds since March, according to Coinshares.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vertex AI by Google Introduces Invisible Watermarks]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154143</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154143/vertex-ai-by-google-introduces-invisible-watermarks"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T19:33:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ability to mark AI-generated images is Google's latest enhancement for privacy and security.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash Up 17% After Grayscale Prevails Over SEC in ETF Case]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154140</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154140/bitcoin-cash-up-after-grayscale-prevails-over-sec-etf-case"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T19:17:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin is rising—but Bitcoin Cash and Stacks have seen much larger gains as the crypto market reacts to Grayscale's court win.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's a Bitcoin Drivechain and Why Are Devs At Odds Over Its Proposal?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154129</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154129/what-is-a-bitcoin-drivechain"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T18:49:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A single Bitcoin upgrade could guarantee the network's victory over all other coins, proponents say. Others think it'll introduce shitcoins to the network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GBTC: Everything You Need To Know About The Grayscale Bitcoin Trust]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=46537</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/gbtc-everything-you-need-to-know-about-the-grayscale-bitcoin-trust"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T15:44:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Grayscale Bitcoin Trust has been grabbing headlines in recent months. Here’s how it works, and what it means for the crypto space.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Stevens,Tim Copeland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is an "Algorithm of Thoughts" (AoT)? Microsoft's Human-like AI Training Method]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154091</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-an-algorithm-of-thoughts-aot-microsofts-human-like-ai-training-method"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T14:58:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The algorithm evaluates whether the initial steps—"thoughts," to use a word generally associated only with humans—are sound, thereby avoiding a situation where an early wrong "thought" snowballs into an absurd outcome.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Euny Hong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale Wins Appeal Against SEC to Convert Bitcoin Trust to ETF]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154119</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154119/grayscale-wins-appeal-against-sec-to-convert-bitcoin-trust-to-etf"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T14:48:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GBTC is Grayscale's flagship Bitcoin fund, with $16 billion in assets under management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Surges After Grayscale Wins Appeal Against SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154118</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154118/bitcoin-surges-after-grayscale-wins-appeal-against-sec"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T14:45:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price of Bitcoin is on the rise after Grayscale prevailed in its court case against the SEC to launch a Bitcoin spot ETF.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward,Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenZeppelin Launches 2.0 Version Of Security Platform Defender]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154110</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154110/openzeppelin-launches-2-0-version-of-security-platform-defender"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T14:01:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“It will become easy for any developer to use blockchain without having to be a security expert,” said OpenZeppelin’s head of product.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interlay Launches MVP of New Bitcoin Layer-2 BOB]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154108</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154108/interlay-releases-mvp-for-new-bitcoin-layer-2-network-for-decentralized-innovation"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the new release, Interlay seeks to empower developers with tools to drive innovation using the existing framework of Bitcoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOJ Wants SBF's Proposed Expert Witnesses Barred From Testifying at FTX Trial]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154100</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154100/doj-wants-sbfs-proposed-expert-witnesses-barred-from-testifying-at-ftx-trial"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T11:24:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“The defense’s proposed experts suffer from an array of deficiencies that warrant preclusion of all seven witnesses,” said the DOJ.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Mulls ‘Full Exit’ From Russia Amid Mounting Regulatory Pressure: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154098</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154098/binance-mulls-full-exit-from-russia-amid-mounting-regulatory-pressure-report"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T10:55:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto exchange is reportedly considering whether to withdraw entirely from the Russian market as regulatory pressure mounts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Genesis, Digital Currency Group Reach In-Principle Agreement to Settle Creditors' Claims]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154092</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154092/genesis-digital-currency-group-reach-in-principle-agreement-to-settle-creditors-claims"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T09:11:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While the agreement could potentially lead to a fair recovery for creditors, Genesis’ former partner Gemini has yet to support it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastering NFT Trading - Degen U]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/HQGt1Vrq/mastering-nft-trading-degen-u</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/HQGt1Vrq/mastering-nft-trading-degen-u"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T07:08:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Take Degen U's new course, Mastering NFT Trading, and earn an on-chain certificate. A top instructor will help you identify trends, seize the right moment to trade, weed out scams—and have fun while doing it!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Infuses AI With Human-Like Reasoning Via an “Algorithm of Thoughts”]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154073</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154073/microsoft-infuses-ai-with-human-like-reasoning-via-an-algorithm-of-thoughts"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T03:40:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new technique combines the strengths of human cognition with algorithmic logic.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DoorDash Follows Wendy's With An AI-Powered Order Taker]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154069</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154069/doordash-follows-wendys-with-an-ai-powered-order-taker"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T00:37:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Doordash believes using AI could boost the bottom line “without sacrificing quality.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Influencers Double Down on PepeCoin Despite Recent Rug Accusations]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154038</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154038/influencers-double-down-on-pepecoin-despite-recent-rug-accusations"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T00:31:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The meme coin has sunk around 17% since insider trades startled investors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grand Theft Auto 6: Everything You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154049</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154049/grand-theft-auto-6-release-date-rumors-leaks-news"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T22:44:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rockstar's next open-world game has been revealed through ample leaks and reports. Here's what we know so far about Grand Theft Auto 6.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto and AI Need Global Regulations, Says India’s Prime Minister]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154043</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154043/global-crypto-regulation-ai-emerging-technology-economies-india"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T21:27:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Narendra Modi will preside over this year’s G20 summit in New Delhi.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ben ‘BitBoy’ Armstrong Booted From YouTube Brand He Created]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154035</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154035/ben-bitboy-armstrong-booted-from-youtube-brand-he-created"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T20:23:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company confirmed Armstrong’s removal on Twitter, making strong allegations that attack the influencer’s character.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI Beckons to Businesses With An Enterprise Edition of ChatGPT]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154036</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154036/chatgpt-openai-for-business-enterprise-privacy-chatbot"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T20:23:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest offering from the AI leader promises better security, privacy, and speed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Premium Glow-in-the-Dark Game Boy Plays All the Classics]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154023</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154023/premium-glow-dark-game-boy-plays-all-classics"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T18:58:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nintendo’s Game Boy gets a modern upgrade with the unofficial Analogue Pocket—now with a spooky vibe in tow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Space Nation CEO on Working With 'Independence Day' Director Roland Emmerich]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LpznLhtx/space-nation-ceo-on-working-with-independence-day-director-roland-emmerich</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LpznLhtx/space-nation-ceo-on-working-with-independence-day-director-roland-emmerich"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T17:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jerome Wu, CEO of Space Nation, tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the upcoming Space Nation Online game in development and shares details on Space Nation Cofounder Roland Emmerich's role in the project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Holds Steady While Major Altcoins SUI and PEPE Plunge]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=153993</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/153993/bitcoin-holds-stead-while-major-altcoins-sui-pepe-plunge"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T16:38:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin seems to be returning to its low volatility having barely moved at all in the past week, but some major altcoin are experiencing a sell-off.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Fines LA Company $6 Million Over NFTs Sold as Securities]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154000</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154000/sec-fines-la-company-6-million-over-nfts-sold-as-securities"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T16:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company has also been ordered to destroy all the Founder's Key NFTs as a result of the settlement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt AI, Edited by Stacy Elliot</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Balancer Suffers Nearly $1M Exploit as Team Urges Users to Withdraw Funds]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154002</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154002/balancer-suffers-nearly-1m-exploit-team-urges-users-withdraw-funds"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T15:56:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Less than a week after the team first announced the vulnerability, DeFi project Balancer has been exploited for roughly $979,000.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Korean Crypto Exchanges Prepare for Tightened Reserves Requirements]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=153987</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/153987/south-korean-crypto-exchanges-prepare-tightened-reserves-requirements"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T15:30:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting from next month, South Korean crypto exchanges with "real-name" bank accounts must maintain a minimum $2.3 million reserve fund.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maui Strong: Hawaii Artist Teams Up With Decrypt for NFT Fundraiser]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=153752</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/153752/maui-strong-hawaii-nft-fundraiser"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T14:43:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto community is called to support Maui wildfire victims with an open-mint digital collectible designed by muralist Jasper Wong.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bankman-Fried’s Legal Team Seeks ‘Temporary Release’ Ahead of October Trial]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=153982</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/153982/bankman-frieds-legal-team-seeks-temporary-release-ahead-october-trial"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T12:55:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Sam Bankman-Fried's trial nears, his defense team argued that the disgraced CEO won't be able to properly prepare whilst in prison.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friend.tech Revenues Plummet 90% as Social App Hype Cools]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=153971</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/153971/friend-tech-revenues-plummet-social-app-hype-cools"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T12:04:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some users are calling the end of Friend.tech, as Dune data shows user activity on the buzzy Base app has dried up dramatically this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SHIB Devs Reopen Ethereum Bridge to Layer-2 Network Shibarium]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=153969</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/153969/shib-devs-reopen-ethereum-bridge-layer-2-network-shibarium"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T09:29:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shibarium, a layer-2 scaling solution for the Shiba Inu blockchain, is now officially live after the network's rocky start this month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Friend.tech? The Social-Token Driven Decentralized Social Network]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=153858</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-friend-tech-the-social-token-driven-decentralized-social-network"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T08:32:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Social tokens combine aspects of traditional cryptocurrencies with patronage systems, allowing influencers, creators, and others to monetize a fan base in exchange for exclusive offers and content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Reiff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prime Trust Filing Reveals Cascade of Failures That Led To Bankruptcy Filing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=153954</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/153954/prime-trust-bankruptcy-wallet-incident"/>
        <updated>2023-08-27T22:08:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company recounted a litany of mistakes that include locking itself out of its own hardware Ethereum wallet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GAME REVIEW: Champions Arena from Gala Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qUE1RlDx/game-review-champions-arena-from-gala-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qUE1RlDx/game-review-champions-arena-from-gala-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Champions Arena is a turn-based fantasy RPG from Gala Games, where characters can become NFTs and crypto can be used to purchase gems, one of the game's synthetic currencies. Decrypt's Kate Irwin takes us inside the game for her thoughts on the fun, mobile-first title.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apex Legends Voice Actor Ben Prendergast on the Future of Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/X3RKdsaG/apex-legends-voice-actor-ben-prendergast-on-the-future-of-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/X3RKdsaG/apex-legends-voice-actor-ben-prendergast-on-the-future-of-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T18:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Voice actor Ben Prendergast, who's voiced characters in games like Apex Legends and God of War Ragnarok, shares his opinions on the tech space's history of "bubbles" and whether blockchain gaming has a future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The future of AI Stardom and Robotics with SingularityNET COO Janet Adams and Desdemona]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yVQaZI71/the-future-of-ai-stardom-and-robotics-with-singularitynet-coo-janet-adams-and-desdemona</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yVQaZI71/the-future-of-ai-stardom-and-robotics-with-singularitynet-coo-janet-adams-and-desdemona"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T16:45:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this interview, SingularityNET COO Janet Adams explains the intricate details that went into creating the Desdemona robot AI from Hanson Robotics and future plans for the AI Diva.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto a 'No-Brainer' for Video Games, Says Mino Games CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rdynom8C/crypto-a-no-brainer-for-video-games-says-mino-games-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rdynom8C/crypto-a-no-brainer-for-video-games-says-mino-games-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T18:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mino Games CEO Sasha MacKinnon, developer of the upcoming Dimensionals game, tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the studio's approach to digital collectibles.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Wagner's 'Controversial Take' on Crypto in Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tc2nKeqA/michael-wagners-controversial-take-on-crypto-in-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tc2nKeqA/michael-wagners-controversial-take-on-crypto-in-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T16:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Solana's PlayGG, Star Atlas CEO Michael Wagner shares his "controversial take" on crypto in games, shares the challenges of developing the upcoming scifi game, and how crypto's volatility has changed his perspective with Decrypt's Jason Nelson.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interview: Angelic CEO on Building the Sci-Fi RPG on Solana and Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/uCzW3K7P/interview-angelic-ceo-on-building-the-sci-fi-rpg-on-solana-and-ethereum</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/uCzW3K7P/interview-angelic-ceo-on-building-the-sci-fi-rpg-on-solana-and-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T15:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Angelic is a sci-fi roleplay game in development that will be free-to-play and offer optional, opt-in crypto features on Solana and Ethereum and a governance token. Metaverse Game Studios CEO and Founder Erkan Bayol tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how he sees AAA traditional games as Angelic's main competitors and shares his vision for the game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apex Legends Voice Actor on AI's Impact on Video Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IOIrmb0N/apex-legends-voice-actor-on-ais-impact-on-video-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IOIrmb0N/apex-legends-voice-actor-on-ais-impact-on-video-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T17:28:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ben Prendergast is an actor who has voiced characters like Apex Legends' Fuse, God of War Ragnarok's Tyr, and Patroclus in Hades. But as debates swirl around the use of artificial intelligence in entertainment in light of the SAG-AFTRA and WGA strikes, Prendergast gives Decrypt's Kate Irwin his honest take on the potential use of AI actors in games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Star Atlas CEO on Developing an MMO Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/WQCaahmH/star-atlas-ceo-on-developing-an-mmo-game</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/WQCaahmH/star-atlas-ceo-on-developing-an-mmo-game"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T13:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Jason Nelson speaks with Star Atlas Founder and CEO Michael Wagner about the MMO game's approach to development, marketing, and blockchain integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aurory's Origin Story: How JRPGs Inspired the Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/O0S201TB/aurorys-origin-story-how-jrpgs-inspired-the-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/O0S201TB/aurorys-origin-story-how-jrpgs-inspired-the-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T16:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Jason Nelson talks to Aurory's Head of Marketing and Business Development Michael Natoli about the origins of the Aurory crypto games at the Solana PlayGG event.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Parallel TCG: Inside the Sci-Fi Card Game’s Closed Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/q8YVWJh4/parallel-tcg-inside-the-sci-fi-card-games-closed-beta</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/q8YVWJh4/parallel-tcg-inside-the-sci-fi-card-games-closed-beta"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T15:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin goes hands-on with Parallel’s closed beta on Windows PC to find out what sets it apart from other crypto card-battlers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 Games Need to Compete with All Games, Says Solana Foundation GM]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ud9wTd4s/web3-games-need-to-compete-with-all-games-says-solana-foundation-gm</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ud9wTd4s/web3-games-need-to-compete-with-all-games-says-solana-foundation-gm"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T19:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Foundation's General Manager of Games Johnny Lee tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about Solana's PlayGG conference and shares his take on crypto gaming and the "play-to-earn" concept.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Many Early Blockchain Games Were 'Cash Grabs,' Says Twitch Streamer Alliestrasza]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BA4yE45A/many-early-blockchain-games-were-cash-grabs-says-twitch-streamer-alliestrasza</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BA4yE45A/many-early-blockchain-games-were-cash-grabs-says-twitch-streamer-alliestrasza"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T16:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["I wrote them off," Twitch streamer Alliestrasza said of her initial thoughts on many early blockchain games. She tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how her perspective on Web3 games has evolved over time and now sees blockchain games getting significantly better.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['MetalCore' Game Preview: Hands-on With the 'Titanfall' Meets 'Destiny' NFT Mashup]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/tjK6i7lv/metalcore-game-preview-hands-on-with-the-titanfall-meets-destiny-nft-mashup</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/tjK6i7lv/metalcore-game-preview-hands-on-with-the-titanfall-meets-destiny-nft-mashup"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T19:46:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MetalCore is an upcoming mech shooter developed by Studio 369, and it's being developed on Ethereum scaling network Immutable zkEVM. Decrypt contributor Ryan Gladwin played through the prologue and tested out the recent Alpha 3 online experience to get a sense of the NFT-infused mashup of Titanfall and Destiny.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Give Projects a Chance,' Says Aurory's Michael Natoli on NFT Game Challenges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/nBNKKZdK/give-projects-a-chance-says-aurorys-michael-natoli-on-nft-game-challenges</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/nBNKKZdK/give-projects-a-chance-says-aurorys-michael-natoli-on-nft-game-challenges"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aurory is an NFT-driven game franchise that started life on Solana and is expanding to other chains. Decrypt's Jason Nelson spoke with Aurory Head of Marketing Michael Natoli at Solana's PlayGG event, where Natoli shared his thoughts on the challenges that blockchain games face in reaching players.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>