<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-07-16T06:20:12.822Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-07-16T06:20:12.822Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Europe Expects Its First Bitcoin ETF This Month, Report]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756c925a67</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/europe-expects-its-first-bitcoin-etf-this-month-report/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T06:08:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Europe’s first bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) is set to launch in July after a 12-month delay caused by the crypto winter. The fund has been authorized in Guernsey, a more flexible jurisdiction, which will ostensibly help to avoid some of the regulatory challenges associated with the European Union.
 
Europe to Have Its First Bitcoin ETF Listed After Year-Long Delay
 
The first bitcoin exchange-traded fund in Europe is expected to be publicly listed by the end of this month, a full year after its initially planned launch, the Financial Times reported on Thursday. The ETF was first announced by Jacobi Asset Management in July 2022.
 
The asset manager wanted to list it on the Euronext exchange last year but decided that “the time wasn’t right” after a string of negative events in the cr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lubomir Tassev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto scams on the decline]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18776726/Crypto-scams-on-the-decline</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18776726/Crypto-scams-on-the-decline"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sharp decrease in crypto capital inflows in the first half of 2023 towards illicit systems]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitget research highlights trends in European crypto trading]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18776727/Bitget-research-highlights-trends-in-European-crypto-trading</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18776727/Bitget-research-highlights-trends-in-European-crypto-trading"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The findings not only lend strength to some existing research, but also provide interesting food for thought]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk ChatGPT Challenger Triggers Surge In AI-Backed Cryptocurrencies]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756c9d34d9</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/elon-musk-rolls-out-chatgpt-challenger/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T05:26:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk recently introduced an artificial intelligence venture called xAI, aimed at revolutionizing the field of AI. This announcement has sparked a notable surge in the value of cryptocurrency tokens associated with AI. 
 
In an intriguing move, xAI has been established as an independent entity, separate from Musk’s prominent technology enterprise, X Corp. This strategic decision reflects the keen interest of Elon Musk in exploring and expanding the boundaries of AI technology beyond his existing ventures.
 
xAI emerges as a formidable contender to the widely acclaimed chatbot ChatGPT, signifying the billionaire’s intention to provide users with an alternative AI experience.
 
 
Rise Of AI Crypto And Their Market Performance
 
In the world of cryptocurrencies, a fascinating trend has em…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IMF Has Not Seen Specific Proposal on BRICS Currency]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756c9a496b</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/imf-has-not-seen-specific-proposal-on-brics-currency/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T04:07:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The International Monetary Fund (IMF) has not seen any specific proposal on a common BRICS currency. However, the IMF acknowledges the presence of “slow-moving trends” indicating shifts in the currency composition of reserves and trade. The Fund’s statement followed reports that the BRICS economic bloc is planning to launch a gold-backed currency.
 
IMF on BRICS Currency
 
The International Monetary Fund (IMF) was asked during a press conference on Thursday about its position on the proposed BRICS currency following media reports that the BRICS nations are launching a gold-backed currency that will be formally announced at the economic bloc’s upcoming leaders’ summit in August. The BRICS nations comprise Brazil, Russia, India, China, and South Africa.
 
Julie Kozack, director of IMF’s Comm…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ANOTHER country mining and buying Bitcoin? #shorts #btc #bitcoinnews]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18776686/ANOTHER-country-mining-and-buying-Bitcoin-shorts-btc-bitcoinnews</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18776686/ANOTHER-country-mining-and-buying-Bitcoin-shorts-btc-bitcoinnews"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T03:45:05.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Debt Soars $210,000,000,000 in Two Weeks As Lawmakers Sound Alarm on Nation’s ‘Unsustainable’ Trajectory]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18776677/US-Debt-Soars-210000000000-in-Two-Weeks-As-Lawmakers-Sound-Alarm-on-Nations-Unsustainable-Trajectory</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18776677/US-Debt-Soars-210000000000-in-Two-Weeks-As-Lawmakers-Sound-Alarm-on-Nations-Unsustainable-Trajectory"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T03:08:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The total amount of debt on America’s balance sheet is skyrocketing. New numbers from the government’s FiscalData platform show that on July 13th, the country’s total public debt hit $32.542 trillion. That’s $210 billion higher than just two weeks prior, and a staggering $2.03 trillion higher...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC could be waiting ‘years’ to file appeal in Ripple case: Brad Garlinghouse]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18776662/SEC-could-be-waiting-years-to-file-appeal-in-Ripple-case-Brad-Garlinghouse</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18776662/SEC-could-be-waiting-years-to-file-appeal-in-Ripple-case-Brad-Garlinghouse"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T02:12:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse, the filing of an appeal by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission would “only further” solidify Judge Torres decision that XRP is not a security.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robert Kennedy Jr Says Biden Is ‘Preparing for Ground War With Russia’ as World War III Warnings Escalate]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756c81660d</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/robert-kennedy-jr-says-biden-is-preparing-for-ground-war-with-russia-as-world-war-iii-warnings-escalate/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T02:06:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. presidential candidate Robert F. Kennedy Jr. (RFK Jr.) has explained that President Joe Biden is “preparing for a ground war with Russia” by signing an executive order to mobilize reserve forces to augment Operation Atlantic Resolve. Multiple people have accused Biden of starting World War III.
 
Biden Preparing for Ground War With Russia, Says Kennedy Jr.
 
U.S. presidential candidate Robert F. Kennedy Jr. (RFK Jr.) has slammed President Joe Biden over his executive order to mobilize select reserve forces in order to augment Operation Atlantic Resolve. Kennedy is a son of former U.S. Attorney General and Senator Robert F. Kennedy and nephew of former U.S. President John F. Kennedy. Operation Atlantic Resolve was launched in 2014 following Russia’s invasion of the Crimean Peninsula.
 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoin TrueUSD To Be Fully Controlled By Asian Owner]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18776654/Stablecoin-TrueUSD-To-Be-Fully-Controlled-By-Asian-Owner</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18776654/Stablecoin-TrueUSD-To-Be-Fully-Controlled-By-Asian-Owner"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T02:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Featured Image From Kraken, Chart From Tradingview. In today’s news, the prominent stablecoin TrueUSD – with the ticker TUSD – is now undergoing a management change.  According to a thread this morning by the project’s official Twitter handle, Archblock Inc., the current TUSD operator, has begun...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BNB completes 6 years; a look back and what to expect]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18776646/BNB-completes-6-years-a-look-back-and-what-to-expect</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18776646/BNB-completes-6-years-a-look-back-and-what-to-expect"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T01:30:17.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum’s YTD turns profits despite price fluctuations]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18776620/Ethereums-YTD-turns-profits-despite-price-fluctuations</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18776620/Ethereums-YTD-turns-profits-despite-price-fluctuations"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T00:30:30.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robert Kiyosaki’s Warnings: Giant Crash Incoming, End of US Dollar Approaching]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756c8fd304</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/robert-kiyosakis-warnings-giant-crash-incoming-end-of-us-dollar-approaching/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T00:11:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rich Dad Poor Dad author Robert Kiyosaki has warned that a giant crash is coming, emphasizing that the end of fiat money, including the U.S. dollar, is near. Noting that the USD “will die,” he urged investors to buy gold, silver, and bitcoin. His warnings came as the BRICS economic bloc is discussing creating a common currency that could be backed by gold.
 
Robert Kiyosaki’s Giant Crash Warnings
 
The author of Rich Dad Poor Dad, Robert Kiyosaki, has issued more warnings about the U.S. economy and the U.S. dollar. Rich Dad Poor Dad is a 1997 book co-authored by Kiyosaki and Sharon Lechter. It has been on the New York Times Best Seller List for over six years. More than 32 million copies of the book have been sold in over 51 languages across more than 109 countries.
 
Kiyosaki tweeted Wedn…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$200,000,000,000 Exits JPMorgan Chase in One Year As Customers Withdraw Cash Amid US Banking Concerns]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18776614/200000000000-Exits-JPMorgan-Chase-in-One-Year-As-Customers-Withdraw-Cash-Amid-US-Banking-Concerns</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18776614/200000000000-Exits-JPMorgan-Chase-in-One-Year-As-Customers-Withdraw-Cash-Amid-US-Banking-Concerns"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T00:04:39.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase and Binance.US Both Restore Support for XRP After Judge Issues Critical Ruling in SEC’s Ripple Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18776609/Coinbase-and-BinanceUS-Both-Restore-Support-for-XRP-After-Judge-Issues-Critical-Ruling-in-SECs-Ripple-Lawsuit</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18776609/Coinbase-and-BinanceUS-Both-Restore-Support-for-XRP-After-Judge-Issues-Critical-Ruling-in-SECs-Ripple-Lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T00:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken Picks Customer Privacy Over IRS As It Fights Tax Compliance Dispute]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756c8a67b8</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/kraken-picks-customer-privacy-over-irs/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T23:26:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[San Francisco-based cryptocurrency exchange Kraken finds itself in the midst of a legal showdown with the Internal Revenue Service (IRS) as it fights against the agency’s request for user data.  On its part, the IRS seeks to investigate potential tax liabilities of Kraken customers who engaged in cryptocurrency transactions between 2016 and 2020. 
 
However, while Kraken has been ordered by the Northern District Court of California to disclose certain information, the exchange seems determined to protect its clients’ privacy and prevent potential harm. The crypto exchange argues that the IRS’s demands go beyond what is necessary and emphasized the importance of consumer security and privacy.
 
Kraken’s Resistance to IRS Summons
 
Kraken’s refusal to comply with the IRS summons has led to a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Man Charged With Stealing NFTs and Crypto by Spoofing OpenSea in 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18776598/Man-Charged-With-Stealing-NFTs-and-Crypto-by-Spoofing-OpenSea-in-2021</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18776598/Man-Charged-With-Stealing-NFTs-and-Crypto-by-Spoofing-OpenSea-in-2021"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T23:13:09.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WebX Conference Welcomes Distinguished Guests: Japan PM, Yuga Labs CEO, Kabosu (Doge), Desdemona (AI Robot)]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18776597/WebX-Conference-Welcomes-Distinguished-Guests-Japan-PM-Yuga-Labs-CEO-Kabosu-Doge-Desdemona-AI-Robot</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18776597/WebX-Conference-Welcomes-Distinguished-Guests-Japan-PM-Yuga-Labs-CEO-Kabosu-Doge-Desdemona-AI-Robot"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T23:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WebX is a conference dedicated to bridging divides - Web2 and Web3, Japanese and English, Japan and the rest of the world.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken Picks Customer Privacy Over IRS As It Fights Tax Compliance Dispute]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18776593/Kraken-Picks-Customer-Privacy-Over-IRS-As-It-Fights-Tax-Compliance-Dispute</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18776593/Kraken-Picks-Customer-Privacy-Over-IRS-As-It-Fights-Tax-Compliance-Dispute"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T23:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[San Francisco-based cryptocurrency exchange Kraken finds itself in the midst of a legal showdown with the Internal Revenue Service (IRS) as it fights against the agency’s request for user data. On its part, the IRS seeks to investigate potential tax liabilities of Kraken customers who engaged in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto spot volumes increase post Ripple ruling]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18776583/Crypto-spot-volumes-increase-post-Ripple-ruling</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18776583/Crypto-spot-volumes-increase-post-Ripple-ruling"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T22:39:31.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Attention: Today is the Last Chance to Airdrop This Altcoin! Here is the Hour Information and Details]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18776584/Attention-Today-is-the-Last-Chance-to-Airdrop-This-Altcoin-Here-is-the-Hour-Information-and-Details</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18776584/Attention-Today-is-the-Last-Chance-to-Airdrop-This-Altcoin-Here-is-the-Hour-Information-and-Details"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T22:37:05.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase’s market cap relative to Uniswap surges]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18776573/Coinbases-market-cap-relative-to-Uniswap-surges</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18776573/Coinbases-market-cap-relative-to-Uniswap-surges"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T22:18:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase's market cap relative to popular DEX uniswap has surged.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Lawmakers Call on Congress to Pass Crypto Law Following SEC v Ripple Ruling on XRP]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756c771991</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/us-lawmakers-call-on-congress-to-pass-crypto-law-following-sec-v-ripple-ruling-on-xrp/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T22:09:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several U.S. lawmakers have called on Congress to pass crypto legislation following the court ruling on the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) v. Ripple case regarding XRP. “Gary Gensler’s SEC cannot continue to pursue its regulation by enforcement approach, which only harms investors and creates uncertainty,” said one lawmaker.
 
US Lawmakers Call on Congress to Pass Crypto Bills Following SEC v Ripple Ruling
 
Following the ruling on the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) v. Ripple case regarding XRP, a number of U.S. lawmakers have called on Congress to pass legislation to regulate crypto and uphold the court ruling.
 
The chairman of the House Financial Services Committee, Patrick McHenry (R-NC), and the chairman of the House Agriculture Committee, Glenn “GT” Thom…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano Surges 23.9% Following Favorable XRP Ruling, Investors Eye Further Gains]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18776563/Cardano-Surges-239-Following-Favorable-XRP-Ruling-Investors-Eye-Further-Gains</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18776563/Cardano-Surges-239-Following-Favorable-XRP-Ruling-Investors-Eye-Further-Gains"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T21:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Synthetix takes on CEXes head-on, more inside]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18776546/Synthetix-takes-on-CEXes-head-on-more-inside</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18776546/Synthetix-takes-on-CEXes-head-on-more-inside"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T21:30:44.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP is not a security, Celsius CEO arrested on criminal charges, and more: Hodler’s Digest, July 9-15]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18776537/XRP-is-not-a-security-Celsius-CEO-arrested-on-criminal-charges-and-more-Hodlers-Digest-July-9-15</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18776537/XRP-is-not-a-security-Celsius-CEO-arrested-on-criminal-charges-and-more-Hodlers-Digest-July-9-15"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T21:13:27.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jimmy Song: From Code to Global Money | The Rise of Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18776529/Jimmy-Song-From-Code-to-Global-Money-The-Rise-of-Bitcoin</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18776529/Jimmy-Song-From-Code-to-Global-Money-The-Rise-of-Bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T20:42:25.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Formally Accepts BlackRock Spot Bitcoin ETF Application for Review]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148752</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148752/sec-blackrock-spot-bitcoin-etf-application"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T20:39:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The procedural move suggests that the federal agency will give the closely-watched application a serious look.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Staking Services Paused In Four US States]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756c7dd988</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/coinbase-staking-services-paused/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T20:25:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase, the biggest cryptocurrency exchange in the United States, has paused staking services for customers in California, New Jersey, South Carolina, and Wisconsin. It would appear that there are some regulatory concerns that need to be addressed by regulators in these states as Coinbase battles with its Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).
 
Staking In The US
 
Staking crypto has become the norm, especially as many blockchains are now relying on the proof-of-stake (PoS) consensus mechanism. The US is home to the biggest crypto stakers in the world, and Coinbase is at the forefront of staking services in the country. 
 
Their staking program allows users to earn rewards for locking in certain crypto assets. And according to the crypto exchange, 46% of those that stake the most Ethe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Reportedly Lays Off Over 1,000 Employees, CZ Says Exchange Is Hiring]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756c7f32d5</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/binance-reportedly-lays-off-over-1000-employees-cz-says-exchange-is-hiring/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T20:06:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leading crypto exchange Binance has cut hundreds of jobs after a string of executive exits, according to a media report. The news, which comes as the coin trading platform marks its sixth anniversary amid increased pressure from regulators, was termed as FUD by founder Changpeng Zhao who said his company is still hiring. 
 
Major Digital Asset Exchange Binance Cutting Jobs Amid U.S. Regulatory Crackdown, Report
 
Binance, the world’s biggest crypto exchange, is reducing its workforce after several executives left the company. Media reports about the layoffs come against the backdrop of an ongoing clampdown on the industry and the trading platform in the U.S. where it’s involved in lawsuits with the securities and futures commissions and is under investigation by the Department of Justice.
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lubomir Tassev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miners Face 'Stress Test' in Next Halving: JP Morgan]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148736</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148736/bitcoin-miners-face-stress-test-in-next-halving-jp-morgan"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T20:02:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price of Bitcoin and transaction fees will need to rise significantly to offset the lower block reward.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Le Clu3 Brings NFT-Based Loyalty Perks to Private Banking]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148743</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148743/le-clu3-brings-nft-based-loyalty-perks-private-banking"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T19:49:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crédit Agricole's Indosuez Wealth Management arm launches Le Clu3, a loyalty program aimed at high-end clientele.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephanie Hirschmiller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Emerges as a Common Enemy for Actors and Writers in Hollywood]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148720</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148720/ai-common-enemy-of-actors-and-writers-in-hollywood"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T18:58:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first joint strike in 63 years grinds productions to a halt over artificial intelligence and compensation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bankman-Fried Requests Court’s Approval for a Mystery List of Visitors to Drop by Without Security]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756c67925c</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bankman-fried-requests-courts-approval-for-a-mystery-list-of-visitors-to-drop-by-without-security/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T18:12:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a legal document lodged on July 13, 2023, Sam Bankman-Fried, the former chief executive officer and founder of FTX, expressed his desire for his “close friends” to drop by his parents’ residence “without the need for a security guard to be present.” The plea from Bankman-Fried petitioned the court to maintain confidentiality regarding the list of “friends and colleagues,” a move that Inner City Press has contested.
 
Bankman-Fried’s Lawyers Advocate for Security-Free Visits for a Secret Group of ‘Close Friends’
 
Christian Everdell, legal counsel for Sam Bankman-Fried, presented a letter to the court advocating that “close friends and colleagues” as well as “household help” be permitted to call on his client without undergoing a security screening.
 
This request arises from the bail st…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: XRP Leads Alt Week as Solana, Cardano and Polygon Outperform Bitcoin and Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148715</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148715/this-week-in-coins-altcoins-xrp-solana-cardano-polygon-bitcoin-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T16:30:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple’s courtroom victory against the SEC was a win for holders of many leading altcoins this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JPMorgan CEO Jamie Dimon Calls 2023’s Banking Fiasco a ‘Mini Crisis’, Foresees Consumer Savings Depleted by Year’s End]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756c690a40</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/jpmorgan-ceo-jamie-dimon-calls-2023s-banking-fiasco-a-mini-crisis-foresees-consumer-savings-depleted-by-years-end/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T16:12:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Four days ago, JPMorgan Chase CEO Jamie Dimon was interviewed by The Economist and he discussed the recent U.S. banking disaster that occurred last March. At that time, the public witnessed the second, third, and fourth largest bank failures in U.S. history. Dimon asserted that “for the most part,” the financial crisis of 2023 is over. He downplayed its severity, dubbing it a “mini-crisis” and stating it was “nothing like 2008 or 2009.” 
 
Dimon: ‘I Think the Odds of Rates Going Higher From Here Are Higher Than What Other People Think’
 
Jamie Dimon, the lead executive at JPMorgan Chase, shared his insights on a myriad of topics including the March 2023 U.S. banking turmoil, soaring interest rates, fluctuating consumer savings, and the escalating conflict in Ukraine. The Economist probed D…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Outlook for July]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756c566aa2</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-price-outlook-for-july/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T15:10:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two weeks into July and bitcoin has risen to a fourteen-month high, as cryptocurrency markets reacted to the Ripple Labs’ ruling. XRP was partially ruled to not be a security by U.S. judge Analisa Torres, after a lawsuit from the Security and Exchange Commission (SEC). However, what does this mean for price action for the remainder of the month? 
 
Current Market Status
 
Prior to Thursday, cryptocurrency markets mostly consolidated to start the month, as traders digested various data points from the United States.
 
Firstly, non-farm payrolls fell below expectations, coming in at 205,000, then inflation also slipped, dropping to a two-year low of 3.0%.
 
Despite this, traders still struggled to define market sentiment, with BTC unable to break out of a ceiling at $31,000, until this week.
 

 
July Outlook
 
Bitcoin (BTC) surged to an intraday peak of $31,862 on Thursday, which was its strongest level since May 2022.
 
The move came following a breakout of a resistance level at $31,400, however, bulls have so far been unable to sustain this.
 
As of writing this, BTC is trading at $30,342.71, after briefly falling below $30,000 during Saturday’s session.
 
 
Looking at the chart, the price has since stabilized, as the relative strength index (RSI) of 14 weeks, fell to a floor at 61.00.
 
Should this floor hold, bitcoin bulls will likely continue to target a breakout above the next key ceiling, which lay at $32,400.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
Where will bitcoin end the month? Let us know your thoughts in the comments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Space Mermaids' Is an Addictive Arcade-Style Game on XRP With NFT Rewards]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148677</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148677/space-mermaids-addictive-arcade-style-game-xrp-rewards"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T14:48:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PREVIEW: Players must dodge asteroids and collect stars as a pixelated mermaid in Space Mermaids, a retro-style game built on XRP.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biggest Movers: SHIB up 7% on Saturday, as DOGE Moves to 2-Month Peak]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756c53d9d5</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/biggest-movers-shib-up-7-on-saturday-as-doge-moves-to-2-month-peak/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T14:09:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba inu was one of Saturday’s biggest movers, as the meme coin rose by as much as 7% to start the weekend. The global crypto market cap was mostly lower, falling by over 2% as traders began to secure recent gains. Despite this, dogecoin also rose, hitting a two-month high in today’s session.
 
Shiba Inu (SHIB)
 
Shiba Inu (SHIB) rose by as much as 7% to start the weekend, despite the wider cryptocurrency market mostly moving lower.
 
SHIB/USD climbed to an intraday peak of $0.000008484 on Saturday, a day after trading at a low of $0.000007705.
 
As a result of today’s high, the meme coin rose to its strongest point since June 5, when the price was trading at $0.00000867.
 
 
The move took place as the 14-day relative strength index (RSI) broke out of a ceiling at the 62.00 mark.
 
At the time of writing this, the index is now at 64.00, with an upcoming resistance point of 68.00 a possible destination for bulls.
 
There is a good chance that SHIB will be trading at $0.00000900, in the event the bulls reach their target.
 
 
Dogecoin (DOGE)
 
Another notable gainer to start the weekend was dogecoin (DOGE), which also cemented a multi-month high.
 
Following a low of $0.0672 on Friday, DOGE/USD jumped 5% higher on Saturday, hitting a peak of $0.07471 in the process.
 
This resulted in the meme coin trading at its highest level since May 8, which is the last time price was above $0.0770.
 
 
Earlier gains have somewhat faded, as traders leave earlier positions, as a result of the RSI colliding with a ceiling at 66.00.
 
The meme coin is now trading at $0.07351, however overall sentiment for the weekend could remain bullish, should it move past the 66.00 point.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
 What is behind today’s meme coin rally? Let us know your thoughts in the comments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Liquid Staking Derivatives in Ethereum Swell by 1.5 Million ETH in 2 Months]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756c590985</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/liquid-staking-derivatives-in-ethereum-swell-by-1-5-million-eth-in-2-months/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T13:09:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the course of the previous 63 days, there’s been a notable 16.98% surge in the quantity of ethereum (ETH) held in liquid staking derivatives protocols, with a substantial addition of roughly 1,507,285 ETH across 23 different platforms. Data reveals that Lido Finance dominates the market, commanding a 74% share of the liquid staked ether sector.
 
Influx of 1.5 Million Ether Bolsters Liquid Staking Derivatives Platforms
 
In a span of barely more than two months, the liquid staking derivatives sector witnessed a substantial swelling of nearly $3 billion in its value. Historical data from defillama.com, dated May 12, 2023, illustrates that an estimated 8.87 million ethereum (ETH) was held in liquid staking platforms. As of today, that number has ascended to a noteworthy 10.38 million ET…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moral Compass: The Political Spectrum And Our Understandings Of Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756c5bebf2</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/how-your-political-views-inform-your-outlook-on-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T12:36:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is an opinion editorial by Dea Rezkitha, an Indonesian Bitcoin educator and podcast host.
In politics, individuals are often grouped into “left” and “right” wings, but the complexities go well beyond this simple dichotomy. To gain a deeper understanding of people’s beliefs and values, and ultimately how these will inform their outlook on Bitcoin, it is crucial to consider their social views as well. This is where a political compass comes into play, serving as a valuable tool for analysis.
What Is A Political Compass?
The political compass is a graphical representation of political ideologies that helps categorize individuals or groups based on their views on two main axes: economic policy (left-right) and social policy (authoritarian-libertarian). It provides a more nuanced understan…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dea Rezkitha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Technical Analysis: Bitcoin Retreats From 14-Month High, as Profit Takers Swoop In]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756c465120</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-ethereum-technical-analysis-bitcoin-retreats-from-14-month-high-as-profit-takers-swoop-in/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T12:08:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin plunged from a recent fourteen-month high to start the weekend, as traders appeared to have begun securing yesterday’s gains. The decline saw the price fall below $30,000, days after almost moving above $32,000. Ethereum also slipped, however remained above $1,900.
 
Bitcoin
 
Bitcoin (BTC) fell below $30,000 to start the weekend, as traders began to take profits, following recent highs.
 
After peaking at $31,354.48 on Saturday, BTC/USD plunged to an intraday low of $29,966.39 earlier today.
 
This sees bitcoin retreat from a high of $31,862, which was the strongest level for the cryptocurrency since last May.
 
 
Looking at the chart, the decline was somewhat inevitable, due to the relative strength (RSI) moving into overbought territory.
 
The index rose to a peak of 65.55 on Thursday, before falling to a current reading of 54.17 earlier today.
 
Since this drop, price strength has since stabilized, with BTC now trading at $30,347.59.
 
 
Ethereum
 
Ethereum (ETH) also moved lower on Saturday, however traders were able to reject a drop below the $1,900 level.
 
ETH/USD slipped to a bottom of $1,901.36 earlier in the day, less than 24-hours after trading at a top of $2,005.96.
 
Since hitting Friday’s three-month high, bulls have opted to abandon previous positions heading into the weekend.
 
 
The world’s second largest cryptocurrency has since rebounded, bouncing away from a floor at $1,900, and now trades at $1,943.27.
 
This comes as the RSI held firm at a support point around the 55.00 zone, going on to climb to a current reading of 56.79.
 
Overall, the next target could be around the 61.00 mark, and if successfully hit, ETH will likely be back over $2,000.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
Will markets consolidate during this weekend? Leave your thoughts in the comments below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pantera Founder Dan Morehead Predicts Upcoming Bull Market: ‘We Can Rally Now’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756c41043b</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/pantera-founder-dan-morehead-predicts-upcoming-bull-market-we-can-rally-now/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T11:38:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dan Morehead, founder and managing partner of Pantera Capital, a digital assets investment hedge fund, has predicted an upcoming bull market for cryptocurrency. In Pantera’s latest letter, Morehead states that blockchain-related assets have started to decouple from market indexes and that the time is right for a new crypto rally.
Pantera’s Founder Dan Morehead: Blockchain Assets Should Trade ‘Independently’
Dan Morehead, founder and managing partner of Pantera, one of the first cryptocurrency and digital assets-focused hedge funds, has predicted an upcoming bull market for cryptocurrencies. Pantera’s latest blockchain letter titled “Bonds Down, Crypto Up” details the struggles that traditional market investors might face as the U.S. Federal Reserve is unable to keep “manipulating” the bond…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Not A Security, NYC Mayor Maintains, Following Disclosure Backlash]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756c4f680d</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-not-a-security-nyc-mayor/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T10:27:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin has become an integral part of New York City Mayor Eric Adams’ financial strategy, as he boldly embraced the cryptocurrency and positioned the city as a thriving hub for the industry.
 
However, an unfortunate oversight occurred when Adams mistakenly failed to disclose a certain aspect of his involvement with Bitcoin, a misstep that stemmed from his belief that it did not qualify as a security, according to his team.
 
 
Renowned for his outspoken support of Bitcoin, Adams, who previously served as a police officer, wholeheartedly advocates for the widespread adoption of the cryptocurrency. 
 
In a bold move, he even opted to receive a portion of his salaries in Bitcoin, favoring the decentralized digital currency over traditional fiat currencies.
 
Bitcoin: A Currency, Not a Secur…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kim Dotcom-Backed Crypto Startup Bitcache Liquidated in New Zealand]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756c342a77</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/kim-dotcom-backed-crypto-startup-bitcache-liquidated-in-new-zealand/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T09:33:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcache, a crypto startup backed by Kim Dotcom, has been liquidated, reportedly over unpaid legal fees. Phil Creagh, an Auckland lawyer who acted as Bitcache’s director until Sept. 2020, is reported to have applied for the startup’s liquidation on May 24. 
 
Bitcache’s Unpaid Legal Fees
 
A New Zealand-based crypto startup previously promoted by prominent crypto advocate and entrepreneur Kim Dotcom, has been reportedly liquidated over unpaid legal fees. According to a report by Newsroom, owners of the startup known as Bitcache have not contested the decision to liquidate.
 
The liquidation of the startup, which Kim Dotcom lauded as a platform that would revolutionize the way online content creators get paid, came more than six years after it was launched. Phil Creagh, an Auckland lawyer who acted as Bitcache’s director until Sept. 2020, is reported to have applied for the startup’s liquidation on May 24.
 
 

Commenting on the decision to liquidate Bitcache before it achieved any of its objectives, Creagh said:
 

It’s pretty straightforward, there are fees owed and not paid. The company has not taken any steps so far to avoid being placed in liquidation. We’ll put it in liquidation and see what, if anything, can be recovered.
 
The lawyer added that his firm Anderson Creagh Lai stopped representing the Kim Dotcom-backed startup some time ago.
 
According to the Newsroom report, Bitcache initially hit a major obstacle in early 2017 when the platform’s planned launch was interrupted by what Dotcom referred to as a “hiccup.” Since then, attempts to launch the platform have all failed. The report added that Bitcache, which reportedly last filed a return to the Companies Office in 2021, is now likely to be removed from the Companies Register.
 
What are your thoughts on this story? Let us know what you think in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spanish National Museum Thyssen to Mint Exclusive Collection of Van Gogh NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148582</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148582/olyverse-and-thyssen-museum-bring-van-gogh-masterpiecemetaverse"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T09:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Olyverse and Thyssen-Bornemisza National Museum partner to bring Van Gogh to the metaverse, offering art lovers a new kind of experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Zimbabwean Economist Says Portion of Goverment Employees’ Salaries Must Be Paid in Gold Coins]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756c3de872</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/report-zimbabwean-economist-says-portion-of-goverment-employees-salaries-must-be-paid-in-gold-coins/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T07:39:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Zimbabwean economist has said authorities should consider paying a portion of government employees’ salaries with gold coins. The economist said partially paying government workers with gold coins can “help curtail the black market dominance” in the country’s currency market. 
 
Dollar Shortages and Rising Inflation
 
A Zimbabwean economist, George Nhepera, has urged authorities in the Southern African nation to consider paying a portion of government workers’ salaries with gold coins. According to the economist, paying part of the workers’ salaries with gold coins can “help curtail the black market dominance” in the country’s currency market.
 
Nhepera’s call for measures to cushion government workers with gold coins follows the local currency’s sharp depreciation in June. The currency’…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Goes All In on AI: Can It Compete With Google, ChatGPT and MidJourney?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148658</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148658/meta-all-in-ai-google-chagpt-midjourney"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T21:40:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meta’s CM3leon model and a reported commercial version of LLaMA could upend the generative AI industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Slashes Staff But Says Reports of Thousands Being Cut Are 'Way Off']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148657</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148657/binance-slashes-staff-wont-say-how-much"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T21:28:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rumors swirled earlier in the year that the controversial digital asset behemoth would drastically reduce its headcount.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jay-Z’s Roc Nation and Puma Drop NFT-Enhanced Sneakers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148651</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148651/jay-z-roc-nation-puma-drop-nft-enhanced-sneakers"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T20:32:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Inspired by the 50th anniversary of hip-hop, each pair of Puma kicks comes tied to exclusive digital content, including new music.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ali Shutler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aave DAO Votes to Launch GHO Stablecoin on Ethereum Mainnet]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148627</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148627/aave-dao-votes-to-launch-gho-stablecoin-on-ethereum-mainnet"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T20:15:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aave's GHO stablecoin has been in development for the last year, and its aim is to make markets more accessible and efficient for its users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Restricts Ethereum, Solana Staking in Four US States]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148648</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148648/coinbase-restricts-ethereum-solana-staking-in-four-us-states"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T20:13:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The announcement comes after 11 states alleged Coinbase was violating securities laws.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kim Dotcom Teases Bitcoin Cash 'Killer App’ as Bitcache Heads for Liquidation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148621</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148621/kim-dotcom-teases-bitcoin-cash-killer-app-as-bitcache-heads-for-liquidation"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T19:55:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kim Dotcom said on Twitter he would "love to see FileShop become a #BitcoinCash killer app."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gucci's Iconic Fashion Is Reimagined in Christie's NFT Art Auction]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148628</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148628/guccis-iconic-fashion-reimagined-christies-nft-art-auction"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T19:44:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artists put a fresh spin on luxury fashion house Gucci's past, paired with other generative digital art pieces—some made with AI tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephanie Hirschmiller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dr. Disrespect's Shooter 'Deadrop' Gets Bigger and Better]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148604</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148604/dr-disrespect-shooter-deadrop-expands-snapshot-vi-release"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T18:22:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PREVIEW: Movement still feels sluggish, but Deadrop's new Snapshot VI build shows progress elsewhere while expanding the experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dr. Disrespect's 'Deadrop': Early Access Gameplay From Snapshot VI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/8l21EHoa/dr-disrespects-deadrop-early-access-gameplay-from-snapshot-vi</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/8l21EHoa/dr-disrespects-deadrop-early-access-gameplay-from-snapshot-vi"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T18:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin playtests Dr. Disrespect and Midnight Society's first-person shooter Deadrop and shares the latest game updates, as well as her opinions on the game in development. Currently, Deadrop offers Polygon Founders Pass NFTs with no other crypto plans revealed just yet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock CEO Larry Fink: Crypto Will 'Transcend Any One Currency']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148612</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148612/blackrock-ceo-larry-fink-crypto-transcend-currency"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T17:34:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The boss of the world’s biggest asset manager today continued to sing Bitcoin’s praises.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Buy 'The Flash' as an NFT Just Weeks After Hitting Theaters]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148597</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148597/you-can-buy-flash-nft-just-weeks-after-hitting-theaters"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T16:19:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DC Comics superhero movie "The Flash" will be released via NFT on July 18, the very same day it hits traditional digital platforms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ali Shutler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Founder Sam Bankman-Fried Is Getting Lonely and Needs a Maid]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148578</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148578/sbf-friends-colleagues-household-help-approved-visitors"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T15:54:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The lawyers asked that "close friends and colleagues of Bankman-Fried’s parents and household help" be allowed to visit without security checks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Are CryptoPunks? The Ethereum NFT Sensation's Wild Ride]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=79859</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-are-cryptopunks-ethereum-nft-avatars"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T13:51:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some of the oldest ever NFTs are now some of the most desirable—and expensive—crypto collectibles. Here’s how they work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken, Crypto.com Join Coinbase in Relisting XRP After Court Ruling]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148562</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148562/kraken-crypto-com-join-coinbase-relisting-after-court-ruling"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T10:47:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Though the judge’s decision didn’t relate to secondary sales, exchanges are signaling greater confidence in trading XRP.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alys Key</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Court Sets Former Celsius CEO Alex Mashinsky’s Bail at $40M]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148554</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148554/court-sets-former-celsius-ceo-alex-mashinsky-bail-40m"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T10:19:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celsius’ boss Alex Mashinsky is set to be released on bail after agreeing to a $40 million personal recognizance bond.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multichain Shutters Operations After Chinese Police Take CEO’s Sister Into Custody]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148559</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148559/multichain-shutters-operations-chinese-police-take-ceo-sister-custody"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T10:01:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese police have detained Multichain's CEO and his sister, and impounded operational funds, forcing the team to shutter operations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Ripple Effect: Crypto Market Soars $73.5B After Judge's Ruling in XRP SEC Case]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148555</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148555/the-ripple-effect-crypto-market-soars-73-5b-after-judges-ruling-xrp-sec-case"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T09:46:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Positive gains spread across the board as Ripple’s partial win against the SEC uplifts the crypto market’s spirits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ruling on Ripple XRP Sales Sparks Optimism at Coinbase]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148541</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148541/ruling-on-ripple-xrp-sales-sparks-optimism-coinbase"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T07:28:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Judge Torres' partial ruling on the SEC vs. Ripple Labs case yesterday has added a new dimension to the agency's lawsuit against Coinbase.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Maximal Extractable Value (MEV)? What Blockchain Miners Need To Know]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148542</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-maximal-extractable-value-mev-what-blockchain-miners-need-to-know"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T02:22:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MEV hinges on the fact that miners and other participants in the validation process can reorder and manipulate transactions for their own personal gain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Reiff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unpacking the Federal Lawsuits Against Celsius Network and Its Ex-CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148522</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148522/unpacking-the-many-damning-federal-lawsuits-against-celsius"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T23:23:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Collapsed crypto lender Celsius Network and its ex-bosses have been sued by the DOJ, SEC, FTC, and the CTFC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['More and More' Game Publishers Will Embrace NFTs: Mythical Games CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/wBWogSkl/more-and-more-game-publishers-will-embrace-nfts-mythical-games-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/wBWogSkl/more-and-more-game-publishers-will-embrace-nfts-mythical-games-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T22:28:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the wake of EA Sports and Fortnite creator Epic Games embracing Nike's NFT platform, Mythical Games CEO John Linden tells Decrypt's Andrew Hayward how quickly he expects to see more major traditional game publishers enter the blockchain space and how quickly the industry will scale.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Actors Approve Strike as AI Fears Bring Hollywood to a Standstill]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148519</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148519/actors-approve-strike-ai-fears-bring-hollywood-standstill"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T21:27:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SAG-AFTRA will officially strike at midnight, joining striking writers with demands over AI, compensation, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase to Restart XRP Trading After Judge's Ruling in Ripple Case]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148517</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148517/coinbase-to-restart-xrp-trading-after-judges-ruling-in-ripple-case"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T20:03:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To be clear, Judge Analisa Torres has not issued a ruling on secondary sales of XRP "because that question is not properly before the Court."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Hits $2,000 for First Time Since May Following XRP Ruling]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148509</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148509/ethereum-hits-2000-for-first-time-since-may-following-xrp-ruling"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T18:56:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nearly everything’s green after a federal judge weighed in on whether XRP is a security, with Ethereum recapturing $2,000.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The US Dollar Is Under Threat, Says Circle CEO in Warning to Congress]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148498</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148498/the-us-dollar-is-under-threat-says-circle-ceo-in-warning-to-congress"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T18:38:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jeremy Allaire warns that US dollar dominance is waning as other nations outpace the US on financial innovation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is XRP? The Cryptocurrency Created by Ripple Founders]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=5709</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/ripple"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T18:31:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XRP is a type of cryptocurrency designed to help banks move money more quickly, and cheaply than existing methods. It is largely spearheaded by Ripple.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Hussey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Did XRP Restart Alt Season? Solana, Cardano, Polygon Up Double Digits]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148503</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148503/did-xrp-restart-alt-season-solana-cardano-polygon-up-double-digits"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T18:11:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most of the tokens previously deemed securities by the SEC are seeing large gains upon a federal court’s ruling in the XRP case.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Waging ‘Unlawful Harassment Campaign’ in Dogecoin Lawsuit, Says Attorney]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148480</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148480/elon-musk-waging-unlawful-harassment-campaign-in-dogecoin-lawsuit-says-attorney"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T17:26:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The billionaire's legal team is using a "bottomless war chest" to fund its dirty tactics, the Dogecoin investors' attorney claims.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CryptoPunk DJ Seedphrase Signs to WME, Plans to Release Music]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148476</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148476/cryptopunk-dj-seedphrase-signs-to-wme-plans-to-release-music"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T17:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Helmet-wearing musician Seedphrase, owner of the rarest CryptoPunks NFT, is also set to launch a new community project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ali Shutler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Are All the Federal Charges Celsius Founder Mashinsky Faces]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148450</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148450/feds-hit-former-celsius-ceo-alex-mashinsky-with-seven-criminal-charges"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T16:21:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The brains behind bankrupt crypto lender Celsius have been hit with a number of serious criminal charges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Judge Rules Ripple Sales of XRP Were Not Securities—Except to Institutions]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148460</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148460/judge-rules-ripple-xrp-securities-institutions"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T16:18:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Programmatic sales of XRP made by the company were not illegal, says the court. But Ripple isn't off the hook just yet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Surges 29% on Judge's Ruling in Ripple SEC Case]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148467</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148467/xrp-surges-29-on-judges-ruling-in-ripple-sec-case"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T16:12:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is XRP a security? Traders react positively to the latest development in the ongoing SEC case against Ripple over the cryptocurrency.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ConsenSys Mesh's TachyonX Fund Wants to Cut the Red Tape for Crypto Founders]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148311</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148311/consensys-mesh-tachyonx"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T15:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TachyonX will offer $150,000 in upfront funding to blockchain startups, along with mentorship from crypto industry heavyweights.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gran Saga Unlimited Early Access: Inside the Anime MMORPG on Aptos]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JeFWMVwo/gran-saga-unlimited-early-access-inside-the-anime-mmorpg-on-aptos</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JeFWMVwo/gran-saga-unlimited-early-access-inside-the-anime-mmorpg-on-aptos"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T21:46:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin plays Gran Saga: Unlimited's second community playtest, reports her findings, and offers her opinion and insights on the upcoming game, which will offer optional Aptos NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[100 Thieves' Moe Says Blockchain Games Will 'Eventually' Be Accepted by Livestreamers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/xHhh62ID/100-thieves-moe-says-blockchain-games-will-eventually-be-accepted-by-livestreamers</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/xHhh62ID/100-thieves-moe-says-blockchain-games-will-eventually-be-accepted-by-livestreamers"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T16:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[100 Thieves content creator and gamer Moe also goes by "Yassuo" online after his favorite League of Legends character. Decrypt's Kate Irwin asks him about 100 Thieves' future crypto plans and whether Moe thinks creators like xQc and Pokimane might ever come around to blockchain games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Games of the Future Are Going to Be Different," Says Splinterlands Cofounder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/sQv6zcil/games-of-the-future-are-going-to-be-different-says-splinterlands-cofounder</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/sQv6zcil/games-of-the-future-are-going-to-be-different-says-splinterlands-cofounder"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T20:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Splinterlands Cofounder Matt Rosen tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about how the game has evolved over its five-year history and why he doesn't listen to the FUD around crypto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Champions Ascension: Like 'For Honor' with NFTs?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/gvM9ajww/inside-champions-ascension-like-for-honor-with-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/gvM9ajww/inside-champions-ascension-like-for-honor-with-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T22:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plai Labs Marketing Director Payton Kaleiwahea tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about player response to the combat game Champions Ascension in development, which offers arena combat, raid bosses, AI landscape features, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Activision VP Michael Lee: Gaming Is Crypto's 'Killer App']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/M9ulXrb3/ex-activision-vp-michael-lee-gaming-is-cryptos-killer-app</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/M9ulXrb3/ex-activision-vp-michael-lee-gaming-is-cryptos-killer-app"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Activision Vice President Michael Lee is now the SVP of Growth at Matter Labs. At the 3XP gaming conference, Lee sat down with Decrypt's Kate Irwin to discuss crypto gaming and give his predictions for the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Behind the Scenes with AMGI Studios and My Pet Hooligan]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/eQ71oapI/behind-the-scenes-with-amgi-studios-and-my-pet-hooligan</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/eQ71oapI/behind-the-scenes-with-amgi-studios-and-my-pet-hooligan"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T21:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin goes to Burbank, California for a behind-the-scenes tour of AMGI Studios, the developers of upcoming game My Pet Hooligan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Legend of Arcardia Chose Sui Over EVM Chains]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/H6JSRJIk/why-legend-of-arcardia-chose-sui-over-evm-chains</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/H6JSRJIk/why-legend-of-arcardia-chose-sui-over-evm-chains"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T21:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Legend of Arcadia Executive Producer Andy Lee tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the game and why they switched from EVM to new protocol Sui.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rumble Racing Star Game Preview: Is This Mario Kart With NFTs?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/lXVkuaeq/rumble-racing-star-game-preview-is-this-mario-kart-with-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/lXVkuaeq/rumble-racing-star-game-preview-is-this-mario-kart-with-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T16:47:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin shares a first look at Delabs' upcoming lawn mower racing game Rumble Racing Star, which offers a large cast of quirky characters pulled from the worlds of Bored Ape Yacht Club, Pudgy Penguins, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Laguna Games Turned Down 'Game of Thrones' for Crypto Unicorns]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/IqET3GYs/why-laguna-games-turned-down-game-of-thrones-for-crypto-unicorns</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/IqET3GYs/why-laguna-games-turned-down-game-of-thrones-for-crypto-unicorns"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T21:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin chats with Laguna Games about why the team chose to move away from an offer with WB Games to develop a Game of Thrones licensed title—and made Crypto Unicorns instead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mythical Games CEO John Linden on NFL Rivals Topping 1M Downloads]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/nDhvMd8r/mythical-games-ceo-john-linden-on-nfl-rivals-topping-1m-downloads</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/nDhvMd8r/mythical-games-ceo-john-linden-on-nfl-rivals-topping-1m-downloads"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T23:49:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mythical Games just raised a $37 million Series C1 round on the back of the early success of NFL Rivals, which has already topped a million downloads in two months. Mythical CEO John Linden joins Decrypt's Andrew Hayward to discuss the launch and impact of NFL Rivals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Ava Labs Is Approaching Gaming on Avalanche]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/M4TqVEkK/how-ava-labs-is-approaching-gaming-on-avalanche</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/M4TqVEkK/how-ava-labs-is-approaching-gaming-on-avalanche"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T22:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At 3XP, Ava Labs Head of Gaming Ed Chang sat down with Decrypt's Kate Irwin to discuss some of the biggest Avalanche-based games on the horizon and how the company is approaching and thinking about Web3 gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ogimi Founder David Gull on Why AI Should Be Your Meditation Coach]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DnNqBruk/ogimi-founder-david-gull-on-why-ai-should-be-your-meditation-coach</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DnNqBruk/ogimi-founder-david-gull-on-why-ai-should-be-your-meditation-coach"/>
        <updated>2023-06-25T18:45:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ogimi founder David Gull speaks with Decrypt's Jason Nelson about its AI-driven meditation guides and how the technology can enable a more unique, custom-tailored meditation experience for users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VaynerSports Gaming VP Discusses Web3 Content Creators, Decentralized Streaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/1MvGbnK5/vaynersports-gaming-vp-discusses-web3-content-creators-decentralized-streaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/1MvGbnK5/vaynersports-gaming-vp-discusses-web3-content-creators-decentralized-streaming"/>
        <updated>2023-06-24T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Darren Glover, VP of Gaming at talent management agency VaynerSports, sat down with Decrypt's Kate Irwin at the 3XP expo to discuss the challenges faced by Web3-centric content creators, the current state of the esports market, and how decentralized streaming platforms can challenge centralized leaders like Twitch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NYXL Co-Founder on the State of Esports and Crypto Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/xDHUNFLB/nyxl-co-founder-on-the-state-of-esports-and-crypto-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/xDHUNFLB/nyxl-co-founder-on-the-state-of-esports-and-crypto-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-06-23T22:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rohit Gupta, co-founder of esports team NYXL, chats with Decrypt's Kate Irwin at the 3XP expo to discuss challenges faced by the esports industry and opportunities and experiments in Web3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is GameBridge? Inside Shrapnel's Gaming Innovation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/xqVjzGLr/what-is-gamebridge-inside-shrapnels-gaming-innovation</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/xqVjzGLr/what-is-gamebridge-inside-shrapnels-gaming-innovation"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marc Mercuri, Head of Platform for Web3 shooter Shrapnel, speaks with Decrypt's Kate Irwin at the 3XP expo about GameBridge, a feature that simplifies blockchain item composability and interoperability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gods Unchained Executive Producer Discusses Epic Games Store Move]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/hjLymzUL/gods-unchained-executive-producer-discusses-epic-games-store-move</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/hjLymzUL/gods-unchained-executive-producer-discusses-epic-games-store-move"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daniel Paez, Executive Producer on Immutable X-based card-battler Gods Unchained, discusses the long-running NFT game's launch on the Epic Games Store and the opportunity it provides.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Play-to-Earn Is Not Dead. It Will Never Die' Says Words with Friends Creator Paul Bettner]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/znmOo9vp/play-to-earn-is-not-dead-it-will-never-die-says-words-with-friends-creator-paul-bettner</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/znmOo9vp/play-to-earn-is-not-dead-it-will-never-die-says-words-with-friends-creator-paul-bettner"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T14:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Words With Friends and Wildcard Creator Paul Bettner tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about his perspective on Axie Infinity and Web3 games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cross the Ages Game Review: A Tough But Rewarding Card Battler]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/2PfzFDVY/cross-the-ages-game-review-a-tough-but-rewarding-card-battler</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/2PfzFDVY/cross-the-ages-game-review-a-tough-but-rewarding-card-battler"/>
        <updated>2023-06-18T12:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cross the Ages is a digital collectible card game that challenges players to duel online opponents—and you can even mint your cards as tradable NFTs. It's complex and difficult to grasp at first, but this mobile-first game has some serious strategic upside. GG contributor Ryan Gladwin puts Cross the Ages through its paces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>