<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-09-11T16:19:09.539Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-09-11T16:19:09.539Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX's $3.4 Billion Crypto Portfolio Includes Solana, Bitcoin and Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155829</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155829/ftx-details-its-3-4-billion-crypto-portfolio-of-solana-bitcoin-and-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T16:06:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FTX's liquid crypto portfolio is worth $3.4 billion in total.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Is Killing Crypto Venture Capital Interest]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754cbd523f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/09/11/ai-is-killing-crypto-venture-capital-interest/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T16:06:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scandals like FTX drove away VCs, leading to a collapse in venture funding. Now, artificial intelligence is soaking up the capital still available in an uncertain macro environment, says Chris Coll-Beswick, at Transcend Labs, a startup accelerator.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coll-Beswick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apocalypse PoW: Bitcoin and the End of Days]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754cbd5782</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/apocalypse-pow-bitcoin-and-the-end-of-days"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T16:06:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Annihilation commencing. Whether through poorly conceived boot up instructions to a novel AI, a global war between desperate nation states, or the final rug pull of our fragile ozone layer - the end of the world hasn’t felt this tangible since school children ducked and covered under desks in the nuclear psychic ashes of the post-WW2 era. Eschatological preachers now claim the end times without needing the Mayan calendar on hand to back them up, with the Covid pandemic still a livid scar on the fragile socially-driven economies that make up our global village. 
When everything is gone, what will remain? For doomsday preppers, tech enthusiasts, and hedge fund managers making the biggest hedge of all - the answer is crypto, in particular Bitcoin, with its time-tested Proof of Work (PoW) econ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Dob</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring The Intersection Of Finance And Trust With Mark Goodwin’s ‘The Bitcoin-Dollar’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754cbd576f</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/bitcoin-books/exploring-finance-and-trust-with-the-bitcoin-dollar"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T16:06:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Only one month after being announced as Editor-in-Chief of Bitcoin Magazine, Mark Goodwin is releasing his premier book “The Bitcoin-Dollar.” The book takes readers on an illuminating journey through the intricate intersection of finance, technology and trust. This groundbreaking work delves deep into the essence of currency and commodity to offer a fresh perspective on the financial landscape of the digital age.
Goodwin posits that currency is not the only function of money; it's a technology that acts as a conduit of trust across time and space. When looking at the history of monetary systems, the line between commodity and currency has been the defining linchpin. However, the dollar, long regarded as the emblem of stability, now finds itself facing an unprecedented challenger, thanks to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Craig Deutsch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ZK Rollups Are Coming To Bitcoin. Here’s All You Need To Know]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754cbd5768</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/technical/zk-rollups-are-coming-to-bitcoin-heres-all-you-need-to-know"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T16:06:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zero-knowledge (ZK) rollups are coming to Bitcoin. Recently, two different projects took turnkey steps into turning this development into a reality for the original cryptocurrency, an advancement that could help Bitcoin scale even more and also provide additional privacy assurances to users that decide to use it.
Chainway last week announced the open-sourcing of their data availability (DA) adapter, a piece of technology that allows developers to leverage Bitcoin’s security and finality to develop rollups with the Sovereign Software Development Kit (SDK). Sovereign provides bundled services for developers to build different kinds of rollups, and Chainway’s launch seeks to enable Bitcoin’s first ZK rollup.
Kasar Labs teamed up with Taproot Wizards to coincidently release a DA adapter for Bi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Namcios</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto market is bearish, but these 2 tokens are still outperforming]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18894856/The-crypto-market-is-bearish-but-these-2-tokens-are-still-outperforming</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18894856/The-crypto-market-is-bearish-but-these-2-tokens-are-still-outperforming"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T16:05:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amid a tough day with the cryptocurrency market down on September 11, the last 30 days were also marked by … Continued]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biggest Movers: SHIB Plunges to Multi-Month Low on Monday]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754cbdbfaa</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/biggest-movers-shib-plunges-to-multi-month-low-on-monday/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T16:03:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba inu started the week by dropping to its lowest point since June, as a red wave swept through cryptocurrency markets. This has pushed the global market cap 1.20% lower at the time of writing. XRP fell by as much as 5%, as Ripple’s battle with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) continued.
 
Shiba Inu (SHIB )
 
Shiba inu (SHIB) edged lower on Monday, as the meme coin fell to its weakest point in over two months.
 
SHIB/USD dropped to an intraday low of $0.000007028 on Monday, following a high of $0.000007413 the day prior.
 
This was the weakest point that shiba inu has traded at since June 20, when the price bottomed out at $0.00000698.
 
 
Looking at the chart, the decline came as the relative strength index (RSI) fell below a support point at the 34.00 level.
 
At the time of writing, the index is tracking at 30.42, with the next visible floor around the 28.00 region.
 
Overall, SHIB has now fallen lower for four consecutive days, and seems to be heading towards the $0.00000680 zone.
 
 
XRP
 
XRP, formerly ripple, fell by as much as 5% on Monday, as markets continued to react to the latest news surrounding a lawsuit with the SEC.
 
The Securities and Exchange Commission said it would appeal a decision by a U.S. judge not to find Ripple Labs guilty of violating securities laws.
 
XRP/USD dropped to a low of $0.4682 on the news, which came following a high of $0.5007 the day prior.
 
 
As a result of the decline in price, XRP slipped to its weakest point since mid-August, falling below a floor on the RSI in the process.
 
Price strength now sits at 26.82, which is deep in oversold territory, with a lower floor of 23.00 still a possible target for traders.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
Could XRP extend declines in the coming days? Let us know your thoughts in the comments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase To Put An End Operations in India – Here’s When]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18894851/Coinbase-To-Put-An-End-Operations-in-India-Heres-When</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18894851/Coinbase-To-Put-An-End-Operations-in-India-Heres-When"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T16:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase, one of the world’s leading cryptocurrency exchanges, has decided to cease operations in India. The company cited regulatory uncertainties and users not meeting their updated standards as the primary factors in this strategic move. India Will No Longer Access Coinbase Trading Services,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase: What this latest update means for users in India]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18894848/Coinbase-What-this-latest-update-means-for-users-in-India</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18894848/Coinbase-What-this-latest-update-means-for-users-in-India"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T16:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase clarifies its presence in India, revealing that its wallet offerings and technology hub continues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Remember That Guy That Lost A Flashdrive With 8,000 BTC? Here’s What He’s Up To Now]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18894828/Remember-That-Guy-That-Lost-A-Flashdrive-With-8000-BTC-Heres-What-Hes-Up-To-Now</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18894828/Remember-That-Guy-That-Lost-A-Flashdrive-With-8000-BTC-Heres-What-Hes-Up-To-Now"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T16:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[James Howells, a Welsh Bitcoin investor and the man who inadvertently lost $557 million worth of BTC in a flash drive is seeking to file a lawsuit against Newport City Council (NCC) in the United Kingdom for refusing his requests to excavate the area he presumed he misplaced the hard drive. ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You no longer need 32 ETH to stake on Coinbase Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18894817/You-no-longer-need-32-ETH-to-stake-on-Coinbase-Cloud</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18894817/You-no-longer-need-32-ETH-to-stake-on-Coinbase-Cloud"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Partial staking will be coming to Coinbase Wallet in “the coming weeks”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Cloud integrates Kiln platform for native ETH staking below 32 ETH]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18894830/Coinbase-Cloud-integrates-Kiln-platform-for-native-ETH-staking-below-32-ETH</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18894830/Coinbase-Cloud-integrates-Kiln-platform-for-native-ETH-staking-below-32-ETH"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T15:59:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The integration will allow Coinbase Wallet users to stake smaller ETH amounts directly from their crypto wallets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Australia Topples Canada in the 75,000 XRP Holder List]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18894799/Australia-Topples-Canada-in-the-75000-XRP-Holder-List</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18894799/Australia-Topples-Canada-in-the-75000-XRP-Holder-List"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T15:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pro-XRP lawyer John E. Deaton has revealed the top three most represented countries in the XRP vs. SEC lawsuit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Squid unveils direct swaps across Cosmos and EVM blockchains]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18894802/Squid-unveils-direct-swaps-across-Cosmos-and-EVM-blockchains</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18894802/Squid-unveils-direct-swaps-across-Cosmos-and-EVM-blockchains"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T15:49:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Squid has enabled swaps simultaneously across Ethereum, various Ethereum Virtual Machine blockchains and the Cosmos ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything to Know About France’s Crypto Influencer Certification]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18894810/Everything-to-Know-About-Frances-Crypto-Influencer-Certification</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18894810/Everything-to-Know-About-Frances-Crypto-Influencer-Certification"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T15:47:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[France’s finance and advertising regulators have united to launch a new certification program for crypto and financial influencers. This initiative aims to professionalize the industry and protect investors. However, this certificate will remain optional for content creators. The Autorité des...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Virtuzone, TOKO launch Dubai’s first tokenized equity crowdfunding platform]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18894796/Virtuzone-TOKO-launch-Dubais-first-tokenized-equity-crowdfunding-platform</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18894796/Virtuzone-TOKO-launch-Dubais-first-tokenized-equity-crowdfunding-platform"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T15:46:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Virtuzone and TOKO Network’s partnership will see them launch Dubai’s inaugural tokenized equity fundraising platform for startups and entrepreneurs. TOKO Network has also secured a VASP operating licence from Dubai’s VARA. Virtuzone, a leading business solutions provider and TOKO Network, a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Does The Future Of XRP Ledger Look Like? Ripple CTO Has Answers]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754cb889c8</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/future-of-xrp-ledger/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T15:45:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple recently amended its XRP Ledger in the face of its ongoing legal battle with the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). As to what to expect, Ripple’s Chief Technology Officer David Schwartz has given the XRP community insights on what will be included in this latest rippled version. 
 
Decentralized Identity On The XRP Ledger
 
Schwartz has revealed that the latest XRP Ledger version will include Decentralized Identity (DID) solutions. He made this revelation during the 2023 Apex XRPL developer summit, an annual event where stakeholders in the industry come to celebrate and discuss everything XRPL-related.
 
 
 
 
This DID feature on the XRPL will give users more control over their digital identities as a centralized institution will no longer control them. Furthermore, these…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ether ‘least loved’ asset as crypto funds see further $59 million in outflows]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18894803/Ether-least-loved-asset-as-crypto-funds-see-further-59-million-in-outflows</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18894803/Ether-least-loved-asset-as-crypto-funds-see-further-59-million-in-outflows"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T15:45:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ether year-to-date outflows reached $108 million, becoming the “least loved digital asset amongst ETP investors this year,” CoinShares said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$PERP Surpasses ADA, Shib in Trading Volume as Prices Surge 40%. Here Are 3 Other Altcoins to Watch]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18894811/PERP-Surpasses-ADA-Shib-in-Trading-Volume-as-Prices-Surge-40-Here-Are-3-Other-Altcoins-to-Watch</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18894811/PERP-Surpasses-ADA-Shib-in-Trading-Volume-as-Prices-Surge-40-Here-Are-3-Other-Altcoins-to-Watch"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Is Killing Crypto Venture Capital Interest]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18894813/AI-Is-Killing-Crypto-Venture-Capital-Interest</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18894813/AI-Is-Killing-Crypto-Venture-Capital-Interest"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T15:43:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scandals like FTX drove away VCs, leading to a collapse in venture funding. Now, artificial intelligence is soaking up the capital still available in an uncertain macro environment, says Chris Coll-Beswick, at Transcend Labs, a startup accelerator.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) Becomes Inflationary Again, Here's Why]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18894804/Ethereum-ETH-Becomes-Inflationary-Again-Heres-Why</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18894804/Ethereum-ETH-Becomes-Inflationary-Again-Heres-Why"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T15:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried still wants out over poor WiFi and laptop access]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18894800/Sam-Bankman-Fried-still-wants-out-over-poor-WiFi-and-laptop-access</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18894800/Sam-Bankman-Fried-still-wants-out-over-poor-WiFi-and-laptop-access"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T15:41:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried says the realities of jail proceedings and poor WiFi have resulted in him unable to prepare for his trial.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aave v3 fork debuts noncustodial liquidity markets on Base]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18894763/Aave-v3-fork-debuts-noncustodial-liquidity-markets-on-Base</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18894763/Aave-v3-fork-debuts-noncustodial-liquidity-markets-on-Base"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T15:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seamless Protocol, a fork of Aave v3 deployed on Base, enables smart contracts with predetermined borrowing strategies to conduct undercollateralized borrowing on-chain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The crucial role of randomness in gaming and web3’s novel solutions: An Interview with Felix Xu]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18894768/The-crucial-role-of-randomness-in-gaming-and-web3s-novel-solutions-An-Interview-with-Felix-Xu</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18894768/The-crucial-role-of-randomness-in-gaming-and-web3s-novel-solutions-An-Interview-with-Felix-Xu"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T15:30:47.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB) on the Verge of Hitting a Major Milestone]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18894726/Shiba-Inu-SHIB-on-the-Verge-of-Hitting-a-Major-Milestone</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18894726/Shiba-Inu-SHIB-on-the-Verge-of-Hitting-a-Major-Milestone"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T15:25:05.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Contracts Across Time – Participants Of Blockchain Masterclass Consider Real World Cases]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18894759/Bitcoin-Contracts-Across-Time-Participants-Of-Blockchain-Masterclass-Consider-Real-World-Cases</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18894759/Bitcoin-Contracts-Across-Time-Participants-Of-Blockchain-Masterclass-Consider-Real-World-Cases"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T15:22:52.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Australia Moves to Third Position on List of XRP Holders: Crypto Lawyer]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18894742/Australia-Moves-to-Third-Position-on-List-of-XRP-Holders-Crypto-Lawyer</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18894742/Australia-Moves-to-Third-Position-on-List-of-XRP-Holders-Crypto-Lawyer"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T15:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pro-XRP lawyer John Deaton recently tweeted how countries fared on the XRP holders list. “I checked the 75K XRP Holder list, and Australia moved to the #3 spot,” tweeted the crypto advocate. Deaton posted this in response to the Australian XRP community’s post about the upcoming XRP Gold Coast...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Holds $1.16B in SOL, $200M in Bahamas Real Estate, Court Filing Says]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754ca560f0</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/09/11/ftx-holds-116b-in-sol-200m-in-bahamas-real-estate-court-filing-says/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T15:15:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company says it paid billions to executives including founder Sam Bankman-Fried before filing for bankruptcy last year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack Schickler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spectacular Solana: Venture Capitalist Sees Unbelievable 2,500% Rally Ahead]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754ca1b8c5</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/solana-vc-sees-unbelievable-2500-rally-ahead/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T14:46:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana (SOL) recently took center stage in the crypto world when Chris Burniske, the visionary behind Placeholder Capital and a former luminary at ARK Invest, engaged in a highly optimistic conversation about its potential.
 
On the social media platform X, Burniske shared his bold projection that a $75,000 investment in Solana could potentially skyrocket to an impressive $2 million. This audacious forecast is based on Burniske’s belief that Solana has the potential not only to compete with Ethereum (ETH) but also to potentially surpass it in the near future. 
 
Burniske’s optimism hinges on Solana doubling its previous all-time high, a feat he deems likely despite acknowledging the inherent volatility of the crypto market.
 
“Assumes SOL goes at least 2x former all-time high, which I thin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$691K Stolen as Hackers Take Over Vitalik Buterin's X Account]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754cad72c4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/09/11/691k-stolen-as-hackers-take-over-vitalik-buterins-x-account/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T14:22:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers who took control of Ethereum founder Vitalik Buterin's X account have stolen more than $691,000 after posting a malicious phishing link that gained access to people's wallets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maple Finance Nearly Imploded, but Sid Powell Wants to Bring Back Its Billion Dollar-Plus Glory]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754cad72af</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/09/11/maple-finance-nearly-imploded-but-sid-powell-wants-to-bring-back-its-billion-dollar-plus-glory/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T14:22:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year’s crypto crash wiped out Maple Finance’s TVL as borrowers crumbled and lenders fled. In an interview with CoinDesk, the protocol’s co-founder and CEO lays out his plan for growth in an era of heightened risk management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Safekeeping Specialist Fireblocks Introduces Non-Custodial Wallet Service]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754caf5213</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/09/11/crypto-safekeeping-specialist-fireblocks-introduces-non-custodial-wallet-service/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T14:09:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fireblocks’ multi-party computation technology works well in a non-custodial setting, shifting counterparty risk away from a corporate entity, Shaulov explained in an interview with CoinDesk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Estate Sues Layerzero Labs for $85M Over Alleged Fraudulent Deals and Asset Withdrawals Amidst Collapse]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754caf54ed</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ftx-estate-sues-layerzero-labs-for-85m-over-alleged-fraudulent-deals-and-asset-withdrawals-amidst-collapse/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T14:09:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bankrupt estate of cryptocurrency exchange FTX is suing blockchain company Layerzero Labs in an attempt to claw back a $45 million deal and over $40 million in withdrawals made in the days before FTX filed for bankruptcy. The lawsuit alleges that Layerzero exploited FTX’s financial distress to negotiate a fire-sale transaction just prior to the bankruptcy filing. Layerzero’s co-founder and CEO Bryan Pellegrino, however, says the lawsuit “is filled with unsubstantiated claims.”
 
Layerzero Accused of Exploiting FTX’s Distress: Lawsuit Highlights Purported Fraudulent Activities
 
The complaint filed by FTX accuses Layerzero of fraudulent transfers, unjust enrichment, and violations of the automatic bankruptcy stay. It seeks to recover equity that FTX subsidiary Alameda Ventures transferr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weekly Bitcoin And Crypto Preview: Don’t Miss These 5 Market-Moving Events]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754caa9776</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-crypto-preview-5-market-moving-events/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T13:47:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bitcoin and crypto market is bracing for a whirlwind week ahead, with pivotal events that could significantly influence trading and regulatory landscapes. From Binance’s legal tussle with the SEC to crucial economic data releases, here are the top five events that market participants should keep an eye on.
 
#1 Binance Responds To SEC’s Orders (Monday)
 
Today, Binance.US, the American arm of the global crypto exchange, is slated to reply to the US Securities and Exchange Commission’s (SEC) motion to file confidential documents and objection to a protective order. The case, which has significant implications for the crypto sector, has experts like pro-XRP attorney John E. Deaton speculating on the nature of these sealed documents.
 
“As I said on Crypto Law and other channels, it will …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Evolution of India's Crypto Policy: From Taxation to Global Collaboration]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754c91b6b3</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/regulation/the-evolution-of-indias-crypto-policy-from-taxation-to-global-collaboration/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T12:58:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[India  
is currently in the process of creating a regulatory framework for  
cryptocurrencies. It is based on recommendations from two significant  
international organizations, the International Monetary Fund (IMF) and the  
Financial Stability Board (FSB). 
This  
regulatory framework aims to provide a legal structure for the use and trading  
of cryptocurrencies in India. It is expected to take shape over the next 5-6  
months.
India's Optimistic Outlook towards  
Cryptocurrency Regulation
The  
IMF-FSB recommends emphasizing the need for regulating the cryptocurrency  
market rather than imposing an outright ban. These recommendations serve as a set  
of guidelines that G20 countries can use to create their independent yet  
coordinated crypto regulations.
The  
blockchain analytic fir…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tareq Sikder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Goes After Celebrities For Millions Of Dollars In Promotional Payments]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754c931194</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ftx-celebrities-payments/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T12:49:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It has been almost one year since the FTX crypto exchange filed for bankruptcy and the contagion brought about by its collapse continues to unfold.
 
So far, the exchange has gone after various companies and institutions in a bid to recover the billions of dollars owed to its creditors and formulate a repayment plan. But this time around, the bankrupt crypto company has turned its attention toward promotional payments paid to celebrities and the like.
 
FTX Wants $18 Million In Promotional Payments
 
During its peak back in 2021, the FTX exchange was known for its far-reaching marketing campaigns. Celebrities were not left out as the likes of Tennis star Naomi Osaka and Basketball legend Shaquille O’Neal were also brought on by the exchange for promotional purposes. These deals saw the sta…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Technical Analysis: ETH Below $1,600 Ahead of Key US Economic Releases]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754c9d8a1b</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-ethereum-technical-analysis-eth-below-1600-ahead-of-key-us-economic-releases/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T12:33:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum has started the week below $1,600, as markets appeared to be awaiting the release of several key data points from the United States. After a quiet week, the coming days will see the latest inflation, retail sales, and consumer sentiment figures released. Bitcoin remained lower on Monday.
 
Bitcoin
 
Bitcoin started yet another week trading under the $26,000 level, as traders began to prepare for upcoming U.S. economic releases.
 
BTC/USD slipped to a low of $25,620.46 earlier in today’s session, after ending the weekend at a peak of $25,978.13.
 
Monday’s decline in price saw bitcoin continue to hover close to a key support point at the $25,600 region.
 
 
Bitcoin chart by TradingView
 

 
 

 
The slippage comes as the 14-day relative strength index (RSI) moved closer to a floor of its own at the 35.00 mark.
 
At the time of writing, the index is tracking at a reading of 37.09, which comes after failing to break out of a ceiling of 45.00 last week.
 
Should bulls reject a drop below 35.00, there is a good chance that BTC reverses in the coming days.
 
 
Ethereum
 
Ethereum (ETH) edged lower to start the week, with price falling below the $1,600 level on Monday.
 
After peaking at $1,627.67 on Sunday, ETH/USD raced to an intraday low of $1,581.79 during today’s session.
 
This resulted in the world’s second largest cryptocurrency falling to its lowest level since August 22.
 
 
Ethereum chart by TradingView
 

 
 

 
The decline arrives as a breakout occurred on a price floor of $1,620, with bears rushing into the market as a result.
 
Price strength is now oversold, and is tracking at 31.27, with the next support point at the 28.00 zone.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
Will ethereum slip further this week? Leave your thoughts in the comments below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Mover Americas: Altcoins Start the Week in the Red]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754c9ece28</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/09/11/first-mover-americas-altcoins-start-the-week-in-the-red/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T12:25:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest price moves in bitcoin (BTC) and crypto markets in context for Sept. 11, 2023. First Mover is CoinDesk’s daily newsletter that contextualizes the latest actions in the crypto markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley, Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Animoca Brands Raises $20M to Pursue ‘Single Native Web3 Project’ Mocaverse]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155770</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155770/animoca-brands-raises-20m-to-pursue-single-native-web3-project-mocaverse"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T12:17:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A set of 8,888 NFTs will provide holders access to the company’s ecosystem and a chance to accumulate loyalty points.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase CEO Hints At ‘Flatcoin’: The Next Wave In Stablecoins]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754c9bd82d</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/coinbase-ceo-hints-at-flatcoin/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T11:49:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong in a recent interview unveiled his interest in a novel concept within the cryptocurrency sphere, known as “flatcoins.” According to Armstrong, flatcoins represent the next evolution of stablecoins, offering a unique approach to maintaining value stability in the volatile world of cryptocurrencies.
 
Flatcoins, as Armstrong explained, are stablecoins that derive their value from a different source compared to traditional stablecoins. Rather than being backed by fiat currency or a basket of assets, flatcoins are pegged to purchasing power or the Consumer Price Index (CPI). 
 
This means that the value of a flatcoin would fluctuate to reflect changes in the cost of goods and services, making it potentially more resilient to inflation and economic fluctuations.
 
 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Turns Inflationary as Gas Fees Plummet to 2023 Lows]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155762</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155762/ethereum-turns-inflationary-as-gas-fees-plummet-to-2023-lows"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T11:49:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain traders are waiting for the next narrative as interest in meme coin and Telegram bot trading cool off.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nigerian Web3 Startup Nestcoin Secures $1.9 million in Funding]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754c852672</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/nigerian-web3-startup-nestcoin-secures-1-9-million-in-funding/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T11:41:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Nigerian Web3 startup Nestcoin has reportedly secured a total of $1.9 million in funding from both existing and new investors. The capital raised will be used to bolster Nestcoin’s finances and further develop the startup’s non-custodial wallet. 
 
Impact of FTX’s Collapse on Nestcoin
 
The Nigerian Web3 startup Nestcoin recently secured $1.9 million via a strategic funding round which was led by Hashed Emergent, a report has said. Existing investors that participated in the round include Alter Global, Magic Fund, CMT Digital, and 4DX Ventures while Adaverse and Base Ecosystem Fund were the two new investors.
 
The startup’s latest fundraising success came almost a year after it lost access to a stash of stablecoins which were held at the now defunct cryptocurrency exchange FTX. As reported by Bitcoin.com News in November 2022, Nestcoin initially responded to the loss of access to digital assets worth millions of dollars by reducing its employee headcount.
 
 
According to a Techcrunch report, the loss of access to funds also forced Nestcoin to re-evaluate its business model. Commenting on what the re-evaluation process has done for the startup, Yele Bademosi, the CEO of Nestcoin, said:
 
“During this transition period, we were trying to make the best decision when there were no good decisions. It helped that we were open and transparent with our investors and community. We had to make tough decisions regarding cutting product lines. We had to transition from a venture studio and investment holding company to a single-product company.”
 
Meanwhile, the report revealed that Nestcoin is planning not only to use the raised funds to bolster its finances but also to develop its non-custodial wallet further.
 
Register your email here to get a weekly update on African news sent to your inbox:
 
 
What are your thoughts on this story? Let us know what you think in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond JPM Coin: JPMorgan Explores Blockchain-Based Digital Deposit Token]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754c85ad8e</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/beyond-jpm-coin-jpmorgan-explores-blockchain-based-digital-deposit-token/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T11:37:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JPMorgan  
Chase, one of the largest banks in the United States, is in the early stages of  
exploring the use of blockchain technology to create a digital deposit token.  
The token would represent a digital version of deposits that customers hold in  
their bank accounts and could be used to make cross-border payments and  
settlements faster and more efficient.
Regulators' Considerations and  
JPMorgan's Preparedness
JPMorgan  
has already developed most of the necessary technology to make this project a  
reality. However, it will only proceed if it receives approval from U.S.  
regulators.
According  
to an anonymous source, JPMorgan Chase is considering launching a blockchain-based digital deposit token for use by corporate clients within a  
year if it receives regulatory approval. …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tareq Sikder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Algorand Boss Steve Kokinos Tapped as CEO for Firm Buying Celsius]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155760</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155760/ex-algorand-boss-steve-kokinos-tapped-as-ceo-for-firm-buying-celsius"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T10:52:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celsius creditors played a prominent role in selecting the board for Fahrenheit Holdings—appointing six of the nine members.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Connor Sephton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feds Want $5.2 Million in Bitcoin Returned by Teen Hacker—And A Sports Car, Too]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155747</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155747/doj-demands-5-million-in-bitcoin-and-bmw-sports-car-from-teen-hacker"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T01:02:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Department of Justice accused the teenager and his accomplices of stealing money from crypto executives in the Silicon Valley area.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacker Steals Over $690,000 After Hijacking Vitalik Buterin's Twitter Account]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155738</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155738/hacker-steals-690000-after-hijacking-vitalik-buterin-x-account"/>
        <updated>2023-09-10T22:42:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A fake link promising an exclusive NFT was posted to the Ethereum inventor's feed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shaq Got Nearly $750,000 From FTX Amid Millions In Celebrity Deals]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155732</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155732/shaq-got-nearly-750000-from-ftx-amid-millions-in-celebrity-deals"/>
        <updated>2023-09-10T22:18:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A bankruptcy filing names names: Shaquille O’Neal, Naomi Osaka, David Ortiz, and Trevor Lawrence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SBF Lawyers Again Ask for Pre-Trial Release Because Prison Internet Sucks]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155728</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155728/sam-bankman-fried-prison-internet-trial-preparation-request"/>
        <updated>2023-09-10T20:03:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Disgraced CEO Sam Bankman-Fried doesn’t have enough time to review the documents in his case, his attorneys claim.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prime Trust Bankruptcy Exposes ‘Widespread’ Self-Custody Risks, Says Anchorage Digital Co-Founder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155714</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155714/prime-trust-bankruptcy-self-custody-risks-anchorage-digital-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-09-10T18:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Diogo Monica says applying existing bank rules, not creating new regulations, can ensure business continuity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week on Crypto Twitter: Bankman-Fried Roughs it in Brooklyn Jail]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155705</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155705/this-week-on-crypto-twitter-bankman-fried-roughs-it-in-brooklyn-jail"/>
        <updated>2023-09-10T17:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to a prison informant, the former billionaire linked up with a gang from Manhattan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ted Cruz Says He Is a ‘Big Believer’ In Bitcoin Mining]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155694</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155694/ted-cruz-texas-senator-bitcoin-mining-dennis-porter-satoshi-act-fund"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T20:15:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Appearing on Fox News Radio, the Texas senator said Bitcoin mining is good for his state’s stressed power grid.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Responds to Ripple Filing, Doubles Down on Appeal Bid]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155689</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155689/sec-ripple-appeal-xrp-securities"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T18:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The regulator claims judge's summary judgment order raises "knotty legal problems" worthy of appellate review]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt AI, Edited by Ryan Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Green Candles—But Barely—for Bitcoin and Ethereum as Global Adoption Grows]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155665</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155665/this-week-in-coins-green-candles-but-barely-for-bitcoin-and-ethereum-as-global-adoption-grows"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T18:01:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Also, a member of the European Central Bank’s executive board criticized PayPal USD and shilled the digital euro.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple to Acquire Crypto Custodian Fortress Trust]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155658</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155658/ripple-fortress-trust-brad-garlinghouse-scott-purcell"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T17:01:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fortress was founded two years ago by former Prime Trust CEO Scott Purcell.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Super Mario Bros. Wonder: Everything You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155605</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155605/super-mario-bros-wonder-nintendo-switch-everything-need-know"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mario and friends enter the fantastical Flower Kingdom. But what else is new in Super Mario Bros. Wonder on Nintendo Switch?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT Plus vs Claude Pro: Choose The Best Paid AI Chatbot For You]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155600</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155600/chatgpt-plus-vs-claude-pro-choose-the-best-paid-ai-chatbot-ally-for-you"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T23:20:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI’s ChatGPT Plus and Anthropic’s Claude Pro come at similar price points, but they have very different strengths and weaknesses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fed's Michael Barr: No Word on CBDC and 'Deeply Concerned' About Stablecoins]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155576</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155576/feds-michael-barr-no-cbdc-decision-deeply-concerned-about-stablecoins"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T23:16:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[He also said that the central bank was "a long way" from any decision on issuing a CBDC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Harry Potter' Actors Protest London Dream Home Plans of Ripple Exec]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155620</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155620/harry-potter-actors-protest-london-dream-home-plans-ripple-exec"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T22:23:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Emma Thompson, Imelda Staunton, and Jim Broadbent appear to be seriously aggrieved about their crypto executive neighbor's remodeling plans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Donation Company Says Gifted Crypto Should Require Less Paperwork]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155601</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155601/bitcoin-donation-company-says-gifted-crypto-should-require-less-paperwork"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T20:59:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's ridiculous to require an appraisal of donations made in dollar-pegged stablecoins, like USDC or USDT, the company argues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LBRY Will Appeal 'Unjust and Incorrect' SEC Lawsuit Ruling, Says CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155569</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155569/lbry-will-appeal-unjust-and-incorrect-sec-lawsuit-ruling-says-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T19:18:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company had previously said it plans to wind down operations and the SEC dropped its financial penalty from $44 million to around $111,000.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[France Now Has Crypto Influencer Training to Encourage Paid Ad Disclosures]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155575</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155575/france-now-has-crypto-influencer-training-to-encourage-paid-ad-disclosures"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T19:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[France requires investment communications to be non-misleading and balanced. “It appears that some influencers are unaware of this," said an official.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roblox Is Finally Coming to PlayStation This Year]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155564</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155564/roblox-finally-coming-playstation-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T18:44:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roblox, which hosts a wide variety of different metaverse game experiences, is finally releasing on PlayStation 4 and PlayStation 5 consoles in October.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[El Salvador's Bitcoin Curriculum Will Teach Students the 'Dark Side of Fiat']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155559</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155559/el-salvadors-bitcoin-curriculum-will-teach-the-dark-side-of-fiat"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T18:04:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Students learn about currency debasement, a nod to Saifedean Ammous's "The Bitcoin Standard" book. But he didn't help write the curriculum.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RIP TCG: How Deadfellaz Is Rethinking Card-Battler Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155545</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155545/rip-tcg-how-deadfellaz-rethinking-card-battler-games"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T17:28:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deadfellaz founders Psych and Betty share how the digital trading card game will help grow the lore of the zombie-themed Ethereum NFT brand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance NFT Marketplace Ends Support for Polygon in Effort to ‘Streamline']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155535</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155535/binance-nft-marketplace-ends-polygon-support"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T16:42:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Users have until the end of the year to withdraw their Polygon NFTs from the exchange's NFT Marketplace.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Review: Should You Spend $20 per Month for the Claude Pro AI Chatbot?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155361</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155361/review-should-you-spend-20-per-month-for-the-claude-pro-ai-chatbot"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T16:22:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t pull out your credit card just yet. Here’s a guide to help you decide whether upgrading to Anthropic's Claude Pro is the right move for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How This African Non-Profit Is Building an Army of Bitcoin Devs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155537</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155537/how-this-african-non-profit-is-building-an-army-of-bitcoin-devs"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T16:11:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The newly renamed Btrust Builders has placed developers with SphinxChat, Galoy, Bitnob, Chaincode Labs, HeartBit, Ibex, and Rigly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Only Up Developer Removes Hit Game From Steam Citing 'Stress']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155540</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155540/only-up-developer-removes-hit-game-steam-citing-stress"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T16:07:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Only Up is now gone forever, apparently, just months after hitting it big with Twitch streamers and intriguing crypto fans with NFT art.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance CEO Brushes Off 'Negative News' Amid Executive Departures]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155530</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155530/binance-ceo-brushes-off-negative-news-amid-executive-departures"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T13:06:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a Twitter post, Changpeng ‘CZ’ Zhao confronted “FUD” surrounding employee turnover at the crypto exchange.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler,Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thodex CEO Gets 11,000-Year Jail Sentence Over $2B Crypto Exchange Collapse]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155522</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155522/thodex-ceo-gets-11000-year-jail-sentence-over-2b-crypto-exchange-collapse"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T11:54:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once the biggest crypto exchange in Turkey, Thodex collapsed in 2021, leaving 400,000 users without access to their crypto deposits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CFTC Charges Three DeFi Protocols With Violating AML Rules, Operating Without Licenses]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155509</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155509/cftc-charges-three-defi-protocols-with-violating-aml-rules-operating-without-licenses"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T11:27:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized exchanges Opyn, ZeroEx and Deridex settled with the CFTC on charges that included failing to geoblock U.S. users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nearly Half Of Institutions Are Holding Digital Assets For Clients: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155507</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155507/nearly-half-of-institutions-are-holding-digital-assets-for-clients-report"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T10:11:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Of 60 institutions surveyed in the U.S., Europe and the U.K., an astounding 48% reported currently managing digital assets for their clients.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Drake and The Weeknd AI Song Went Viral—Could It Win a Grammy?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155479</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155479/drake-weeknd-ai-song-went-viral-now-could-win-grammy"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T23:48:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ghostwriter created "Heart on My Sleeve" with help from AI. It was pulled from streaming services, but it could it really win music's highest honor?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shaq Played Active Role in Solana NFT Project Before Abandoning It, Lawsuit Alleges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155470</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155470/shaq-played-active-role-solana-nft-project-before-abandoning-lawsuit-alleges"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T23:20:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Basketball legend Shaquille O'Neal bailed after FTX's collapse, the amended complaint claims, allegedly tanking the NFT project's value.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Bitcoin Miners in Texas Are Making Millions Without Mining at All]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155460</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155460/how-bitcoin-miners-in-texas-are-making-millions-without-mining-at-all"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T21:34:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Miners “either mine BTC or curtail energy when prices are high to sell it back to the grid,” Compass Mining told Decrypt, giving them a better return than mining.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EA Sports UFC 5: Everything You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155400</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155400/ea-sports-ufc-5-everything-you-need-know"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T20:14:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you ready to rumble? EA Sports UFC 5 will be the first Mature-rated entry in the MMA fighting series, coming to PlayStation 5 and Xbox Series X/S.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former FTX Exec Ryan Salame Forfeits $1.5 Billion in Plea Deal]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155340</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155340/former-ftx-exec-ryan-salame-plead-guilty"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T20:04:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Salame, co-CEO of FTX Digital Markets, pleaded guilty to campaign finance violations and fraud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Basketball Title Rumble Kong League and Stance Launch In-Game and IRL HyperSocks]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154226</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154226/basketball-title-rumble-kong-league-and-stance-launch-in-game-and-irl-hypersocks"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T19:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The partnership will kick off with the launch of NFT HyperSocks by Stance, alongside IRL counterparts and an augmented reality filter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FBI Says North Korea’s Lazarus Group Was Behind $41 Million Stake Hack]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155360</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155360/fbi-says-north-koreas-lazarus-group-was-behind-41-million-stake-hack"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T18:58:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The hacker group is one of crypto’s most prolific, allegedly responsible for stealing $2 billion worth of assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Skyrim Creator's Starfield Tops One Million Concurrent Players on Launch Day]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155330</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155330/skyrim-creators-starfield-tops-million-concurrent-players-launch-day"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T18:32:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bethesda Game Studios' Starfield is making waves with a huge player turnout on day one and broadly positive reviews.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Mino Games is Using Artificial Intelligence]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/SrT1Afj7/how-mino-games-is-using-artificial-intelligence</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/SrT1Afj7/how-mino-games-is-using-artificial-intelligence"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T22:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mino Games CEO Sasha McKinnon tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about how the studio's upcoming game Dimensionals will use real-time AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INTERVIEW: How Will Aurory Use NFTs and Crypto?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qv3VwNmM/interview-how-will-aurory-use-nfts-and-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qv3VwNmM/interview-how-will-aurory-use-nfts-and-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T15:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Natoli, Aurory's Head of Marketing and Business Development, tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how the Aurory games will use NFTs and crypto and shares the studio's broader stance on the tech.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Cloud's James Tromans on the Intersection of AI and Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OeD4uoLj/google-clouds-james-tromans-on-the-intersection-of-ai-and-web3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OeD4uoLj/google-clouds-james-tromans-on-the-intersection-of-ai-and-web3"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google's Global Head of Google Cloud for Web3 James Tromans sat down with Decrypt's Jason Nelson to discuss how AI can help Web3 companies come to market faster and the real value of Web3 tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastering NFT Trading - Degen U]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/HQGt1Vrq/mastering-nft-trading-degen-u</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/HQGt1Vrq/mastering-nft-trading-degen-u"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T07:08:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Take Degen U's new course, Mastering NFT Trading, and earn an on-chain certificate. A top instructor will help you identify trends, seize the right moment to trade, weed out scams—and have fun while doing it!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Space Nation CEO on Working With 'Independence Day' Director Roland Emmerich]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LpznLhtx/space-nation-ceo-on-working-with-independence-day-director-roland-emmerich</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LpznLhtx/space-nation-ceo-on-working-with-independence-day-director-roland-emmerich"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T17:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jerome Wu, CEO of Space Nation, tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the upcoming Space Nation Online game in development and shares details on Space Nation Cofounder Roland Emmerich's role in the project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GAME REVIEW: Champions Arena from Gala Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qUE1RlDx/game-review-champions-arena-from-gala-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qUE1RlDx/game-review-champions-arena-from-gala-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Champions Arena is a turn-based fantasy RPG from Gala Games, where characters can become NFTs and crypto can be used to purchase gems, one of the game's synthetic currencies. Decrypt's Kate Irwin takes us inside the game for her thoughts on the fun, mobile-first title.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apex Legends Voice Actor Ben Prendergast on the Future of Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/X3RKdsaG/apex-legends-voice-actor-ben-prendergast-on-the-future-of-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/X3RKdsaG/apex-legends-voice-actor-ben-prendergast-on-the-future-of-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T18:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Voice actor Ben Prendergast, who's voiced characters in games like Apex Legends and God of War Ragnarok, shares his opinions on the tech space's history of "bubbles" and whether blockchain gaming has a future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The future of AI Stardom and Robotics with SingularityNET COO Janet Adams and Desdemona]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yVQaZI71/the-future-of-ai-stardom-and-robotics-with-singularitynet-coo-janet-adams-and-desdemona</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yVQaZI71/the-future-of-ai-stardom-and-robotics-with-singularitynet-coo-janet-adams-and-desdemona"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T16:45:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this interview, SingularityNET COO Janet Adams explains the intricate details that went into creating the Desdemona robot AI from Hanson Robotics and future plans for the AI Diva.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto a 'No-Brainer' for Video Games, Says Mino Games CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rdynom8C/crypto-a-no-brainer-for-video-games-says-mino-games-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rdynom8C/crypto-a-no-brainer-for-video-games-says-mino-games-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T18:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mino Games CEO Sasha MacKinnon, developer of the upcoming Dimensionals game, tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the studio's approach to digital collectibles.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Wagner's 'Controversial Take' on Crypto in Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tc2nKeqA/michael-wagners-controversial-take-on-crypto-in-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tc2nKeqA/michael-wagners-controversial-take-on-crypto-in-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T16:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Solana's PlayGG, Star Atlas CEO Michael Wagner shares his "controversial take" on crypto in games, shares the challenges of developing the upcoming scifi game, and how crypto's volatility has changed his perspective with Decrypt's Jason Nelson.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interview: Angelic CEO on Building the Sci-Fi RPG on Solana and Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/uCzW3K7P/interview-angelic-ceo-on-building-the-sci-fi-rpg-on-solana-and-ethereum</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/uCzW3K7P/interview-angelic-ceo-on-building-the-sci-fi-rpg-on-solana-and-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T15:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Angelic is a sci-fi roleplay game in development that will be free-to-play and offer optional, opt-in crypto features on Solana and Ethereum and a governance token. Metaverse Game Studios CEO and Founder Erkan Bayol tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how he sees AAA traditional games as Angelic's main competitors and shares his vision for the game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apex Legends Voice Actor on AI's Impact on Video Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IOIrmb0N/apex-legends-voice-actor-on-ais-impact-on-video-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IOIrmb0N/apex-legends-voice-actor-on-ais-impact-on-video-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T17:28:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ben Prendergast is an actor who has voiced characters like Apex Legends' Fuse, God of War Ragnarok's Tyr, and Patroclus in Hades. But as debates swirl around the use of artificial intelligence in entertainment in light of the SAG-AFTRA and WGA strikes, Prendergast gives Decrypt's Kate Irwin his honest take on the potential use of AI actors in games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Star Atlas CEO on Developing an MMO Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/WQCaahmH/star-atlas-ceo-on-developing-an-mmo-game</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/WQCaahmH/star-atlas-ceo-on-developing-an-mmo-game"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T13:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Jason Nelson speaks with Star Atlas Founder and CEO Michael Wagner about the MMO game's approach to development, marketing, and blockchain integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aurory's Origin Story: How JRPGs Inspired the Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/O0S201TB/aurorys-origin-story-how-jrpgs-inspired-the-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/O0S201TB/aurorys-origin-story-how-jrpgs-inspired-the-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T16:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Jason Nelson talks to Aurory's Head of Marketing and Business Development Michael Natoli about the origins of the Aurory crypto games at the Solana PlayGG event.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>