<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-06-21T02:32:13.729Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-06-21T02:32:13.729Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BTC Trader Fatigue Sets In: Bitcoin Struggles at $65,000 Ahead of Potential Bounce]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19608227/BTC-Trader-Fatigue-Sets-In-Bitcoin-Struggles-at-65000-Ahead-of-Potential-Bounce</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19608227/BTC-Trader-Fatigue-Sets-In-Bitcoin-Struggles-at-65000-Ahead-of-Potential-Bounce"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T02:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin has dropped by more than 9% over the last 30 days to now trade around the $65,000 mark in a plunge that has seen investors become “mainly fearful or disinterested” toward the cryptocurrency. That’s according to on-chain analytics firm Santiment, which noted in a post on the microblogging...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitwise’s latest Ethereum ad can be minted as an NFT]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19608224/Bitwises-latest-Ethereum-ad-can-be-minted-as-an-NFT</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19608224/Bitwises-latest-Ethereum-ad-can-be-minted-as-an-NFT"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T02:16:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Proceeds from the NFT mints are being paid to Protocol Guild, a collective funding mechanism created by Ethereum core contributors and the ad’s two actors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Market Enters Undervalued Region: Here Are The Altcoins To Watch]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740954610d</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-undervalued-altcoins/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T02:04:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto market has entered an undervalued region with market intelligence platform, Santiment, revealing three major altcoins to watch out for. Santiment’s analysis has indicated the potential for these three altcoins to outperform Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH) and XRP in this market cycle. 
 
Cardano, Shiba Inu, and Dogecoin Are The Altcoins To Watch
 
In an X (formerly Twitter) post on June 19, Santiment indicated that the crypto market was currently undervalued, noting three popular cryptocurrencies, Cardano (ADA), Shiba Inu (SHIB) and Dogecoin (DOGE), displaying highly bullish potentials. 
 
 
According to Santiment’s analysis, the lower a cryptocurrency’s 30-day Market Value to Real Value (MVRV), the higher the potential for a short-term rebound. This essentially means that the cry…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Market Enters Undervalued Region: Here Are The Altcoins To Watch]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19608198/Crypto-Market-Enters-Undervalued-Region-Here-Are-The-Altcoins-To-Watch</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19608198/Crypto-Market-Enters-Undervalued-Region-Here-Are-The-Altcoins-To-Watch"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T02:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto market has entered an undervalued region with market intelligence platform, Santiment, revealing three major altcoins to watch out for. Santiment’s analysis has indicated the potential for these three altcoins to outperform Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH) and XRP in this market cycle....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum, Dogecoin Remain Rangebound: Analysts Says 'The Reversal Is On The Horizon']]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19608219/Bitcoin-Ethereum-Dogecoin-Remain-Rangebound-Analysts-Says-The-Reversal-Is-On-The-Horizon</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19608219/Bitcoin-Ethereum-Dogecoin-Remain-Rangebound-Analysts-Says-The-Reversal-Is-On-The-Horizon"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T01:53:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leading cryptocurrencies remained rangebound as investors search for catalysts amid hawkish signals from the Federal Reserve. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Indian Authority Uncovers Large-Scale Crypto and Hawala Operation, Arrests Key Player]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7409563ec9</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/indian-authority-uncovers-large-scale-crypto-and-hawala-operation-arrests-key-player/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T01:39:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[India’s Directorate of Enforcement (ED) has arrested Manideep Mago under the Prevention of Money Laundering Act (PMLA), 2002, in connection with an “illegal foreign remittances case” involving cryptocurrency. The investigation uncovered that a Delhi-based company sold cryptocurrencies worth over Rs. 1858 crore ($223 million) on crypto exchanges and made foreign remittances exceeding Rs. 3500 crore. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Judge signals likely continuation of SEC lawsuit against Kraken]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19608148/Judge-signals-likely-continuation-of-SEC-lawsuit-against-Kraken</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19608148/Judge-signals-likely-continuation-of-SEC-lawsuit-against-Kraken"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T01:30:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A federal judge in California indicated that he is inclined to let the US Securities and Exchange Commission’s (SEC) lawsuit against Kraken proceed, casting doubt on the exchange’s efforts to have the case dismissed, according to media reports. According to The Block, Judge William Orrick said...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sweeping Raid: UK Authorities Nab Suspects In £1 Billion Crypto Scandal]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74095115a5</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/sweepin-crypto-raid-uk-authorities-suspects-scandal/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T01:03:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a significant development within the UK’s cryptocurrency landscape, authorities have recently apprehended two individuals linked to an alleged illicit digital currency exchange operation, reportedly involving over £1 billion.
 
This move underscores an ongoing effort by regulatory bodies to clamp down on unregulated financial activities within the crypto sector.
 
 
Arrests Made In Billion-Pound Crypto Laundering Bust
 
The arrests, carried out by the Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) in collaboration with the London police, targeted a 38-year-old and a 44-year-old, who have since been released on bail pending further investigations.
 
The crackdown occurred amidst increasing vigilance against money laundering activities through digital currencies. The FCA’s Executive Director of Enforc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can Dogecoin, Shiba Inu shake off their double-digit price drops soon?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19608110/Can-Dogecoin-Shiba-Inu-shake-off-their-double-digit-price-drops-soon</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19608110/Can-Dogecoin-Shiba-Inu-shake-off-their-double-digit-price-drops-soon"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T01:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu and Dogecoin witnessed major price corrections last week, but the coming days might look different.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sweeping Raid: UK Authorities Nab Suspects In £1 Billion Crypto Scandal]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19608111/Sweeping-Raid-UK-Authorities-Nab-Suspects-In-1-Billion-Crypto-Scandal</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19608111/Sweeping-Raid-UK-Authorities-Nab-Suspects-In-1-Billion-Crypto-Scandal"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T01:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a significant development within the UK’s cryptocurrency landscape, authorities have recently apprehended two individuals linked to an alleged illicit digital currency exchange operation, reportedly involving over £1 billion. This move underscores an ongoing effort by regulatory bodies to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bullish sign for Ethereum as exchange balances drop]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19608112/Bullish-sign-for-Ethereum-as-exchange-balances-drop</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19608112/Bullish-sign-for-Ethereum-as-exchange-balances-drop"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T01:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week has been an eventful one for Ethereum, with the launch of spot ETH ETFs imminent by the end of summer. The SEC has closed its long-running investigation into Ethereum 2.0, determining that the sales of ETH did not constitute securities transactions. The June 19 decision is a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PEPE Has 80% Of Holders In Profit: How It Compares To DOGE & BTC]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19608100/PEPE-Has-80-Of-Holders-In-Profit-How-It-Compares-To-DOGE-BTC</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19608100/PEPE-Has-80-Of-Holders-In-Profit-How-It-Compares-To-DOGE-BTC"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T01:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data shows the memecoin Pepe currently has 80% of its holders in profit. Here’s how Dogecoin, Bitcoin, and other top coins compare. PEPE Is Among The Coins With The Highest Profitability Ratio Right Now In a new post on X, the market intelligence platform IntoTheBlock has shared a chart...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Short Sellers Target Cardano ($ADA) and $XRP as Crypto Market Looks for Rebound]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19608096/Short-Sellers-Target-Cardano-ADA-and-XRP-as-Crypto-Market-Looks-for-Rebound</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19608096/Short-Sellers-Target-Cardano-ADA-and-XRP-as-Crypto-Market-Looks-for-Rebound"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T00:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Short sellers have been increasing their bets against both Cardano ($ADA) and the native token of the XRP Ledger ($XRP) in a potential positive development for poatenti long-term investors as liquidated shorts can help propel these cryptocurrencies’ prices. That’s according to on-chain analytics...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Law Enforcement Holds Positive Views on Crypto Despite Crime Concerns, Chainalysis Reports]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7409537ae6</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/law-enforcement-holds-positive-views-on-crypto-despite-crime-concerns-chainalysis-reports/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T00:31:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain analytics firm Chainalysis has found that law enforcement finds cryptocurrency relevant to many investigations and holds positive overall views. The firm also notes the growing adoption of cryptocurrency and its increased criminal exploitation, including intellectual property theft and drug trafficking. Despite the availability of various tools, many respondents are dissatisfied with current resources, highlighting […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoins expand volumes by 10X in four years, but Euro stablecoins are still rare]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19608066/Stablecoins-expand-volumes-by-10X-in-four-years-but-Euro-stablecoins-are-still-rare</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19608066/Stablecoins-expand-volumes-by-10X-in-four-years-but-Euro-stablecoins-are-still-rare"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T00:30:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoins’ overall volumes have grown by 10X in just four years, thanks to growing supply. Increased transfers, trading activity, and presence on multiple networks are elevating stablecoins’ importance. Tether (USDT) and USD Circle (USDC) remain the chief sources of liquidity. Since the market...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Case May End Without SEC Appeal, Ex-Official Suggests]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74095d4756</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ripple-case-may-end-without-sec-appeal/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T00:09:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) may opt not to appeal the summary judgment ruling from Judge Analisa Torres partially favoring Ripple Labs, signaling a strategic shift to avoid establishing a potentially unfavorable precedent in higher courts. This possibility has come to light as the crypto community awaits the court’s remedies phase ruling expected by the end of Summer 2024, after which the SEC’s window to appeal will open.
 
Why The SEC May Want To Avoid An Appeal Vs. Ripple
 
Kristina Littman, former head of the SEC’s Enforcement’s Cyber Unit, weighed in on the SEC’s potential course of action during a recent conference on digital assets. She speculated that given the mixed judicial opinions in similar cases, the SEC might choose to accept the district court’s decision.
 
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[London pair arrested for running illegal crypto exchange]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19608021/London-pair-arrested-for-running-illegal-crypto-exchange</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19608021/London-pair-arrested-for-running-illegal-crypto-exchange"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T00:05:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A London pair has been arrested for allegedly running an illegal exchange in the city that traded more than £1 billion in cryptocurrency. A search at the individuals’ offices and residential properties unearthed digital assets exchanged on their platform. Also read: Turkish crypto kingpin Faruk...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken recovers $3M as criticism mounts against CertiK]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19608018/Kraken-recovers-3M-as-criticism-mounts-against-CertiK</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19608018/Kraken-recovers-3M-as-criticism-mounts-against-CertiK"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T00:01:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto community has heavily criticized blockchain security firm CertiK for its issues with the crypto exchange Kraken. On June 19, the company revealed itself as the ‘security research’ company Kraken had attributed a theft worth $3 million worth of digital assets to. Also read: Kraken...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Approaching Post-Halving Parabolic Advance Phase, According to Real Vision Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19608003/Bitcoin-Approaching-Post-Halving-Parabolic-Advance-Phase-According-to-Real-Vision-Analyst</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19608003/Bitcoin-Approaching-Post-Halving-Parabolic-Advance-Phase-According-to-Real-Vision-Analyst"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T00:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Real Vision macro expert Julien Bittel believes that Bitcoin (BTC) is on the verge of going parabolic based on historical precedence. Bittel tells his 69,400 followers on the social media platform X that Bitcoin is in a historical “boring” phase ahead of an expected “banana” rally that has come...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Case May End Without SEC Appeal, Ex-Official Suggests]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19608009/Ripple-Case-May-End-Without-SEC-Appeal-Ex-Official-Suggests</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19608009/Ripple-Case-May-End-Without-SEC-Appeal-Ex-Official-Suggests"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T00:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) may opt not to appeal the summary judgment ruling from Judge Analisa Torres partially favoring Ripple Labs, signaling a strategic shift to avoid establishing a potentially unfavorable precedent in higher courts. This possibility has come to light as...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto rumors spark panic in Korea, Binance airdrops for BNB hodlers: Asia Express]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19608014/Crypto-rumors-spark-panic-in-Korea-Binance-airdrops-for-BNB-hodlers-Asia-Express</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19608014/Crypto-rumors-spark-panic-in-Korea-Binance-airdrops-for-BNB-hodlers-Asia-Express"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T23:59:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[South Korean investors panic sell on altcoin delisting rumors, Binance to reward faithful BNB hodlers, Australian Bitcoin ETFs. Asia Express]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lyn Alden Explains Why Money Is Broken #bitcoin #bitcoinnews #shorts]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19608020/Lyn-Alden-Explains-Why-Money-Is-Broken-bitcoin-bitcoinnews-shorts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19608020/Lyn-Alden-Explains-Why-Money-Is-Broken-bitcoin-bitcoinnews-shorts"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T23:48:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why does society run on "chuck e cheese" tokensBrought to you by Bitcoinwell.com a bitcoin-only platform on a mission to enable independence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHY ARE WE BULLISH? JP Sears, Dave Bradley, Scott Dedels]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19607966/WHY-ARE-WE-BULLISH-JP-Sears-Dave-Bradley-Scott-Dedels</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19607966/WHY-ARE-WE-BULLISH-JP-Sears-Dave-Bradley-Scott-Dedels"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T23:26:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FOLLOW TODAY’S PANELISTS:https://x.com/AwakenWithJPhttps://x.com/BitcoinBrainshttps://x.com/LanternBitcoinBOOK private one-on-one sessions with BITCOIN MENTOR! Learn self custody, hardware, multisig, lightning, privacy, running a node, and plenty more - all from a team of top notch educators...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Circle CEO Shares ‘Super Bullish’ Stance and Unprecedented Optimism on Crypto]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74095903fb</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/circle-ceo-shares-super-bullish-stance-and-unprecedented-optimism-on-crypto/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T23:23:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Circle CEO Jeremy Allaire has expressed unprecedented optimism about the future of crypto, highlighting its transformative potential. “I have been building Circle for over 11 years, and at no time have I been more optimistic than right now,” he emphasized. The executive envisions a future where digital tokens, smart contracts, and decentralized governance revolutionize finance […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘More Bullish Than Ever’: Circle CEO Explains Why He’s Optimistic About Crypto]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74095a312c</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/more-bullish-than-ever-circle-ceo-explains-why-hes-optimistic-about-crypto/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T23:09:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Circle’s co-founder and Chief Executive Officer said he is exceptionally optimistic about crypto’s future. In an X post, the CEO noted why he’s “more bullish than ever before” on the industry.
 
 
Why Is Circle CEO Bullish On Crypto?
 
On Wednesday, Jeremy Allaire shared the reasons behind his increasing optimism with his X followers. This perspective was based on the CEO’s 35-year career. During this time, he has watched the waves of innovation and technology adoption transform several industries and improve utility for people.
 

 
 
As he entered the industry, Allaire considered that crypto was “the next logical layer of infrastructure for the internet.” 11 years later, “crypto seems like it’s on the cusp of catapulting society and the economy forward in tremendously powerful new ways.”…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rubmar Garcia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s $100,000 Target Remains Feasible]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19607959/Bitcoins-100000-Target-Remains-Feasible</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19607959/Bitcoins-100000-Target-Remains-Feasible"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T23:09:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s potential to hit $100,000 remains a topic of keen interest among investors. Various market dynamics and economic indicators suggest that this ambitious target is still within reach. Experts share insights on what it will take for Bitcoin to achieve this milestone. The Path to a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘More Bullish Than Ever’: Circle CEO Explains Why He’s Optimistic About Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19607933/More-Bullish-Than-Ever-Circle-CEO-Explains-Why-Hes-Optimistic-About-Crypto</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19607933/More-Bullish-Than-Ever-Circle-CEO-Explains-Why-Hes-Optimistic-About-Crypto"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T23:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Circle’s co-founder and Chief Executive Officer said he is exceptionally optimistic about crypto’s future. In an X post, the CEO noted why he’s “more bullish than ever before” on the industry. Related Reading: Bitcoin Receives Renewed Support From Argentine President Milei Why Is Circle CEO...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scammers Are Using AI Phishing and ‘Juice Jacking’ to Target Travelers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236402</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236402/ai-phishing-smishing-juice-jacking-scamming-travelers"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T22:50:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Email attacks are up 4,151%, says security firm SlashNext, as fake USB chargers threaten to steal smartphone data.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Indian Authority Fines Crypto Exchange Binance $2.25 Million for AML Violations]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7409464f6c</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/indian-authority-fines-crypto-exchange-binance-2-25-million-for-aml-violations/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T22:23:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[India’s Financial Intelligence Unit has fined crypto exchange Binance $2.25 million (₹18.8 crore) for non-compliance with anti-money laundering (AML) regulations. Binance’s return to India is seen as challenging, especially after the government’s tax measures significantly reduced daily trades on some major local crypto exchanges. This fine follows Binance’s global scrutiny and former CEO Changpeng Zhao […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana ETF Proposal Aims to Be First in North America]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236391</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236391/solana-etf-proposal-3iq-canada"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T22:20:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After Bitcoin and Ethereum ETF approvals in the United States, a firm aims to launch Canada's first Solana ETF. Can the U.S. be far behind?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Kawailani Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Winklevoss Twins Say They Each Gave $1 Million to Trump Presidential Campaign]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740947a95f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/06/20/winklevoss-twins-say-they-each-gave-1-million-to-trump-presidential-campaign/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T22:09:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gemini CEO Tyler and his twin brother Cameron Winklevoss, the company's president, have made two of the first major presidential contributions from prominent crypto executives, favoring former President Donald Trump with $1 million each in support, Tyler explained Thursday in a extensive posting on X.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF Invasion: VanEck’s Australian Launch Sparks Crypto Craze]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740940527b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/australia-joins-trend-with-vaneck-bitcoin-etf-debut/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T22:02:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s growing adoption among institutional and retail investors has now extended to Australia, with the debut of the VanEck Bitcoin ETF on the country’s main stock exchange. 
 
Asia-Pacific Poised For Crypto ETF Boom? 
 
Following similar products approved in the United States and Hong Kong earlier this year, the VanEck Bitcoin ETF commenced trading on the exchange operated by the Australia Stock Exchange (ASX) with a seed investment of approximately A$985,000 ($657,000).
 
 
The VanEck Bitcoin ETF launch in Australia is accompanied by the preparations of other players, such as BetaShares Holdings Pty and DigitalX, who plan to list their crypto ETFs on the main Australian board. While VanEck has received approval, the ASX confirms ongoing engagement with other issuers. 
 
Additionally,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Marathon Uses Bitcoin Mining To Heat Town of 11,000 in Finland]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740941d9b4</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/marathon-uses-bitcoin-mining-to-heat-town-of-11000-in-finland"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T21:46:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, Marathon Digital Holdings, Inc. (NASDAQ: MARA), a leader in Bitcoin mining, has launched an innovative pilot project to recycle heat generated from Bitcoin mining to warm a community in Finland. The 2-megawatt data center, energized at the end of May, is located in the Satakunta region, home to 11,000 residents.

JUST IN: Marathon is now warming a town of over 11,000 in Finland using heat from #Bitcoin mining 🤯 🇫🇮
 pic.twitter.com/BUEzj7zqOi
— Bitcoin Magazine (@BitcoinMagazine) June 20, 2024
 
 
 
“This pilot project in Finland is a critical step forward in our strategy to expand globally and innovate sustainably,” said Fred Thiel, Marathon’s chairman and CEO. “We are not just producing digital assets; we are heating homes and integrating sustainable practices into our business …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nik Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Winklevoss Twins Donate $2 Million in Bitcoin to Donald Trump]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740941d9af</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/winklevoss-twins-donate-2-million-in-bitcoin-to-donald-trump"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T21:46:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tyler and Cameron Winklevoss, co-founders of cryptocurrency exchange Gemini, have donated 30.94 Bitcoin, valued at over $2 million, to former President Donald Trump's campaign. Both Cameron and Tyler Winklevoss announced on their X accounts that they contributed 15.47 BTC ($1 million) each to Trump to "put an end to the Biden Administration's war on crypto," Cameron stated, stemming from the twins' discontent with the Biden Administration's stance on cryptocurrency regulation.

JUST IN: Winklevoss twins donated 30.94 #Bitcoin worth over $2 million to Donald Trump to "put an end to the Biden Admin's war on crypto." 🇺🇸 pic.twitter.com/cHD2ENnqZM
— Bitcoin Magazine (@BitcoinMagazine) June 20, 2024
  
  
  
Tyler Winklevoss criticized the Biden Administration for its hostile approach towards…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nik Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet the AI Wingman That Helps Dudes Get Dates]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236373</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236373/ai-wingman-helps-dudes-get-dates-rizz"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T21:39:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A burgeoning industry teaching men how to talk to women is taking off worldwide. What hath tech wrought?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[California Judge Breaks With New York Counterpart, Sends Ripple Securities Lawsuit to Trial]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7409438cd9</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/06/20/california-judge-breaks-with-new-york-counterpart-sends-ripple-securities-lawsuit-to-trial/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T21:29:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A California judge has ruled that a civil securities lawsuit against Ripple will proceed to trial, denying in part the crypto firm’s motion for summary judgment in a suit alleging that Ripple’s CEO violated state securities laws in 2017.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cheyenne Ligon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sorry Dogecoin Fans: Elon Musk’s Twitter Payments Plan Doesn’t Include Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236396</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236396/sorry-dogecoin-fans-elon-musk-twitter-payments-no-crypto"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T21:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin supporter Elon Musk is working toward the launch of a Twitter payments service, but it reportedly doesn’t feature crypto for now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Reiff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Canada's 3iQ Files to List Solana ETP in Toronto]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74094c6cc5</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/06/20/canadas-3iq-files-to-list-solana-etp-in-toronto/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T21:20:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[3iQ was a leader in getting some of the first crypto ETFs past the finish line and listed on the TSX]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Holograph Begins Process to Remove 1 Billion Illegally Minted Tokens, Burns 53 Million HLG]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74094d797d</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/holograph-begins-process-to-remove-1-billion-illegally-minted-tokens-burns-53-million-hlg/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T21:11:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The recently hacked tokenization platform, Holograph, has unveiled a token-burning process to eliminate one billion illegally minted HLG tokens. The Holograph team stated that this process, which has resulted in the burning of more than 53 million tokens so far, is expected to reduce the total number of tokens in circulation to 10 billion. Holograph […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Open Interest Remains High Despite Price Drop, What’s The Significance?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74094e5fbd</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-open-interest-high/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T21:02:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an interesting turn of events, the Bitcoin open interest has remained high even at a time when the price has been dropping. This suggests that despite the price crash, investors are still looking favorably at the pioneer cryptocurrency.
 
Bitcoin Open Interest Stays Close To All-Time High
 
The Bitcoin price has seen a decline over the last week, pushing it from over $70,000 to below $66,000 in the process. Usually, a decline such as this would be greatly reflected in the open interest of the cryptocurrency. However, that has not been the case, as Coinglass data shows.
 
 
Rather than see a significant fall, the open interest has held up quite nicely, staying close to its all-time high. To put this in context, the Bitcoin open interest had hit a new all-time high of $36.87 billion earli…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Winklevoss Twins Donate $2 Million in Bitcoin to Trump to Fight Biden's 'War on Crypto']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236372</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236372/winklevoss-twins-donate-2-million-bitcoin-trump"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T21:01:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Gemini co-founders said they sided with Donald Trump and donated $1 million in Bitcoin apiece to take down President Biden's re-election campaign.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LayerZero Airdrop Is Creating Chaos for Polymarket Bettors]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236367</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236367/layerzero-zro-airdrop-wager-dispute"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T20:28:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LayerZero Labs requiring a donation to receive ZRO tokens left Polymarket with a $680,000 wager disputed by its users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin Responds to Criticism on the Institutionalization of the Crypto Space: We’re Still Here]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7409342fb5</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/vitalik-buterin-responds-to-criticism-on-the-institutionalization-of-the-crypto-space-were-still-here/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T20:10:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin, one of Ethereum’s co-founders, answered the criticism regarding the new institutional focus of blockchain and cryptocurrency projects. Buterin told Joe Weisenthal, co-host of Bloomberg’s financial podcast Odd Lots, that crypto culture “idealistic hippies” were still in the space, and that projects in this regard have moved forward quite a bit, citing Lens and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Hamster Kombat’ Telegram Game Airdrop: Everything You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236360</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236360/hamster-kombat-telegram-game-airdrop-everything-need-know"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T20:07:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram’s hottest game is planning an airdrop via The Open Network (TON)—and Hamster Kombat has teased tips for yielding the best bag.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are Ethereum DeFi Titans Like Uniswap, Maker, And Lido Are Grossly Undervalued?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7409353e93</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-defi-uniswap-maker-lido-undervalued/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T20:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum is the home of decentralized finance (DeFi), looking at the over $100 billion in total value locked (TVL). Even though the figure fluctuates, mainly depending on the performance of ETH, it is clear that DeFi has proven revolutionary, opening up new use cases spanning multiple sectors, including finance and insurance.
 
Are Ethereum DeFi Protocols Undervalued?
 
Taking to X, one analyst is now convinced that a group of established DeFi protocols on Ethereum, including Uniswap and Aave, are highly likely to be grossly undervalued. 
 
 
To put it in context, DeFiLlama data shows that Uniswap, a decentralized exchange, Aave–a decentralized money market, and Lido Finance–a liquidity staking platform, are among the largest by TVL. 
 
The analyst noted that these protocols’ price-to-fees…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dalmas Ngetich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Preps for Primetime With TV Commercial Ahead of ETF Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236351</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236351/ethereum-tv-ad-etf-launch-bitwise"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T19:24:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitwise is again first to release an ETF ad—and they’re minting it as an NFT on Ethereum.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Volatile Bitcoin Movement Causes $118M in Crypto Liquidations]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7409334def</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/volatile-bitcoin-movement-causes-118m-in-crypto-liquidations/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T19:09:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Thursday, bitcoin (BTC) peaked at $66,455 per coin around 7 a.m. EDT but dropped to approximately $64,516 by noon. The volatile movements resulted in $118.82 million in liquidations across the crypto economy, with long positions accounting for $61 million of that total. Bitcoin’s Rapid Rise and Fall Triggers Major Liquidations in Crypto Economy Bitcoin […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VanEck Executive Praises Argentina and El Salvador’s Commitment To Bitcoin And Crypto Freedom]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74093c40de</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/gurbacs-praises-argentina-crypto-freedom/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T19:02:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gabor Gurbacs, an executive at VanEck and the founder of PointsVille in a recent acknowledgment of the expanding significance of cryptocurrencies in the financial landscape has commended Argentina and El Salvador for their innovative efforts in promoting Bitcoin and establishing a free crypto economy.
 
Gurbacs emphasized how these countries’ leaders, Javier Milei and Nayib Bukele, have set El Salvador and Argentina at the forefront of the adoption of digital currencies, by utilizing creative legislation and economic integration.
 
Both Nations Crypto Freedom Efforts Is Commendable
 
The VanEck Executive Gabor Gurbacs’ appreciative insights were triggered by Argentina’s president Javier Milei’s recent support for Bitcoin and the free competition of cryptocurrencies within the country’s eco…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Godspower Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is 'Yescoin'? The Telegram Tap-to-Earn Game and Airdrop Details]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236328</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-yescoin-telegram-game-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T18:32:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram-based game Yescoin puts a sspin on the clicker genre, attracting 18 million players as a token airdrop looms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leonardo AI Launches a New Model—Can It Dethrone Ideogram as Best Image Generator?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236173</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236173/leonardo-ideogram-ai-image-generator-comparison"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T18:23:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leonardo AI's latest release, Leonardo Phoenix, brings a host of new features and improvements.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Germany Begins Selling Its Bitcoin Billions, Triggering Volatility Fears]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236329</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236329/germany-begins-selling-bitcoin-billions-volatility-fears"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T17:57:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The German government is starting to sell off its stockpile of over $3 billion in seized Bitcoin, says Arkham. Will it tank the market?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tornado Cash Use Could Complicate CertiK's Defense Against Kraken ‘Extortion’ Claims]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236323</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236323/tornado-cash-certik-defense-kraken-extortion-claims"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T17:02:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain sleuths have discovered that CertiK researchers engaged with U.S.-banned crypto mixer Tornado Cash after the "white-hat" Kraken hack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin to $1 Million? These Analysts Think It Gets There—Eventually]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236319</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236319/bitcoin-1-million-analysts-think-it-gets-there"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T16:04:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bernstein has doubled down on predictions that Bitcoin is about to surge to unprecedented highs—and may hit $200,000 in less than a year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 142 - ETH LEADS THE RALLY]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/teZMC9Tb/fomo-hour-142-eth-leads-the-rally</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/teZMC9Tb/fomo-hour-142-eth-leads-the-rally"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T15:46:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH continues to lead gains, SOL underperforms. BTC may rebound as Fed liquidity rips higher. ETH sees large amount of bullish call activity. LayerZero launches today, 25% unlock. Funding level the lowest in 3 months. German government sends 1000 BTC to exchanges. Stablecoins to become 10% of money: Circle CEO. Stabelcoin transfers up 16x in 4 years. BTC exchanges balances hit 3 year low. SOL again flips ETH for DEX volumes. Kraken reports $3m bug exploit found by CertiK. Debate about whether CertiK were whitehats. Jump Crypto gives $10m to crypto PAC. Binance launches HODLer airdrops. TipLink allows SOL transfers by email. ETHFI proposes 50% revenue for buybacks. JTO teases LSD backed stablecoin. JUP team proposes to reduce 30% of supply.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop Sinks as Meme Stock Trader Roaring Kitty Goes Quiet]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236313</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236313/gamestop-sinks-roaring-kitty-goes-quiet"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T15:44:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is this the end of the latest meme stock revival? GameStop shares keep dipping without Roaring Kitty to pump up traders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Not Enough People’: This Robotics Company Is Tackling a Labor Shortage]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236160</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236160/this-robotics-company-aims-to-solve-a-labor-shortage-in-manufacturing"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T15:01:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Millions of manufacturing jobs are going unfilled, says the CEO of GrayMatter, which today announced raising $45 million to expand its manufacturing efforts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Robotics Company Aims to Solve a Labor Shortage in Manufacturing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ub9yvCXi/this-robotics-company-aims-to-solve-a-labor-shortage-in-manufacturing</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ub9yvCXi/this-robotics-company-aims-to-solve-a-labor-shortage-in-manufacturing"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GrayMatter Robotics Co-founder and CEO Ariyan Kabir explains the origin of the company, the need for artificial intelligence and robotics to offset a growing labor shortage, and takes Decrypt on a tour of its AI-powered facility.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy Just Bought Another $786 Million in Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236302</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236302/microstrategy-bought-786-million-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T14:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Saylor’s software firm has purchased another huge sum of Bitcoin, widening its lead as the top corporate holder.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NBCUniversal Will Continue Building on Aptos via Long-Term Agreement]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236289</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236289/nbcuniversal-aptos-long-term-agreement"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T14:01:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following “Exorcist” and “Renfield” experiences on Aptos, NBCUniversal will keep collaborating with Aptos Labs for years to come.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘PixelTap’ Daily Combo Guide: How to Earn Millions of Free Coins in the Pixelverse Telegram Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235998</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/pixeltap-daily-combo-guide-earn-free-coins-pixelverse-telegram-game"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T13:14:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram game PixelTap lets you battle robots to earn coins ahead of a token airdrop—and you can earn way more with this easy bonus.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Stays Above $3,500 as Open Interest Drops]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236287</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236287/ethereum-stays-above-3500-as-open-interest-drops"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T12:49:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum kept its ground above $3,500 as open interest drops—a sign that traders don't expect wild swings in either direction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarang Khaitan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Up 1.4% as Exchange Reserves Hit 3-Year Low]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236279</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236279/bitcoin-exchange-reserves-3-year-low"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T12:27:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The current market structure favors arbitrage traders, according to Glassnode.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump and Son Barron Are Not Involved in DJT Solana Meme Coin, Says Roger Stone]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236270</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236270/donald-trump-barron-djt-solana-meme-coin"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T12:04:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former political consultant to Donald Trump, Roger Stone, has shot down claims that the Trump family created the DJT Solana token.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Exec Who Fled Detainment in Nigeria Has Human Rights Suit Dismissed]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236266</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236266/binance-exec-who-fled-detainment-in-nigeria-has-human-rights-suit-dismissed"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T10:44:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[But Tigran Gambaryan, who's still in custody in a Nigerian prison and was recently treated for malaria, can proceed with his lawsuit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chidirim Ndeche</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Metal Gear Solid' Game Maker Konami Launching Avalanche NFT Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236221</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236221/metal-gear-solid-game-maker-konami-avalanche-nft"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T10:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gaming giant Konami has revealed an NFT platform called Resella on Avalanche, offering tech that can be used for crypto games and other apps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Tokens Surge 15% as Nvidia Tailwinds Boost Fetch.ai and Render]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236255</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236255/ai-tokens-surge-15-as-nvidia-tailwinds-boost-fetch-ai-and-render"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T09:17:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Fetch.ai token has surged 40% in the past month, while Render Network is up nearly 30%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Minsberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Treasury Firm DeFi Technologies Claps Back at Report That Tanked Its Stock]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236203</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236203/defi-technologies-coinsnacks-bitcoin-treasury-stock"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T23:46:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company’s hot stock saw a 35% correction after a crypto newsletter claimed its gains were unjustified.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 141 - SEC DROPS ETH PROBE]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zFpVKbtL/fomo-hour-141-sec-drops-eth-probe</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zFpVKbtL/fomo-hour-141-sec-drops-eth-probe"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T22:41:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC: 65.4k (0%), ETH: 3545 (+3%), SOL: 139 (+2%). Top Gainers: LDO, BRETT, PEPE, AR. ETH & beta lead gains after SEC headline. SEC drops probe into ETH as a security. BTC ETFs see another $152m outflow. Pantera show $100m buying interest in ETH ETF. Pantera aims to raise new $1bn fund. Lack of staking won’t harm ETH ETF: 21 Shares. LayerZero airdrop coming June 20th. SEC concerns on USDC may delay Circle IPO. Hayes increasing PENDLE & DOGE positions. Fox News to build L2 with Polygon. EIGEN trades at $10bn pre-market. Drift & Ondo partner on RWAs. Commercial real estate coming on-chain: KPMG.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Certik Extorting Kraken for Millions? Here's What's Going On]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236152</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236152/certik-kraken-extortion-white-hat-hack"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T21:39:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The security firm claimed it had been given too little time to return Kraken’s funds as it tested an exploit’s scope.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are Solana and Polygon Safe Now That SEC’s Ethereum Investigation Is Over?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236154</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236154/solana-polygon-safe-sec-ethereum-investigation-over"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T21:17:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The short answer is: probably not—but it’s complicated.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former OpenAI Chief Scientist Launches ‘Safe’ Rival AI Lab]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236147</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236147/ilya-sutskever-new-ai-ssi-openai-rival"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T20:48:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ilya Sutskever is launching a company to Scale AI in peace, with no distractions or “commercial pressures.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Gets Into Airdrops With New ‘HODLer’ Rewards]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236144</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236144/binance-airdrop-bnb-holder-rewards-crypto-projects"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T20:06:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Customers with BNB will get tokens from select projects preparing to launch on the exchange.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Greg Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Whales Are Taking Profits, Cashing In $1.2 Billion in 2 Weeks: Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236141</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236141/bitcoin-whales-are-taking-profits-cashing-in-1-2-billion-in-2-weeks-analyst"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T18:56:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whales just cashed out BTC harder than they ever have, nearly doubling the previous record.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum ETF Hopeful Hashdex Waives Fees for Europe Fund]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236137</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236137/bitcoin-ethereum-etf-hashdex-waives-fees-for-europe"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T18:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With a Bitcoin spot ETF launched and two more funds pending in the U.S., the firm moves to bring in more European investors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chidirim Ndeche</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Boredom Will Continue Until ETF Withdrawals Improve]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236129</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236129/bitcoin-boredom-etf-withdrawals-2"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T16:25:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bitcoin price is seemingly range bound between $65,500 and $64,000 until sentiment improves, according to an analyst.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarang Khaitan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Happened to Putting Dogwifhat on the Las Vegas Sphere?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236105</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236105/dogwifhat-solana-las-vegas-sphere-what-happened"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T16:04:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Three months after raising $700,000, Dogwifhat fundraiser organizers claim they are still working on the ambitious marketing stunt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 140 - MARKETS DOWN BAD]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/7BwSoeRf/fomo-hour-140-markets-down-bad</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/7BwSoeRf/fomo-hour-140-markets-down-bad"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T17:35:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC touches 1-month lows, dominance hits 56%. $500m of liquidations in fall, $146m ETF outflows. VanEck to launch first ETF in Australia. Coinbase to launch pre-market trading. 56% of Fortune 500 building in web3. Uphold to delist USDT in EU due to MiCA. TON flips DOGE in sell-off. Base DEX users now 2nd place after SOL. Ethena launches staking & restaking with Symbiotic. Lens aiming to raise $50m at $500m valuation. Two ‘crazy’ MATIC announcements coming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 139 - WHATS THE NEXT META?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zEW6uY5Z/fomo-hour-139-whats-the-next-meta</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zEW6uY5Z/fomo-hour-139-whats-the-next-meta"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T17:32:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC again breaks $66k, dominance rises. Fear & Greed index hits 3 month low. Whales continue to be in accumulation mode. Miners 33 days into capitulation, average 41 days. Financial advisors not buying BTC yet: BlackRock. Crypto funds saw $600m outflows last week. ZKsync airdrop live, prices at $5bn FDV. ZKsync defend sybil measures. Low float, high FDV coins get hammered again. Tether launches product backed by Gold. Korean exchanges reviewing 600 coins for delisting. ETH ETF ‘sell the rumour, buy the news event’. BTC ETF basis buyers roughly 15% of demand. CVX bounces 100% after loan liquidation. TON sees fastest user growth in crypto history. APT may flip SOL in 1-3 years: Hayes. Crypto lifetime funding eclipses $100bn. SEC claims $876m Ripple fine still fair. Gensler could cost Biden election: Cuban.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 138 - MORE CELEB COINS!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/KzCZzgqx/fomo-hour-138-more-celeb-coins</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/KzCZzgqx/fomo-hour-138-more-celeb-coins"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T18:05:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Altcoins bleed out heavy, BTC dominance rises towards 60%. Miners continue to be large BTC sellers, whales accumulate. ETF inflows slow, hedge fund allocations point to basis trades. ETH ETFs approvals see little movement, coming 'in the summer’. Stocks continue to hit ATHs as CPI & PPI both come in soft. TON performs best in L1s, active wallets eclipse ETH. Andrew Tate joins celebrity memecoin meta, DADDY hits $350m. SOL DEX volumes eclipse ETH in memecoin frenzy. Curve founder defaults on CRV debt as DeFi coins tumble. Terraform Labs & Do Kwon to pay $4.5bn fine to SEC. BAMK hits $350m in Runes as it issues BTC stablecoin. Gaming tokens face huge sell-off, PRIME changes tokenomics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 137 - CRYPTO DIPS FURTHER]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mJ28rAx5/fomo-hour-137-crypto-dips-further</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mJ28rAx5/fomo-hour-137-crypto-dips-further"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T15:46:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto falls after slightly hawkish Fed speech. BTC whales buy $1.4bn in 24hrs. Miners continue to be large sellers of BTC. BTC ETFs see $100m inflows. MicroStrategy to raise $500m to buy BTC. Egorov CRV debt positions begin to liquidate  . Circle to support SOL for wallets. 4% of Turkey GDP used to buy stablecoins. QuantMatter say $11m stolen from OKX account. Biden to use Coinbase for crypto donations. Terraform Labs & Do Kwon set to pay $4.5bn fine. Franklin Templeton write report on SOL DePin. TON flips ETH for active addresses. Moonpay & Paypal integration goes live in EU & UK.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 136 - FIRST MOTHER, NOW DADDY?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LEzSMpGz/fomo-hour-136-first-mother-now-daddy</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LEzSMpGz/fomo-hour-136-first-mother-now-daddy"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T18:01:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETFs see another $200m outflows. Another $190m of liquidations in volatility. $1.2bn BTC leaves exchanges in a day. ETF flows largely driven by basis trades: Pal. ‘Perfect setup’ for longs into macro news today. ETH ETF approvals ‘expected this month’. Crypto in best place it has ever been: Circle CEO. China’s ICBC calls ETH ‘digital oil’. Trump wants ‘made in the USA’ BTC. Crypto hacks $19bn since 2011. Symbiotic restaking protocol sees $150m inflows. Polygon launches $720m grants program. ZKsync accused of insider allocations. CRV drop leaves $90m loans at risk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Has AI Already Changed Gaming Forever?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mZlR3He5/has-ai-already-changed-gaming-forever</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mZlR3He5/has-ai-already-changed-gaming-forever"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T19:51:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt’s Sander Lutz and Rug Radio creator Puke sat down with Simon Davis of Mighty Bear Games and VC Kyle Klemmer to discuss how AI has already remade the gaming industry—for better and for worse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 135 - BTC FALLS ON OUTFLOWS]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/bA3jJ5aA/fomo-hour-135-btc-falls-on-outflows</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/bA3jJ5aA/fomo-hour-135-btc-falls-on-outflows"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T19:03:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto falls as ETFs see first outflow in 19 days. Short positions grow on downwards move in BTC. BTC short-term realised price now at $64k. ETH ETF issuers still waiting for SEC response. UK ETNs continue to see tiny volume. SOL validators get kicked out for sandwich attacks. ZKsync airdrop happening next week. ZKsync to give 17.8% to the community. OP launches Fraud Proofs. Bitfarms plans poison pill to counter takeover bid. OKX sees outflows after security incidents. Bybit considers shutting China offices. COIN may get added to S&P500.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 134 - EU SNAP ELECTIONS LAND]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pZksMKIV/fomo-hour-134-eu-snap-elections-land</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pZksMKIV/fomo-hour-134-eu-snap-elections-land"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T15:46:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Volatility remains low, TL continues to be divisive. 2nd highest weekly close ever for BTC. Crypto funds saw $2bn inflows last week. Rumour that BlackRock will apply for SOL ETF. Base TVL hits $8bn, top of L2s for activity. zk Sync hint at TGE this week. PENDLE enters top 5 for DeFi TVL. Berachain v2 testnet goes live.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 133 - RUGGED BY HOGEN?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MSvAS9qX/fomo-hour-133-rugged-by-hogen</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MSvAS9qX/fomo-hour-133-rugged-by-hogen"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T17:26:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC still just below ATH after $218m ETF inflows. BTC OI hits record $37bn as long-short ratio rises. Amount of ETH on exchanges lowest since 2015. Franklin Templeton explores broader crypto fund. Mining stocks rise on takeover frenzy. Kraken considers $100m funding round. Binance reinstates crypto buys with Mastercard. Phantom & Jito partner for native staking.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 132 - CRYPTO STRENGTH IS GROWING]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/bQBFWC0w/fomo-hour-132-crypto-strength-is-growing</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/bQBFWC0w/fomo-hour-132-crypto-strength-is-growing"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T19:49:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto consolidates near ATH, $488m ETF inflow. BTC correlation to tech stocks highest since 2023. BTC options anticipate $74-80k move. ETH to $22k by 2030: VanEck. Robinhood to acquire Bitstamp.
Coinbase launches Smart Wallet. ByBit opens up explicitly to China users. Global liquidity breaks out to $94T. US President given new powers to block crypto. Cramer & Gensler continue to bash crypto. Gensler hints at prolonged ETH ETF process. Stand with Crypto PAC hits 1m advocates. Turkey denies plans to tax crypto. EigenLayer surpasses $20bn TVL. IONET to launch on Binance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webinar: Unleashing The Power Of Permissionless Markets With Vega Protocol]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OvA845JA/webinar-unleashing-the-power-of-permissionless-markets-with-vega-protocol</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OvA845JA/webinar-unleashing-the-power-of-permissionless-markets-with-vega-protocol"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T08:23:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join our expert panel for an insightful discussion on Vega Protocol's revolutionary approach to decentralized derivatives trading. Discover how Vega's permissionless markets enable anyone to create and trade futures and perpetuals on a fully decentralized network. Explore the potential of Vega's innovative features, such as the ability to add new assets, transfer network assets, and adjust network parameters—as well as the protocol's active markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 131 - BIG BITCOIN INFLOWS!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/a37DNT7n/fomo-hour-131-big-bitcoin-inflows</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/a37DNT7n/fomo-hour-131-big-bitcoin-inflows"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T17:06:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETFs see large $900M inflows, biggest in weeks. $800M of shorts would be liquidated above $72K. BTC to $100K if it breaks $73K in a week: Novogratz. BNB hits new ATH, breaks $100B market cap. FTX reaches $200M tax settlement with IRS. Most investors should hold BTC: Fidelity. Tether CEO criticises EU on stablecoin regulation. Japanese exchange raises $320M to recover funds. ETH ETFs could see $4B inflows in 5 months: K33. Paradigm propose MEV taxes. StarkWare plans ZK scaling for BTC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 130 - $DOG TARGETS 1B MC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ke2mFBwr/fomo-hour-130-dog-targets-1b-mc</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ke2mFBwr/fomo-hour-130-dog-targets-1b-mc"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T22:05:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Runes & Ordinals soar as DOG passes $900M. rekt Brands opens up its shares claim for NFT holders. BTC led NFT trading volume with $6.3M on the day. NodeMonkes +10% 0.289, Puppets +35% at 0.198. Runes up by DOG which soared 23% to $922M mc. BUS won the Blast Jackpot last night for a 3% win. Memecoin majors are mostly red this AM. Trader buys 10k SOL of GME. Base brings back Onchain Summer. Dapper settles massive lawsuit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 129 - ROARING RETURNS, AGAIN!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ABOejLBT/fomo-hour-129-roaring-returns-again</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ABOejLBT/fomo-hour-129-roaring-returns-again"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T21:42:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto bounces, BTC breaks 2-week downtrend. BTC low volatility points to trend continuation. BTC will top at $150k in September 2025: Brandt. $3bn ETH withdrawn from exchanges since ETF. ETH ETF inflows imply ‘base case’ price $5.3k. ETH ETF inflows won’t be like BTC: Fireblocks. BTC logo projected on ECB building. Ethena USDe hits $3bn market cap in 4 months. Maple launches DeFi institutional lending platform. OKX launches in the Netherlands. Matter Labs drops ZK ticker. Linea shuts down chain after hack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 128 - PUMP DOT FUN KEEPS PUMPING!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cziNL3TF/fomo-hour-128-pump-dot-fun-keeps-pumping</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cziNL3TF/fomo-hour-128-pump-dot-fun-keeps-pumping"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T21:41:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto nears break-out then falls on Trump verdict. 13 straight days of BTC ETF inflows, BTC whale accumulation ‘echoes 2020’. Crypto apps next year will onboard millions: Burniske. Elon denies talking crypto policy with Trump. RFK has bought 21 BTC during campaign. TON market cap falls after updating supply data. a16z donates $25m to crypto PAC. Vitalik sends 30ETH to Tornado devs. DBS Bank in Singapore custodies $650m ETH. Backlash grows over zkSync using ZK ticker. Implementing FIT21 a slow process: CFTC. Pierce recommends UK & US cross-border sandbox. Vitalik writes blog on block size wars. Hong Kong government expresses support for web3. Do Kwon & Terraform reach settlement with SEC. Large unlocks for a number of alts next month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 127 - CELEB COINS CRASH!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mGbE2GHV/fomo-hour-127-celeb-coins-crash</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mGbE2GHV/fomo-hour-127-celeb-coins-crash"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T20:28:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NYSE to launch BTC options. CME has ‘no plans’ to offer SOL futures. Stablecoin market cap rises to 2 year high. Inflation below 3.3% ‘means BTC ATH’. Crypto market cap heading to $200T: Yat Siu. Gemini recovers $2.2bn for Earn users. PayPal stablecoin will offer ‘confidential transfers’. Mastercard launches Crypto Credential pilot on BTC. Layer Zero launches on SOL. L2s are cultural extensions of ETH: Vitalik. FTX’s Salame says he will share story. SEI announces 27m SEI airdrop. ASI merger complete, to launch June 13th.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 126 - MEMECOIN MADNESS!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/eA3xqKLr/fomo-hour-126-memecoin-madness</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/eA3xqKLr/fomo-hour-126-memecoin-madness"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T21:30:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock ETF flips Grayscale in size. BTC ETFs see 11 straight days of inflows. ZKasino gives 72hours for ETH withdrawals. ENS to migrate to L2. ADA drops out of top 10 coins. Salame sentenced to 7.5 years in jail. Riot Platforms attempts takeover of Bitfarms. Ripple donates $25m to Fairshake PAC. Pump(.)fun launches live streaming. Iggy Azelea MOTHER coin leads celeb tokens. Beeple Everyday features many coins. Runes bounce, DOG hits $560m. PEPE active wallets double during rally. Cristiano Ronaldo launches 4th NFT. Friend Tech announces club wars.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>