<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-10-18T16:22:00.391Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-10-18T16:22:00.391Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Spot ETF On The Horizon: Galaxy Digital CEO Forecasts Imminent Approval In 2023]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b402624d</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-etf-galaxy-ceo-forecasts-approval-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T16:10:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amid recent fake news that rattled the crypto community, the anticipation and excitement surrounding the potential approval of Bitcoin (BTC) spot exchange-traded funds (ETFs) by the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) have not waned. 
 
Adding to the growing optimism, Galaxy Digital CEO Mike Novogratz has provided further hope for the imminent approval of these funds.
 
Novogratz Sees Promising Signs For Bitcoin Spot ETFs
 
During a recent interview with CNBC, Novogratz, the CEO of the crypto asset management company, expressed his belief that the Bitcoin spot ETF will receive regulatory approval from the SEC in 2023. 
 
He cited the constructive discussions between Bitcoin ETF issuers and the SEC as an indicator of the likelihood of a spot Bitcoin ETF approval shortly. Novogratz e…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin At Risk Of 50% Drop Before Next Halving If Historical Trend Repeats, Warns Influential Crypto Guru]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18978070/Bitcoin-At-Risk-Of-50-Drop-Before-Next-Halving-If-Historical-Trend-Repeats-Warns-Influential-Crypto-Guru</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18978070/Bitcoin-At-Risk-Of-50-Drop-Before-Next-Halving-If-Historical-Trend-Repeats-Warns-Influential-Crypto-Guru"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T16:08:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin hit a two-month high earlier today following amendments to a spot ETF application by Fidelity, but some forecasts still see the alpha cryptocurrency dropping considerably in the coming months before the next halving.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lightning Labs Rolls Out Taproot Assets Mainnet Alpha]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18978058/Lightning-Labs-Rolls-Out-Taproot-Assets-Mainnet-Alpha</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18978058/Lightning-Labs-Rolls-Out-Taproot-Assets-Mainnet-Alpha"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T16:06:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lightning Labs unveils the mainnet alpha of Taproot Assets, a significant milestone to bring dollar stablecoins and other assets natively to Bitcoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Takes Action Against Hamas Funding Amid Israel War]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18978065/Coinbase-Takes-Action-Against-Hamas-Funding-Amid-Israel-War</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18978065/Coinbase-Takes-Action-Against-Hamas-Funding-Amid-Israel-War"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T16:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A look at how Coinbase navigates the complex issue of Hamas funding in cryptocurrency during the ongoing Israel war.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF Could Boost Crypto Market by $1 Trillion, Analysts Say]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202170</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202170/bitcoin-etf-crypto-market-1-trillion"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T16:04:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data firm CryptoQuant says the approval of Bitcoin ETFs is likely to bring a wave of fresh capital, nearly doubling Bitcoin's market cap.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF may be a ‘limited’ benefit for Coinbase stock: Barclays]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18978061/Bitcoin-ETF-may-be-a-limited-benefit-for-Coinbase-stock-Barclays</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18978061/Bitcoin-ETF-may-be-a-limited-benefit-for-Coinbase-stock-Barclays"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T16:01:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mike Novogratz expects SEC to approve a Spot Bitcoin ETF this year. Barclays analyst does not expect that to be a huge benefit for Coinbase. Coinbase stock is currently down over 30% versus its year-to-date high. Mike Novogratz – the Chief Executive of Galaxy Investment Partners expects the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Depicts Fascinating Images of What Aliens May Look Like]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18978067/AI-Depicts-Fascinating-Images-of-What-Aliens-May-Look-Like</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18978067/AI-Depicts-Fascinating-Images-of-What-Aliens-May-Look-Like"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T16:01:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The mystery of aliens is one that has been carried on for decades. Nobody could say for sure whether aliens actually exist because they have never been discovered, at least, according to a September 2021 report by NASA. However, that does not completely mean that extraterrestrial life doesn’t...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Spot ETF On The Horizon: Galaxy Digital CEO Forecasts Imminent Approval In 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18978060/Bitcoin-Spot-ETF-On-The-Horizon-Galaxy-Digital-CEO-Forecasts-Imminent-Approval-In-2023</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18978060/Bitcoin-Spot-ETF-On-The-Horizon-Galaxy-Digital-CEO-Forecasts-Imminent-Approval-In-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T16:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amid recent fake news that rattled the crypto community, the anticipation and excitement surrounding the potential approval of Bitcoin (BTC) spot exchange-traded funds (ETFs) by the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) have not waned. Adding to the growing optimism, Galaxy Digital CEO...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Federal Reserve Governor voices concerns on CBDCs. Details inside…]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18978032/Federal-Reserve-Governor-voices-concerns-on-CBDCs-Details-inside</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18978032/Federal-Reserve-Governor-voices-concerns-on-CBDCs-Details-inside"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T16:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Federal Reserve Board Governor Michelle Bowman voices skepticism about CBDCs, emphasizing the importance of proper regulation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Bill Clinton to NYC Mayor Adams: SBF’s Political Entanglements That Endanger His Defense]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18978044/From-Bill-Clinton-to-NYC-Mayor-Adams-SBFs-Political-Entanglements-That-Endanger-His-Defense</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18978044/From-Bill-Clinton-to-NYC-Mayor-Adams-SBFs-Political-Entanglements-That-Endanger-His-Defense"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T15:59:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried political shenanigans continue to surface as the trial against the disgraced founder of FTX enters its third week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[100x Ethereum Scaling Scroll L2 Goes Live on Mainnet]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18978049/100x-Ethereum-Scaling-Scroll-L2-Goes-Live-on-Mainnet</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18978049/100x-Ethereum-Scaling-Scroll-L2-Goes-Live-on-Mainnet"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T15:54:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scroll, the new ethereum L2 breaks all previous records by showing 100x compression on the day of mainnet launch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Bull Scaramucci Sees 3X Gains For Bitcoin, Ethereum, And Algorand — Here's Why]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18978059/Crypto-Bull-Scaramucci-Sees-3X-Gains-For-Bitcoin-Ethereum-And-Algorand-Heres-Why</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18978059/Crypto-Bull-Scaramucci-Sees-3X-Gains-For-Bitcoin-Ethereum-And-Algorand-Heres-Why"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T15:53:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SkyBridge Capital founder, Anthony Scaramucci has shed a bullish light on the future price trajectories of Bitcoin (CRYPTO: BTC), Ethereum (CRYPTO: ETH), and Algorand (CRYPTO: read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Education: Resources and Tools for Learning about Blockchain and Digital Assets]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b40d30f0</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/crypto-education-resources-and-tools-for-learning-about-blockchain-and-digital-assets/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T15:52:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In any  
industry, the value of education cannot be emphasized. Individuals and  
institutions are seeking reputable sources to expand their understanding of  
cryptocurrencies and blockchain as interest in these disruptive technologies  
grows. Fortunately, there are numerous resources and tools accessible to help  
with crypto education, appealing to both novices and seasoned enthusiasts. 
Websites and  
blogs for education
Accessing  
credible websites and blogs dedicated to blockchain and cryptocurrency is one  
of the first stages in crypto education as they provide an abundance of  
articles, news updates, and in-depth studies on many elements of the  
cryptocurrency world. They are good places to start if you want to stay up to  
date on the latest industry advancements and trends a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Ferreira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Death of Compromise, and a Way Forward for Crypto]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b40e343c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/10/18/the-death-of-compromise-and-a-way-forward-for-crypto/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T15:46:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kim Greenberg of CoinDesk Indices finds a lesson for crypto in LEGO.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kim Greenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Investment as a Service: Table Stakes for the Next Crypto Cycle]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b40e33fe</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/10/18/investment-as-a-service-table-stakes-for-the-next-crypto-cycle/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T15:46:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Colton Dillion and Sonya Mann of Hedgehog Technologies explain why exchanges and other major players in crypto need to expand their horizons.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Colton Dillion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Sen. Warren Leads Lawmakers to Push Administration on Crypto-Backed Terrorism]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b40e33a4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/10/18/us-sen-warren-leads-lawmakers-to-push-administration-on-crypto-backed-terrorism/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T15:46:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Sen. Elizabeth Warren (D-Mass.) led more than a hundred lawmakers in demanding top officials share their plans for heading off crypto-financed terrorism.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried Witness Contrasts His Public Comments With FTX's Dangerous Secrets]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b40e336a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/10/18/sbf-trial-a-witness-contrasts-sam-bankman-frieds-house-testimony-with-ftxs-dangerous-secrets/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T15:46:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former FTX lobbyist Eliora Katz appeared to mostly be on the stand to allow prosecutors to bring attention to Bankman-Fried's tweets and House testimony, and how they differed from the secret reality that led to the crypto exchange's demise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Doctor hires hitman to kill girlfriend, sends bitcoin to wrong address]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18978026/Doctor-hires-hitman-to-kill-girlfriend-sends-bitcoin-to-wrong-address</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18978026/Doctor-hires-hitman-to-kill-girlfriend-sends-bitcoin-to-wrong-address"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T15:45:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[James Wan pleaded guilty to the plot that saw him give a dark web hitman $19,200 in bitcoin to kill his girlfriend.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Is Physical: Bits And Bytes Have To Live Somewhere]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b40e5976</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/technical/bitcoin-is-physical-bits-and-bytes-have-to-live-somewhere"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T15:45:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sound money is money that is not prone to sudden debasement. The conversation surrounding sound money has reached a critical point, given the present uncertainties in the global financial landscape. 
The spiraling debt of sovereign nations have heightened concerns about currency debasement. In contrast to fiat, which can be created out of thin air, sound money is linked to tangibility: it is something you can touch, weigh, and stow away. There's a growing chorus of people convinced that gold is the sole antidote to the hyperinflationary threat to fiat money. 
The question of whether Bitcoin is sound money has long provoked debates among economists, investors, and financial pundits. Bitcoin, being an intangible digital asset, is often dismissed by sound money advocates because it doesn't of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave Birnbaum</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Death of Compromise, and a Way Forward for Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18978022/The-Death-of-Compromise-and-a-Way-Forward-for-Crypto</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18978022/The-Death-of-Compromise-and-a-Way-Forward-for-Crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Investment as a Service: Table Stakes for the Next Crypto Cycle]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18978023/Investment-as-a-Service-Table-Stakes-for-the-Next-Crypto-Cycle</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18978023/Investment-as-a-Service-Table-Stakes-for-the-Next-Crypto-Cycle"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biggest Movers: SHIB, DOGE Fall, as Crypto Markets Consolidate]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b40ee13e</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/biggest-movers-shib-doge-fall-as-crypto-markets-consolidate/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T15:42:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meme coins were one of the biggest casualties of Wednesday’s price consolidation, falling by as much as 2% in today’s session. The decline comes as a result of profit taking, following strong gains to start the week. Shiba inu and dogecoin remain in the red, as of writing.
 
Shiba Inu (SHIB)
 
Shiba inu (SHIB) was a notable mover on Wednesday, as the meme coin fell for a second consecutive day.
 
Following a high of $0.000006945 during yesterday’s session, SHIB/USD slipped to an intraday low at $0.000006842 earlier today.
 
The move saw SHIB drop towards a key support level of $0.00000670, which was last hit on October 12.
 
 
This decline comes as the relative strength index (RSI) collided with a floor of its own, at the 39.00 zone.
 
At the time of writing, price strength is tracking marginally below this point at 38.49, and should it continue to fall, could be heading to a lower support level of 35.00.
 
Wednesday’s sell-off comes after shiba inu rose to one week high of $0.00000729 on Monday.
 
 
Dogecoin (DOGE)
 
Dogecoin (DOGE) also dropped lower on hump-day, as it moved closer to a key support level of its own.
 
DOGE/USD hit a bottom of $0.0588 during today’s session, less than 24 hours after peaking at the $0.05961 point.
 
As referenced earlier, the move, which is also the second consecutive drop in price for DOGE, pushed it towards a floor at $0.0570.
 
 
Unlike with shiba inu’s RSI, which was still hovering close to support, price strength on dogecoin fell under its point of stability of 40.00.
 
Currently, the index is at a reading of 38.85, which coincides with the 10-day (red) moving average extending a downtrend.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
Will meme coins continue to decline this week? Let us know your thoughts in the comments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Delists 80 Trading Pairs From Platform, Max Keiser Shares When BTC Will Hit $220,000, SHIB Whale Makes Massive $31.6 Million Transfer: Crypto News Digest by U.Today]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18978030/Coinbase-Delists-80-Trading-Pairs-From-Platform-Max-Keiser-Shares-When-BTC-Will-Hit-220000-SHIB-Whale-Makes-Massive-316-Million-Transfer-Crypto-News-Digest-by-UToday</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18978030/Coinbase-Delists-80-Trading-Pairs-From-Platform-Max-Keiser-Shares-When-BTC-Will-Hit-220000-SHIB-Whale-Makes-Massive-316-Million-Transfer-Crypto-News-Digest-by-UToday"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T15:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yuga Labs sails into Metaverse: Restructuring complete]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18977998/Yuga-Labs-sails-into-Metaverse-Restructuring-complete</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18977998/Yuga-Labs-sails-into-Metaverse-Restructuring-complete"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T15:38:59.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Shakes Up Its Portfolio: Multiple Trading Pair Delistings, New Additions Unveiled]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18978036/Binance-Shakes-Up-Its-Portfolio-Multiple-Trading-Pair-Delistings-New-Additions-Unveiled</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18978036/Binance-Shakes-Up-Its-Portfolio-Multiple-Trading-Pair-Delistings-New-Additions-Unveiled"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T15:38:18.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brokers are Encouraged to Embrace AI Gradually for Sustainable Growth]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18977999/Brokers-are-Encouraged-to-Embrace-AI-Gradually-for-Sustainable-Growth</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18977999/Brokers-are-Encouraged-to-Embrace-AI-Gradually-for-Sustainable-Growth"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T15:37:35.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Korean FSS Probes SUI Token Over Distribution Concerns]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18977996/South-Korean-FSS-Probes-SUI-Token-Over-Distribution-Concerns</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18977996/South-Korean-FSS-Probes-SUI-Token-Over-Distribution-Concerns"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T15:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Revealed: Bankman-Fried’s high-profile meetings before FTX collapse]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18978000/Revealed-Bankman-Frieds-high-profile-meetings-before-FTX-collapse</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18978000/Revealed-Bankman-Frieds-high-profile-meetings-before-FTX-collapse"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T15:32:27.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Bitcoin on the cusp of a new uptrend?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18977990/Is-Bitcoin-on-the-cusp-of-a-new-uptrend</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18977990/Is-Bitcoin-on-the-cusp-of-a-new-uptrend"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T15:30:42.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried's Lawyer Refutes Claims of Reckless Investments at FTX: Report]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b40a6a18</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/sam-bankman-frieds-lawyer-refutes-claims-of-reckless-investments-in-ftx-report/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T15:21:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF) is fighting to defend the  
legitimacy of FTX's investments. His lawyer has argued that these investments  
were not "reckless and frivolous," countering former Executive Nishad  
Singh's portrayal of excessive spending on marketing and celebrity  
endorsements, Reuters reported.
Singh, FTX's former Chief Technology Engineer,  
testified for a second consecutive day in SBF's fraud trial at the Manhattan  
federal court today (Wednesday). Under cross-examination, Singh stated that he  
thought FTX could handle its challenges after discovering a shortfall of $13  
billion in customer funds in September 2022. 
Challenging the Testimony of FTX’s Former Top Executive
FTX declared bankruptcy on November 11, 2022, and  
Singh had previously testified that the company's ven…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stellar, Early Blockchain Built for Payments, Adds Smart Contracts to Take on Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b40b0e0f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/10/18/stellar-early-blockchain-built-for-payments-adds-smart-contracts-to-take-on-ethereum/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T15:17:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The nine-year-old project, one of the earliest major blockchains, is getting a facelift to incorporate  "smart contracts," that theoretically could attract new applications and users – and potentially more demand for the XLM token.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bradley Keoun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Price Decline: Is Ripple Selling Off Tokens?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b5f40e7d</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/xrp-price-ripple-selling-tokens/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T15:11:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After surging above the $0.51 mark on Monday, the XRP price has been on a decline once more. This has seen the asset drop back below $0.49 as obvious selling pressure continues to mount on the altcoin. The major focus of holders has been on where this sell pressure is coming from and a number of large transfers from Ripple have raised eyebrows.
 
Ripple Transfers Over $50 Million XRP
 
On Monday, two transactions from Ripple caught the attention of the XRP community. The transactions which were detected by whale tracking platform Whale Alert were carrying a significant amount of XRP tokens, leading to speculations that the crypto firm is selling part of its holdings.
 
 
The first transaction which was carrying 75 million tokens worth $36.92 million was being sent to an unknown wallet. In …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unchained Debuts Bitcoin-Focused Financial Advisory Services]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b5f4dd7a</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/unchained-debuts-bitcoin-focused-financial-advisory-services"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T15:06:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sound Advisory / Unchained
 
    
Unchained, a leading Bitcoin financial services provider, has launched its new service, Sound Advisory, per a press release sent to Bitcoin Magazine. This new platform offers registered investment advisor (RIA) services, specifically designed for investors looking to include bitcoin in their portfolios.
The introduction of Sound Advisory comes at a time when there's a growing interest from investors in BTC. Moreover, there's a clear gap in the market for financial advisors who specialize in bitcoin.
With Sound Advisory, Unchained seeks to give clients access to financial planners who deeply understand the nuances of bitcoin. These advisors will help clients plan their bitcoin investments, navigate potential tax issues, and set up inheritance plans. The pri…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Evidence Sam Bankman-Fried's Lawyers Didn't Want Us to See]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202023</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202023/evidence-sam-bankman-fried-lawyers-didnt-want-us-to-see"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T15:04:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From yachts to Sam Bankman-Fried’s thoughts on the uncanny valley, the defense has swatted at several exhibits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What to Expect From the AI World Fair in Decentraland]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202148</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202148/what-expect-ai-world-fair-decentraland"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T15:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AI World Fair is coming to the metaverse, as AI founders and companies like NVIDIA and SingularityNET discuss the buzzy tech topic in Decentraland.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ali Shutler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentraland AI World Fair Trailer]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/3tUb56Fv/decentraland-ai-world-fair-trailer</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/3tUb56Fv/decentraland-ai-world-fair-trailer"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A trailer for the AI World Fair event in metaverse game Decentraland, taking place from October 25-27. Courtesy: Decentraland.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mike Novogratz Says a Spot Bitcoin ETF Will Be Approved in 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202165</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202165/mike-novogratz-says-a-spot-bitcoin-etf-will-be-approved-in-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T14:56:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Novogratz joins a growing contingent who are much more optimistic that the industry will see a Bitcoin ETF sooner rather than later.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Digital Euro Project Moves to 'Preparation' Phase]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b5f6bbb1</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/10/18/digital-euro-project-moves-to-preparation-phase/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T14:54:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The move is not a decision to issue a central bank digital currency, the European Central Bank said Wednesday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandali Handagama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RareSkills Launches Free Zero-Knowledge Proofs (ZKPs) E-Book]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202138</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202138/rareskills-launches-free-zero-knowledge-proofs-zkps-e-book"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T14:24:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The book is designed to provide programmers with all the information needed to code a prover and verifier from scratch that is usable in modern smart contracts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chainwire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum’s ‘Billionaire’ Wallets Own One-Third Of Supply For First Time Since 2016]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b5fd49b1</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereums-billionaires-own-one-third-supply-2016/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T14:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data shows that Ethereum billionaire-sized wallets now control almost one-third of the entire supply, the highest level since 2016.
 
Ethereum Addresses With At Least 1 Million ETH Now Hold 32.3% Of Supply
 
According to data from the on-chain analytics firm Santiment, the Ethereum whales with more than 1 million ETH have grown their holdings recently. The relevant indicator here is the “Supply Distribution,” which keeps track of the percentage of the Ethereum supply that each investor group is holding currently.
 
The holders or addresses are divided into these groups based on the number of coins that they are carrying in their balances. The 100-1,000 coins cohort, for instance, includes all investors who own at least 100 and at most 1,000 ETH.
 
In the context of the current discussion, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Treasury Targets Gaza Crypto Business in Sanctions to Squeeze Hamas]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b5fd6179</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/10/18/us-treasury-targets-gaza-crypto-business-in-sanctions-to-squeeze-hamas/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T14:11:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Treasury Department issued a list of sanctions that included a business providing money transfers and digital assets exchange services in Gaza.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Time for a Purpose-Built Disclosure Framework for Crypto]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b5fd6133</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/10/18/its-time-for-a-purpose-built-disclosure-framework-for-crypto/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T14:11:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Without looking at the unique attributes of crypto, it will be difficult (or even impossible) to understand and place a valuation on a crypto asset.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rob Krugman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto World Cautiously Hopeful as California Acts in Absence of U.S. Feds]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b5fd60f8</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/10/18/crypto-world-cautiously-hopeful-as-california-acts-in-absence-of-us-feds/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T14:11:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto insiders feel they've been burned before in the cauldron of New York’s BitLicense, but they fell that California’s implementation leaves some room for hope.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Financial Services Firm Unchained Looks to Attract Wealthy Clients With New Advisory Service]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b5feb539</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/10/18/bitcoin-financial-services-firm-unchained-looks-to-attract-wealthy-clients-with-new-advisory-service/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T14:02:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The service will offer a network of "bitcoin-competent" financial planners to help HNWIs build distribution and utilization strategies and address potential tax and inheritance issues, Unchained said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Crypto Regulatory Fog Keeps Standard Chartered Rooted in UAE, Asia]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b5feb522</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/10/18/us-crypto-regulatory-fog-keeps-standard-chartered-rooted-in-uae-asia/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T14:02:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Standard Chartered chose Dubai to launch crypto services from. However, reading between the lines, almost anywhere is preferable to the U.S. – that’s the message coming from banks and large institutions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Tokens MOON and BRICK Plunge as Reddit Sunsets Community Points]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74b5fef177</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/crypto-tokens-moon-and-brick-plunge-as-reddit-sunsets-community-points/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T14:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Tuesday, the social news hub Reddit unveiled that it would be drawing the curtains on the Community Points project. This revelation promptly sent two cryptocurrency coins from r/cryptocurrency and r/fortnite spiraling downward, showcasing a notable dip in value following the news. This development also irked a multitude of Redditors, with conversations surrounding the plan to sunset the points spiraling into chaos.
 
Redditors’ Discontent Simmers as Community Points Project Faces the Axe
 
While they might not ring a bell, two digital currencies, MOON and BRICK, have witnessed a significant plunge in value over the past 24 hours. This tumble springs from Reddit’s decision to back away from offering Community Points, setting the sun on the project come November 8, 2023. Although Reddit h…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFT Games Are Not to Be Considered Gambling, Votes French National Assembly]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202145</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202145/nft-games-are-not-to-be-considered-gambling-votes-french-national-assembly"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T13:42:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It still needs to be approved by the Constitutional Council, but the so-called Sorare law would be a big win for French crypto games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK's $252B in Crypto Activity Dominated by DEX Trading, NFT Swapping: Chainalysis]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202139</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202139/uks-252b-crypto-activity-dominated-dex-trading-nft-swapping-chainalysis"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T13:07:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Platforms like OpenSea, Sorare, and Uniswap are the top choices among British crypto users, according to a new Chainalysis report.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken’s Powell: Reddit Should Offer ‘Redemption Path’ for Community Points]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202131</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202131/krakens-powell-reddit-should-offer-redemption-path-for-community-points"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T11:23:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken co-founder Jesse Powell offered several suggestions following Reddit’s “sunsetting” of its crypto-powered Community Points.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUI Hits All-Time Low, Foundation Addresses 'Unfounded' Token Manipulation Claims]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202128</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202128/sui-hits-all-time-low-foundation-addresses-unfounded-claims-about-token-manipulation"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T10:26:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amid calls from regulators in South Korea that they would investigate manipulation claims around the SUI token, the project's Foundation has called the statements "materially false" and "unfounded."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Louvre Augmented Reality Exhibit With Snapchat Uncovers Ancient Egypt]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202106</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202106/louvre-augmented-reality-exhibit-snapchat-uncovers-ancient-egypt"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T04:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Beginning Wednesday, the Louvre's "Egypt Augmented" exhibition offers a new way to learn about Ancient Egypt in partnership with Snap.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephanie Hirschmiller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roblox Debunks 'Inaccurate' XRP Support Claims, Says Crypto Payments Not Allowed]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202077</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202077/roblox-debunks-inaccurate-xrp-claims-says-crypto-payments-not-allowed"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T02:15:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is Roblox adding support for XRP, the token used by Ripple? Nope. Despite rapidly spreading claims, the gaming platform says it's false.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[East Meets West: Baidu's New Ernie 4.0 Chatbot Embodies China's Growing AI Ambitions]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202082</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202082/east-meets-west-baidus-new-ernie-4-0-chatbot-embodies-chinas-growing-ai-ambitions"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T00:23:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Baidu unveils its upgraded Ernie 4.0 and Alibaba goes open for the enterprise, China's AI landscape may mirror America's.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Metaverse Token Pre-Sale From ‘Life Beyond’ Team Raises $3.5M]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202088</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202088/bitcoin-metaverse-token-pre-sale-from-animoca-studio-raises-3-5m"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T00:09:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Animoca Brands subsidiary’s metaverse ambitions are backed by several investors, including Gamefi Ventures and Animoca Ventures.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gucci Cosmos Showcases Fashion Brand's Legacy With Head-Turning Tech]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202056</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202056/gucci-cosmos-showcases-fashion-brands-legacy-head-turning-tech"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T23:18:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Currently in London, the Gucci Cosmos exhibition pairs the history of innovative tech with key moments from the luxury giant's own rich past.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephanie Hirschmiller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Canadian Citizens In This City Have Lost $22.5 Million to Crypto Scams]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202050</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202050/canadian-citizens-in-this-city-have-lost-22-5-million-to-crypto-scams"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T23:01:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One survey found a third of crypto-holding Canadians reported being victims of crypto scams.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Promised $100M to Maker of SBF's Favorite Game 'League of Legends']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202029</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202029/ftx-promised-100m-maker-sbf-favorite-game-league-legends"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T22:25:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FTX inked a massive sponsorship deal with League of Legends studio Riot Games before going bankrupt, but much of it may remain unpaid.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypties 2023 Nominees Revealed: Vote for Crypto's Top Projects and Creators]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202019</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202019/crypties-2023-nominees-revealed-vote-crypto-top-projects-creators"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T21:27:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Claim your free Crypties voting pass and cast your ballot to help choose this year’s most exciting crypto and emerging tech creators.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blending Tech and Tunes, $4 Million Riffusion Raise Lights Up AI Music Scene]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202018</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202018/blending-tech-and-tunes-4-million-riffusion-raise-lights-up-ai-music-scene"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T20:58:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As society grapples with the role of AI in the arts, Riffusion stands at the crossroads, exploring the possibilities of AI-generated melodies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BackTheBunny - Money, Conspiracy, Milady]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BRoKZzer/backthebunny-money-conspiracy-milady</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BRoKZzer/backthebunny-money-conspiracy-milady"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T19:48:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our host Reza Jafery sits down with BackTheBunny to dive deep into money, the fight against crypto that we're witnessing in real-time, and milady culture. 

Our Host: https://twitter.com/rezajafery
Our Guest: https://twitter.com/BackTheBunny

Our Sponsors
https://decrypt.co/1000x]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reddit Is Killing Crypto Community Points Tokens—And Holders Are Dumping Their Bags]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202014</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202014/reddit-killing-crypto-community-points-tokens-holders-dumping-bags"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T18:54:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reddit is removing its blockchain tokens due to regulatory and "resourcing" concerns, and prices for MOON and BRICK are plunging.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[God Mode: 9 Things to Watch, Read, and Play Before 'Alan Wake 2']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201876</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201876/god-mode-9-things-watch-read-play-before-alan-wake-2"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T18:30:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Remedy's survival horror sequel Alan Wake 2 drops later this month. Start savoring the spooky vibes early with these recommendations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Frederiksen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['A Grand Experiment': Shrapnel Studio Head Don Norbury Talks Game Economics]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Z2OMMsC5/a-grand-experiment-shrapnel-studio-head-don-norbury-talks-game-economics</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Z2OMMsC5/a-grand-experiment-shrapnel-studio-head-don-norbury-talks-game-economics"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T17:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How much of Shrapnel's in-game items are tradeable NFTs? Don Norbury, Studio Head at Shrapnel and CTO at game studio NEON, tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about Shrapnel's approach to game economics, including different game pricing models and how NFT game economies create different challenges for developers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miner Using Paraguay Itaipu Dam to Power Its New Facility]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201963</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201963/bitcoin-miner-sazmining-paraguay-itaipu-dam"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T15:59:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sazmining President Kent Halliburton thinks the surplus of hydroelectic power and low costs could make Paraguary "the new Texas" for Bitcoin miners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SBF Trial Live Updates: Nishad Singh Details Excessive Spending at FTX]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199892</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199892/trial-sam-bankman-fried-live-blog-latest-news-insights"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T15:05:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried faces seven criminal charges related to the dramatic collapse of his crypto empire. Here's the latest on his trial.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trezor Safe 3 and Trezor Keep Metal Unboxing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/IjqnO9pR/trezor-safe-3-and-trezor-keep-metal-unboxing</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/IjqnO9pR/trezor-safe-3-and-trezor-keep-metal-unboxing"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T14:45:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trezor has launched the Safe 3, a hardware wallet aimed at "new entrants to crypto," alongside the new Keep Metal recovery seed storage device. We take a first look at what comes in the box.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Staking Is Losing Its Appeal–Here's Why]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201968</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201968/line-validators-looking-stake-ethereum-is-getting-shorter-heres-why"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T13:37:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With staking demand after Ethereum’s latest upgrade drying up, analysts suggest institutions will take up the lead next.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi,Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFT Creator Royalties Are Broken—Yuga Labs and Magic Eden Join Group Trying to Fix Them]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201917</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201917/yuga-labs-magic-eden-join-collective-rethinking-nft-creator-royalties"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T13:01:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OMA3 has tapped industry leaders—including Bored Ape creator Yuga Labs—to help develop new NFT royalty standards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Sandbox Hires Ex-PlayStation, Apple Exec to Drive Game's Creator Economy]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201877</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201877/the-sandbox-hires-ex-playstation-apple-exec-to-drive-games-creator-economy"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nicola Sebastiani, who previously worked at Ubisoft and PlayStation, is joining The Sandbox to lead its creator economy push.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Wearable Tech: Smart Clothing, Jewelry, and Other Stuff on Your Body]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201977</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-wearable-tech-smart-clothing-jewelry-and-other-stuff-on-your-body"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T12:55:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When people think of wearable technology today, they likely picture smart watches, fitness trackers, virtual reality headsets, and similar products. The history of wearable tech is an important part of the longstanding connection between the fashion world and the technology sector and in fact extends back to well before those products existed. Wearable tech is […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Reiff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To AI: Best AI Tools for YouTube]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201080</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201080/how-to-ai-get-started-on-youtube"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T12:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Perfect for beginner YouTubers, this list includes applications that feature both paid and free versions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Creditors Could See $9 Billion Dispersement by Next June]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201950</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201950/ftx-creditors-could-see-9-billion-dispersement-next-june"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T10:18:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chief restructuring officer John J. Ray III celebrated the milestone, calling FTX's collapse "the most challenging financial disaster" he has seen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance US Says Crypto Deposits Are No Longer FDIC Insured]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201949</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201949/binance-us-says-crypto-deposits-are-no-longer-fdic-insured"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T10:17:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The updated terms of service for Binance US indicate that users must first convert their dollars to stablecoins or crypto before withdrawing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can the Bitcoin Lightning Network Disrupt Media Monetization?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201951</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201951/bitcoin-lightning-network-disrupt-media-monetization"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T10:06:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ad rates are declining and subscription models rarely work. Mash and TFTC says the Bitcoin LIghtning Network fixes this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alyssa Hertig</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ApeCoin Community Accelerator Launches From Animoca Brands' Forj]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201865</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201865/forj-animoca-brands-nft-apecoin-community-accelerator"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T06:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animoca Brands' Forj says it went with ApeCoin because "it has the most collaborative and socially engaged community across Web3."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia’s Text-to-3D AI Tool Debuts While Its Hardware Business Hits Regulatory Headwinds]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201918</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201918/nvidia-masterpiece-studio-x-3d"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T00:15:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From developing pioneering 3D software to navigating geopolitics for its hardware, Nvidia's ups and downs reflect an equally unsteady market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Takes the Reigns in Spotting Exploding Stars]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201899</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201899/ai-takes-the-helm-in-supernova-classification"/>
        <updated>2023-10-16T23:59:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bright Transient Survey bot project can quickly identify supernovae with the help of machine learning.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock Boss Says Bitcoin Pump on Fake ETF News Shows ‘Pent Up Interest in Crypto’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201898</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201898/blackrock-boss-says-bitcoin-pump-on-fake-etf-news-shows-pent-up-interest-in-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-10-16T22:54:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While the CEO claimed his company’s Bitcoin spot ETF application was only in a better place after Monday’s events, others were skeptical.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taxes Targeting DeFi Would be ‘Awfully Challenging’: Coinbase VP]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201879</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201879/decentralized-exchange-dex-defi-tax-proposal"/>
        <updated>2023-10-16T22:08:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[His comments come after he called a proposed tax rule changed “unchecked and unlimited tracking on the daily lives of Americans.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum DeFi Exchange Uniswap Adds Fees, Sparks Controversy]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201881</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201881/ethereum-defi-exchange-uniswap-adds-fees-sparks-controversy"/>
        <updated>2023-10-16T21:57:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A 0.15% fee on front-end interface swaps has some Web3 investors calling it a case of misaligned incentives.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Playable Grand Theft Auto on Netflix? Just 'Rumors,' Says Streaming Giant]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201875</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201875/playable-grand-theft-auto-on-netflix-just-rumors-says-streaming-giant"/>
        <updated>2023-10-16T21:13:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new report this week suggests that Netflix may license a Grand Theft Auto game. But the streaming giant isn't fueling the speculation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether Freezes Wallets Linked to Terrorist Groups in Israel and Ukraine]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201860</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201860/tether-freezes-crypto-tied-to-warfare-in-israel-and-ukraine"/>
        <updated>2023-10-16T18:23:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tether has frozen over $835 million in collaboration with governments to date.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining Activity Surges as Difficulty Soars to New Peak]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201821</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201821/bitcoin-mining-activity-surges-difficulty-soars-new-peak"/>
        <updated>2023-10-16T17:19:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With about six and a half months until the next halving event, Bitcoin’s mining difficulty level has just hit a new all-time high.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OnePiece Labs and Sei to Showcase Web3 Startups at Demo Day]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201851</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201851/onepiece-labs-and-sei-to-showcase-web3-startups-at-demo-day"/>
        <updated>2023-10-16T16:59:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The event will spotlight 11 startups from the partnership’s incubator program, including GameFi, SocialFi, and AI+Web3 firms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why AI Arena is Building on Arbitrum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Gl80TQOm/why-ai-arena-is-building-on-arbitrum</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Gl80TQOm/why-ai-arena-is-building-on-arbitrum"/>
        <updated>2023-10-12T14:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI Arena CEO Brandon Da Silva and COO Wei Xie discuss the challenges that come with building on Ethereum, ETH sidechains, and layer-two blockchains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pet3rPan_ on venture DAOs and blockchain games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DawNLI3O/pet3rpan-on-venture-daos-and-blockchain-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DawNLI3O/pet3rpan-on-venture-daos-and-blockchain-games"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T18:24:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the 4th episode of this time will be different.

Our guest for today's episode is Pet3rpan_ from Metacartel, 1kx, HydraVentures, and more!

https://twitter.com/pet3rpan_

This Time Will Be Different is sponsored by 1000x
https://decrypt.co/1000x]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Shrapnel's Marketplace, New Map, and 'AI Director' Feature]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/F5RQCmvH/inside-shrapnels-marketplace-new-map-and-ai-director-feature</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/F5RQCmvH/inside-shrapnels-marketplace-new-map-and-ai-director-feature"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T16:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin chats with Shrapnel's Head of Studio Don Norbury to get the latest updates on how the NFT-powered first-person sci-fi extraction shooter's development is progressing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Art of the Times': Art Blocks Founder Erick Calderon on the State of Generative Art]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zSjfRrl5/art-of-the-times-art-blocks-founder-erick-calderon-on-the-state-of-generative-art</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zSjfRrl5/art-of-the-times-art-blocks-founder-erick-calderon-on-the-state-of-generative-art"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T18:10:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Art Blocks founder and CEO Erick Calderon sat down with Sander Lutz, lead culture reporter at Decrypt's SCENE, at Art Blocks Marfa Weekend 2023. They discuss the evolution of the company and the generative art world, along with what draws art enthusiasts to be an active part of the community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt Learn: Digital Ownership Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/6udZCotB/decrypt-learn-digital-ownership-explained</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/6udZCotB/decrypt-learn-digital-ownership-explained"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T10:57:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most powerful aspects of blockchain technology is its ability to provide us genuine ownership of our digital assets. This is called digital ownership. In this video, we’ll deep dive into digital ownership, why it matters, and how web3 makes owning digital assets like our social networks, music libraries, personal data, and beyond possible. Author: Clarissa Watson, Senior Writer at Consensys.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Martin Shkreli on E/ACC and SBF in Prison]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QONaWXKZ/martin-shkreli-on-e-acc-and-sbf-in-prison</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QONaWXKZ/martin-shkreli-on-e-acc-and-sbf-in-prison"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T22:03:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reza Jafery and Martin Shkreli sit down for a casual conversation about the growing movement that is E/ACC, what songs they could recite at gunpoint, and whether or not SBF will thrive or just survive during his time in prison.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Can AI Do in Gaming?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JKuqCMao/what-can-ai-do-in-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JKuqCMao/what-can-ai-do-in-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T17:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI Arena CEO Brandon Da Silva and COO Wei Xie discuss how artificial intelligence can shape the video game experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['There Are No Real Standards': Ready Player Me CEO Timmu Tõke on Building for an Open Gaming Ecosystem]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TH3KEAI0/there-are-no-real-standards-ready-player-me-ceo-timmu-tke-on-building-for-an-open-gaming-ecosystem</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TH3KEAI0/there-are-no-real-standards-ready-player-me-ceo-timmu-tke-on-building-for-an-open-gaming-ecosystem"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T17:29:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Timmu Tõke, co-founder and CEO of Ready Player Me, joins Decrypt contributor Ryan Gladwin to discuss the startup's approach to powering avatars that are interoperable across games and metaverse platforms—and what's needed to convince the industry to adopt standards and open up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain Is 'Only Way' Forward for Gaming, Says Shrapnel Studio Head]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/fhoy7Z8f/blockchain-is-only-way-forward-for-gaming-says-shrapnel-studio-head</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/fhoy7Z8f/blockchain-is-only-way-forward-for-gaming-says-shrapnel-studio-head"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T21:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shrapnel Studio Head Don Norbury tells Kate Irwin the reasons why the upcoming first-person shooter game will offer a wide range of NFTs. He also reveals team-based gameplay plans and shares how game maps have already changed this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Social Media Sentiment Is Key to Crypto Price Discovery]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/981TBppa/social-media-sentiment-is-key-to-crypto-price-discovery</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/981TBppa/social-media-sentiment-is-key-to-crypto-price-discovery"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T23:47:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sacha Ghebali, Director of Strategy and Business Development at The TIE, says social media sentiment remains a key factor in price movements for major cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin and Ethereum. However, he notes that sentiment has turned more negative lately amid regulatory uncertainty. Ghebali believes events like the Ripple lawsuit ruling significantly impacted sentiment and prices. André Beganski interviewed him at Messari Mainnet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[500Altcoins discusses DeFi Summer and the Dubai Crypto Scene - This Time Will Be Different - Episode 2]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cI7p8AK3/500altcoins-discusses-defi-summer-and-the-dubai-crypto-scene-this-time-will-be-different-episode-2</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cI7p8AK3/500altcoins-discusses-defi-summer-and-the-dubai-crypto-scene-this-time-will-be-different-episode-2"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our host Reza Jafery is joined by Gareth Fenney aka 500Altcoins. They discuss the glory days of DeFi Summer and whether or not its a smart move for builders in the crypto space to relocate to Dubai.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralize Derivatives Trading with Custom Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/lfmwAjB9/decentralize-derivatives-trading-with-custom-blockchain</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/lfmwAjB9/decentralize-derivatives-trading-with-custom-blockchain"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T10:37:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Gogel of dYdX discusses how the decentralized exchange is building a custom blockchain to fully decentralize derivatives trading. He explained how the new dYdX chain will allow validators to run order books in memory, enabling decentralized order matching at scale. This shift aims to increase security and transparency for traders while maintaining the performance of centralized exchanges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Accounting Challenges and Opportunities]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/0Sezz6pZ/crypto-accounting-challenges-and-opportunities</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/0Sezz6pZ/crypto-accounting-challenges-and-opportunities"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As crypto matures, accounting and tax regulations are evolving. Amy Kalnoki of Bitwave explains how her company helps crypto companies properly account for digital assets. She notes the importance of flexibility as new crypto assets emerge and regulations change. Stacy Elliott interviewed her at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Most Crypto Users Don't Trust Themselves to Keep Their Seed Phrase Safe: Ledger CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/0kYf2Qed/most-crypto-users-dont-trust-themselves-to-keep-their-seed-phrase-safe-ledger-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/0kYf2Qed/most-crypto-users-dont-trust-themselves-to-keep-their-seed-phrase-safe-ledger-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Stacy Elliott sat down with Ledger CEO Pascal Gauthier to discuss crypto custody post-FTX, and the hardware wallet manufacturer's controversial Ledger Recover service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[India's 1% Crypto Tax Has Been a Nightmare for High-Frequency Traders, Says Shardeum CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/fxygwLvH/indias-1-crypto-tax-has-been-a-nightmare-for-high-frequency-traders-says-shardeum-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/fxygwLvH/indias-1-crypto-tax-has-been-a-nightmare-for-high-frequency-traders-says-shardeum-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As India figures out its regulatory approach to the crypto industry, one thing is clear to Shardeum co-founder Nischal Shetty: “If you're a high-frequency trader, you can't afford to lose a percentage every time you sell,” he told Decrypt's Andre Beganski at Messari Mainnet in New York. “That's something that's caused a lot of issues.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Newly Partnered with Visa, Solana Focuses on Reliability]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/MZoxvulr/newly-partnered-with-visa-solana-focuses-on-reliability</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/MZoxvulr/newly-partnered-with-visa-solana-focuses-on-reliability"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana has improved network reliability through upgrades like Quick and local fee markets. It recently partnered with Visa to allow settling transactions in USDC on Solana. This could enable merchants to receive instant payments and save on credit card processing fees. Stacy Elliott spoke with Austin Federa, Head of Strategy for the Solana Foundation, at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>