<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-06-04T07:15:48.424Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-06-04T07:15:48.424Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Edward Snowden Makes A Bold Statement On Bitcoin: Details]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741dd0bd89</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/edward-snowden-bold-statement-bitcoin/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T07:08:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Monday, NSA whistleblower Edward Snowden once again expressed his support for Bitcoin (BTC). Snowden’s statement came in the wake of a significant market disruption that saw Berkshire Hathaway shares plummet by 99% due to a technical glitch on the New York Stock Exchange (NYSE). This incident has reignited discussions about the robustness and reliability of traditional financial systems versus decentralized alternatives.
 
Bitcoin Fixes This
 
A technical glitch on the NYSE triggered extreme price swings in several securities, causing a temporary suspension of trading. Approximately two hours after the NYSE halted trading, it was reported that all systems were operational again.
 
Among the affected securities, shares of Berkshire Hathaway, Warren Buffett‘s storied investment company, a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Sees Profit-Taking Around $70K Amid ‘Stubbornly Bullish’ Sentiment]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741dd0d4b0</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/06/04/bitcoin-sees-profit-taking-around-70k-amid-stubbornly-bullish-sentiment/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T07:07:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data shows over 50% of Bitcoin supply remains inactive, a sign of strong long-term conviction in the asset.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Legendary Trader Peter Brandt Says Bitcoin Could Rally to $150,000 Before Bull Market Ends – Here’s His Timeline]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19553023/Legendary-Trader-Peter-Brandt-Says-Bitcoin-Could-Rally-to-150000-Before-Bull-Market-Ends-Heres-His-Timeline</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19553023/Legendary-Trader-Peter-Brandt-Says-Bitcoin-Could-Rally-to-150000-Before-Bull-Market-Ends-Heres-His-Timeline"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T07:04:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Veteran trader Peter Brandt believes that Bitcoin (BTC) can soar to a high of $150,000 before the bull market comes to a close. In a new blog post, Brandt says the timeline of each bull cycle has been more or less the same since 2012. “The number of weeks from the start of each bull […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Edward Snowden Makes A Bold Statement On Bitcoin: Details]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19553020/Edward-Snowden-Makes-A-Bold-Statement-On-Bitcoin-Details</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19553020/Edward-Snowden-Makes-A-Bold-Statement-On-Bitcoin-Details"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T07:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Monday, NSA whistleblower Edward Snowden once again expressed his support for Bitcoin (BTC). Snowden’s statement came in the wake of a significant market disruption that saw Berkshire Hathaway shares plummet by 99% due to a technical glitch on the New York Stock Exchange (NYSE). This incident...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Statement on the Giant US Organization Announcing Bitcoin Investment: Will Acquisitions Continue?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19552994/Statement-on-the-Giant-US-Organization-Announcing-Bitcoin-Investment-Will-Acquisitions-Continue</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19552994/Statement-on-the-Giant-US-Organization-Announcing-Bitcoin-Investment-Will-Acquisitions-Continue"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T06:51:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Will the purchases of the giant pension fund, which announced that it purchased Bitcoin Spot ETF in the USA, continue? Here's the prediction. Continue Reading: Statement on the Giant US Organization Announcing Bitcoin Investment: Will Acquisitions Continue?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JPEX Scandal: Victims Fight to Reclaim $700,000 in Hong Kong Court]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19553005/JPEX-Scandal-Victims-Fight-to-Reclaim-700000-in-Hong-Kong-Court</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19553005/JPEX-Scandal-Victims-Fight-to-Reclaim-700000-in-Hong-Kong-Court"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T06:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two individuals connected to the JPEX scandal have filed a lawsuit in Hong Kong courts seeking to recover HK$5.5 million (approximately $703,300). The lawsuit names plaintiffs Herbert Lee Sung-him and Chan Wing-yan against JPEX Crypto Asset Platform, a firm accused of financial fraud totaling...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deutsche Bank and BitPanda join forces for real-time crypto payments]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19552940/Deutsche-Bank-and-BitPanda-join-forces-for-real-time-crypto-payments</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19552940/Deutsche-Bank-and-BitPanda-join-forces-for-real-time-crypto-payments"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T06:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The partnership with Deutsche Bank allows BitPanda to offer real-time inbound and outbound cash payments for German crypto traders using German International Bank Account Numbers (IBAN).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Sees Profit-Taking Around $70K Amid ‘Stubbornly Bullish’ Sentiment]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19552939/Bitcoin-Sees-Profit-Taking-Around-70K-Amid-Stubbornly-Bullish-Sentiment</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19552939/Bitcoin-Sees-Profit-Taking-Around-70K-Amid-Stubbornly-Bullish-Sentiment"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T06:27:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data shows over 50% of Bitcoin supply remains inactive, a sign of strong long-term conviction in the asset.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Implements MiCA Stablecoin Rules in Europe, CZ Addresses Delisting Concerns]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19552970/Binance-Implements-MiCA-Stablecoin-Rules-in-Europe-CZ-Addresses-Delisting-Concerns</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19552970/Binance-Implements-MiCA-Stablecoin-Rules-in-Europe-CZ-Addresses-Delisting-Concerns"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T06:22:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance, the world’s largest cryptocurrency exchange by trading volume, is implementing new Markets in Crypto-Assets (MiCA) stablecoin rules across the European Economic Area (EEA). The MiCA rules, effective June 30, 2024, mark a significant shift in the stablecoin market, with new regulations...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global X Drops Fees to Zero on European Crypto ETPs]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19552925/Global-X-Drops-Fees-to-Zero-on-European-Crypto-ETPs</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19552925/Global-X-Drops-Fees-to-Zero-on-European-Crypto-ETPs"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T06:18:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US-based ETF provider Global X has temporarily eliminated fees for two physically backed cryptocurrency exchange-traded products in Europe.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notcoin Becomes Top 50 Crypto as Telegram Game Goes Viral]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19552961/Notcoin-Becomes-Top-50-Crypto-as-Telegram-Game-Goes-Viral</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19552961/Notcoin-Becomes-Top-50-Crypto-as-Telegram-Game-Goes-Viral"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T06:15:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Notcoin (NOT) surged over the weekend, posting significant gains following a surge in popularity and user base. The token, recently listed on leading crypto exchanges, has experienced a strong uptrend. Data from CoinMarketCap shows Notcoin (NOT) is up 17.62% in the past 24 hours, trading at...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ERC-6900 Website Launches, Co-Authored by Ethereum Foundation, Alchemy, Circle and Quantstamp]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741ddfc55e</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/erc-6900-website-launches-co-authored-by-ethereum-foundation-alchemy-circle-and-quantstamp/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T06:12:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The official resource for ERC-6900, www.erc6900.io, has been launched, co-authored by the Ethereum Foundation, Alchemy, Circle, and Quantstamp. The website is a comprehensive guide to ERC-6900, a groundbreaking proposal that standardizes interfaces for composable smart accounts. The core idea behind ERC-6900 is to foster permissionless innovation by making it easier for developers to build secure, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken Sees Largest Bitcoin And Ethereum Outflows Since 2017, What’s going On?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741dd8423d</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/kraken-sees-largest-bitcoin-ethereum-outflows-2017/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T06:08:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recent data shows that Kraken, one of the premier crypto exchanges in the market, has witnessed its largest outflows of Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) since 2017. This signals a significant shift in digital asset holdings, which could have broad implications for the market.
 
Kraken’s Historic Outflows, What Is Going On?
 
Insights from Joao Wedson of Dominando Cripto shared on CryptoQuant’s quick-take platform highlight a startling trend at Kraken. The exchange recorded an outflow of 49,100 BTC, translating to approximately $3.33 billion.
 
 
This massive withdrawal marks the largest movement of funds from the exchange in dollar terms. Ethereum was not left behind, with roughly 572,100 ETH, valued at around $2.15 billion, also exiting the platform.
 
This substantial reduction has broug…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily Discussion, June 04, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19552898/Daily-Discussion-June-04-2024</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19552898/Daily-Discussion-June-04-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T06:07:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Please utilize this sticky thread for all general Bitcoin discussions! If you see posts on the front page or /r/Bitcoin/new which are better suited for this daily discussion thread, please help out by directing the OP to this thread instead. Thank you! If you don't get an answer to your...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Galaxy Digital Tokenizes $9 Million Stradivarius Violin For Loan]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19552895/Galaxy-Digital-Tokenizes-9-Million-Stradivarius-Violin-For-Loan</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19552895/Galaxy-Digital-Tokenizes-9-Million-Stradivarius-Violin-For-Loan"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T06:05:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Galaxy Digital has tokenized a 316-year-old $9 million Stradivarius violin owned by Animoca Brands co-founder Yat Siu as collateral to back a multimillion-dollar loan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF Wars: BlackRock, Fidelity Gain Ground on Vanguard as Grayscale Lags]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19552930/Bitcoin-ETF-Wars-BlackRock-Fidelity-Gain-Ground-on-Vanguard-as-Grayscale-Lags</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19552930/Bitcoin-ETF-Wars-BlackRock-Fidelity-Gain-Ground-on-Vanguard-as-Grayscale-Lags"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T06:03:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock’s and Fidelity’s Bitcoin ETFs are driving significant inflows for the firms, accounting for 26% and 56% of their respective year-to-date totals, according to Bloomberg Intelligence data cited by Eric Balchunas. The BlackRock iShares Bitcoin Trust (IBIT) and the Fidelity Wise Origin...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Devs Warn of Treat Token Scams on Shibaswap]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19552929/Shiba-Inu-Devs-Warn-of-Treat-Token-Scams-on-Shibaswap</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19552929/Shiba-Inu-Devs-Warn-of-Treat-Token-Scams-on-Shibaswap"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T06:03:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Shibarium community is on high alert as reports surface of fraudulent tokens claiming false associations with Shiba Inu developers. These bad actors are exploiting Shibarium’s decentralized platform to promote their schemes, posing significant risks to investors. DaVinci, a prominent figure...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ASIC Fails to Impose Any Penalty on Block Earner for Unlicensed Offerings]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741dd8fe1a</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/asic-fails-to-impose-any-penalty-on-block-earner-for-unlicensed-offerings/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T06:02:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A federal court in Australia has favoured Block Earner, a cryptocurrency company, by relieving it from the liability of paying a penalty for offering interest-bearing crypto products without an appropriate licence.
A Regulatory Disappointment?
The judgement today (Tuesday) followed actions by the Australian Securities and Investments Commission (ASIC) against Web3 Ventures Pty Ltd, which operates as Block Earner. The regulator said it is “reviewing the decision.”
Block Earner offered several cryptocurrency-based fixed-yield earning products, including USD Earner, Gold Earner, and Crypto Earner, collectively known as Earner Products. The company operated as an AUSTRAC-registered digital currency exchange but did not hold an Australian Financial Services (AFS) licence.
According to ASIC, the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arnab Shome</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[May Sees Record Surge in Google Search Interest for ‘Onchain’ Term]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19552881/May-Sees-Record-Surge-in-Google-Search-Interest-for-Onchain-Term</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19552881/May-Sees-Record-Surge-in-Google-Search-Interest-for-Onchain-Term"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T06:01:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In May, the term "onchain" witnessed an unprecedented surge in Google search interest, reaching an all-time high, as indicated by data from Google Trends.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken Sees Largest Bitcoin And Ethereum Outflows Since 2017, What’s going On?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19552875/Kraken-Sees-Largest-Bitcoin-And-Ethereum-Outflows-Since-2017-Whats-going-On</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19552875/Kraken-Sees-Largest-Bitcoin-And-Ethereum-Outflows-Since-2017-Whats-going-On"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T06:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recent data shows that Kraken, one of the premier crypto exchanges in the market, has witnessed its largest outflows of Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) since 2017. This signals a significant shift in digital asset holdings, which could have broad implications for the market. Kraken’s Historic...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin vs Shiba Inu: Which memecoin will dominate June?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19552872/Dogecoin-vs-Shiba-Inu-Which-memecoin-will-dominate-June</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19552872/Dogecoin-vs-Shiba-Inu-Which-memecoin-will-dominate-June"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T06:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On the 30th of May, the dormant circulation of DOGE saw a massive spike, which might foreshadow a selling wave.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto News Today: Final Manufacturing PMI Fuel Crypto Surge]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19552857/Crypto-News-Today-Final-Manufacturing-PMI-Fuel-Crypto-Surge</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19552857/Crypto-News-Today-Final-Manufacturing-PMI-Fuel-Crypto-Surge"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[S&P Global's May Manufacturing Index has been adjusted upward to 51.3, exceeding initial projections. E-Trade may bar "Roaring Kitty" for potential GameStop stock manipulation after his investments sparked a 30% surge in shares. Major Events To Watch Crypto Fear and Greed Index:The Crypto Fear...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beginner Here with zero knowledge]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19552836/Beginner-Here-with-zero-knowledge</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19552836/Beginner-Here-with-zero-knowledge"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T05:55:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How can one make a life changing wealth with Bitcoin starting from scratch?   submitted by   /u/therealnavy2 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will you sell your Bitcoin?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19552843/Will-you-sell-your-Bitcoin</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19552843/Will-you-sell-your-Bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T05:52:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just wondering if any of you plan to keep and hold your Bitcoin now and forever. With all the interest and marketing with the etf’s will we see bitcoin ever again at todays price. Just curious if any one you will follow Saylor and Mallers and either never sell or go all in on btc. It’s early but...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My US-based accountant seems to think the IRS has released new guidelines on what makes crypto taxable. Don't I have to report only if I have gains/losses?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19552842/My-US-based-accountant-seems-to-think-the-IRS-has-released-new-guidelines-on-what-makes-crypto-taxable-Dont-I-have-to-report-only-if-I-have-gainslosses</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19552842/My-US-based-accountant-seems-to-think-the-IRS-has-released-new-guidelines-on-what-makes-crypto-taxable-Dont-I-have-to-report-only-if-I-have-gainslosses"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T05:43:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks!   submitted by   /u/CharlieBirdlaw [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Community Backlash Forces Matter Labs to Drop ‘ZK’ Trademark Bid]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741dc4f443</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/community-backlash-forces-matter-labs-to-drop-zk-trademark-bid/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T05:28:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The developer of the Zksync Ethereum Layer 2 network, Matter Labs, abandoned its bid to trademark the term ‘ZK’ just days after asserting its right to do so. Matter Labs’ trademark bid withdrawal follows a furious community backlash that ultimately saw co-inventors of zero-knowledge proofs publicly chastise the developer. Community Backlash Ends Matter Labs’ ZK […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thailand Approves First Bitcoin ETF]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741dc6e513</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/thailand-approves-first-bitcoin-etf/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T05:12:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thailand has joined the Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) trend by approving One Asset Management (ONEAM) to launch a Bitcoin ETF, as reported by the Bangkok Post. However, access to the instrument will be limited to wealthy and institutional investors.
Thailand’s Bitcoin ETF
As approved by the Thai Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), the ETF is named the ONE Bitcoin ETF Fund of Funds Unhedged and is scheduled to be distributed between May 31 and June 6. The Bitcoin ETF comes with an investment risk level of eight.
The approval came about two months after the Thai SEC amended its local rules to allow local asset management firms to launch private funds offering Bitcoin ETFs. However, the rule strictly limits the offerings to wealthy and institutional investors.
While ONEAM has recei…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arnab Shome</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Sellers Running Out? Short-Term Holder Realized Profit Dips 32%]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741dc74382</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-sellers-short-term-holder-profit-taking-32/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T05:09:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data shows that Bitcoin short-term holders have seen a decrease in their realized profit, a sign that their appetite for harvesting gains may be diminishing.
 
Bitcoin Short-Term Holders Are Realizing Much Fewer Profits Now
 
As explained by CryptoQuant author Axel Adler Jr in a post on X, the BTC short-term holders have been realizing much lower amounts of profits recently. The “short-term holders” (STHs) here refer to the Bitcoin investors who bought their coins within the past 155 days.
 
Statistically, the longer an investor holds their coins, the less likely they become to sell them. As the STHs are the new entrants in the market, they are unlikely to hold for too long.
 
 
Because of this weak resolve, the investors of this cohort tend to easily panic sell whenever something notable …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitfarms Sees 42% Revenue Drop in May Post-Bitcoin Halving]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741dc2ed11</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitfarms-sees-42-revenue-drop-in-may-post-bitcoin-halving/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T04:38:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitfarms, a Bitcoin mining firm, reported a 42% drop in crypto mining revenue in May, the first full month following the Bitcoin halving in mid-April, which reduced their Bitcoin production from 263 BTC in April to 156 BTC in May. The company attributed part of the decline in production to “unusually cold temperatures” at its […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Woman Pleads Guilty to Using Bitcoin for Dark Web Hitman]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741dcd446e</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/woman-pleads-guilty-to-using-bitcoin-for-dark-web-hitman/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T04:18:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Salt Lake City, Krista Renae Stone, 23, pleaded guilty to using the dark web to arrange a murder-for-hire in 2023. According to court documents, Stone utilized bitcoin to pay $5,000 for the hit. Between March and September 2023, she accessed a website offering “hitman for hire” services, providing detailed information about the intended victim, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Crypto Trader Loses $1 Million From Binance After Chrome Plugin Exploit]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741dce8b93</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/chinese-crypto-trader-loses-1-million-from-binance-after-chrome-plugin-exploit/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T04:07:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Chinese crypto trader shared his experience after losing most of his savings from Binance due to a Chrome plugin exploit. The trader called out the exchange’s allegedly slow response that allowed his funds to be stolen.
 
 
Malicious Chrome Extension Swipes $1 Million In Crypto
 
In late February, crypto investor Doomxbt shared his “peculiar” experience getting his Binance account drained. The user watched his $70,000 holdings vanish in real time without the possibility of stopping it.
 
Per the post, the investor received several notifications from Binance about orders being filled out. The customer quickly checked his account and contacted support before his balance went to $0. While trying to get assistance, he helplessly observed how his funds rapidly disappeared.
 
At the time, the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rubmar Garcia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong Police Advisory Group Warns of Surge in Digital Asset-Linked Crime]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741dc9c528</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/hong-kong-police-advisory-group-warns-of-surge-in-digital-asset-linked-crime/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T03:37:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Hong Kong Technology Crime Police Advisory Group has warned about the rise of digital asset-linked crime, calling for the establishment of a regulatory system to identify and eliminate risks associated with this tech. According to police data, almost $550 million was involved in digital asset crimes during 2023, with 90% of these cases involving […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dapper Labs Agrees to $4M Settlement in Class Action Securities Suit]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741dcb3b33</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/06/04/dapper-labs-agrees-to-4m-settlement-in-class-action-securities-suit/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T03:22:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dapper Labs has reached a tentative settlement agreement with a group of investors who sued the non-fungible token (NFT) company and its co-founder and CEO Roham Gharegozlou for allegedly violating federal securities laws.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cheyenne Ligon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bull Michael Saylor To Pay $40M And Settle Tax Fraud Lawsuit – Details]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741db52258</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/microstrategy-bitcoin-btc-michael-saylor-to-pay-40m/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T03:04:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to Bloomberg, Michael Saylor, the chairman of business intelligence software company MicroStrategy and a Bitcoin (BTC) bull, has agreed to pay $40 million to settle a tax fraud lawsuit. 
 
The lawsuit, filed by the attorney general’s office in Washington, D.C., accused Saylor of evading over $25 million in income taxes despite living in Washington for over a decade.
 
MicroStrategy’s Saylor Resolves Tax Evasion Allegations
 
In August 2022, the lawsuit alleged that Michael Saylor had “knowingly evaded tax payments,” a claim which he vehemently denied at the time, stating that he was a Florida resident. 
 
Interestingly, according to an official statement, the settlement reached is considered the largest income tax recovery in the District of Columbia’s history. However, as stated…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dubai Financial Services Authority Updates Regulatory Framework for Crypto Tokens]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741db6d52f</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/dubai-financial-services-authority-updates-regulatory-framework-for-crypto-tokens/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T02:46:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Dubai Financial Services Authority (DFSA) announced amendments to its crypto token regime on Monday, enhancing the regulatory environment for crypto tokens in the Dubai International Financial Centre (DIFC), a special economic zone. The amendments address investment in recognized and unrecognized crypto tokens, custody and staking of crypto tokens, compliance with financial crime regulations including […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s Next Leap:: Billionaire Points To $500,000 Per BTC—Here’s When & How]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741db2e3a1</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoins-next-leap-billionaire-predicts-500000-btc/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T02:06:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chamath Palihapitiya, a well-known billionaire investor, has joined the dialogue about future Bitcoin Halving events and their implications for the asset in the long term.
 
According to the Billionaire, this notable event that occurs in the Bitcoin ecosystem every four years could propel Bitcoin’s value to as high as $500,000 in the upcoming years, and here’s how.
 
 
Post-Halving Price Movements: A Historical Insight
 
The premier cryptocurrency has historically shown significant price movements post-halving, with most substantial gains typically occurring 12 to 18 months after the event.
 
Palihapitiya points out that while the price tends to show modest increases initially, substantial surges have followed previous Halvings. For instance, the first Halving led to a more than tenfold in…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[India Repatriates 100 Tonnes of Gold From UK, Aims to Move More]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741dbdc382</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/india-repatriates-100-tonnes-of-gold-from-uk-aims-to-move-more/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T01:37:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to local media reports, the Reserve Bank of India has repatriated 100 tonnes of gold that was held in the vaults of the Bank of England. The operation, carried out in special circumstances due to the quantity of gold moved, may be repeated as India seeks to hold more gold domestically for logistical reasons […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Australia’s First Spot Bitcoin ETF With Direct Holdings Officially Begins Trading]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741dbfb975</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/markets/australias-first-spot-bitcoin-etf-with-direct-holdings-officially-begins-trading"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T01:18:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Australia now officially has its first spot Bitcoin ETF that directly holds BTC. The Monochrome Asset Management's Bitcoin ETF (IBTC) just began trading as the Cboe Australia exchange opened. Trading under the ticker IBTC, the ETF carries a management fee of 0.98%.

BREAKING: 🇦🇺 Australia's first spot #Bitcoin ETF to hold #BTC directly officially begins trading. pic.twitter.com/k4OPyPDm5O
— Bitcoin Magazine (@BitcoinMagazine) June 4, 2024
  
  
  
This milestone makes IBTC the first fund in the country to offer direct Bitcoin holdings, providing investors with straightforward access to BTC. This new product stands apart from the two existing spot Bitcoin ETFs in Australia, which provide exposure to spot Bitcoin without holding Bitcoin directly. Monochrome's ETF fills this gap, by providing an ETF that actually holds Bitcoin.
“Before IBTC, Australian investors were only able to invest in ETFs that indirectly hold bitcoin or through offshore bitcoin products, both of which don’t benefit from the investor protection rules under the directly held crypto asset Australian Financial Services Licensing (AFSL) licensing regime,” the company stated.
This development in Australia follows the successful launch of spot Bitcoin ETFs in the United States earlier this year. These ETFs have seen considerable success, reflecting strong investor interest and confidence in Bitcoin. Additionally, Bitcoin ETPs have gone live on the London Stock Exchange, and Bitcoin Exchange-Traded Commodities (ETCs) have gone live in Germany as well, further highlighting the global trend towards accessible Bitcoin investment products.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nik Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Conviction Barely Dents His Odds of Winning Election: Prediction Markets]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741db8731a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/news-analysis/2024/06/03/trump-conviction-barely-dents-his-odds-of-winning-election-prediction-markets/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T01:10:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus: Polymarket traders doubt Trump will go to prison; Kalshi bettors are at odds with the CME FedWatch poll on rate cuts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Major Milestone: Hong Kong Regulator Approves 11 Crypto Exchanges To Operate In The City]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741db8bf88</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/hong-kong-regulator-approves-11-crypto-exchanges/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T01:06:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Hong Kong Securities and Futures Commission (SFC) has recently granted initial approval to 11 cryptocurrency exchanges to continue operating in the city. 
 
This marks the first step towards issuing virtual asset trading platform (VATP) licenses since 2022. The move comes as Hong Kong aims to establish itself as a prominent crypto hub alongside global counterparts like Singapore and Dubai.
 
Hong Kong’s Crypto Exchange Scene Faces Regulatory Hurdles
 
According to a South China Morning Post report, among the approved exchanges, Crypto.com, originally founded in Hong Kong and now operating from Singapore, stands out as the largest exchange “deemed to be licensed.” 
 
Notably, it is the only exchange within the top 20 by 24-hour trading volume measured by CoinGecko, still seeking a licen…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dapper Labs Reaches $4 Million Settlement in NBA Top Shot NFT Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233621</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233621/dapper-labs-reaches-4-million-settlement-nba-top-shot-nft-lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T23:39:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since the suit’s filing in 2021, Dapper Labs has taken steps to decentralize its NFT ecosystem. Now the class action lawsuit has been settled.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iggy Azalea Goes Full Solana With Mad Lads PFP as MOTHER Nears $90 Million Market Cap]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233633</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233633/iggy-azalea-solana-mad-lads-pfp-mother-nears-90-million"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T23:10:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just days after launching MOTHER, rapper Iggy Azalea donned a custom Mad Lads PFP and continued bull-tweeting the meme coin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global AI Adoption Hits 72%, Generative AI Use Doubles in 2024: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233623</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233623/global-ai-adoption-hits-72-generative-ai-use-doubles-in-2024-report"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T22:45:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study by McKinsey shows Asia and China leading the charge in AI adoption—and lost jobs a fading business priority.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Game On: The Hottest Upcoming Gaming Token Airdrops]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211029</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211029/game-on-hottest-upcoming-gaming-token-airdrops"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T22:34:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATED: Hamster Kombat is the latest Telegram sensation to tease a token, plus details on Illuvium, BloodLoop, Crypto Unicorns, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 129 - ROARING RETURNS, AGAIN!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ABOejLBT/fomo-hour-129-roaring-returns-again</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ABOejLBT/fomo-hour-129-roaring-returns-again"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T21:42:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto bounces, BTC breaks 2-week downtrend. BTC low volatility points to trend continuation. BTC will top at $150k in September 2025: Brandt. $3bn ETH withdrawn from exchanges since ETF. ETH ETF inflows imply ‘base case’ price $5.3k. ETH ETF inflows won’t be like BTC: Fireblocks. BTC logo projected on ECB building. Ethena USDe hits $3bn market cap in 4 months. Maple launches DeFi institutional lending platform. OKX launches in the Netherlands. Matter Labs drops ZK ticker. Linea shuts down chain after hack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 128 - PUMP DOT FUN KEEPS PUMPING!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cziNL3TF/fomo-hour-128-pump-dot-fun-keeps-pumping</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cziNL3TF/fomo-hour-128-pump-dot-fun-keeps-pumping"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T21:41:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto nears break-out then falls on Trump verdict. 13 straight days of BTC ETF inflows, BTC whale accumulation ‘echoes 2020’. Crypto apps next year will onboard millions: Burniske. Elon denies talking crypto policy with Trump. RFK has bought 21 BTC during campaign. TON market cap falls after updating supply data. a16z donates $25m to crypto PAC. Vitalik sends 30ETH to Tornado devs. DBS Bank in Singapore custodies $650m ETH. Backlash grows over zkSync using ZK ticker. Implementing FIT21 a slow process: CFTC. Pierce recommends UK & US cross-border sandbox. Vitalik writes blog on block size wars. Hong Kong government expresses support for web3. Do Kwon & Terraform reach settlement with SEC. Large unlocks for a number of alts next month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Bitcoin Fixes This’: Bitcoiners Take Aim at Berkshire Hathaway Amid Stock Glitch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233613</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233613/bitcoin-fixes-this-berkshire-hathaway-stock-glitch"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T21:41:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An NYSE technical blunder saw Berkshire stock plummet to near zero on Monday, making its price chart look a lot like a rug pull.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roaring Kitty Faces ETrade Ban as GameStop Holdings Surge 48%: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233610</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233610/etrade-ban-roaring-kitty-gamestop-holdings-48-percent-wsj"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T21:15:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The investment firm's financial crimes unit has been engaged, according to the Wall Street Journal, but removing Keith Gill could have repercussions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Kawailani Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There Is a Second Best: Bitcoin Bull Michael Saylor Softens on Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233605</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233605/there-is-second-best-bitcoin-bull-michael-saylor-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T19:52:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the wake of spot Ethereum ETF approvals, the MicroStrategy founder appears to be warming to the notion of a crypto industry bigger than just Bitcoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who Is Roaring Kitty, and What Does His Return Mean for Crypto?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230566</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230566/who-is-roaring-kitty-keith-gill-deepfuckingvalue-back-on-twitter"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T19:04:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATE: Keith Gill's Twitter account came back to life after more than two years, sparking a GameStop stock frenzy. Two weeks later, his Reddit account revealed a big bet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Funds Attract Another $185 Million Amid ETH ETF Hype]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233588</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233588/bitcoin-ethereum-funds-grow-185-million-eth-etf"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T18:26:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto funds worldwide have brought in $15 billion so far this year, with most of the fresh cash flowing into Bitcoin spot ETFs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Donates $25 Million to Fairshake to Defeat 'Anti-Crypto Candidates']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233571</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233571/coinbase-donates-25-million-fairshake-anti-crypto-candidates"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T18:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fairshake has nearly doubled its fundraising haul in recent weeks, to $160 million, following donations from Coinbase, Ripple, and Andreessen Horowitz.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Hamster Kombat’ Daily Combo Guide: How to Earn 5 Million Free Coins in the Telegram Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233516</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/hamster-kombat-daily-combo-guide-earn-5-million-free-coins"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T17:40:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram game Hamster Kombat offers a huge daily bonus of in-game coins ahead of the airdrop. Here’s how to claim it each day.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GME Solana Meme Coin Spikes 150% as Roaring Kitty Revives GameStop Frenzy]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233578</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233578/gme-solana-meme-coin-spikes-150-roaring-kitty-gamestop"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T17:11:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The GameStop tribute token on Solana is up huge alongside GME shares, which jumped due to the return of bull trader Roaring Kitty.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There's More Evidence 'Cryptoqueen' Was Murdered by Drug Kingpin: BBC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233510</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233510/theres-more-evidence-cryptoqueen-was-murdered-by-drug-kingpin-bbc"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T15:56:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new episode of the BBC’s The Missing Cryptoqueen podcast suggests previous reports about her murder are true.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ali Shutler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notcoin Surges 219% With Billions in Trading Volume as TON Reenters Top 10]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233498</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233498/notcoin-surges-billions-trading-volume-ton-top-10"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T15:45:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The token of Telegram-based game Notcoin is skyrocketing, crossing a $2 billion market cap as The Open Network's own Toncoin rises.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop Short Sellers Lose Nearly $1 Billion as GME Surges on Roaring Kitty’s Trades]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233494</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233494/gamestop-short-sellers-lose-nearly-1-billion-as-gme-surges-on-roaring-kittys-trades"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T15:21:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Keith Gill’s Reddit post showed the online influencer held over $200 million worth of GameStop shares and call options.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy and Michael Saylor Reach $40 Million Settlement in DC Tax Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233492</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233492/microstrategy-michael-saylor-40-million-settlement-dc-tax-lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T13:48:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The attorney general said in 2022 that Saylor engaged in a "fraudulent scheme" to avoid paying taxes on "hundreds of millions of dollars in income."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop Nearly Doubles in Pre-Market Trading as Roaring Kitty Returns Again]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233474</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233474/gamestop-nearly-doubles-in-pre-market-trading-as-roaring-kitty-returns-again"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T11:50:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a Reddit post, Keith Gill's DeepFuckingValue account shared a screenshot showing a $200 million GME whale position.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matter Labs Pulls ZK Trademark Application After Backlash]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233461</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233461/matter-labs-pulls-zk-trademark-application-after-backlash"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T10:56:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The firm abandoned its trademark application for the term "ZK," short for "zero-knowledge," following pushback from competitors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spider-Verse Producer Promises to Never Use Generative AI in Franchise]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233462</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233462/spider-verse-producer-promises-to-never-use-generative-ai-in-franchise"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T10:05:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA['Spider-verse' producer Chris Miller said he doesn't want to "steal the generic plagiarized average of other artists’ work.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ali Shutler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Runes Resurgence? Why Asia’s Institutional Investors Could Fuel Growth]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233430</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233430/bitcoin-runes-resurgence-asia-institutional-investors"/>
        <updated>2024-06-02T20:07:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bitcoin meme coin protocol cooled off quickly after its explosive debut. But institutional investors in Asia are uniquely optimistic about Runes' long-term potential.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz,NFT Dudu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Hamster Kombat? The Telegram Crypto Game and Airdrop]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233407</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-hamster-kombat-telegram-game-token-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2024-06-02T16:59:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hamster Kombat is the latest Telegram-based crypto game to go viral, just like Notcoin. Here's what you need to know.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week on Crypto Twitter: Celebrities Dive (Back) Into Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233386</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233386/this-week-on-crypto-twitter-celebrity-crypto-meme-coins"/>
        <updated>2024-06-02T16:08:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In fueling meme coin madness, Caitlyn Jenner and Iggy Azalea turn out to be utter degens.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum ETFs May Have Ended the SEC’s War on Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233357</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233357/ethereum-etfs-may-have-ended-sec-war-crypto"/>
        <updated>2024-06-02T14:01:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC might have just undermined its own anti-crypto legal arguments by approving spot Ethereum ETFs. Attorney Carlo D'Angelo explains why.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carlo D’Angelo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Crypto Games: 'Notcoin' Hits $1 Billion, 'Hamster Kombat' Token, Tickle-to-Earn]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233288</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233288/this-week-crypto-games-notcoin-hamster-kombat-token-tickle"/>
        <updated>2024-06-02T13:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Catch up on this week’s biggest crypto and NFT gaming news and find some weekend reads in our latest roundup.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Caitlyn Jenner Dives Into the World of Memes As Bitcoin and Ethereum Lay Flat]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233112</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233112/this-week-in-coins-caitlyn-jenner-meme-coins-bitcoin-ethereum-flat"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T16:31:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While the top tokens held steady, meme coin movements tracked some crazy headlines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI ‘Opens Up the Field’ for Filmmakers: AIFA Awards Founders]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233236</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233236/ai-opens-field-filmmakers-aifa-awards-founders"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T16:01:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The awards at NFC Lisbon accompanied the launch of the AI Film Academy, aimed at “democratizing the film industry.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI Board Defends CEO Sam Altman Amid ‘Toxic Culture’ Claims]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233372</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233372/openai-toxic-culture-former-current-board-members-argue"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T01:53:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former OpenAI board members claimed there was “psychological abuse,” but their replacements say Altman was “consistently collegial.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[President Biden Vetoes Pro-Crypto Resolution, Defends SEC's Judgement]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233358</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233358/biden-veto-sab-121-resolution"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T23:30:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The White House said the bipartisan-passed bill would “jeopardize the well-being of consumers and investors.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Kawailani Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin Explains Why ‘Big Blockers’ Lost the Bitcoin Scaling Wars]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233339</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233339/vitalik-buterin-on-why-big-blockers-lost-the-bitcoin-scaling-wars"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T22:01:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum’s creator says the best way to prevent future disputes will require new technologies like ZK-SNARKs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Franklin Templeton Reveals Ethereum ETF Fee]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233336</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233336/franklin-templeton-reveals-ethereum-etf-fee"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T21:14:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The global asset manager will charge investors 0.19%, in line with the low fees in the competitive spot Bitcoin ETF race.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Caitlyn Jenner Releasing a Meme Coin Is Riskier Than Kim Kardashian Shilling Ethereum Max, Legal Experts Say]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233315</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233315/caitlyn-jenner-meme-coin-risk-kim-kardashian-ethereum-max"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T20:34:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week wasn’t the first time a Kardashian-linked token turned heads in crypto, but the stakes could be higher this time around.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Runes Are Back? Meme Coin Surge Pushes Market Cap Over $2 Billion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233318</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233318/bitcoin-runes-back-meme-coin-surge-2-billion"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T19:44:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the last week, the value of assets on the Runes protocol for Bitcoin meme coins has doubled—and DOG is leading the charge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Should Join UK in ‘Blockchain Sandbox’ Free of Regulatory Meddling, SEC Commissioner Says]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233170</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233170/blockchain-regulatory-sandbox-us-uk-hester-peirce-unikely"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T19:14:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Commissioner Hester Peirce says a safe space for blockchain experimentation could foster better crypto regulations—but experts doubt it will happen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Ethereum Meme Coin Price Hits New High After Post-Verdict Dip]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233310</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233310/trump-ethereum-meme-coin-price-new-high"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T18:52:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Donald Trump-themed MAGA meme coin surged late Thursday after a short-lived crash prompted by his “hush money” trial verdict.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Bitcoin Game Boy’ Gets a Runes Makeover—Here’s How to Win One]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233296</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233296/bitcoin-game-boy-runes-makeover-giveaway"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T17:52:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The BitBoy One is a Bitcoin-centric gaming handheld, and a new limited-edition Runes model gives it a sleek overhaul.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Next Notcoin? Telegram-Based Game ‘Hamster Kombat’ to Launch Token on TON]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233287</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233287/next-notcoin-telegram-game-hamster-kombat-open-network-token"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T17:10:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hamster Kombat, another tap-to-earn game akin to Notcoin—and based around a hamster CEO—is launching a token on The Open Network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 127 - CELEB COINS CRASH!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mGbE2GHV/fomo-hour-127-celeb-coins-crash</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mGbE2GHV/fomo-hour-127-celeb-coins-crash"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T20:28:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NYSE to launch BTC options. CME has ‘no plans’ to offer SOL futures. Stablecoin market cap rises to 2 year high. Inflation below 3.3% ‘means BTC ATH’. Crypto market cap heading to $200T: Yat Siu. Gemini recovers $2.2bn for Earn users. PayPal stablecoin will offer ‘confidential transfers’. Mastercard launches Crypto Credential pilot on BTC. Layer Zero launches on SOL. L2s are cultural extensions of ETH: Vitalik. FTX’s Salame says he will share story. SEI announces 27m SEI airdrop. ASI merger complete, to launch June 13th.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 126 - MEMECOIN MADNESS!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/eA3xqKLr/fomo-hour-126-memecoin-madness</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/eA3xqKLr/fomo-hour-126-memecoin-madness"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T21:30:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock ETF flips Grayscale in size. BTC ETFs see 11 straight days of inflows. ZKasino gives 72hours for ETH withdrawals. ENS to migrate to L2. ADA drops out of top 10 coins. Salame sentenced to 7.5 years in jail. Riot Platforms attempts takeover of Bitfarms. Ripple donates $25m to Fairshake PAC. Pump(.)fun launches live streaming. Iggy Azelea MOTHER coin leads celeb tokens. Beeple Everyday features many coins. Runes bounce, DOG hits $560m. PEPE active wallets double during rally. Cristiano Ronaldo launches 4th NFT. Friend Tech announces club wars.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum DN-404 Tokens Are a Sensation in Asia. Are They the West’s Next Big Trend?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/drcV3Zte/ethereum-dn-404-tokens-are-a-sensation-in-asia-are-they-the-wests-next-big-trend</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/drcV3Zte/ethereum-dn-404-tokens-are-a-sensation-in-asia-are-they-the-wests-next-big-trend"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T19:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz and Rug Radio creator Pukerainbow sat down for a conversation with some of the biggest adopters involved in Ethereum’s newest trend: dividing NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Buying Crypto Simplified with Mika]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/Z9rxTcnJ/buying-crypto-simplified-with-mika</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/Z9rxTcnJ/buying-crypto-simplified-with-mika"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T16:54:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the first part of our series turning crypto beginners into crypto pros, Rug Radio creator Mika guides you through the process of purchasing cryptocurrency using crypto exchange Kraken.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 125 - ETH NEARS 4K]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BrgFfEe8/fomo-hour-125-eth-nears-4k</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BrgFfEe8/fomo-hour-125-eth-nears-4k"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T17:40:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH leads rally on continued bullish ETF sentiment. Previous anti-crypto Trump comments highlighted. Wave of influencers and celebrities hacked, release coins. Phantom becomes no.1 finance app in the US. Argentina & El Salvador hold talks on BTC adoption. LINK to have large announcement on May 30th. PEPE, MOG, TURBO, TRUMP hit ATHs in ETH memes. MOG up 60%, mentioned in Beeple Everyday. Caitlyn Jenner hacker releases JENNER coin. Garga outlines future plans for BAYC. Friend Tech founder offers $200k to migrate off Base.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 124 - THE ETH ETF IS APPROVED!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5ELzjWt4/fomo-hour-124-the-eth-etf-is-approved</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5ELzjWt4/fomo-hour-124-the-eth-etf-is-approved"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T18:43:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH ETFs get approved 19b-4 forms. ETFs won’t trade until July or August: Galaxy. ETF means many coins not securities: Coinbase CLO. Coinbase relists XRP in US. SOL ETF coming: Scaramucci. US House passes vote to ban CBDC. Building a pro-crypto army in congress: Sen. Lummis. Polymarket backlash over if ETH ETF truly approved. Expect ETH ETFs to be 10-15% of BTC: Bloomberg. BTC ETFs see $1.75bn inflows over 9 days. BTC to $150k in 2024 is base case: Tom Lee. ETH co-founder moves $37m ETH to exchanges. Grayscale launches trusts for STX & NEAR. Coinbase loses against SEC on DOGE sweepstakes. ALGO ad attacks BTC, SOL, ETH. Phantom now no.2 finance App on Google Play.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 123 - ETHEREUM KEEPS GOING!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JE3lB00G/fomo-hour-123-ethereum-keeps-going</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JE3lB00G/fomo-hour-123-ethereum-keeps-going"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T15:43:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH soars, ETF S1 approvals expected in hours. US house greenlights FIT21 bill with broad support. Gensler says SEC already has rules for crypto. Hong Kong set to allow ETH staking for ETFs. ETH OI continues to soar. SOL mentioned as next ETF candidate on CNBC. SOL ETF will take years: Bloomberg. MetaMask plans BTC integration. Fed says only 7% of Americans own crypto. SBF heads to a new prison. Hong Kong orders WLD shutdown. TON added to Binance ahead of potential listing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 122 - ETH ETF MOVES CLOSER!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/FlTuDkm9/fomo-hour-122-eth-etf-moves-closer</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/FlTuDkm9/fomo-hour-122-eth-etf-moves-closer"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T16:33:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH ETFs move closer to approval, drop staking. Blackrock ETF see biggest inflow in 6 weeks. Grayscale ETH discount narrows under 10%. BTC & ETH heading for ATH: StanChart. Banana zone squared coming for ETH: Raoul Pal. Trump accepts crypto donations including DOGE. Pelosi mulls support of crypto bill. Farcaster raises $150M, DEGEN up 20%. Coinbase to launch gold & oil futures trading. Uniswap ‘ready to fight’ against SEC. Vitalik proposes solutions to MEV problems. Phantom may soon support email sign-up. Jupiter announces initiative to tokenise RWAs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 121 - ETHEREUM GOD CANDLES!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/EE1S4Hf4/fomo-hour-121-ethereum-god-candles</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/EE1S4Hf4/fomo-hour-121-ethereum-god-candles"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T16:17:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH ETF suddenly seems likely, flurry of amendments. ETH biggest daily gain ever, gains SOL market cap. ETF approval shifted due to political pressure. ETF approval may come as soon as tomorrow. Squeeze liquidates $230M of shorts. ETH OI hits record of $14B on exchanges. BTC nears ATH amid 6th straight day of ETF inflows. SOL flips ETH in Google search trends. House Democrats will not whip against crypto bills. Anti-crypto FDIC chair Gruenberg to step-down. Grayscale CEO steps down, ETHE discount narrows. Genesis settles for $2B with creditors. Binance to focus launchpad on higher float projects. SEI v2 launch coming next week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Do A Little With Chikai]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BGCnTbKb/we-do-a-little-with-chikai</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BGCnTbKb/we-do-a-little-with-chikai"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T18:21:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week’s episode, we sit down with our good friend and one of the biggest supporters of the pod, Chikai Ohazama. Chikai is the co-founder of Keyhole which was acquired by Google and became Google Earth. He is one of the most caring art collectors in our space, as well as an extremely talented AI artist.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 120 - SOLANA LEADS THE CHARGE]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/7jrsiszc/fomo-hour-120-solana-leads-the-charge</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/7jrsiszc/fomo-hour-120-solana-leads-the-charge"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T18:08:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SOL again leads majors, DEX volume dwarfs others. BTC whales buys $106M in 24hrs. ETH ETF decision on Thursday or Friday. 5 of 7 onchain indicators ‘point to bull-run’. ETH ETF may be rejected due to weak link to futures. AI coins in focus ahead of Nvidia earnings. Cobie inks new article on low float, high FDV coins. ETH foundation staff reveal links to EigenLayer. 12 L2 & L3s controlled by single multisig. Layer Zero pauses sybil rewards. Aevo to airdrop pre-launch tokens on platform. FTM to migrate one-to-one to Sonic S coin. UK judge rules Craig Wright is not Satoshi.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 119 - GOOD MORNING BULLS!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ikMRioZH/fomo-hour-119-good-morning-bulls</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ikMRioZH/fomo-hour-119-good-morning-bulls"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T11:02:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SOL leads majors higher again, BTC stable. ETFs see $257M inflow, volumes hit 2 month high. 414 holders of BlackRock ETF ‘blows away record’. SOL continues to be fastest blockage despite usage. Pump. fun exploited for $1.9M by ex-employee. LINK up 20% after partnership with top banks. Senate also repeals SEC crypto rule. US Senator uses laser eyes PFP. Tether mints another $1B USDT. Bitcoin production costs now $45K: JP Morgan. Pink Drainer retires after stealing $85m assets. PancakeSwap to reimburse fees on Uniswap. TON & Tether partnership on payment solution. Trabucco writes character defence of Ryan Salame.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 118 - ARE THE ETFS BACK?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/KJXI4MVU/fomo-hour-118-are-the-etfs-back</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/KJXI4MVU/fomo-hour-118-are-the-etfs-back"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T11:02:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin has best day in 2 months after dovish CPI. ETFs see $300M inflow, highest in weeks. ETH continues to underperform ahead of ETF ruling. Millennium buys $2B of BTC ETF. CME group to launch BTC spot trading. Fed’s Kashkari compares BTC to beanie babies. Tate says he will buy $100M BTC. El Salvador now owns 5750 BTC. Binance creates ‘antidote’ to address poisoning. Tornado Cash developer appeals conviction. China busts $1.9B USDT banking racket. MEV bot operators charged with fraud by DoJ. Swiss to adopt global crypto tax rules. FTX repayments create ‘bullish overhang’ for crypto. SEI up 30% after proposing v2 upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 117 - BITCOIN GAINS ON CPI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JMdi3Lp7/fomo-hour-117-bitcoin-gains-on-cpi</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JMdi3Lp7/fomo-hour-117-bitcoin-gains-on-cpi"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T11:02:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC bounces driven by spot buying. US ETF sees $100M+ inflow for first time in weeks. State of Wisconsin buys $170M of BTC ETF. Vanguard appoints Bitcoin friendly CEO. Coinbase sees billions of BTC leave exchange. BTC to consolidate between $55-75K: Novogratz. SOL beats ETH TEV for first time ever. ETH may be labelled a security by SEC next week. AI & memes the only two positive sectors this week. Crypto hostility led by TradFi: Lubin. Tornado Cash developer guilty of money laundering. Circle shifts legal hope to US ahead of IPO. Cypher developer gambled $300K of customer funds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 116 - ROARING KITTY RETURNS!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cXfQ3AJh/fomo-hour-116-roaring-kitty-returns</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cXfQ3AJh/fomo-hour-116-roaring-kitty-returns"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T11:02:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto falls, stays in range ahead of CPI tomorrow. US ETFs see small net inflow led by Fidelity HK ETFs wipe 2 weeks of inflows in a single day. Bracebridge bought $363m of BTC ETFs. Coinbase has system wide outage. Poloniex hacker sends funds to Tornado Cash. Brazil biggest in LATAM for crypto trading. Biden removes China BTC miner near military base. CertiK patches $5m flaw in Aptos bridge. LayerZero sees 100k bot accounts self-report. DYDX CEO set to leave. Tate sells $500k BTC to buy GME.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Do A Little With  Roger Dickerman]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/F6mt1fXu/we-do-a-little-with-roger-dickerman</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/F6mt1fXu/we-do-a-little-with-roger-dickerman"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T14:38:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week’s episode, we sit down with our good friend and founder of the 24 Hours of Art, Roger Dickerman. We dive into Roger’s background in trading and fitness, his love of art, founding Artifex and 24 Hours of Art, the power of routines, and so much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Do A Little With Funghi]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9USXAFZb/we-do-a-little-with-funghi</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9USXAFZb/we-do-a-little-with-funghi"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T13:44:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week’s episode, we sit down with our good friend and co-founder of Shillr, Funghibull. Funghi is one of our favorite collectors, builders and overall people in the space. 

We dive into Funghi’s background playing rugby, going to medical school in Scotland, 10 gram mushroom trips, finding punks, forming Shillr, and so much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mika Breaks Down Solana Congestion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/5lkvPCM1/mika-breaks-down-solana-congestion</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/5lkvPCM1/mika-breaks-down-solana-congestion"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T10:12:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rug Radio Creator and crypto influencer Mika explains what happened during Solana's Q1 2024 network congestion through Kraken's Learn Center.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>