<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-08-11T21:11:45.671Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-08-11T21:11:45.671Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scientists used AI to find and track 95K ‘cryptocurrency free giveaway’ scams on Twitter]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18832914/Scientists-used-AI-to-find-and-track-95K-cryptocurrency-free-giveaway-scams-on-Twitter</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18832914/Scientists-used-AI-to-find-and-track-95K-cryptocurrency-free-giveaway-scams-on-Twitter"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The San Diego State University team uncovered nearly a million dollars were scammed from victims via the Lists feature on Twitter — now called X.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BREAKING: FTX Founder Sam Bankman-Fried Locked Up For Evidence Tampering]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755db6145c</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ftx-founder-bankman-fried-locked-evidence-tampering/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T20:51:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a stunning turn of events, FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried has been ordered to await trial behind bars after a bail hearing revealed alleged attempts to influence witnesses against him, according to a recent report by the St. Louis Post. 
 
The decision, made by US District Judge Lewis A. Kaplan, came after prosecutors presented evidence suggesting Bankman-Fried had engaged in harassment tactics, including disclosing the private writings of a key witness to a journalist.
 
FTX Founder Sentenced To Jail
 
Bankman-Fried, a 31-year-old cryptocurrency entrepreneur, had been under house arrest at his parent’s residence in Palo Alto, California, since his extradition from the Bahamas in December.
 
 
Facing charges of defrauding investors and diverting millions of dollars worth of cryptocurrenc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former FTX CEO Arrives New York For Hearing To Determine If He Will Be Jailed Until Trial]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755db61457</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/former-ftx-ceo-arrives-new-york/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T20:51:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried, Founder and CEO of the insolvent crypto exchange FTX, has made a return to New York City amidst intensifying legal pressures. 
 
Bankman-Fried’s arrival in New York comes as prosecutors push for his incarceration and the cryptocurrency exchange founder awaits a court hearing in the Manhattan federal court on Friday, August 11, to determine his fate on getting jail term while he awaits trial. 
 
Prosecutors Allege Witness Intimidation by FTX CEO
 
Sam Bankman-Fried’s return to New York follows a request by prosecutors to Judge Lewis A. Kaplan to withdraw the former FTX CEO’s bail. The request stated that Bankman-Fried violated court rules by “harassing a key witness” against his upcoming trial. 
 
According to prosecutors, Bankman-Fried attempted to ruin Caroline Ellison’…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Custodia Bank Now Accepting US Dollar Deposits, Adding Bitcoin Custody]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152245</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152245/custodia-bank-now-accepting-us-dollar-deposits-adding-bitcoin-custody"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T20:50:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“The bar is very high for banks to launch, and we cleared it," Custodia Bank CEO Caitlin Long told Decrypt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BREAKING: Bankman-Fried sent to jail after judge revokes bail]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18832907/BREAKING-Bankman-Fried-sent-to-jail-after-judge-revokes-bail</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18832907/BREAKING-Bankman-Fried-sent-to-jail-after-judge-revokes-bail"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T20:49:35.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Rise of Ally Crypto: Why You Should Start Investing Now]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18832910/The-Rise-of-Ally-Crypto-Why-You-Should-Start-Investing-Now</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18832910/The-Rise-of-Ally-Crypto-Why-You-Should-Start-Investing-Now"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T20:44:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As ally crypto continues to gain traction in the crypto investment space, it's definitely worth taking a closer look. By understanding the benefits, risks, and mechanics of the allied crypto ecosystem, you'll be in a better position to make informed investment decisions that align with your...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Federal Reserve Goes Broke as Debt Rises $5.2B a Day?! | Bitcoin's Time to Shine!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18832923/Federal-Reserve-Goes-Broke-as-Debt-Rises-52B-a-Day-Bitcoins-Time-to-Shine</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18832923/Federal-Reserve-Goes-Broke-as-Debt-Rises-52B-a-Day-Bitcoins-Time-to-Shine"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T20:44:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jerome Powell the Chairman of the Federal Reserve lost all muscle control when asked a simple question, "Why 2% inflation, how does that help people?” The government must steal from you but can't explain why as they are adding $5,200,000,000 to the government debt per day! Presidential Candidate...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Boss Sam Bankman-Fried in Custody, Bail Revoked, Remanded to Jail]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755db6d544</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ftx-boss-sam-bankman-fried-in-custody-bail-revoked-remanded-to-jail/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T20:43:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FTX co-founder Sam Bankman-Fried was taken into custody and his bail was rescinded on Friday, in anticipation of his trial scheduled for October. Matthew Russell Lee of the Inner City Press disclosed a synopsis of the August 11 hearing on the social media outlet X, where Bankman-Fried’s legal counsel revealed that the attorneys intended to challenge the ruling. However, despite these intentions, Bankman-Fried was subsequently taken into custody by the U.S. Marshals.
 
Sam Bankman-Fried Remanded to Jail After Bail Revocation
 
In the past fortnight, the legal team prosecuting the case against Sam Bankman-Fried has been striving to incarcerate the former FTX CEO on grounds of suspected witness tampering. Bankman-Fried disseminated selected passages from an online journal penned by former Ala…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Team's Cryptic 'Soon' Message Sparks Speculation]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18832924/Shiba-Inu-Teams-Cryptic-Soon-Message-Sparks-Speculation</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18832924/Shiba-Inu-Teams-Cryptic-Soon-Message-Sparks-Speculation"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T20:42:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Shiba Inu cryptocurrency team has ignited waves of speculation with a single cryptic tweet, "Soon ™️" as the digital coin sees a market capitalization surge]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Seeks to 'Usurp Congress's Authority' in Coinbase Lawsuit: Blockchain Association]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152239</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152239/sec-seeks-to-usurp-congresss-authority-in-coinbase-lawsuit-blockchain-association"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T20:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["The SEC is trying to short-circuit the legislative process" the consortium of crypto associations argued in its court brief.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Scammy Dumpster Fire'—Overwatch 2 Steam Debut Review Bombed Into Oblivion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152231</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152231/scammy-dumpster-fire-overwatch-2-steam-debut-review-bombed-oblivion"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T20:37:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over 47,000 negative player reviews have taken Blizzard to task for various complaints, from the free-to-play model to the missing PvE mode.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Scammy Dumpster Fire'—Overwatch 2 Steam Debut Review Bombed Into Oblivion]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18832909/Scammy-Dumpster-FireOverwatch-2-Steam-Debut-Review-Bombed-Into-Oblivion</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18832909/Scammy-Dumpster-FireOverwatch-2-Steam-Debut-Review-Bombed-Into-Oblivion"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T20:37:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over 47,000 negative player reviews have taken Blizzard to task for various complaints, from the free-to-play model to the missing PvE mode.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Ethereum’s integration with Visa can ease things for ETH holders]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18832894/How-Ethereums-integration-with-Visa-can-ease-things-for-ETH-holders</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18832894/How-Ethereums-integration-with-Visa-can-ease-things-for-ETH-holders"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T20:30:12.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Santiment Highlights Newly Observed Data For Chainlink (LINK)]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18832886/Santiment-Highlights-Newly-Observed-Data-For-Chainlink-LINK</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18832886/Santiment-Highlights-Newly-Observed-Data-For-Chainlink-LINK"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T20:28:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency analysis firm Santiment and analyst Ali Martinez commented on the emerging data for Chainlink. Continue Reading: Santiment Highlights Newly Observed Data For Chainlink (LINK)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Invests $10 Million in Helio, Partners With Liquid for KYC]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18832884/Binance-Invests-10-Million-in-Helio-Partners-With-Liquid-for-KYC</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18832884/Binance-Invests-10-Million-in-Helio-Partners-With-Liquid-for-KYC"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T20:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance, the largest cryptocurrency exchange in the world, recently disclosed that Binance Labs, its venture arm, has invested in the decentralized finance (DeFi) platform Helio Protocol. With the liquid staking becoming increasingly popular, the crypto exchange believes its investment in Helio...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Price analysis 8/11: BTC, ETH, BNB, XRP, DOGE, ADA, SOL, MATIC, LTC, DOT]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18832873/Price-analysis-811-BTC-ETH-BNB-XRP-DOGE-ADA-SOL-MATIC-LTC-DOT</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18832873/Price-analysis-811-BTC-ETH-BNB-XRP-DOGE-ADA-SOL-MATIC-LTC-DOT"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T20:19:23.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BREAKING: FTX Founder Sam Bankman-Fried Locked Up For Evidence Tampering]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18832854/BREAKING-FTX-Founder-Sam-Bankman-Fried-Locked-Up-For-Evidence-Tampering</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18832854/BREAKING-FTX-Founder-Sam-Bankman-Fried-Locked-Up-For-Evidence-Tampering"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T20:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a stunning turn of events, FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried has been ordered to await trial behind bars after a bail hearing revealed alleged attempts to influence witnesses against him, according to a recent report by the St. Louis Post. The decision, made by US District Judge Lewis A. Kaplan,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former FTX CEO Arrives New York For Hearing To Determine If He Will Be Jailed Until Trial]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18832855/Former-FTX-CEO-Arrives-New-York-For-Hearing-To-Determine-If-He-Will-Be-Jailed-Until-Trial</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18832855/Former-FTX-CEO-Arrives-New-York-For-Hearing-To-Determine-If-He-Will-Be-Jailed-Until-Trial"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T20:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried, Founder and CEO of the insolvent crypto exchange FTX, has made a return to New York City amidst intensifying legal pressures. Bankman-Fried’s arrival in New York comes as prosecutors push for his incarceration and the cryptocurrency exchange founder awaits a court hearing in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Argentina’s Data Privacy Agency Investigating Controversial Crypto Project Worldcoin (WLD)]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18832837/Argentinas-Data-Privacy-Agency-Investigating-Controversial-Crypto-Project-Worldcoin-WLD</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18832837/Argentinas-Data-Privacy-Agency-Investigating-Controversial-Crypto-Project-Worldcoin-WLD"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T20:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Argentina’s data privacy government agency is following in France and the United Kingdom’s footsteps by investigating the eye-scanning crypto project Worldcoin (WLD). The Agency of Access to Public Information (AAIP) says in a new press release it’s looking into how the Worldcoin Foundation...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Curve Finance Resurgence: 70% Of Stolen Funds Recovered, Redemption On The Horizon]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18832836/Curve-Finance-Resurgence-70-Of-Stolen-Funds-Recovered-Redemption-On-The-Horizon</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18832836/Curve-Finance-Resurgence-70-Of-Stolen-Funds-Recovered-Redemption-On-The-Horizon"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T20:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Curve Finance (CRV), a leading decentralized finance (DeFi) protocol, announced significant progress in its recovery efforts following a recent hack that resulted in losing $73.5 million across several projects within its factory pools.  The attack on July 30 exploited a critical security flaw...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Analyst Breaks Down Bitcoin (BTC) and XRP, Doubles Down on Bull Run Prediction]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18832838/Crypto-Analyst-Breaks-Down-Bitcoin-BTC-and-XRP-Doubles-Down-on-Bull-Run-Prediction</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18832838/Crypto-Analyst-Breaks-Down-Bitcoin-BTC-and-XRP-Doubles-Down-on-Bull-Run-Prediction"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T19:55:29.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US-China AI Tech Race Sparks Tensions and Regulatory Reactions Globally]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18832842/US-China-AI-Tech-Race-Sparks-Tensions-and-Regulatory-Reactions-Globally</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18832842/US-China-AI-Tech-Race-Sparks-Tensions-and-Regulatory-Reactions-Globally"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T19:54:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The rapid advancement of high-level artificial intelligence (AI) technology has ignited a competitive race between...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Lawyers Confident in Ripple’s Case as SEC’s Appeal Sparks Speculation]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18832841/Crypto-Lawyers-Confident-in-Ripples-Case-as-SECs-Appeal-Sparks-Speculation</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18832841/Crypto-Lawyers-Confident-in-Ripples-Case-as-SECs-Appeal-Sparks-Speculation"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T19:52:42.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Layer 2 Network Base Records Rapid Adoption After Launch]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755dbc0543</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/coinbase-newly-launched-layer-2-network-records/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T19:51:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase’s newly launched layer-2 network, Base, has reached a new all-time high in user base. According to data from Dune Analytics, Base recorded a 30% increase in daily users, exceeding 100,000 a day following its official launch.
 
The Dune Analytics data shows that on August 10, over 136,000 daily users were recorded using the layer 2 network. This figure is the highest ever recorded in Base’s short period of existence.
 
Base Gains More Traction Following Its Public Release
 
Base is an Ethereum-based layer-2 network introduced by crypto exchange Coinbase on February 23. According to the firm, Base offers developers a safe, developer-friendly, and cheaper way to build web3-based applications on-chain.
 
 
The launch of Base’s beta version in February sparked enthusiasm and anticipati…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kent Glory</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Royal Canadian Mounted Police wants a digital asset repository]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18832831/The-Royal-Canadian-Mounted-Police-wants-a-digital-asset-repository</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18832831/The-Royal-Canadian-Mounted-Police-wants-a-digital-asset-repository"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T19:50:22.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Friend.tech a Friend or Foe? A Dive Into the New Social App Driving Millions in Trading Volume]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755dbcaa9c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/web3/2023/08/11/is-friendtech-a-friend-or-foe-a-dive-into-the-new-social-app-driving-millions-in-trading-volume/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T19:44:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new social app has driven over 4,400 ETH ($8.1 million) in trading volume in less than 24 hours since its launch, far surpassing OpenSea’s in the same time frame. But with its mysterious origins, lack of privacy policy and lagging network, it raises some red flags.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cam Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking: Sam Bankman-Fried arrested after bail review]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18832826/Breaking-Sam-Bankman-Fried-arrested-after-bail-review</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18832826/Breaking-Sam-Bankman-Fried-arrested-after-bail-review"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T19:44:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The disgraced blockchain executive was immediately reprimanded after his bail was revoked the same day.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase's Base Blockchain Sees $175M In Transfers, Surpasses Optimism In Daily User Count]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18832830/Coinbases-Base-Blockchain-Sees-175M-In-Transfers-Surpasses-Optimism-In-Daily-User-Count</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18832830/Coinbases-Base-Blockchain-Sees-175M-In-Transfers-Surpasses-Optimism-In-Daily-User-Count"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T19:40:33.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spot Bitcoin ETF Applications Face More Delays]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755dbdaf17</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/spot-bitcoin-etf-applications-face-more-delays/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T19:33:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) on Friday asked for additional public feedback on a proposal to list a spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF), likely delaying any decision on the high-profile applications.
 
SEC Seeks Public Opinion on Spot Bitcoin ETF
 
The SEC put out a 34-page request for comment on the Ark Invest and 21Shares application, seeking views on whether the proposal meets regulatory standards. The move pushes any decision on the bitcoin ETF beyond the initially reported August deadline.
 
The agency asked for public input on concerns around potential manipulation of the proposed ETF and the underlying bitcoin market. It raised questions about whether the CME bitcoin futures market is a “regulated market of significant size” for the spot ETF.
 
The SEC also seeks feedback on the liquidity and efficiency of bitcoin markets and plans for the ETF sponsors to share surveillance data with the agency. “Written data, views, and arguments” are due in 21 days, the request details.
 
 
This marks the latest roadblock for approval of a spot bitcoin ETF after years of applications. The SEC has greenlighted bitcoin futures ETFs but resisted spot funds over worries about manipulation and insufficient regulation of crypto markets.
 
Friday’s request likely extends the long wait for a spot bitcoin ETF, which issuers say would provide a safer way for mainstream investors to gain exposure. The SEC will weigh the new feedback before making any final decision on the Ark and 21Shares application. The senior ETF analyst for Bloomberg, Eric Balchunas, said the SEC move was “pretty standard.”
 
What do you think about the SEC’s request for comment from the public? Share your thoughts and opinions about this subject in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried Is Going to Jail, Judge Revokes Bail Over Witness Tampering]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152210</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152210/sam-bankman-fried-going-to-jail-judge-revokes-bail"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T19:28:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Disgraced FTX CEO Sam Bankman-Fried's bail has been revoked. He will be detained in jail until the start of his criminal trial in October.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried Jailed Ahead of Trial]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755dbe5882</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/08/11/sam-bankman-fried-jailed-ahead-of-trial/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T19:27:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried has been remanded into custody ahead of his October trial on multiple financial crime charges after a federal judge revoked his release on bond.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De, Elizabeth Napolitano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Grand Theft Auto 5 Mod Lets AI NPCs Insult You]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152196</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152196/grand-theft-auto-5-mod-lets-ai-npcs-insult-you"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T19:06:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rockstar's open-world smash gains new life via AI—and the NPCs really have a mind of their own, with one ranting about a "divine AI god."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Troubled Crypto Custodian Prime Trust Might Cut 75% of Jobs: Report]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755db8f14a</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/troubled-crypto-custodian-prime-trust-might-cut-75-of-jobs-report/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T19:01:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prime  
Trust, the beleaguered cryptocurrency custodian, might be on the brink of  
significant job cuts, CoinDesk  
revealed today (Friday), quoting ex-employees. Anonymous sources suggest that  
up to 75% of positions might be at risk, based on insider information.
Layoffs on  
the Horizon?
The news of  
the possible massive downsizing comes as the crypto custodian was recently placed in receivership on the order  
of the Eighth District Court of Nevada. The action trailed the filing by the Nevada Financial Institutions Division (NFID) to freeze  
the custodian’s assets and take over the business.
Earlier,  
the state regulator issued a cease-and-desist  
order against  
Prime Trust, alleging that the company had a “shortfall in customer funds” and  
was using its customers’ funds to mee…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Solomon Oladipupo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Hater Peter Schiff’s Reaction To CPI Data: ‘The Fed Has Lost’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755dba0fd6</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-hater-the-fed-has-lost/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T18:50:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Schiff, a Bitcoin hater and prominent financial analyst renowned for his insights into economic trends, has turned his scrutiny toward the recent United States inflation data, raising questions about the efficacy of the Federal Reserve’s campaign to curb escalating prices. 
 
The Consumer Price Index (CPI), a headline indicator meticulously tracked by economists, exhibited a modest 0.2% uptick in July, contributing to a cumulative inflation rate of 3.2%, a figure slightly below the anticipated 3.3%. 
 
 
Notably recognized for his skeptical stance on Bitcoin and cryptocurrencies as a whole, Schiff asserts that the central bank’s arduous endeavors might be faltering in the face of mounting inflationary pressures.
 
Peter Schiff Challenges Fed’s Inflation Battle
 
Schiff is casting dou…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are You Not Entertained? Elon Musk Says Fight With Zuck Will Be Livestreamed via Twitter, Meta]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152212</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152212/are-you-not-entertained-elon-musk-says-fight-zuck-livestreamed-twitter-meta"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T18:48:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk suggests the clash of the tech titans will happen in "an epic location" in Italy—though he may need surgery first.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Good Luck' Convincing a Jury: Cameron Winklevoss Rebuts DCG Court Filing]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755dbbab58</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/08/11/good-luck-convincing-a-jury-cameron-winklevoss-rebuts-dcg-court-filing/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T18:35:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[His Gemini crypto exchange and conglomerate Digital Currency Group are battling – in and out of court – over the failure of Gemini's Earn lending service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Baker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is The Digital Euro Doomed To Fail? Here’s What The Experts Say]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755da09788</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/digital-euro-doomed-to-fail/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T17:51:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The impending launch of a digital version of the euro has been a topic of much discussion in recent years. Seen as a European answer to the rise of digital currencies and an attempt to modernize its monetary system, the European Union’s commitment towards a digital euro has garnered both anticipation and skepticism. 
 
With the global race to launch central bank digital currencies (CBDCs) heating up, European economists are raising eyebrows over the design and intent of the European Central Bank’s (ECB) approach to their Central Bank Digital Currency (CBDC).
 
Questionable Design Choices
 
Many financial experts and academics closely observing this journey have expressed concerns over whether the project will truly cater to the public or primarily serve banking intermediaries. A report fro…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visa Eyes Mass Adoption of Crypto by Testing On-Chain Gas Fee Payment Through Fiat]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755da13d5f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/08/11/visa-eyes-mass-adoption-of-crypto-by-testing-method-of-paying-on-chain-gas-fees-through-fiat/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T17:45:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visa says managing ether (ETH) balance to cover gas fees is “burdensome” and too complex, according to a blog post.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Base’s Rapid Ascent: 136,000 Daily Users and $175 Million TVL in Ethereum’s L2 Defi Space]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755da2800c</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bases-rapid-ascent-136000-daily-users-and-175-million-tvl-in-ethereums-l2-defi-space/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T17:35:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Base, the Ethereum layer two (L2) scaling solution supported by Coinbase, has experienced over $175 million funneled into its decentralized finance (defi) protocol since its creation. The majority of value locked comprises 75,244 ether and nearly $26 million worth of the USDC stablecoin.
 
Coinbase’s Base Grows to $175 Million TVL
 
As one of the pioneer publicly-listed firms to roll out its own L2 blockchain, Coinbase’s Base has witnessed consistent growth. On July 30, 2023, daily active Base users reached 55,417 and surged to an all-time high of 136,047 just 11 days later. This surpassed L2 Optimism’s 114,736 daily active users on the same day.
 
Unlike Coinbase’s Base protocol, Optimism’s usage also benefited from the Worldcoin launch since its native asset WLD resides on the L2 network…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried Could Go Back to Jail Thanks to His Big Fat Mouth]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755da3b7dc</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/08/11/sam-bankman-fried-could-go-back-to-jail-thanks-to-his-big-fat-mouth/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T17:24:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fallen FTX founder didn’t just violate his bail — he violated the trust of his family’s last remaining allies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Z. Morris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There’s More Evidence ChatGPT Is a Good Doctor But a Bad Coder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152107</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152107/chatgpt-good-doctor-bad-coder"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T17:13:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two research papers evaluating ChatGPT's accuracy conclude that the AI chatbot seems to be better at writing prescriptions than writing code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PayPal’s Stablecoin Is No Libra. Why the Timing Feels Right]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755daed1c7</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/08/11/paypals-stablecoin-is-no-libra-why-the-timing-feels-right/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T16:59:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like Facebook's ill-fated Libra project, PYUSD is getting some pushback in Washington D.C. But its prospects seem more promising, says Michael J. Casey.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael J. Casey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Delays ARK Invest And 21 Shares Spot Bitcoin ETF Application]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755dafa504</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/markets/sec-delays-ark-invest-and-21-shares-spot-bitcoin-etf-application"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T16:52:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Friday morning, the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) solicited comments on 21 Shares and Cathie Wood's ARK Invest's spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) application, further delaying the process.



This is the second delay in the listing process for this ETF, with the first delay happening earlier this year. The third deadline for the SEC's decision is scheduled for later this year for November 11. If the SEC delays the application again, it will go to its fourth and final deadline on January 10, 2024. 
The race for approval for a spot Bitcoin ETF in the United States gained huge momentum earlier this year when the worlds largest asset manager, BlackRock, filed for one of their own. After that, big institutions including Fidelity, VanEck and WisdomTree among others, piled in and filed for their own spot Bitcoin ETFs.  
The first mover advantage of being the first to have its Bitcoin ETF approved and listed may prove to be vital in its performance. Galaxy Digital CEO and billionaire Mike Novogratz said in an earnings call earlier this week, "The news of both BlackRock filing ETF and quite frankly, Invesco plus Galaxy, we're going to fight like cats and dogs to win market share there once it gets approved. It's a big, big deal."
Earlier this year on July 27, the SEC approved a leveraged, 2x Bitcoin futures ETF, which leaves many scratching their heads as to how that is safe for investors, but not a spot ETF. Grayscale, who is currently in a legal battle with the SEC over the denial of its spot Bitcoin ETF application, sent a letter to the U.S. Court of Appeals protesting exactly this. 



More information on the spot Bitcoin ETF race can be found here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nik Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[End Of The Road? Court Dismisses Class Action Lawsuit Against Robinhood]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755dafe033</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/court-dismisses-lawsuit-against-robinhood/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T16:51:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood seems to be finally done with a legal battle that has spanned the course of more than two years. Robinhood Markets recently defeated a group of investors as a United States Federal Appeals court just dismissed the appeal of a class action lawsuit against the crypto and stock trading firm.
 
Appeals Court Throws Out Case Against Robinhood
 
The lawsuit’s background dates back to January 2021, when Robinhood placed restrictions on trades of certain volatile “meme” stocks like GameStop and AMC Entertainment. The limits, including temporarily preventing buys of some stocks, outraged users who couldn’t take advantage of price swings. 
 
 
As a result, the stock trading platform was taken to court in September 2021 by 16 investors who claimed Robinhood prioritized its interests over us…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum DeFi Dashboard DeBank Launches Layer-2 on Optimism’s OP Stack]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152202</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152202/ethereum-defi-dashboard-debank-launches-layer-2-on-optimisms-op-stack"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T16:19:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DeBank plans to launch a social media platform, DeBank Stream, by leveraging the 200,000-plus users on its chat app DeBank Hi.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Parallel' Puts an Epic Sci-Fi Spin on Complex NFT Card Battles]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152075</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152075/parallel-puts-epic-sci-fi-spin-complex-nft-card-battles-preview"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T16:02:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PREVIEW: Parallel is a competitive trading card game with NFTs—for fans of the genre and space operas alike. We go hands-on with the beta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Could Bitcoin Be Our Best Chance To Mitigate Runaway Methane Emissions?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755d969736</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/bitcoin-is-the-best-way-to-mitigate-runaway-methane-emissions"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T15:58:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is an opinion editorial by Daniel Batten, a Bitcoin ESG analyst, climate tech investor, author and environmental campaigner.
I didn’t get interested in Bitcoin because of its ability to solve financial issues. My background is in investing in climate tech. When I first heard about Bitcoin, I was highly skeptical and regarded it as a negative to the environment. However, I was persuaded to put prejudice to one side and evaluate it as I would any other technology I was doing due diligence on. After evaluating the claims and data from both sides I reached the conclusion that on net balance, Bitcoin had the unique ability to solve more than one difficult-to-solve climate-change issue.
First, some context: I have been a climate activist since the 1990s. Several years ago, I channeled this …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Batten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Struggling Crypto Custodian Prime Trust Looks Poised for Potentially Massive Layoffs, Sources Say]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755d96b254</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/08/11/struggling-crypto-custodian-prime-trust-looks-poised-for-potentially-massive-layoffs-sources-say/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T15:57:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nevada regulators recently ordered the crypto company, which BitGo had planned to buy, to cease operations and noted a shortfall in customer funds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Napolitano, Ian Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Musician Nick Cave Rails Against AI: ChatGPT Is the 'Commodification of the Human Spirit']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152185</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152185/musician-nick-cave-rails-against-ai-chatgpt-is-the-commodification-of-the-human-spirit"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T15:57:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cave asserts AI overlooks the struggles in creativity and mechanizes the artistic process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Gas Fees Made Easy: Visa Explores Credit Card Payments]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755d97a86c</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/visa-credit-card-payments-for-ethereum-gas/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T15:49:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a groundbreaking move, Visa has announced the successful testing of a mechanism that allows users to pay Ethereum’s on-chain gas fees directly using fiat through credit or debit cards. This experiment, conducted on the Ethereum Goerli testnet, could potentially revolutionize the way users interact with the Ethereum blockchain, making it more accessible and user-friendly.
 
In a blog post, Visa’s technical team stated, “blockchain technology has gained significant adoption in recent years, and while it has the potential to shape the future of money movement, blockchain transactions bring a heightened level of complexity that isn’t seen in traditional payment methods.” They further elaborated on the challenges faced by users, especially when it comes to managing ETH balances to cover gas …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Pumps Brakes on ARK 21Shares Bitcoin ETF]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152184</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152184/sec-pumps-brakes-on-ark-21shares-bitcoin-etf"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T15:37:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With more attention than ever on Bitcoin ETFs, the SEC has again delayed its decision on the ARK 21Shares Bitcoin ETF application.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Parallel TCG: Inside the Sci-Fi Card Game’s Closed Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/q8YVWJh4/parallel-tcg-inside-the-sci-fi-card-games-closed-beta</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/q8YVWJh4/parallel-tcg-inside-the-sci-fi-card-games-closed-beta"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T15:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin goes hands-on with Parallel’s closed beta on Windows PC to find out what sets it apart from other crypto card-battlers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visa Trials Ethereum Gas Fee Payments Using Cards]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152178</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152178/visa-trials-ethereum-gas-fee-payments-using-cards"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T15:13:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Global payment technology giant Visa has successfully completed a test that enables users to pay Ethereum gas fees using credit or debit cards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining Could Help Decarbonize Energy Grids, Researchers Say]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152088</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152088/bitcoin-mining-carbon-footprint-decarbonization"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T14:54:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin mining can indeed help achieve decarbonization, but faces some stiff practical challenges along the way, researchers find.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fool Me Once: Ethereum Traders Make More Money After Being Scammed]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152179</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152179/ethereum-traders-make-more-money-after-being-scammed"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T14:36:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the researchers said "burning your fingers is good for you," to an extent, because traders diversify and de-risk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generative AI a Top Emerging Risk for Organizations: Gartner Survey]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152161</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152161/generative-ai-a-top-emerging-risk-for-organizations-gartner-survey"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T12:22:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intellectual property, data privacy and cybersecurity are three areas that need to be addressed quickly, according to Gartner.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$170M Bridged to Coinbase Layer-2 Base as Daily Active Users Hit 136,000]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152164</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152164/170m-bridged-to-coinbase-layer-2-base-as-daily-active-users-hit-136000"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T11:38:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new chain has entered the top five layer-2 networks by total amount bridged, while daily active users hit 136,000.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These Are the High-Profile Ethereum Futures ETF Applications Currently in Play]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151012</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151012/these-are-the-high-profile-ethereum-futures-etf-applications-currently-in-play"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T10:10:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first Ethereum futures ETF could be launched as soon as October 2023—that is, if the SEC approves it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Labs Invests $10M to Accelerate Helio Protocol's Liquid Staking Pivot]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151990</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151990/binance-labs-invests-10m-accelerate-helio-protocols-liquid-staking-pivot"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T01:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LSDfi is a fast growing space within DeFi. Now Binance is throwing capital into it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Post Malone Disses CBDCs on Joe Rogan Podcast—And Bitcoiners Love It]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152126</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152126/post-malone-disses-cbdcs-joe-rogan-podcast-bitcoiners-love"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T00:03:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin supporters back the celebs’ take on CBDCs as the “digital dollar” discussion reaches mainstream audiences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[As Coach Swallows Versace, A Crypto Divide Grows in Luxury Fashion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152121</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152121/as-coach-swallows-versace-crypto-divide-grows-luxury-fashion"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T23:29:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An $8.5 billion merger between luxury giants could have major implications for the future of blockchain in fashion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Gaming Investments Surged in July as Metaverse NFTs Fizzled Out]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152091</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152091/crypto-gaming-investments-surged-july-metaverse-nfts-fizzled-out"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T22:24:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Investors pumped $297 million into the fledging crypto video game industry in July, but metaverse NFT sales have slowed significantly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Godfather of Generative Art Goes Global]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151933</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151933/godfather-generative-art-goes-global-casey-reas"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T21:50:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pioneering generative artist Casey Reas will release "923 Empty Rooms" with Bright Moments and Art Blocks at live events spanning six cities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alameda Hits a Snag in Lawsuit Over $9 Billion Locked in Grayscale Bitcoin Trust]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152089</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152089/alameda-lawsuit-grayscale-bitcoin-trust"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T21:41:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The FTX affiliate first sued Grayscale in March. Now it says it needs more time to find a co-plaintiff.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Exchange Bittrex Agrees to Pay $24 Million to Settle SEC Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152090</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152090/crypto-exchange-bittrex-agrees-pay-24-million-settle-sec-lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T21:33:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Four months after the SEC sued, bankrupt exchange Bittrex has agreed to a settlement without admitting to or denying the allegations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Is Literally Trying to Kill You With This Grocery Store App]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152060</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152060/ai-is-literally-trying-to-kill-you-with-this-grocery-store-app"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T19:31:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trying to use up leftovers? An AI-powered app produced ghastly results when users input things like "turpentine" and "ant-poison."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roblox Is Tapping AI to Generate 'More Rich and Dynamic' Games: CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152058</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152058/roblox-tapping-ai-generate-more-rich-dynamic-games-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T18:59:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the biggest games on the planet wants to let creators design games by typing prompts. Here’s how Roblox is approaching AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Digital Currency Group Wants 'Hodgepodge' Gemini Lawsuit Tossed Out]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152059</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152059/digital-currency-group-wants-hodgepodge-gemini-lawsuit-tossed-out"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T18:46:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A letter supporting the motion accused Cameron and Tyler Winklevoss of a “Twitter-based character assassination campaign.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gemini Opens XRP Deposits and Trading Following Ripple Labs Partial Victory]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152045</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152045/gemini-announces-xrp-deposits-following-ripple-labs-partial-victory"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T18:23:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Users will soon be able to trade the cryptocurrency on the platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Trade Sideways as Inflation Jumps to 3.2% in July]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152013</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152013/bitcoin-ethereum-trade-sideways-inflation-jumps-3-2-july"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T12:52:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Inflation has trended downward since it hit 9.1% last June, but the Fed’s target of 2% is the ultimate goal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jump Crypto Leads $5 Million Seed Round in Bitcoin Wallet Xverse]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152012</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152012/jump-crypto-leads-5m-fundingbitcoin-based-web-wallet-xverse"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T12:26:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Xverse wallet supports projects like Ordinals, Stacks, and the blockchain’s speedy Lightning Network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maker Founder Proposes ‘Pre-Farming Airdrop’ for Spark Lending Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152000</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152000/maker-founder-proposes-pre-farming-airdrop-for-spark-lending-platform"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T12:05:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The airdrop proposal is aimed at increasing borrowing activity through Spark, and allowing early users to “secure early SPK tokens.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Derivatives Are Industry's Next Key Source of Growth, Says Genesis Trading]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151991</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151991/crypto-derivatives-are-industrys-next-key-source-growth-says-genesis-trading"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T10:47:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the spot market drying up, Genesis Trading points to rising derivatives volumes as the industry's next growth engine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aptos Futures Demand Hits 3-Month High as Traders Rush to Short APT]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151983</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151983/aptos-futures-demand-hits-3-month-high-traders-rush-short-apt"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T10:15:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Traders are lining up to bet against the APT token amid a hyped new AI partnership with Microsoft and a massive token unlock this weekend.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Circle CEO Urges Industry to Keep Dollar Stablecoins 'On Shore']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151981</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151981/dollar-strength-global-economy-is-under-threat-says-circle-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T09:27:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Resharing a recent video on crypto's role in the future of finance, Circle CEO has urged the industry to keep stablecoin development "on shore."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bolero 'Song Shares' Paints Bright Future for Future of NFT-fueled Music]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151977</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151977/bolero-song-shares-model-paints-bright-future-future-nft-fueled-music"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T08:50:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bolero Music's blockchain-based model lets fans to invest in music, and gives them a fraction of a song’s master recording.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Hungers for More Data to Train Its AI—But At What Cost?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151970</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151970/google-ai-web-scraping-australia-investigation-training-data"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T01:42:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google stands ready to use your online content to train its AI models, unless it's told to stop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Did Special Counsel Jack Smith Get Donald Trump's Twitter DMs?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151966</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151966/trump-twitter-special-counsel-jack-smith-search-warrant"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T01:11:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twitter loses its appeal of a contempt ruling and $350,000 fine over Donald Trump's account.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeGods Ditch Polygon, Moving y00ts to Ethereum and Returning $3 Million Grant]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151959</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151959/degods-ditch-polygon-moving-y00ts-ethereum-returning-3-million-grant"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T23:51:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From Solana to Polygon—and ultimately Ethereum, as DeLabs reveals plans to bring y00ts to the same chain as DeGods.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frens Forever? Building a Social Graph on Bitcoin With Ordinals]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151956</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151956/frens-forever-building-a-social-graph-on-bitcoin-with-ordinals"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T23:47:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The creator calls it "a way to use Ordinals to come closer to the Web3 ethos of a decentralized social network on Bitcoin."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 Games Need to Compete with All Games, Says Solana Foundation GM]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ud9wTd4s/web3-games-need-to-compete-with-all-games-says-solana-foundation-gm</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ud9wTd4s/web3-games-need-to-compete-with-all-games-says-solana-foundation-gm"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T19:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Foundation's General Manager of Games Johnny Lee tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about Solana's PlayGG conference and shares his take on crypto gaming and the "play-to-earn" concept.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Many Early Blockchain Games Were 'Cash Grabs,' Says Twitch Streamer Alliestrasza]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BA4yE45A/many-early-blockchain-games-were-cash-grabs-says-twitch-streamer-alliestrasza</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BA4yE45A/many-early-blockchain-games-were-cash-grabs-says-twitch-streamer-alliestrasza"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T16:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["I wrote them off," Twitch streamer Alliestrasza said of her initial thoughts on many early blockchain games. She tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how her perspective on Web3 games has evolved over time and now sees blockchain games getting significantly better.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['MetalCore' Game Preview: Hands-on With the 'Titanfall' Meets 'Destiny' NFT Mashup]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/tjK6i7lv/metalcore-game-preview-hands-on-with-the-titanfall-meets-destiny-nft-mashup</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/tjK6i7lv/metalcore-game-preview-hands-on-with-the-titanfall-meets-destiny-nft-mashup"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T19:46:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MetalCore is an upcoming mech shooter developed by Studio 369, and it's being developed on Ethereum scaling network Immutable zkEVM. Decrypt contributor Ryan Gladwin played through the prologue and tested out the recent Alpha 3 online experience to get a sense of the NFT-infused mashup of Titanfall and Destiny.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Give Projects a Chance,' Says Aurory's Michael Natoli on NFT Game Challenges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/nBNKKZdK/give-projects-a-chance-says-aurorys-michael-natoli-on-nft-game-challenges</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/nBNKKZdK/give-projects-a-chance-says-aurorys-michael-natoli-on-nft-game-challenges"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aurory is an NFT-driven game franchise that started life on Solana and is expanding to other chains. Decrypt's Jason Nelson spoke with Aurory Head of Marketing Michael Natoli at Solana's PlayGG event, where Natoli shared his thoughts on the challenges that blockchain games face in reaching players.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Is Only Network Ready for Gaming: Solana Foundation's Johnny Lee]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5OvV3ZXn/solana-is-only-network-ready-for-gaming-solana-foundations-johnny-lee</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5OvV3ZXn/solana-is-only-network-ready-for-gaming-solana-foundations-johnny-lee"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T17:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Foundation General Manager Johnny Lee tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how the Solana network will tackle the scaling problem that blockchain games pose for the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Com2uS Is Going "Full Speed" on Crypto Gaming: Kyu Lee]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pYMZRoYy/com2us-is-going-full-speed-on-crypto-gaming-kyu-lee</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pYMZRoYy/com2us-is-going-full-speed-on-crypto-gaming-kyu-lee"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kyu Lee is the President of game studio Com2uS USA. In an interview, he shares the studio's approach to Web3 and crypto gaming with Decrypt GG's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Discord Game with AI and Blockchain: 'Alchemy: Battle for Ankhos' Creative Lead Alex Finden]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mF18GHGo/building-a-discord-game-with-ai-and-blockchain-alchemy-battle-for-ankhos-creative-lead-alex-finden</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mF18GHGo/building-a-discord-game-with-ai-and-blockchain-alchemy-battle-for-ankhos-creative-lead-alex-finden"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T21:55:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Jason Nelson interviews Alchemy: Battle for Ankhos Creative Director Alex Finden at the Solana PlayGG event in San Diego, California.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Big Respect Between Ethereum and Cosmos Developer Communities': dYdX Foundation CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/XU5MbCGE/big-respect-between-ethereum-and-cosmos-developer-communities-dydx-foundation-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/XU5MbCGE/big-respect-between-ethereum-and-cosmos-developer-communities-dydx-foundation-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T13:24:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CEO of the dYdX Foundation Charles d'Haussy unpacks the decision behind moving one of the largest decentralized exchange protocol's over to its very own chain built on Cosmos. A key driver, he told Decrypt at this year's EthCC event, was that instead of launching on a rollup or another layer-1, launching a fully customized chain will allow dYdX to fine tune the network for its product's needs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Staking Solution Lido 'Had Perfect Product Market Fit' at Launch, Says DAO's Biz Dev Contributor]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/fUHhelhV/ethereum-staking-solution-lido-had-perfect-product-market-fit-at-launch-says-daos-biz-dev-contributor</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/fUHhelhV/ethereum-staking-solution-lido-had-perfect-product-market-fit-at-launch-says-daos-biz-dev-contributor"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T08:43:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marin Tvrdić, a business development contributor to the Lido DAO, sat down with Decrypt during this year's EthCC to break down how the liquid staking protocol has managed such a massive lead, how it plans to keep that lead, and the protocol's new dual-governance tokenomics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's Going to Stop All the DeFi Hacks? 'Standards,' Says OpenZepplin Security Architect]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/aYNuFdAi/whats-going-to-stop-all-the-defi-hacks-standards-says-openzepplin-security-architect</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/aYNuFdAi/whats-going-to-stop-all-the-defi-hacks-standards-says-openzepplin-security-architect"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T08:04:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenZeppelin's security solutions architect Michael Lewellen sat down with Decrypt to discuss how the industry can become a little safer for users at this year's EthCC Paris. The key? Introducing security standards across the industry so folks know what an audit actually means and where risks lie, be it bad faith actors or poor implementation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Ev.io' Game Review: Earn Solana While Blasting Enemies]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/2ZmkuhL2/evio-game-review-earn-solana-while-blasting-enemies</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/2ZmkuhL2/evio-game-review-earn-solana-while-blasting-enemies"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T22:21:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ev.io is a web-based first-person shooter that's free to play, but lets NFT holders earn in-game currency that can be redeemed for Solana (SOL). Decrypt contributor Ryan Gladwin shares his review of the fun throwback to Quake-style blasting, albeit with a modern crypto twist.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Moving Fast and Breaking Things Isn't the Web3 Ethos': MetaMask Product Lead]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/l1EbLgl3/moving-fast-and-breaking-things-isnt-the-web3-ethos-metamask-product-lead</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/l1EbLgl3/moving-fast-and-breaking-things-isnt-the-web3-ethos-metamask-product-lead"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T15:45:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Account abstraction this, smart wallets that. Discussions at EthCC Paris about improving user experience have pointed at industry leader MetaMask as an example of what not to do. But that may soon change, with a host of updates and optimizations coming to crypto's number one wallet, said its product lead Alex Jupiter. It still may take some time, though, before these changes take effect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling Smart Wallets on Starknet 'Was The Winning Combination', Says Argent Co-Founder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/gnBsxw4D/scaling-smart-wallets-on-starknet-was-the-winning-combination-says-argent-co-founder</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/gnBsxw4D/scaling-smart-wallets-on-starknet-was-the-winning-combination-says-argent-co-founder"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T07:35:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Argent co-founder Julien Niset told Decrypt at EthCC Paris that he wants to make crypto wallets disappear. Or at least how they're currently conceived. From clunky seed phrases to a stiff user experience, Argent hopes to make using crypto a little less intimidating and a whole lot more fun.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Mighty Action Heroes' Open Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/litL6kKs/inside-mighty-action-heroes-open-beta</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/litL6kKs/inside-mighty-action-heroes-open-beta"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T18:23:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mighty Action Heroes is the flagship blockchain title from Mighty Bear Games. But is the browser-based battle royale shooter worth checking out? Decrypt's Kate Irwin offers her thoughts and a first look at the upcoming game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dr. Disrespect's 'Deadrop': Early Access Gameplay From Snapshot VI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/8l21EHoa/dr-disrespects-deadrop-early-access-gameplay-from-snapshot-vi</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/8l21EHoa/dr-disrespects-deadrop-early-access-gameplay-from-snapshot-vi"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T18:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin playtests Dr. Disrespect and Midnight Society's first-person shooter Deadrop and shares the latest game updates, as well as her opinions on the game in development. Currently, Deadrop offers Polygon Founders Pass NFTs with no other crypto plans revealed just yet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['More and More' Game Publishers Will Embrace NFTs: Mythical Games CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/wBWogSkl/more-and-more-game-publishers-will-embrace-nfts-mythical-games-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/wBWogSkl/more-and-more-game-publishers-will-embrace-nfts-mythical-games-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T22:28:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the wake of EA Sports and Fortnite creator Epic Games embracing Nike's NFT platform, Mythical Games CEO John Linden tells Decrypt's Andrew Hayward how quickly he expects to see more major traditional game publishers enter the blockchain space and how quickly the industry will scale.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>