<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-04-27T08:18:39.798Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-04-27T08:18:39.798Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Buterin Defends Ethereum's Shift from PoW to PoS]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19440765/Buterin-Defends-Ethereums-Shift-from-PoW-to-PoS</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19440765/Buterin-Defends-Ethereums-Shift-from-PoW-to-PoS"/>
        <updated>2024-04-27T07:45:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Buterin counters nostalgia highlights PoW's centralization before Ethereum's PoS shift]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Uses Mango Markets Case to Strengthen Defense Against SEC Charges]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19440764/Binance-Uses-Mango-Markets-Case-to-Strengthen-Defense-Against-SEC-Charges</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19440764/Binance-Uses-Mango-Markets-Case-to-Strengthen-Defense-Against-SEC-Charges"/>
        <updated>2024-04-27T07:39:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance cites the Mango Markets case to bolster its SEC defense strategy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pepe's Price Whizzing In The Cryptocurrency Market]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19440747/Pepes-Price-Whizzing-In-The-Cryptocurrency-Market</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19440747/Pepes-Price-Whizzing-In-The-Cryptocurrency-Market"/>
        <updated>2024-04-27T07:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meme coin is perceiving growth after the Bitcoin Halving event. Pepe coin, a popular meme cryptocurrency attracted crypto traders in the market. Pepe captivated the crypto investors due to the increase in the prices of Pepe coin (PEPE). This price rally gave birth to the frog-based meme token....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How will the game of confiscating assets between Russia and the USA pan out? Say cheese!!!!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19440751/How-will-the-game-of-confiscating-assets-between-Russia-and-the-USA-pan-out-Say-cheese</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19440751/How-will-the-game-of-confiscating-assets-between-Russia-and-the-USA-pan-out-Say-cheese"/>
        <updated>2024-04-27T07:28:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The two countries that head different spectrums of the world, the USA in the West and Russia in Europe, are now on an asset-confiscation battle royale. Over the years, the USA has thrived on imposing sanctions on any country they deem fit. However, since the war broke out between Ukraine and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pro-XRP Lawyer John Deaton Backs Coinbase In SEC Case With Amicus Brief]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74367ce3c2</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/john-deaton-backs-coinbase-in-with-amicus-brief/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-27T07:21:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pro-XRP lawyer and crypto advocate John Deaton has filed an amicus brief supporting Coinbase’s motion to certify an interlocutory appeal in the exchange’s ongoing case with the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). In this petition submitted to the US District Court for the Southern District of New York, Deaton also heavily criticized the SEC’s regulatory approach while emphasizing the need for legal clarity in the crypto space. 
 
 
John Deaton Stands As Amicus Curiae For Coinbase Customers
 
On April 12, Coinbase submitted a motion seeking an interlocutory appeal in its legal battle with the SEC over charges of violations of US securities law. The largest American exchange approached the court seeking clarification on whether an investment contract can be established solely throug…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Semilore Faleti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Japanese Yen Falls To Multi-Year Lows: Will Banks Adopt XRP By 2025?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19440733/Japanese-Yen-Falls-To-Multi-Year-Lows-Will-Banks-Adopt-XRP-By-2025</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19440733/Japanese-Yen-Falls-To-Multi-Year-Lows-Will-Banks-Adopt-XRP-By-2025"/>
        <updated>2024-04-27T07:20:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recent reports revealed a subsequent decline in the Japanese Yen, keeping investors anxious. While the Yen dropped to a multi-year low, SBI CEO Yoshitaka Kitao’s previous statement on the potential of XRP once again gained traction. A crypto enthusiast, known on X as Amelie shared an X post...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pro-XRP Lawyer John Deaton Backs Coinbase In SEC Case With Amicus Brief]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19440728/Pro-XRP-Lawyer-John-Deaton-Backs-Coinbase-In-SEC-Case-With-Amicus-Brief</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19440728/Pro-XRP-Lawyer-John-Deaton-Backs-Coinbase-In-SEC-Case-With-Amicus-Brief"/>
        <updated>2024-04-27T07:12:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pro-XRP lawyer and crypto advocate John Deaton has filed an amicus brief supporting Coinbase’s motion to certify an interlocutory appeal in the exchange’s ongoing case with the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). In this petition submitted to the US District Court for the Southern...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Assault on Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19440724/Assault-on-Crypto</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19440724/Assault-on-Crypto"/>
        <updated>2024-04-27T07:10:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Weekly Recap: FBI goes after crypto, TradFi embraces it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Just Entered a ‘Second Danger Zone,’ Warns Crypto Analyst – Here Are His Targets]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19440718/Bitcoin-Just-Entered-a-Second-Danger-Zone-Warns-Crypto-Analyst-Here-Are-His-Targets</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19440718/Bitcoin-Just-Entered-a-Second-Danger-Zone-Warns-Crypto-Analyst-Here-Are-His-Targets"/>
        <updated>2024-04-27T07:04:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A cryptocurrency analyst and trader is warning that Bitcoin (BTC) may see another move to the downside in the next two weeks. The analyst pseudonymously known as Rekt Capital tells his 74,300 YouTube subscribers that the current Bitcoin correction may be mirroring its 2016 halving price action...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No Man's Land]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19440722/No-Mans-Land</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19440722/No-Mans-Land"/>
        <updated>2024-04-27T07:04:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto markets are sailing into the unknown.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin’s May 2024 price prediction – Look out for these price targets!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19440712/Dogecoins-May-2024-price-prediction-Look-out-for-these-price-targets</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19440712/Dogecoins-May-2024-price-prediction-Look-out-for-these-price-targets"/>
        <updated>2024-04-27T07:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The attention other memecoins are getting may invalidate a parabolic move for Dogecoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 37 Tokens Like XRP, ADA Still Available at Massive Discounts in This Bull Cycle]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19440695/Top-37-Tokens-Like-XRP-ADA-Still-Available-at-Massive-Discounts-in-This-Bull-Cycle</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19440695/Top-37-Tokens-Like-XRP-ADA-Still-Available-at-Massive-Discounts-in-This-Bull-Cycle"/>
        <updated>2024-04-27T06:44:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cycle’s crypto bull market commenced in late 2023, specifically around October, but took full shape this year when Bitcoin cracked its 2021 all-time high. However, some digital assets are yet to capitalize on this buoyant market led by Bitcoin. Prominent Asian-based reporter Colin Wu...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Study: Half of Canadian Institutional Investors Actively Offered One Crypto Asset Product in 2023]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e743678e3a8</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/study-half-of-canadian-institutional-investors-actively-offered-one-crypto-asset-product-in-2023/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-27T06:40:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to a recent survey, half of Canadian institutional investors and financial services organizations have actively offered at least one type of cryptocurrency asset product or service to clients in the past year. The study revealed that half of the institutional investors surveyed were exposed to crypto through exchange-traded funds (ETFs), closed-end trusts, or other […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meow Scientist to Rally 6,500%, Looks to Challenge Shiba Inu and Dogecoin]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19440686/Meow-Scientist-to-Rally-6500-Looks-to-Challenge-Shiba-Inu-and-Dogecoin</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19440686/Meow-Scientist-to-Rally-6500-Looks-to-Challenge-Shiba-Inu-and-Dogecoin"/>
        <updated>2024-04-27T06:29:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meow Scientist (MEOWSC) could become a viral memecoin, like Shiba Inu (SHIB) and Dogecoin (DOGE)....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Interest in Ethereum is waning,” Analyst Says, Revealing the Altcoin That’s Gaining Interest Instead of ETH]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19440683/Interest-in-Ethereum-is-waning-Analyst-Says-Revealing-the-Altcoin-Thats-Gaining-Interest-Instead-of-ETH</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19440683/Interest-in-Ethereum-is-waning-Analyst-Says-Revealing-the-Altcoin-Thats-Gaining-Interest-Instead-of-ETH"/>
        <updated>2024-04-27T06:24:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A cryptocurrency analyst claimed that investors are losing interest in Ethereum and are turning to another altcoin instead. Continue Reading: “Interest in Ethereum is waning,” Analyst Says, Revealing the Altcoin That’s Gaining Interest Instead of ETH]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily Discussion, April 27, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19440671/Daily-Discussion-April-27-2024</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19440671/Daily-Discussion-April-27-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-04-27T06:01:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Please utilize this sticky thread for all general Bitcoin discussions! If you see posts on the front page or /r/Bitcoin/new which are better suited for this daily discussion thread, please help out by directing the OP to this thread instead. Thank you! If you don't get an answer to your...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Rise of Game Media: How UGCverse is Pioneering New Pathways in Digital Engagement]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19440681/The-Rise-of-Game-Media-How-UGCverse-is-Pioneering-New-Pathways-in-Digital-Engagement</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19440681/The-Rise-of-Game-Media-How-UGCverse-is-Pioneering-New-Pathways-in-Digital-Engagement"/>
        <updated>2024-04-27T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UGCverse stands out as a groundbreaking platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Altcoins You Should Keep an Eye on in May]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19440719/5-Altcoins-You-Should-Keep-an-Eye-on-in-May</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19440719/5-Altcoins-You-Should-Keep-an-Eye-on-in-May"/>
        <updated>2024-04-27T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The changing dynamics of the crypto market have opened up Harmony (ONE), Render (RNDR), Near Protocol (NEAR), dogwifhat (WIF), and Stellar Lumens (XLM) to potential profits. BeInCrypto has analyzed the direction these cryptocurrencies could take and how it would affect the entire crypto market....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain: what is Proof-of-Stake (PoS)]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19440680/Blockchain-what-is-Proof-of-Stake-PoS</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19440680/Blockchain-what-is-Proof-of-Stake-PoS"/>
        <updated>2024-04-27T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PoS and PoW are terms widely used in the crypto sector, but how many really know what they refer to and how they work?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia shares up 15% in 5 days — Will AI crypto tokens follow?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19440635/Nvidia-shares-up-15-in-5-days-Will-AI-crypto-tokens-follow</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19440635/Nvidia-shares-up-15-in-5-days-Will-AI-crypto-tokens-follow"/>
        <updated>2024-04-27T05:53:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia's share price saw a 15% increase after a brief slump during the previous trading week, prompting analysts to speculate about the price movements of AI crypto tokens.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[32 People Indicted In Taiwanese Crypto Exchange Fraud Case]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7436614bf3</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/32-people-indicted-in-taiwanese-crypto-exchange-fraud-case/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-27T05:10:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ongoing saga between the Taiwanese authorities and former executives from crypto exchange ACE continues with a new round of charges pressed against its founder, David Pan, and another 31 individuals linked to the case.
 
The exchange and its former directors have been under investigation over alleged fraud and money laundering since January 2024. Authorities previously conducted massive raids on ACE’s headquarters and other related addresses and apprehended several individuals.
 
 
Crypto Tokens Scheme Sees 32 People Indicted
 
Local news outlet Taipei Times informed of a recent development in the ongoing investigation of former ACE exchange executives. On Friday, the Taipei District Prosecutors’ Office indicted 32 people related to the ACE case.
 
Among the accused, Pan, his business …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rubmar Garcia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[32 People Indicted In Taiwanese Crypto Exchange Fraud Case]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19440610/32-People-Indicted-In-Taiwanese-Crypto-Exchange-Fraud-Case</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19440610/32-People-Indicted-In-Taiwanese-Crypto-Exchange-Fraud-Case"/>
        <updated>2024-04-27T05:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ongoing saga between the Taiwanese authorities and former executives from crypto exchange ACE continues with a new round of charges pressed against its founder, David Pan, and another 31 individuals linked to the case. The exchange and its former directors have been under investigation over...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A16z Exec Blasts Meme Coins: They Make Crypto Look ‘Like a Risky Casino’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74366cdc4d</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/a16z-exec-blasts-meme-coins-they-make-crypto-look-like-a-risky-casino/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-27T04:29:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eddy Lazzarin, CTO of A16z Crypto, one of the largest cryptocurrency-focused venture capital funds, has criticized the meme coins’ effect on the broad appreciation of the cryptocurrency market. Lazzarin stated that meme coins undermined the “long-term vision of crypto” that has maintained some actors in the space, making it look “like a risky casino.” A16z […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Senator Warren: Crypto Is The “Payment Of Choice” For Child Sexual Abuse, Urges DOJ Action]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74366e87d0</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/senator-warren-crypto-payment-child-sexual-abuse/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-27T04:10:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a joint effort to combat the illicit trafficking of child sexual abuse material (CSAM), US senators Elizabeth Warren and Bill Cassidy have written a letter to the US Department of Justice (DOJ) and Department of Homeland Security (DHS) expressing concern about the alleged use of crypto to facilitate these activities. 
 
Alleged Link Between Crypto And Child Sexual Abuse
 
In the letter, the senators highlight the “pseudonymity” provided by cryptocurrencies, which they say has enabled the rapid movement of payments for CSAM into the crypto world.
 
It was also stated that both Warren and Cassidy are committed to ensuring that Congress and the Administration have the tools necessary to end CSAM and hold those responsible for its distribution accountable.
 
 
The legislators’ concerns are …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[American rapper Eminem’s crypto ad deal sparks market debate]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19440587/American-rapper-Eminems-crypto-ad-deal-sparks-market-debate</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19440587/American-rapper-Eminems-crypto-ad-deal-sparks-market-debate"/>
        <updated>2024-04-27T04:07:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[American rapper Marshall Mathers, who goes by Eminem, has recently partnered with Crypto.com for their new ad campaign. The commercial shows Eminem walking in a gym and combines the metaphor of the peak industry with phrases related to crypto, such as “proof-of-work.” Besides, a slogan is...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOJ Disputes Roman Storm's Characterization of Tornado Cash Operations in New Filing]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74366f42fe</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/04/27/doj-disputes-roman-storms-characterization-of-tornado-cash-operations-in-new-filing/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-04-27T04:01:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Department of Justice rebuffed Roman Storm's motion to dismiss criminal charges against him late Friday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Republic First Bank Fails, Triggers Minor Crypto Market Downturn Amid Banking Sector Concerns]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74365565f0</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/republic-first-bank-fails-triggers-minor-crypto-market-downturn-amid-banking-sector-concerns/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-27T02:48:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The United States witnessed its first banking failure of 2024 with the closure of Philadelphia-based Republic First Bank, creating ripples within the cryptocurrency community as Bitcoin, Ether, and various altcoins experienced slight price drops following the announcement. This event has spurred discussions among crypto enthusiasts and investors, with some seeing bank failures as a compelling […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Data Reveals Bitcoin Mining May No Longer Be Profitable – Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74365627ae</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/new-data-reveals-bitcoin-mining-may-no-longer/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-27T02:39:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New data has revealed that Bitcoin (BTC) mining might no longer be as lucrative as it used to be. Bloomberg has reported that the profitability of Bitcoin mining is nearing a record low, not seen since the days following the collapse of FTX, posing significant challenges for those securing the network.
 
The data indicates that the “hashprice,” a metric that gauges the revenue a miner earns daily for each petahash of computing power, has dipped alarmingly close to its all-time low.
 
This decrease is notable, considering it came after the recent Bitcoin halving event on April 20, which traditionally boosted the cryptocurrency’s value but, this time, failed to counteract the bearish pressures from global economic uncertainties.
 
 
Notably, the term “hashprice,” coined by Luxor Technologies…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New UK Law Empowering Authorities to Seize and Destroy Crypto Assets Takes Effect Today]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7436563b6d</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/new-uk-law-empowering-authorities-to-seize-and-destroy-crypto-assets-takes-effect-today/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-27T02:38:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new law enabling the National Crime Agency and police to seize, freeze, and destroy crypto assets is now in effect in the UK. Under this law, police can seize crypto from suspects without needing to make an arrest first. Additionally, victims have the right to request the release of funds held in crypto accounts […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoins Gain Ground as Global Financial Asset]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e743657eb96</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/stablecoins-gain-ground-as-global-financial-asset/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-27T02:17:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to Chainalysis’ “Crypto Spring Report,” stablecoin adoption and market importance are seeing a rapid increase in 2024, with a significant rise in the number of addresses holding them and their use in on-chain transactions, making them a global financial asset. Legislation efforts in the U.S., such as the Lummis-Gillibrand Payment Stablecoin Act, aim to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Sell Side Liquidity Thinning On CEXes: Time For $4,000?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74365da036</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-sell-side-liquidity-thinning-on-cexes/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-27T01:05:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Taking to X on April 26, one analyst notes that there is a high probability of Ethereum spiking in the sessions ahead because of thinning sell-side liquidity across major centralized exchanges like Binance and Coinbase. 
 
Thin Sell-Side, Big Potential Move For ETH
 
Thinning sell-side liquidity, as seen on order books across CEXes, means that few sellers are willing to liquidate. With few sellers on the market, a small upsurge in demand could theoretically see prices skyrocket. 
 
 
Even so, market makers could fill this imbalance by considering how the market works. At the same time, prices are not guaranteed to rally even if they remain as they are. 
 
Unlike new meme coins, for instance, Ethereum is extremely liquid; it is the second largest coin by market cap, only trailing Bitcoin. T…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dalmas Ngetich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Swiss National Bank Chief Raises Concerns About Adding Bitcoin to Currency Reserves]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74365fd584</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/swiss-national-bank-chief-raises-concerns-about-adding-bitcoin-to-currency-reserves/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-27T00:39:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The chairman of the Swiss National Bank has expressed reservations about incorporating bitcoin into the central bank’s currency reserves. He stated that no decision has been made yet to invest in bitcoin, underscoring the necessity for currency reserves to be liquid, sustainable, and easily tradable, given their use in international payments. Swiss National Bank on […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Runes Hype Dissipates: Why This Makes Life Difficult For Miners]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74365ae5f4</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-runes-hype-why-life-difficult-miners/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-27T00:03:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data suggests the hype around the new Bitcoin Runes has severely dropped, something that’s not a good sign for miner revenues.
 
Bitcoin Halving Effect Settles In On Miner Revenue As Runes Interest Drops
 
A few days back, the much-anticipated Bitcoin Halving went through. Halvings are periodic events coded into the blockchain in which the BTC block rewards are cut exactly in half. They occur every four years, and the newest one was the fourth such event.
 
The block rewards, which the Halvings drastically affect, are one of the two main ways miners make income. Miners receive these rewards as compensation for solving blocks, which have historically also been their dominant revenue source.
 
 
As such, the Halvings can be troublesome for this group’s financials, as their revenue undergoes …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Conference to Bring Star-Studded Lineup of Speakers to Hong Kong on Dawn of Historic ETFs]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e743647f67e</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-conference-to-bring-star-studded-lineup-of-speakers-to-hong-kong-on-dawn-of-historic-etfs/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T23:09:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. Excitement is brewing in the heart of Asia as Hong Kong regulators pave the way for a new era of innovation with the recent approval of spot Bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs). This groundbreaking development underscores Hong Kong’s commitment to becoming a regulated hub for Bitcoin. At the same time, the Bitcoin Conference is […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Exchange Predicts That Shiba Inu Will Reach $0.00008 In May, New ATH Loading?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e743640b243</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-0-00008-in-may/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T23:01:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Global digital currency exchange, Changelly has forecasted a bullish outlook for doggy-themed meme coin, Shiba Inu, predicting a surge to new all-time highs followed by subsequent bearish movements. 
 
SHIB Expected To Reach New ATH In May
 
On Wednesday, April 24, Changelly shared a price forecast for Shiba Inu, predicting the future value of the cryptocurrency from May 2024 to the end of 2024. Following its rise to record highs of about $0.00004, Shiba Inu plummeted significantly, dropping by approximately 14.06%, according to CoinMarketCap.
 
 
Analysts from Changelly have predicted that a potential price surge to new all-time highs is likely to occur in Shiba Inu next month. They expect the value of the cryptocurrency to steadily increase to an average price of $0.000312 in April befor…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bank of Russia and Rosfinmonitoring Reveal Fiat-to-Crypto Tracking System Pilot]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e743643de7d</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bank-of-russia-and-rosfinmonitoring-reveal-fiat-to-crypto-tracking-system-pilot/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T22:29:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bank of Russia and Rosfinmonitoring revealed the existence of a ‘know your crypto customer’ system pilot, that aims to link the fiat operations of crypto users with their blockchain actions. The pilot, which has been ongoing since 2023, involves five banks in Russia and is expected to run until April, but can be extended. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Texas Crypto Mining Firm And Co-Founders Face SEC Charges In $5M Fraud Allegations]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e743649ff8b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/texas-crypto-mining-firm-face-sec-charges/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T21:32:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has taken legal action against Geosyn Mining, LLC, a Texas-based crypto mining and hosting company, and its co-founders, Caleb Ward and Jeremy McNutt, over allegations of engaging in unregistered and fraudulent activities.
 
Geosyn’s Alleged Fraud Scheme
 
According to the SEC, Geosyn, Ward, the company’s CEO, and McNutt, the firm’s then-COO, raised approximately $5.6 million from more than 60 investors between November 2021 and December 2022. 
 
According to the complaint, Geosyn told investors it would purchase, operate, and distribute crypto assets mined by mining machines, such as Bitcoin (BTC), for an undisclosed fee. 
 
However, the SEC alleges that the defendants made false claims, failed to disclose material information to investors, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Altman, Satya Nadella Join High-Powered AI Safety Board for Homeland Security]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228348</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228348/openai-sam-altman-microsoft-satya-nadella-homeland-security-ai-safety-board"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T21:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twenty leading AI developers—including OpenAI, Microsoft, NVIDIA, and Google—pledge to help the US Department of Homeland Security protect critical infrastructure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Acinq to Withdraw Phoenix Wallet From US Markets Amid Regulatory Concerns]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74364bc35f</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/acinq-to-withdraw-phoenix-wallet-from-us-markets-amid-regulatory-concerns/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T21:16:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Friday, April 26, Acinq announced that its Lightning Network bitcoin wallet, Phoenix, will cease services for U.S. residents from May 3, 2024. This announcement followed closely on the heels of the Samourai Wallet indictment and what is perceived as a targeted U.S. government effort against financial privacy and non-custodial solutions. Lightning Network Platform Phoenix […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Contrary to Crypto Influencer Hype, Data Reveals ‘It is Not Altcoin Season’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7436308b51</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/contrary-to-crypto-influencer-hype-data-reveals-it-is-not-altcoin-season/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T20:36:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past 90 days, while bitcoin has shown steady performance, 19 other cryptocurrencies have outpaced the leading digital asset in terms of price growth. However, the Altcoin Season Index, which measures the performance of these cryptocurrencies against bitcoin, has dropped from 59 to 39 since early April, signaling that an altcoin season is unlikely […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Chops Around $64K, With Japanese Yen's Tumble Maybe Signaling 'Currency Turmoil,' Analyst Says]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e743632a236</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/04/26/bitcoin-chops-around-64k-with-japanese-yens-tumble-maybe-signaling-currency-turmoil-analyst-says/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T20:18:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The yen's volatile episode may spread to other fiat currencies as U.S. rate cuts remain elusive amid sticky inflation, which could drive investors to gold and bitcoin, Noelle Acheson said in an interview.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Notcoin’ Game Token Is Launching Soon—Here's How the Claim Works]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228345</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228345/notcoin-game-token-launch-how-to-claim"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T19:56:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NOT token is dropping in a matter of days, Notcoin’s co-creator told Decrypt’s GG. Here’s what to expect from the claim process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Releases 8 Small AI Language Models To Compete With Microsoft’s Phi-3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228325</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228325/apple-small-ai-models-openelm-microsoft-phi-mini"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T19:46:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Competition in the AI space has started to shift from building the largest models to the smallest, most capable tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yuga Labs ‘Lost Its Way’ Says CEO as Bored Ape NFT Maker Reveals Layoffs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228336</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228336/yuga-labs-lost-way-says-ceo-bored-ape-nft-layoffs"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T19:19:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bored Ape Yacht Club creator Yuga Labs is restructuring with an aim to get back to its smaller, scrappier early days.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Allies: Arbitrum Team Helps Optimism Avoid ‘High Risk’ Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228318</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228318/arbitrum-offchain-labs-optimism-vulnerability"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T18:54:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reaching out to combat potential fraud, from one layer-2 to another.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elizabeth Warren Claims Crypto Is the ‘Payment of Choice’ for Child Abuse Material]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228317</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228317/elizabeth-warren-claims-crypto-is-the-payment-of-choice-for-child-abuse-material"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T18:21:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The top senator wants to help the Justice Department and Homeland Security clamp down on the use of cryptocurrency in child exploitation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Game On: The Hottest Upcoming Gaming Token Airdrops]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211029</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211029/game-on-hottest-upcoming-gaming-token-airdrops"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T17:45:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATED: Here's what you need to know about gaming airdrops and rewards around Notcoin, Immutable zkEVM, Saga, Illuvium, Apeiron, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETFs Bleed Badly as Skittish Investors Cash Out $218 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228300</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228300/bitcoin-etf-outflows-end-71-day-run"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T17:25:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nearly $218 million exited the formerly red-hot investment vehicles in the wake of a weak U.S. economic report.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase, Uniswap Execs Praise Ethereum Giant Consensys for Taking On SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228274</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228274/coinbase-uniswap-ethereum-consensys-sec"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T17:07:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The heads of crypto industry titans like Coinbase and Uniswap are rallying behind Consensys in its fight to get the SEC to concede Ethereum is not a security.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Heroes of Mavia' Delays Ethereum Token Unlocks as Price Falls 65% Since February]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228271</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228271/heroes-mavia-delays-ethereum-token-unlocks"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T14:14:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MAVIA surged in price soon after its February launch, but has plunged since. Now the Heroes of Mavia team is shaking up its plans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Week in Polkadot: Web3 Foundation Backs Decentralized Storage]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228242</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228242/the-week-in-polkadot-web3-foundation-backs-decentralized-storage"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T12:11:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Web3 Foundation backs decentralized storage project StorageHub, while Polkadot founder Gavin Wood launches a new podcast.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will McCurdy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More of FTX's Solana Has Gone to Pantera Capital in Auction: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228191</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228191/more-of-ftxs-solana-has-gone-to-pantera-capital-in-auction-report"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T11:45:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More of FTX's Solana tokens have gone to Pantera Capital, as the bankrupt exchange's estate liquidates its $2.6 billion SOL holdings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK Police, National Crime Agency Gain New Crypto Seizure Powers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228197</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228197/uk-police-national-crime-agency-gain-new-crypto-seizure-powers"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T11:12:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the new powers, the UK government singled out privacy coins as "not conducive to the public good."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana ‘Chapter 2’ Airdrops Could Cover the Price of the Phone]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228171</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228171/solana-chapter-2-phone-maneki-mew-airdrops"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T23:33:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Saga Chapter 2 pre-orders could have their price offset by new MEW and MANEKI airdrops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Game 'MetalCore' Adding MON Token Rewards From 'Pixelmon']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228168</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228168/ethereum-game-metalcore-mon-token-rewards-pixelmon"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T22:53:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Immutable zkEVM allies MetalCore and Pixelmon are teaming up, with the mech shooter set to add MON token rewards for completing quests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Payments Giant Stripe Reenters Crypto With USDC on Ethereum, Solana and Polygon]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228152</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228152/stripe-stablecoin-payments-usdc-ethereum-solana"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T22:16:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A decade after an early attempt to support Bitcoin payments, the company sees a stablecoin-powered future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Sasha Stiles’ Experiential, AI-Infused NFT Drop with Bang & Olufsen]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/6Vi2IgYj/inside-sasha-stiles-experiential-ai-infused-nft-drop-with-bang-olufsen</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/6Vi2IgYj/inside-sasha-stiles-experiential-ai-infused-nft-drop-with-bang-olufsen"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T22:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At a launch party for the collection in New York’s SoHo neighborhood, the artist broke down her latest art experiment, “Four Core Texts,” with Decrypt’s Sander Lutz.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Immutable zkEVM Offering Up to $50 Million in Token Rewards to Ethereum Gamers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228155</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228155/immutable-zkevm-50-million-token-rewards-ethereum-gamers"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T21:51:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum users can earn IMX rewards for playing games, using exchanges, trading NFTs, and more on Immutable zkEVM.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rabbit R1 Reviews Herald ‘Standout’ AI Assistant After Disastrous Humane Pin Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228146</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228146/rabbit-r1-ai-reviews-gadget-hardware"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T20:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Affordability, user-friendly design, and impressive capabilities help the latest AI gadget hop ahead of its scant competition.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Franklin Templeton Enables Peer-to-Peer Trades of Blockchain Fund]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228135</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228135/franklin-templeton-enables-peer-to-peer-trades-of-blockchain-fund"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T19:46:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Participants in the OnChain U.S. Government Money Fund can now swap shares directly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consensys Sues SEC Over Attempts to Regulate Ethereum as a Security]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228134</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228134/consensys-sues-sec-attempts-regulate-ethereum-security"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T19:25:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum giant Consensys filed a preemptive suit against the SEC, revealing that it received a Wells Notice over MetaMask.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ohio Mulls Law to Protect Bitcoin Rights, Scrap Capital Gains Taxes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228124</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228124/ohio-mulls-law-to-protect-bitcoin-rights-scrap-capital-gains-taxes"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T18:33:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bill would also require state pension funds to consider investing in Bitcoin spot ETFs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Dip as Inflation Figures Hamstring Rate Cut Hopes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228113</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228113/bitcoin-ethereum-gdp-fed-rate-cuts-inflation"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T18:17:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Fed’s preferred inflation gauge showed personal expenditures grew 3.7% in the first quarter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CyberKongz Reveal Bitcoin Runes Airdrop Details, 'Mad Rush' Behind Etching]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228112</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228112/cyberkongz-reveal-bitcoin-runes-airdrop-details"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T17:51:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The "DECENTRALIZED" airdrop of Bitcoin Runes tokens is nearing. The CyberKongz team shared exclusive details with Decrypt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erika Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meme Coins Are Causing 'Damage' to Crypto, Says Andreessen Horowitz Exec]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228099</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228099/meme-coins-causing-damage-crypto-andreessen-horowitz-exec"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T16:58:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CTO of VC firm Andreessen Horowitz, Eddy Lazzarin, argued that meme coins are "undermining the long-term vision of crypto."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin 'Epic Sat' From the Halving Sells for $2.1 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228084</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228084/bitcoin-epic-sat-halving-sells-over-2-1-million"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T16:13:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first satoshi mined on Bitcoin after the halving, one of just four "epic sats" to date, fetched 33.3 BTC at auction. Here's why.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CryptoPunk Sells for $12.4 Million in Ethereum—One of the Biggest NFT Sales Ever]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228076</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228076/cryptopunk-sells-12-4-million-ethereum-one-biggest-nft-sales"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T15:56:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CryptoPunks NFT was the third ultra-rare Alien Punk to sell for over $10 million worth of Ethereum in the last two months alone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Gaming Tokens Battered as Bitcoin Price Sinks to $63,000]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228073</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228073/ethereum-gaming-tokens-battered-bitcoin-price-sinks"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T15:34:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some of the biggest Ethereum tokens tied to gaming projects, such as Immutable and Parallel, have plunged over the past 24 hours.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kokodi’s New NFT Collection 'The Masks' Is Set for Mint on Xterio Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228057</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228057/kokodis-new-nft-collection-the-masks-is-set-for-mint-on-xterio-games"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T13:51:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kokodi Inc, a modern video game company, is the mastermind behind the Mask NFT Mint. It’s the project’s second collection for an upcoming extraction shooter game built by the developer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>gamingwire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Started With Bitcoin Runes: A Guide to Etching, Minting and Trading]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=227968</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/how-get-started-bitcoin-runes-guide-etching-minting-trading"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Runes tokens are taking over the network, but they can be tricky to handle. Here's a guide on how to get started with Runes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erika Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Buy Bitcoin’ Notepad Held Behind Janet Yellen Sells for $1M]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228037</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228037/buy-bitcoin-notepad-held-behind-janet-yellen-sells-for-1m"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T12:08:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The iconic sign was held before cameras during a televised House Financial Services Committee hearing in 2017.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interview: Hot 'Notcoin' Will Evolve After the NOT Token Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PprnGP14/interview-hot-notcoin-will-evolve-after-the-not-token-launch</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PprnGP14/interview-hot-notcoin-will-evolve-after-the-not-token-launch"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Open Builders founder Sasha Plotvinov speaks with Decrypt's Sander Lutz at Token 2049 Dubai about how he envisions Notcoin's expansion and evolution after the token drop—into something akin to the "Netflix of social, viral games."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Magic Runes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IGWg0R64/magic-runes</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IGWg0R64/magic-runes"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T13:59:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC stables at $66k, liquidations in narrow range. BTC funding again turns negative in bullish sign. ETFs net inflow after Grayscale moves to lower fees. BTC demand 5x vs supply post-halving: Bitfinex. SOL congestion issue now largely solved. Two SEC lawyers resign after ‘gross abuse of power’. Ripple fights to lower $2bn SEC fine. SAFE trades at $2.8bn FDV after OKX lists. MANEKI hits $150m on first day, China memes pump. Memecoins are ‘black hole you can’t ignore’. DeGods up 20%, may switch back to SOL. Magic Eden launches Runes platform ahead of time.  Louis Vuitton gifts Pharrell jacket to NFT holders. Melania Trump launches necklace with SOL NFTs. Hoodie Punk trades for $620K.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Luxury Watches, Designer Shoes Will Soon Trade Like NFTs: Arianee CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/CSNQG2md/luxury-watches-designer-shoes-will-soon-trade-like-nfts-arianee-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/CSNQG2md/luxury-watches-designer-shoes-will-soon-trade-like-nfts-arianee-ceo"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arianee CEO Pierre-Nicolas Hurstel sat down with Rug Radio founder Farokh and Decrypt’s Sander Lutz at NFT Paris to discuss everything from the future of on-chain luxury to the secret hack to finding the best restaurants in France.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notcoin's Co-Creator Explains the Game's Token Delay—And When to Expect NOT Now]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/7Zx33xo5/notcoins-co-creator-explains-the-games-token-delayand-when-to-expect-not-now</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/7Zx33xo5/notcoins-co-creator-explains-the-games-token-delayand-when-to-expect-not-now"/>
        <updated>2024-04-22T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Notcoin co-creator Sasha Plotvinov spoke with Decrypt's Sander Lutz at Token 2049 Dubai to discuss why the NOT token launch was pushed back from the original 4/20 target, when to expect the listing, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TON’s Justin Hyun Breaks Down The Importance of USDT Coming to Telegram]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ODQI6ACA/tons-justin-hyun-breaks-down-the-importance-of-usdt-coming-to-telegram</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ODQI6ACA/tons-justin-hyun-breaks-down-the-importance-of-usdt-coming-to-telegram"/>
        <updated>2024-04-19T10:14:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Token 2049 in Dubai, The Open Network’s director of investments sat down with Decrypt’s Sander Lutz to discuss what he sees as the game-changing integration of USDT onto TON, and his plans for getting Telegram’s 900 million users to start using crypto in the immediate future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Influencer Ansem Explains His Meme Coin Thesis and Why He’s Bullish on Bitcoin Runes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/u9DHFoK0/crypto-influencer-ansem-explains-his-meme-coin-thesis-and-why-hes-bullish-on-bitcoin-runes</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/u9DHFoK0/crypto-influencer-ansem-explains-his-meme-coin-thesis-and-why-hes-bullish-on-bitcoin-runes"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T21:56:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ansem, the crypto trader who's amassed a sizable following on the back of meme coin Dogwifhat (WIF) and other calls, chats with Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz at Token 2049 Dubai about his meme coin thesis, why he's bullish on Bitcoin Runes, and what he sees ahead for the crypto markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Sander Lutz Braves the Dubai Floods for a Crypto Conference]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/mtjVHGa3/decrypts-sander-lutz-braves-the-dubai-floods-for-a-crypto-conference</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/mtjVHGa3/decrypts-sander-lutz-braves-the-dubai-floods-for-a-crypto-conference"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T21:33:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz reports from Dubai amid a historic storm that flooded the famed city, trudging through the streets to complete his essential task: Attending the Token 2049 crypto conference.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gold Beats Its All Time High]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/6ULgUKVk/gold-beats-its-all-time-high</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/6ULgUKVk/gold-beats-its-all-time-high"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T09:53:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) maintains its trend of reaching higher lows amidst choppy market conditions. Exchange-traded funds (ETFs) witness another influx of $125 million. There's anticipation of Hong Kong approving ETFs for both Bitcoin and Ethereum (ETH) come Monday. Notable institutional investor BlackRock shows interest in Bitcoin. Recent filings reveal increased Bitcoin purchases by banks. A Bitcoin-friendly political party secures victory in the South Korean election. Analyst Kang predicts Bitcoin could surge to $80-100k by May. Meanwhile, Ethereum sees accumulation by stablecoin whales on the rise. A new Ethereum Improvement Proposal (EIP) aims to streamline signing requests. Solana (SOL) experiences a resurgence in activity, reaching yearly highs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NASA’s Next Deep Space Mission Won’t Use Artificial Intelligence]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/0WGP33Rp/nasas-next-deep-space-mission-wont-use-artificial-intelligence</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/0WGP33Rp/nasas-next-deep-space-mission-wont-use-artificial-intelligence"/>
        <updated>2024-04-13T18:42:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Thursday, Decrypt Media visited NASA's Jet Propulsion Laboratory in Pasadena, CA to meet with the Engineering team behind the Europa Clipper before its launch to Jupiter's Europa moon in October.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Do A Little with Weesh]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LnaOT9bF/we-do-a-little-with-weesh</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LnaOT9bF/we-do-a-little-with-weesh"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T07:46:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week’s episode, we did a little something different. We took the man who is usually behind the camera and put him in front of it. We sat down with our producer Weesh to dive into how in fell in love with art and became a collector, how he met Andy and fun childhood memories together, his biggest wins in crypto, and so much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside VanEck’s Crypto Takeover of the New York Stock Exchange]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9YAY4wGD/inside-vanecks-crypto-takeover-of-the-new-york-stock-exchange</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9YAY4wGD/inside-vanecks-crypto-takeover-of-the-new-york-stock-exchange"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T14:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worlds collide as Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz heads to the floor of the NYSE to witness a special closing bell ceremony hosted by VanEck in honor of Web3. Featuring Choose Rich Nick, VanEck Head of Web3 Matt Bartlett, and more!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wormhole Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9SNiIVfU/wormhole-wednesday</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9SNiIVfU/wormhole-wednesday"/>
        <updated>2024-04-07T17:42:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC hits $64.5K then rebounds, SOL outperforms. Government sends $2B BTC to Coinbase to sell. Funding rates stay low after sweep lower. ETFs see small inflow, Ark outflow more than GBTC. Wormhole W launches at $15B FDV. BTC ‘inflection point’ if it follows rates or gold. Gold & BTC very correlated for the last year. Expect slower ETF volume this month: Bloomberg. BTC 2x and 3x levered ETFs launch yesterday. BTC ETFs now half the size of gold.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Dogs, Now Cats]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/2KrbCFNp/first-dogs-now-cats</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/2KrbCFNp/first-dogs-now-cats"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T14:06:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC falls another 6% amid $400m liquidations. ETF outflows and dollar strength blamed for move. Funding completely reset to lows in move. BTC lower high leaves market in ‘no trade zone’. This cycle acting ‘nothing like previous cycle’. ETH unlikely to be classed a security: Coinbase CFO. Crypto VC funding up 53% in MarchAnsem’s cat coin sees more volume than NFT market. Most memecoins down 10-20% given move in majors. MEW up 10% after HTX lists, airdrop to Saga phones. MEME to launch memecoin chain, NFTs rise. Pixelmon releases trailer for Anime series.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Do A Little With Spencer Gordon-Sand]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/jSsgl6SQ/we-do-a-little-with-spencer-gordon-sand</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/jSsgl6SQ/we-do-a-little-with-spencer-gordon-sand"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T17:11:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week’s episode, we sit down with Spencer Gordon Sand, the mastermind behind Spencer Ventures. Before launching Spencer Ventures, Spencer was a competitive fencer, Magic the gathering player, and startup enjoyooor. 

We dive into Spencer’s investment thesis behind NFTs and how his fund invests, finding and buying distressed assets in a bear market , point farming optimization, a peak behind the 3AC liquidation and dickbutt buys, and so much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Get Your Foot In Ihe Door And Building During Bear Markets]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/d8FYP5tO/how-to-get-your-foot-in-ihe-door-and-building-during-bear-markets</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/d8FYP5tO/how-to-get-your-foot-in-ihe-door-and-building-during-bear-markets"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T11:37:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week’s episode, we sit down with Intern and Tunez from the Monad team. Prior to Monad, Tunez was working with Delphi Digital and Intern was working at CMS Holdings. They’re two of my oldest friends from crypto twitter.

We get into why they joined the Monad team, alpha for finding jobs in the space, biggest lessons from previous cycles, and so much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SBF Sentencing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZmRslhIl/sbf-sentencing</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZmRslhIl/sbf-sentencing"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T11:29:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC: 70.7k (+1%), ETH: 3585 (0%), SOL: 186 (-1%). Top 100 gainers: DOGE, GT, BCH, RBN. Crypto mixed, BTC-beta & memes outperform. SEC case vs Coinbase set to go to trial. DeFi win as case dismissed vs Coinbase wallet. ETFs see $244m inflows led by Ark. BlackRock ETF fastest growing in history: Fink. ETH ETF possible even if its a security: Fink. ETH spot ETF by May chances only 20%: GSR. SBF sentencing today, faces 50 years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>