<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-06-12T17:14:39.968Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-06-12T17:14:39.968Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BREAKING: Terraform Labs Settled with SEC in Terra-SEC Case! Here are the Details]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19581320/BREAKING-Terraform-Labs-Settled-with-SEC-in-Terra-SEC-Case-Here-are-the-Details</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19581320/BREAKING-Terraform-Labs-Settled-with-SEC-in-Terra-SEC-Case-Here-are-the-Details"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T17:09:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to the latest development, Terraform Labs reached a settlement in its lawsuit with the SEC and agreed to pay $4.47 billion. Continue Reading: BREAKING: Terraform Labs Settled with SEC in Terra-SEC Case! Here are the Details]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Whales Buy While Market Panics As $950M Worth Of BTC Leaves Exchanges]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7417c8daf3</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-whales-buy-market-panics-950m-btc-exchanges/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T17:06:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data shows Bitcoin whales may have quietly been accumulating at the recent price lows as exchanges have registered large withdrawals.
 
Bitcoin Exchange Reserve Has Observed A Decline Recently
 
As pointed out by analyst Ali Martinez in a post on X, exchanges have seen significant withdrawals over the last couple of days. The on-chain metric of interest here is the “Exchange Reserve,” which keeps track of the total amount of Bitcoin currently sitting in the wallets of all centralized exchanges.
 
When the value of this metric goes up, it means that these platforms are receiving a net amount of deposits right now. As one of the main reasons why investors would transfer their coins to exchanges is for selling-related purposes, this kind of trend can potentially be bearish for the as…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AxonDAO Unveils A+Voice: Pioneering Biometric AI Voice Collection]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7417c9538f</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/axondao-unveils-avoice-pioneering-biometric-ai-voice-collection/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T17:04:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. Cheyenne, WY, June 12, 2024 – AxonDAO (Axon DAO LLC, Wyoming) proudly announces the launch of A+Voice, an innovative research platform designed to monitor vocal biomarkers. This platform is an exceptionally effective tool for the early detection and ongoing assessment of conditions such as Alzheimer’s, Parkinson’s, dementia, post-traumatic stress disorder (PTSD), and Huntington’s […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. inflation drops to 3.3%, beating forecasts]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19581312/US-inflation-drops-to-33-beating-forecasts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19581312/US-inflation-drops-to-33-beating-forecasts"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T17:02:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. inflation has fallen to 3.3%, beating predictions and reviving the crypto market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Pharma Bro' Martin Shkreli Ordered to Stop Sharing Wu-Tang Clan Album After DAO Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234983</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234983/pharma-bro-martin-shkreli-wu-tang-clan-album-pleasrdao"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T17:02:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto collective PleasrDAO sued Martin Shkreli for allegedly violating a court ruling by copying and playing the Wu-Tang Clan album.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Pharma Bro' Martin Shkreli Ordered to Stop Sharing Wu-Tang Clan Album After DAO Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19581311/Pharma-Bro-Martin-Shkreli-Ordered-to-Stop-Sharing-Wu-Tang-Clan-Album-After-DAO-Lawsuit</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19581311/Pharma-Bro-Martin-Shkreli-Ordered-to-Stop-Sharing-Wu-Tang-Clan-Album-After-DAO-Lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T17:02:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto collective PleasrDAO sued Martin Shkreli for allegedly violating a court ruling by copying and playing the Wu-Tang Clan album.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WARNING   It is the BIGGEST Crypto Trap Ever]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19581296/WARNING-It-is-the-BIGGEST-Crypto-Trap-Ever</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19581296/WARNING-It-is-the-BIGGEST-Crypto-Trap-Ever"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T17:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://bit.ly/New_BTC_CashTectum’s Softnotes are a great way to transact with Bitcoin in a way that’s faster and more private than transactions on Bitcoin’s own public chain. Bring privacy back to small transactions with Softnotes.Check out Edu3labs:...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zimbabwe launches study to map and regulate crypto industry]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19581276/Zimbabwe-launches-study-to-map-and-regulate-crypto-industry</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19581276/Zimbabwe-launches-study-to-map-and-regulate-crypto-industry"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T17:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Zimbabwean government has initiated a study to develop regulations for the virtual asset industry. On June 12, the Zimbabwe Mail reported that the government had established a committee to collect data from crypto companies operating within the country. This study aims to provide a detailed...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MoonPay announces PayPal fiat on-ramp for UK and EU]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19581305/MoonPay-announces-PayPal-fiat-on-ramp-for-UK-and-EU</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19581305/MoonPay-announces-PayPal-fiat-on-ramp-for-UK-and-EU"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T17:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MoonPay noted that PayPal is the third most commonly used payment option in the United States, behind Apple Pay and traditional bank cards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Whales Buy While Market Panics As $950M Worth Of BTC Leaves Exchanges]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19581300/Bitcoin-Whales-Buy-While-Market-Panics-As-950M-Worth-Of-BTC-Leaves-Exchanges</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19581300/Bitcoin-Whales-Buy-While-Market-Panics-As-950M-Worth-Of-BTC-Leaves-Exchanges"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data shows Bitcoin whales may have quietly been accumulating at the recent price lows as exchanges have registered large withdrawals. Bitcoin Exchange Reserve Has Observed A Decline Recently As pointed out by analyst Ali Martinez in a post on X, exchanges have seen significant...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s Up With Notcoin? $NOT Price Surges 18% While Mysterious Token Suddenly Raises $1 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19581262/Whats-Up-With-Notcoin-NOT-Price-Surges-18-While-Mysterious-Token-Suddenly-Raises-1-Million</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19581262/Whats-Up-With-Notcoin-NOT-Price-Surges-18-While-Mysterious-Token-Suddenly-Raises-1-Million"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T16:57:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[$NOT, the token underpinning crypto’s viral new Telegram-based social clicker game Notcoin, has surged 18% overnight and about 109% since this time a fortnight ago. The Notcoin token currently changes hands at $0.01858. It has been rallying steadily since it launched three weeks ago, with the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These Three Stocks Can Surge if the Fed Cuts Rates in September]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19581268/These-Three-Stocks-Can-Surge-if-the-Fed-Cuts-Rates-in-September</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19581268/These-Three-Stocks-Can-Surge-if-the-Fed-Cuts-Rates-in-September"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T16:56:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Inflation is not so sticky after all. Will the Fed finally yield to popular demand?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Exchange OKX Sees $204,000,000 in Outflows Following Reports of Security Incidents]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19581258/Crypto-Exchange-OKX-Sees-204000000-in-Outflows-Following-Reports-of-Security-Incidents</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19581258/Crypto-Exchange-OKX-Sees-204000000-in-Outflows-Following-Reports-of-Security-Incidents"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T16:55:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Global cryptocurrency exchange OKX is witnessing a massive outflow amid reports of a security breach, according to the decentralized finance (DeFi) data aggregator DefiLlama. Per DefiLlama approximately $204.67 million in crypto assets has exited OKX over the past 24 hours. Over the past seven...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop (GME) Short Seller Citron Throws in the Towel Citing ‘Market’s Irrationality’]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19581309/GameStop-GME-Short-Seller-Citron-Throws-in-the-Towel-Citing-Markets-Irrationality</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19581309/GameStop-GME-Short-Seller-Citron-Throws-in-the-Towel-Citing-Markets-Irrationality"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T16:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Citron Research, a prominent short seller known for its bearish position on meme stock GameStop (GME), has revealed it exited its short position on the company’s shares as it noted it respects the “market’s irrationality.” In an announcement on the microblogging platform X (formerly known as...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Holders Should Be Watching This Dot Plot At Today's FOMC Meeting]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19581303/Bitcoin-Holders-Should-Be-Watching-This-Dot-Plot-At-Todays-FOMC-Meeting</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19581303/Bitcoin-Holders-Should-Be-Watching-This-Dot-Plot-At-Todays-FOMC-Meeting"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T16:48:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wednesday’s highly anticipated Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC) meeting could set the stage for a bullish run in the cryptocurrency market if one important indicator aligns, according to a crypto analyst. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brace for a breakout: Solana key support and resistance levels to watch]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19581250/Brace-for-a-breakout-Solana-key-support-and-resistance-levels-to-watch</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19581250/Brace-for-a-breakout-Solana-key-support-and-resistance-levels-to-watch"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T16:48:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana (SOL) is poised for more aggressive moves once it breaks out from its current consolidation period. On that note, … Continue reading]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zimbabwe seeks global input on its crypto regulations]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19581225/Zimbabwe-seeks-global-input-on-its-crypto-regulations</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19581225/Zimbabwe-seeks-global-input-on-its-crypto-regulations"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T16:45:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zimbabwe is creating new crypto regulations and wants input from international service providers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Politics of Bitcoin Development]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7417b4a47e</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/technical/politics-of-bitcoin-development"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T16:45:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent conversation with Christian Decker from Blockstream, Bitcoin Magazine's Shinobi delved into the intricate politics of Bitcoin development. Decker, a lead Lightning developer, provided a candid look at the current competitive atmosphere where developers often find themselves entangled in political maneuvering rather than engineering matters. 
Decker did not mince words when describing the challenges developers face. "We have been trying way too long to be clever in as much that we try to sidestep the discussion of whether we want covenants, what kind of covenants we want, or introspection, as we like to call it," he said. The community's cleverness has led to fragmented efforts, with narrowly focused proposals struggling to gain traction amidst limited review cycles and intense …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Orange Man Good: Selling Out On The Campaign Trail]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7417b4a475</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/orange-man-good-selling-out-on-the-campaign-trail-"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T16:45:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After 20 years of forever wars, growing social decline and exacerbating economic demise, it seems that we are still immune to learning that politicians lie. Practically, the US is still in the same place it was in 2004, fueling raging conflicts across the Middle East. The treasury is still overleveraged to both its ears, the stock and housing markets again lie on the brink of implosion, homelessness still continues to rise, jobs are still scarce, and still nobody really knows how to pay for anything. 
If there is a point to be made about US politics, it’s that it doesn’t matter whether the man in alleged charge of the country is an army-dodging goon that can’t figure out how to use binoculars, a progressive in t-shirts campaigning for unity and peace while bombing the life out of Somalians…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>L0la L33tz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Between Bitcoin Layers: Boltz Builds Trustless Transfers]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7417b4a469</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/between-bitcoin-layers-boltz-builds-trustless-transfers"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T16:45:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Company Name: Boltz
Founders: Kilian and Michael
Date Founded: Project began in 2019 | Incorporated in 2023
Location of Headquarters: Remote | Incorporated in El Salvador
Amount of Bitcoin Held in Treasury: 100% of treasury is BTC
Number of Employees: 5
Website: https://boltz.exchange/
Public or Private? Private
Swapping sats between Bitcoin layers can be difficult, but Boltz makes it easier.
Boltz is a non-custodial exchange that lets users send their bitcoin between the Bitcoin base chain, the Lightning Network and the Liquid Network.
While Boltz is now used by both everyday bitcoin users and institutions alike, the platform, which is almost as old as the Lightning Network itself, was born out of necessity and was foundational in helping the Lightning Network function in its early days.
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Frank Corva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brazil's Largest Bank Itaú Opens Bitcoin and Crypto Trading to All Users]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7417b4a461</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/brazils-largest-bank-ita%C3%BA-opens-bitcoin-and-crypto-trading-to-all-users"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T16:45:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Itaú Unibanco, Brazil and Latin America's biggest bank has opened Bitcoin and crypto trading to over 60 million customers, as per reports.

BREAKING: 🇧🇷 60,000,000 customers at Brazil's largest bank can now start buying #Bitcoin and crypto.
Gradually then suddenly 🙌 pic.twitter.com/KXSjPLFzCP
— Bitcoin Magazine (@BitcoinMagazine) June 12, 2024
  
  
  
The bank's investment app, Ion, now allows users to buy and sell Bitcoin and Ethereum after initially offering crypto trading to only select clients in December 2023.
In an interview, Itaú digital assets head Guto Antunes said the move followed weekly surveys, with initial users showing strong demand for Bitcoin and crypto services. 
While not disclosing user numbers, Antunes said the Ion app has surpassed 3.5 million downloads, which is significant interest for Bitcoin and crypto in Brazil.
The bank opted to build its custody solution for clients' wallets rather than using third parties. Each user gets a separate wallet to ensure asset segregation.
As Brazil's largest bank with extensive reach, opening Bitcoin access will boost mainstream adoption. With Bitcoin's popularity in Brazil, the bank aims to be their preferred gateway into this new asset class.
The embrace of Bitcoin and crypto by a conservatively regulated institution like Itaú also further validates Bitcoin as an investable innovation that is here to stay. More banks in the region may follow suit.
For bitcoiners in Brazil, buying and selling through their existing bank provides accessibility and removes adoption hurdles. Itaú opening the floodgates marks a milestone in Bitcoin's financial mainstreaming in a major Latin American economy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vivek Sen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lightning Is the Common Language of the Bitcoin Economy]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7417b4a45a</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/technical/lightning-is-the-common-language-of-the-bitcoin-economy-"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T16:45:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the best parts about running Breez is the diverse range of people I get to meet and work with. We have partners from Jamaica, the USA, Switzerland, Germany, Canada, Estonia, and who knows where else. We have users in Finland, Wales, Namibia, India, and almost everywhere else. The people behind Breez are split across three continents and come from a broad range of national and ethnic backgrounds. 
Agreeing on a communication platform (Telegram? Slack? Zoom? Discord?) sometimes takes a bit of coordination. What never needs coordination, though, is the language we use to communicate. It’s always automatically English. For many of us, English is our second (or third, or fourth) language, and parts of it are baffling, but it doesn’t matter. Every initial contact is in English, all channe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roy Sheinfeld</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ghana’s Cedi Hits Record Low Against US Dollar Amid Cocoa Output Decline]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7417b4b0e3</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ghanas-cedi-hits-record-low-against-us-dollar-amid-cocoa-output-decline/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T16:44:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ghanaian cedi recently plunged to a record low, trading at GHS 14.9335 against the U.S. dollar, which led to its designation as the fourth-worst-performing currency globally. Additionally, a decline in cocoa production has further complicated matters for the cedi, a currency previously ranked as the world’s worst-performing during the last quarter of 2022. Cedi […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fringe to Forefront: the Institutional Embrace of Digital Assets]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7417b5d969</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/opinion/2024/06/12/fringe-to-forefront-the-institutional-embrace-of-digital-assets/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T16:38:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin and other major assets offer unique advantages to investors seeking growth and diversification, says Jason Leibowitz.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Leibowitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What ETF Approval Could Mean for Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7417b5d964</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/opinion/2024/06/12/what-etf-approval-could-mean-for-ethereum/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T16:38:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC’s recent decision sets Ethereum up for success in numerous new ways, says Ilan Solot, Senior Global Markets Strategist, Marex Solutions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ilan Solot</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miners Cash in on BTC Rally as Exchange Transfers Hit Two-Month High]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7417b5d960</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2024/06/12/bitcoin-miners-cash-in-on-btc-rally-as-exchange-transfers-hit-two-month-high/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T16:38:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Transfers from bitcoin {{BTC}} mining pools to exchanges reached a two-month high this week as BTC hovered around its local high $70,000.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MultiversX and Cornell launch sponsored blockchain education program]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19581195/MultiversX-and-Cornell-launch-sponsored-blockchain-education-program</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19581195/MultiversX-and-Cornell-launch-sponsored-blockchain-education-program"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T16:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once students complete the course, they’ll be eligible for follow-on mentorship, support, and funding.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop Stock Jumps as Speculation Over Roaring Kitty Intensifies]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234978</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234978/gamestop-stock-jumps-speculation-roaring-kitty-intensifies"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T16:32:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GME traders are avidly awaiting Roaring Kitty’s plans as the GameStop influencer shares another cryptic meme.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop Stock Jumps as Speculation Over Roaring Kitty Intensifies]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19581194/GameStop-Stock-Jumps-as-Speculation-Over-Roaring-Kitty-Intensifies</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19581194/GameStop-Stock-Jumps-as-Speculation-Over-Roaring-Kitty-Intensifies"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T16:32:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GME traders are avidly awaiting Roaring Kitty’s plans as the GameStop influencer shares another cryptic meme.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether Invests $100M In Bitdeer To Boost Bitcoin Mining Operations]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19581239/Tether-Invests-100M-In-Bitdeer-To-Boost-Bitcoin-Mining-Operations</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19581239/Tether-Invests-100M-In-Bitdeer-To-Boost-Bitcoin-Mining-Operations"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T16:30:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitdeer Group receives $100M investment from Tether. Investment to fuel growth in Bitcoin mining sector. Tether aims to enhance its mining activities. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zimbabwe Opens Consultation on Cryptocurrency Regulation]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19581255/Zimbabwe-Opens-Consultation-on-Cryptocurrency-Regulation</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19581255/Zimbabwe-Opens-Consultation-on-Cryptocurrency-Regulation"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zimbabwe is gearing up to regulate cryptocurrency regulations, seeking public input to develop policies in the digital asset sector. In a statement published in the state-run Herald newspaper, the government revealed its intention to assess and understand the cryptocurrency landscape. inviting...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stocks to Watch Today: Apple, Oracle, and Tesla]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19581160/Stocks-to-Watch-Today-Apple-Oracle-and-Tesla</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19581160/Stocks-to-Watch-Today-Apple-Oracle-and-Tesla"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T16:27:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple reclaimed its position as the biggest company on Wall Street, Oracle got a boost on AI partnerships, and Tesla surged on Cathie Wood’s aspiring 2029 price target for the EV firm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Andrew Tate’s DADDY token shows “huge insider activity”; investigator profile blocked]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19581163/Andrew-Tates-DADDY-token-shows-huge-insider-activity-investigator-profile-blocked</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19581163/Andrew-Tates-DADDY-token-shows-huge-insider-activity-investigator-profile-blocked"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T16:26:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An investigation by Bubblemaps recently identified substantial insider trader activity related to Andrew Tate's token DADDY. Insiders reportedly acquired 30% of the token's supply at its inception, before Tate's promotion on social media platforms. These insiders allegedly hold over $45 million...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MoonPay Brings PayPal on Board for EU and UK Crypto Purchases]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7417b3df81</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/moonpay-brings-paypal-on-board-for-eu-and-uk-crypto-purchases/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T16:02:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MoonPay has announced the expansion of PayPal as a payment  
option to users in the European Union and the United Kingdom, following a  
successful launch in the United States last month. Now, MoonPay users in 24 EU  
member states and the UK can buy cryptocurrency using their PayPal accounts. 
PayPal Integration Draws Mature User Base
The recent US launch, which has reached all users, showed  
strong demand for PayPal, becoming the third most popular payment method,  
overtaking Google Pay, and ranking just behind cards and Apple Pay. 
Nearly 90%  
of users who connect to PayPal complete a transaction, and new customers using  
PayPal as their first payment method convert at a rate 1.3 times higher than  
those using cards. The integration also attracts a more mature user base, with  
an …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tareq Sikder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Should Banks Be Crime Fighters? The Hidden (and Not So Hidden) Costs]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7417bf9075</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/opinion/2024/06/12/should-banks-be-crime-fighters-the-hidden-and-not-so-hidden-costs/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T15:41:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pointlessly onerous anti-money laundering rules lead to debanking of individuals and even entire regions, just as “financial inclusion” is thrown around as a social objective. We need a viable alternative, says Noelle Acheson.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Noelle Acheson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Prices Pop as US Inflation Growth Slows]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234957</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234957/bitcoin-ethereum-prices-pop-us-inflation-growth-slows"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T15:23:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Major cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin rallied Wednesday as a U.S. inflation gauge showed prices rose less in May than economists had forecast.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Major Entities Hold Over 4 Million Bitcoin, Accounting for 27% of Supply]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7417a41b3b</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/report-major-entities-hold-over-4-million-bitcoin-accounting-for-27-of-supply/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T15:14:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest Glassnode onchain report reveals that major labeled entities collectively hold approximately 4.23 million bitcoin, representing over 27% of the adjusted circulating supply. This significant concentration of BTC holdings underscores the prominent role these entities play within the bitcoin ecosystem. Institutional Holdings: ETFs, Miners, Government, and Exchanges Control 4.23 Million Bitcoin According to Glassnode’s […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Viral Meme Coin Base Dawgz Raises $1M as Crypto Expert Forecasts 10x Potential]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7417a5d84f</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/new-viral-meme-coin-base-dawgz-raises-1m-as-crypto-expert-forecasts-10x-potential/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T15:04:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Base Dawgz (DAWGZ), a brand-new multi-chain meme coin, has raised over $1 million in its presale. And now, one prominent analyst is predicting that DAWGZ could 10x from its current price after listing on DEXs. Base Dawgz – The Multi-Chain Meme Coin with Staking Rewards So, what’s fueling Base Dawgz’s early momentum? It’s mainly down […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Completes Acquisition of Standard Custody & Trust Company]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7417a18a76</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ripple-completes-acquisition-of-standard-custody-trust-company/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T14:43:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple has completed its acquisition of Standard Custody & Trust Company, a regulated digital asset custodian. This acquisition, announced by Ripple earlier this year, involves a trust company regulated by the New York Department of Financial Services. It broadens Ripple’s portfolio of licenses, which now includes nearly 40 U.S. money transmitter licenses, a Major Payment […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meme Coin Economy Gains $4 Billion Capital Injection Ahead of Fed Meeting]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7417aee23f</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/meme-coin-economy-gains-4-billion-capital-injection-ahead-of-fed-meeting/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T14:11:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The meme coin economy is thriving on Wednesday, ahead of the U.S. Federal Reserve meeting, as the sector saw nearly $4 billion injected over the last 12 hours. Several meme tokens experienced substantial gains, with BENJI rising 36.9%, MAGA increasing 23.2%, and the runes-based DOG gaining 22.1%. Crypto Market Rises 3.24% as Meme Coins Drive […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stability AI Releases SD3: The Most Powerful, Open-Source Image Generator is Available in HuggingFace]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234935</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234935/stability-ai-releases-sd3-the-most-powerful-open-source-image-generator-is-available-in-huggingface"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T14:10:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The weights of the open-source, uncensored, customizable text-to-image generator are available for AI artists and enthusiasts to try locally.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zimbabwe Steps Up To The Crypto Plate: Public Input Sought For Regulations]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7417afb044</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/zimbabwe-steps-up-to-the-crypto-plate-public-input-sought-for-regulations/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T14:05:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zimbabwe is taking an exciting step into the future by launching a public consultation to get opinions on regulating cryptocurrency operations in the country, Bloomberg reports. This is a big change for a nation that has historically struggled with currency issues.
 
 
By asking for feedback from the public and talking to industry experts, Zimbabwe aims to balance encouraging innovation in the growing crypto sector with making sure it’s done responsibly and in line with international standards.
 
From Tough Times To Digital Future
 
Zimbabwe’s economic history is full of challenges, including several currency crashes, the latest one in 2019. In response, the government introduced a gold-backed virtual asset called the ZiG in April 2024.
 
This move showed that the country is becoming more …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Whale Moves $535 Million After Over 5 Years Of Dormancy]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234934</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234934/bitcoin-whale-moves-535-million-after-over-5-years-of-dormancy"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T13:27:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An unidentified whale transferred 8,000 BTC to Binance yesterday—if sold, it would net them over half a billion dollars in profit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarang Khaitan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rivals: Dogs Vs Squirrels (RVLS) Token – The Only Platform Which Deserves Your Attention]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741797bc40</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/rivals-dogs-vs-squirrels-rvls-token-the-only-platform-which-deserves-your-attention/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T13:15:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Memecoin world never sleeps as it keeps evolving, innovating, and expanding regardless of the market condition. Despite the abundance of innovative memes, most of them have a fundamental flaw- meme coins with unrealistic hype go insanely high and drop back down at the same pace as the hype fades. Investors lose millions to the whales and this vicious cycle continues. 
 
However, amongst all this chaos, Rivals: Dogs Vs Squirrels, or the RVLS Token, has boldly stepped in with a unique proposition. Rivals: Dogs Vs Squirrels envisions to introduce true utility in the memecoin world and create a loyal community around itself. It aims to be a totally different breed of the meme. Let’s break it down to understand what it has to offer: 
 
Introducing Rivals: Dogs Vs Squirrels
 
Rivals: Dogs Vs…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blast’s Rebasing Stablecoin USDB Now Ranks 9th Among Dollar-Pegged Crypto Tokens]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741790c46b</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/blasts-rebasing-stablecoin-usdb-now-ranks-9th-among-dollar-pegged-crypto-tokens/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T13:09:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new stablecoin has emerged among the top ten U.S. dollar-pegged tokens. Known as USDB, this auto-rebasing stablecoin was developed by the Blast team. Despite the stablecoin economy being underwhelming over the past 30 days, USDB has quietly secured the ninth-largest market capitalization among all U.S. dollar stablecoins. USDB Climbs the Ranks The decentralized finance […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[9 Must-See Trailers from the Xbox, Ubisoft, and Summer Game Fest Events]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234844</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234844/9-must-see-trailers-xbox-ubisoft-summer-game-fest"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T12:01:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Catch a look at Doom: The Dark Ages, Perfect Dark, Fable, and several other huge upcoming games as publishers showcase what's next.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Frederiksen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meme Coins Brett, Bonk and Pepe Top Gainers Amid Market Lull]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234902</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234902/brett-bonk-and-pepe-top-gainers-amid-market-lull"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T11:26:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meme coins and the broader crypto market are struggling to perform while Base chain's Brett, Solana's Bonk, and Ethereum's Pepe rise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF Net Outflows Hit $200 Million Ahead of FOMC Meeting]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234886</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234886/bitcoin-etf-net-outflows-fomc-meeting"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T10:14:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Market participants are expecting the Federal Reserve to keep the interest rate unchanged, but investors still seem cautious.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarang Khaitan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MetaMask Adds Pooled Ethereum Staking Service—But Not for US or UK]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234739</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234739/metamask-adds-pooled-ethereum-staking-service-but-not-for-us-or-uk"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T10:01:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum users now have an "easy way to stake ETH in enterprise-grade validators while maintaining full control of their ETH," said Consensys.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump Calls for 'Made in the USA' BTC After Meeting With Bitcoin Miners]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234876</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234876/donald-trump-champions-made-in-the-usa-btc-after-meeting-with-bitcoin-miners"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T08:36:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trump said mining more BTC in the states will make the country "energy dominant" and that it "may be our last line of defense against a CBDC."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Drops ‘Founding Agreement’ Lawsuit Against OpenAI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234865</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234865/elon-musk-drops-lawsuit-against-openai"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T23:15:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Musk has withdrawn the lawsuit he filed in February against OpenAI and Sam Altman over its for-profit AI development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral Is Now Worth $6 Billion, Drawing Fresh Cash Amid Open-Source AI Boom]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234859</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234859/mistral-ai-draws-huge-influx-of-cash-amid-open-source-ai-boom"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T22:46:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A $644 million funding round triples the Microsoft-backed French AI startup’s valuation and will fuel development of both its proprietary and open-source AI models.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The ‘MicroStrategy of Japan’ Just Bought More Bitcoin—And Its Stock Predictably Pumped]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234851</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234851/metaplanet-japan-stock-microstrategy-bitcoin-buy"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T22:31:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MetaPlanet stock is up more than 4X since adopting a Bitcoin standard in April.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop Stock Surges as Roaring Kitty Skewers Recent Losses]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234856</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234856/gamestop-stock-surges-roaring-kitty-skewers-losses"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T22:13:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After two days of rough declines, GameStop (GME) shares shot up Tuesday—and influencer Roaring Kitty poked fun at his recent paper losses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Has AI Already Changed Gaming Forever?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mZlR3He5/has-ai-already-changed-gaming-forever</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mZlR3He5/has-ai-already-changed-gaming-forever"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T19:51:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt’s Sander Lutz and Rug Radio creator Puke sat down with Simon Davis of Mighty Bear Games and VC Kyle Klemmer to discuss how AI has already remade the gaming industry—for better and for worse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Alliance Merger Delayed for a Month As Token Prices Fall]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234802</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234802/ai-token-merger-delay-asi"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T19:25:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The three tokens set to become one are down over 20% for the week, along with much of the crypto market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BODEN Solana Meme Coins Soar on Hunter Biden Guilty Verdict]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234823</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234823/boden-solana-meme-coins-soar-hunter-biden-guilty-verdict"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T19:20:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hunter Biden was found guilty on three felony gun charges Tuesday—and Solana meme coins inspired by the Bidens pumped afterwards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 135 - BTC FALLS ON OUTFLOWS]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/bA3jJ5aA/fomo-hour-135-btc-falls-on-outflows</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/bA3jJ5aA/fomo-hour-135-btc-falls-on-outflows"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T19:03:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto falls as ETFs see first outflow in 19 days. Short positions grow on downwards move in BTC. BTC short-term realised price now at $64k. ETH ETF issuers still waiting for SEC response. UK ETNs continue to see tiny volume. SOL validators get kicked out for sandwich attacks. ZKsync airdrop happening next week. ZKsync to give 17.8% to the community. OP launches Fraud Proofs. Bitfarms plans poison pill to counter takeover bid. OKX sees outflows after security incidents. Bybit considers shutting China offices. COIN may get added to S&P500.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Plunges as $245 Million in Crypto Longs Are Liquidated]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234815</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234815/bitcoin-price-plunges-245-million-crypto-longs-liquidated"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T17:57:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto liquidations are soaring Tuesday as Bitcoin sinks 5% to a price of nearly $66,000, with long positions seeing the biggest impact.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward,Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin's Value Is ‘Many Multiples’ Above Its Current Price: Billionaire Investor Bill Miller]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234803</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234803/bitcoin-value-many-multiples-above-current-price-bill-miller"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T17:56:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The famed investor predicts Bitcoin deniers will suffer over the next decade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Just Don’t Call It Blockchain: Apple's New AI Privacy Tech Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234801</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234801/apple-blockchain-ai-privacy-cloud-compute"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T17:32:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple says its new AI model uses “blockchain-ish” tech to preserve privacy. But what does that really mean?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Doxxing and Conspiracy Theories: GameStop Hero Roaring Kitty's Fans Are Getting Carried Away]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234769</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234769/doxxing-conspiracy-theories-roaring-kitty-gamestop"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T16:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reddit moderators have urged fans of the GameStop bull to stop posting photos of Roaring Kitty’s family on the social media site.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETFs Break 19-Day Inflow Streak As Net Outflows Hit $65 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234780</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234780/bitcoin-etfs-break-19-day-inflow-streak-as-net-outflows-hit-65-million"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T14:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale’s GBTC has seen net outflows of over $113 million across the past three days, as Bitcoin's price dipped below $67,000.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarang Khaitan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No More Betting With Crypto on Australian Gambling Sites, Says Regulator]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234770</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234770/no-more-betting-with-crypto-on-australian-gambling-sites-says-regulator"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T12:32:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Failure to comply could see companies fined up to $155,000.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Lightning Network and Layer 2 Scaling Could Be 'Abused by Criminals', Says EU]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234748</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234748/bitcoin-lightning-network-and-layer-2-scaling-could-be-abused-by-criminals-says-eu"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T11:19:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An EU Innovation Hub for Internal Security report argues that layer 2 solutions could cause "problems for law enforcement investigations."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Drops 3% Ahead of Interest Rate Decision and US Inflation Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234754</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234754/bitcoin-drops-3-ahead-of-interest-rate-decision-and-us-inflation-report"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T10:58:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin has dropped by 3% ahead of tomorrow's Federal Open Markets Committee interest rates decision and new U.S. inflation data.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarang Khaitan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ZkSync Will Airdrop 3.7 Billion ZK Tokens to User Wallets Next Week]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234747</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234747/zksync-will-airdrop-3-7-billion-zk-tokens-to-user-wallets-next-week"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T10:03:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There'll be no lock-up period for the community airdrop, but distribution has been capped at 100,000 tokens per wallet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sora Who? Kling Is the New AI Video Generator Everyone Is Talking About]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234706</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234706/kling-ai-video-generator-china-beats-pika-runwayml-openai-sora"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T23:30:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hailing from China, the Kling AI video model is a potential game changer, blasting past mainstays like Pika or RunwayML. Here's what you need to know.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Call of Duty: Black Ops 6 Preview: Everything You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=214893</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/214893/call-of-duty-2024-preview-leaks-rumors-release-date"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T22:45:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATED: Activision just shared a ton of details about Call of Duty: Black Ops 6—including some big changes from last year's entry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Says He Will Ban Apple Devices From His Companies If They Integrate OpenAI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234689</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234689/elon-musk-apple-device-ban-chatgpt-security-privacy"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T22:22:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“That is an unacceptable security violation,” the Tesla CEO declared, asserting that Apple can't guarantee that OpenAI will keep user data secure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 134 - EU SNAP ELECTIONS LAND]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pZksMKIV/fomo-hour-134-eu-snap-elections-land</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pZksMKIV/fomo-hour-134-eu-snap-elections-land"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T15:46:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Volatility remains low, TL continues to be divisive. 2nd highest weekly close ever for BTC. Crypto funds saw $2bn inflows last week. Rumour that BlackRock will apply for SOL ETF. Base TVL hits $8bn, top of L2s for activity. zk Sync hint at TGE this week. PENDLE enters top 5 for DeFi TVL. Berachain v2 testnet goes live.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 133 - RUGGED BY HOGEN?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MSvAS9qX/fomo-hour-133-rugged-by-hogen</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MSvAS9qX/fomo-hour-133-rugged-by-hogen"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T17:26:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC still just below ATH after $218m ETF inflows. BTC OI hits record $37bn as long-short ratio rises. Amount of ETH on exchanges lowest since 2015. Franklin Templeton explores broader crypto fund. Mining stocks rise on takeover frenzy. Kraken considers $100m funding round. Binance reinstates crypto buys with Mastercard. Phantom & Jito partner for native staking.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 132 - CRYPTO STRENGTH IS GROWING]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/bQBFWC0w/fomo-hour-132-crypto-strength-is-growing</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/bQBFWC0w/fomo-hour-132-crypto-strength-is-growing"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T19:49:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto consolidates near ATH, $488m ETF inflow. BTC correlation to tech stocks highest since 2023. BTC options anticipate $74-80k move. ETH to $22k by 2030: VanEck. Robinhood to acquire Bitstamp.
Coinbase launches Smart Wallet. ByBit opens up explicitly to China users. Global liquidity breaks out to $94T. US President given new powers to block crypto. Cramer & Gensler continue to bash crypto. Gensler hints at prolonged ETH ETF process. Stand with Crypto PAC hits 1m advocates. Turkey denies plans to tax crypto. EigenLayer surpasses $20bn TVL. IONET to launch on Binance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webinar: Unleashing The Power Of Permissionless Markets With Vega Protocol]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OvA845JA/webinar-unleashing-the-power-of-permissionless-markets-with-vega-protocol</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OvA845JA/webinar-unleashing-the-power-of-permissionless-markets-with-vega-protocol"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T08:23:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join our expert panel for an insightful discussion on Vega Protocol's revolutionary approach to decentralized derivatives trading. Discover how Vega's permissionless markets enable anyone to create and trade futures and perpetuals on a fully decentralized network. Explore the potential of Vega's innovative features, such as the ability to add new assets, transfer network assets, and adjust network parameters—as well as the protocol's active markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 131 - BIG BITCOIN INFLOWS!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/a37DNT7n/fomo-hour-131-big-bitcoin-inflows</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/a37DNT7n/fomo-hour-131-big-bitcoin-inflows"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T17:06:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETFs see large $900M inflows, biggest in weeks. $800M of shorts would be liquidated above $72K. BTC to $100K if it breaks $73K in a week: Novogratz. BNB hits new ATH, breaks $100B market cap. FTX reaches $200M tax settlement with IRS. Most investors should hold BTC: Fidelity. Tether CEO criticises EU on stablecoin regulation. Japanese exchange raises $320M to recover funds. ETH ETFs could see $4B inflows in 5 months: K33. Paradigm propose MEV taxes. StarkWare plans ZK scaling for BTC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 130 - $DOG TARGETS 1B MC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ke2mFBwr/fomo-hour-130-dog-targets-1b-mc</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ke2mFBwr/fomo-hour-130-dog-targets-1b-mc"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T22:05:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Runes & Ordinals soar as DOG passes $900M. rekt Brands opens up its shares claim for NFT holders. BTC led NFT trading volume with $6.3M on the day. NodeMonkes +10% 0.289, Puppets +35% at 0.198. Runes up by DOG which soared 23% to $922M mc. BUS won the Blast Jackpot last night for a 3% win. Memecoin majors are mostly red this AM. Trader buys 10k SOL of GME. Base brings back Onchain Summer. Dapper settles massive lawsuit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 129 - ROARING RETURNS, AGAIN!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ABOejLBT/fomo-hour-129-roaring-returns-again</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ABOejLBT/fomo-hour-129-roaring-returns-again"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T21:42:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto bounces, BTC breaks 2-week downtrend. BTC low volatility points to trend continuation. BTC will top at $150k in September 2025: Brandt. $3bn ETH withdrawn from exchanges since ETF. ETH ETF inflows imply ‘base case’ price $5.3k. ETH ETF inflows won’t be like BTC: Fireblocks. BTC logo projected on ECB building. Ethena USDe hits $3bn market cap in 4 months. Maple launches DeFi institutional lending platform. OKX launches in the Netherlands. Matter Labs drops ZK ticker. Linea shuts down chain after hack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 128 - PUMP DOT FUN KEEPS PUMPING!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cziNL3TF/fomo-hour-128-pump-dot-fun-keeps-pumping</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cziNL3TF/fomo-hour-128-pump-dot-fun-keeps-pumping"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T21:41:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto nears break-out then falls on Trump verdict. 13 straight days of BTC ETF inflows, BTC whale accumulation ‘echoes 2020’. Crypto apps next year will onboard millions: Burniske. Elon denies talking crypto policy with Trump. RFK has bought 21 BTC during campaign. TON market cap falls after updating supply data. a16z donates $25m to crypto PAC. Vitalik sends 30ETH to Tornado devs. DBS Bank in Singapore custodies $650m ETH. Backlash grows over zkSync using ZK ticker. Implementing FIT21 a slow process: CFTC. Pierce recommends UK & US cross-border sandbox. Vitalik writes blog on block size wars. Hong Kong government expresses support for web3. Do Kwon & Terraform reach settlement with SEC. Large unlocks for a number of alts next month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 127 - CELEB COINS CRASH!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mGbE2GHV/fomo-hour-127-celeb-coins-crash</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mGbE2GHV/fomo-hour-127-celeb-coins-crash"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T20:28:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NYSE to launch BTC options. CME has ‘no plans’ to offer SOL futures. Stablecoin market cap rises to 2 year high. Inflation below 3.3% ‘means BTC ATH’. Crypto market cap heading to $200T: Yat Siu. Gemini recovers $2.2bn for Earn users. PayPal stablecoin will offer ‘confidential transfers’. Mastercard launches Crypto Credential pilot on BTC. Layer Zero launches on SOL. L2s are cultural extensions of ETH: Vitalik. FTX’s Salame says he will share story. SEI announces 27m SEI airdrop. ASI merger complete, to launch June 13th.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 126 - MEMECOIN MADNESS!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/eA3xqKLr/fomo-hour-126-memecoin-madness</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/eA3xqKLr/fomo-hour-126-memecoin-madness"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T21:30:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock ETF flips Grayscale in size. BTC ETFs see 11 straight days of inflows. ZKasino gives 72hours for ETH withdrawals. ENS to migrate to L2. ADA drops out of top 10 coins. Salame sentenced to 7.5 years in jail. Riot Platforms attempts takeover of Bitfarms. Ripple donates $25m to Fairshake PAC. Pump(.)fun launches live streaming. Iggy Azelea MOTHER coin leads celeb tokens. Beeple Everyday features many coins. Runes bounce, DOG hits $560m. PEPE active wallets double during rally. Cristiano Ronaldo launches 4th NFT. Friend Tech announces club wars.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum DN-404 Tokens Are a Sensation in Asia. Are They the West’s Next Big Trend?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/drcV3Zte/ethereum-dn-404-tokens-are-a-sensation-in-asia-are-they-the-wests-next-big-trend</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/drcV3Zte/ethereum-dn-404-tokens-are-a-sensation-in-asia-are-they-the-wests-next-big-trend"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T19:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz and Rug Radio creator Pukerainbow sat down for a conversation with some of the biggest adopters involved in Ethereum’s newest trend: dividing NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Buying Crypto Simplified with Mika]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/Z9rxTcnJ/buying-crypto-simplified-with-mika</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/Z9rxTcnJ/buying-crypto-simplified-with-mika"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T16:54:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the first part of our series turning crypto beginners into crypto pros, Rug Radio creator Mika guides you through the process of purchasing cryptocurrency using crypto exchange Kraken.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 125 - ETH NEARS 4K]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BrgFfEe8/fomo-hour-125-eth-nears-4k</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BrgFfEe8/fomo-hour-125-eth-nears-4k"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T17:40:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH leads rally on continued bullish ETF sentiment. Previous anti-crypto Trump comments highlighted. Wave of influencers and celebrities hacked, release coins. Phantom becomes no.1 finance app in the US. Argentina & El Salvador hold talks on BTC adoption. LINK to have large announcement on May 30th. PEPE, MOG, TURBO, TRUMP hit ATHs in ETH memes. MOG up 60%, mentioned in Beeple Everyday. Caitlyn Jenner hacker releases JENNER coin. Garga outlines future plans for BAYC. Friend Tech founder offers $200k to migrate off Base.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 124 - THE ETH ETF IS APPROVED!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5ELzjWt4/fomo-hour-124-the-eth-etf-is-approved</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5ELzjWt4/fomo-hour-124-the-eth-etf-is-approved"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T18:43:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH ETFs get approved 19b-4 forms. ETFs won’t trade until July or August: Galaxy. ETF means many coins not securities: Coinbase CLO. Coinbase relists XRP in US. SOL ETF coming: Scaramucci. US House passes vote to ban CBDC. Building a pro-crypto army in congress: Sen. Lummis. Polymarket backlash over if ETH ETF truly approved. Expect ETH ETFs to be 10-15% of BTC: Bloomberg. BTC ETFs see $1.75bn inflows over 9 days. BTC to $150k in 2024 is base case: Tom Lee. ETH co-founder moves $37m ETH to exchanges. Grayscale launches trusts for STX & NEAR. Coinbase loses against SEC on DOGE sweepstakes. ALGO ad attacks BTC, SOL, ETH. Phantom now no.2 finance App on Google Play.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 123 - ETHEREUM KEEPS GOING!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JE3lB00G/fomo-hour-123-ethereum-keeps-going</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JE3lB00G/fomo-hour-123-ethereum-keeps-going"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T15:43:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH soars, ETF S1 approvals expected in hours. US house greenlights FIT21 bill with broad support. Gensler says SEC already has rules for crypto. Hong Kong set to allow ETH staking for ETFs. ETH OI continues to soar. SOL mentioned as next ETF candidate on CNBC. SOL ETF will take years: Bloomberg. MetaMask plans BTC integration. Fed says only 7% of Americans own crypto. SBF heads to a new prison. Hong Kong orders WLD shutdown. TON added to Binance ahead of potential listing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 122 - ETH ETF MOVES CLOSER!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/FlTuDkm9/fomo-hour-122-eth-etf-moves-closer</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/FlTuDkm9/fomo-hour-122-eth-etf-moves-closer"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T16:33:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH ETFs move closer to approval, drop staking. Blackrock ETF see biggest inflow in 6 weeks. Grayscale ETH discount narrows under 10%. BTC & ETH heading for ATH: StanChart. Banana zone squared coming for ETH: Raoul Pal. Trump accepts crypto donations including DOGE. Pelosi mulls support of crypto bill. Farcaster raises $150M, DEGEN up 20%. Coinbase to launch gold & oil futures trading. Uniswap ‘ready to fight’ against SEC. Vitalik proposes solutions to MEV problems. Phantom may soon support email sign-up. Jupiter announces initiative to tokenise RWAs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 121 - ETHEREUM GOD CANDLES!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/EE1S4Hf4/fomo-hour-121-ethereum-god-candles</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/EE1S4Hf4/fomo-hour-121-ethereum-god-candles"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T16:17:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH ETF suddenly seems likely, flurry of amendments. ETH biggest daily gain ever, gains SOL market cap. ETF approval shifted due to political pressure. ETF approval may come as soon as tomorrow. Squeeze liquidates $230M of shorts. ETH OI hits record of $14B on exchanges. BTC nears ATH amid 6th straight day of ETF inflows. SOL flips ETH in Google search trends. House Democrats will not whip against crypto bills. Anti-crypto FDIC chair Gruenberg to step-down. Grayscale CEO steps down, ETHE discount narrows. Genesis settles for $2B with creditors. Binance to focus launchpad on higher float projects. SEI v2 launch coming next week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Do A Little With Chikai]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BGCnTbKb/we-do-a-little-with-chikai</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BGCnTbKb/we-do-a-little-with-chikai"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T18:21:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week’s episode, we sit down with our good friend and one of the biggest supporters of the pod, Chikai Ohazama. Chikai is the co-founder of Keyhole which was acquired by Google and became Google Earth. He is one of the most caring art collectors in our space, as well as an extremely talented AI artist.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>