<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-09-18T13:17:10.035Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-09-18T13:17:10.035Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Money Laundering Concerns: South Korean Regulators Target Unregulated OTC Crypto Trades]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7540e462bf</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/money-laundering-concerns-south-korean-regulators-target-unregulated-otc-crypto-trades/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T13:13:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[South  
Korean financial regulators are intensifying their scrutiny of over-the-counter  
(OTC) cryptocurrency trades due to rising anxieties about their potential use  
in criminal activities. Reports indicate that regulatory authorities in the  
country are closely monitoring transactions in the unregulated OTC crypto  
market.
South Korean Authorities Address Criminal Aspects  
of Virtual Assets
Deputy  
Chief Prosecutor Ki No-Seong and Park Min-woo from the Financial Services  
Commission (FSC), along with other key regulatory officials, convened for a  
session titled "Criminal Legal Issues Related to Virtual Assets." In  
the meeting focusing on the unregulated OTC crypto market, No-Seong stressed  
the need for regulatory oversight to combat money laundering concerns.
Seong's statem…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tareq Sikder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin miners seek alternative energy sources to cut costs]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18910799/Bitcoin-miners-seek-alternative-energy-sources-to-cut-costs</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18910799/Bitcoin-miners-seek-alternative-energy-sources-to-cut-costs"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T13:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The next generation of crypto mining will focus on alternative energy sources for efficiency.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quieting The Storm: Shiba Inu Marketing Lead Addresses Important Community Questions]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18910796/Quieting-The-Storm-Shiba-Inu-Marketing-Lead-Addresses-Important-Community-Questions</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18910796/Quieting-The-Storm-Shiba-Inu-Marketing-Lead-Addresses-Important-Community-Questions"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T13:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu’s Shibarium has gained traction in the month following its launch, as the adoption of the Ethereum layer-2 solution seems to be growing at an impressive rate. However, while Shibarium seems to be doing well, this hasn’t really translated into a steady growth in the price of SHIB,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chainlink (LINK) Notches 9% In One Day As Market Rebounds, What’s Next?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18910814/Chainlink-LINK-Notches-9-In-One-Day-As-Market-Rebounds-Whats-Next</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18910814/Chainlink-LINK-Notches-9-In-One-Day-As-Market-Rebounds-Whats-Next"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T13:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oracle service provider Chainlink native token LINK has surged today as the crypto market records a significant uptick. The cryptocurrency is up by 9.02%, trading at $6.80 with a trading volume of $198 million, representing an over 179% increase in the last 24 hours. One of the factors likely to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[​​Orbs teams up with QuickSwap to introduce Liquidity Hub]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18910756/Orbs-teams-up-with-QuickSwap-to-introduce-Liquidity-Hub</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18910756/Orbs-teams-up-with-QuickSwap-to-introduce-Liquidity-Hub"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T13:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Orbs, a Layer-3 infrastructure network designed for decentralized applications, has just introduced Liquidity Hub. This innovative platform aims to provide … Continued]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain data visualization firm Bubblemaps raises $3.2 million in seed funding]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18910761/Blockchain-data-visualization-firm-Bubblemaps-raises-32-million-in-seed-funding</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18910761/Blockchain-data-visualization-firm-Bubblemaps-raises-32-million-in-seed-funding"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T13:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The firm visualizes on-chain data in colorful clusters of circles called a bubble map, aiming to make blockchain data easier to understand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong Influencer Arrested Over JPEX Exchange Promotion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197573</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197573/hong-kong-influencer-arrested-over-jpex-exchange-promotion"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T12:55:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joseph Lam’s arrest followed the suspension of trading on crypto exchange JPEX, which regulators allege was operating without a license.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Hussey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Technical Analysis: BTC Surges Above $27,000 as Bulls Return Ahead of Upcoming FOMC Meeting]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7540e75167</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-ethereum-technical-analysis-btc-surges-above-27000-as-bulls-return-ahead-of-upcoming-fomc-meeting/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T12:54:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin pushed past the $27,000 level on Monday, as markets prepared for the upcoming Federal Reserve interest rate decision. Bullish sentiment was in full force in today’s session, despite the prospect of yet another rate hike. Ethereum was also higher to start the week.
 
Bitcoin
 
Bitcoin surged to a multi-week high on Monday, as traders began to anticipate the upcoming Federal Reserve meeting.
 
BTC/USD rallied to an intraday high of $27,222.98 earlier in today’s session, following a low of $26,415.52 the day prior.
 
As a result of the move, bitcoin climbed to its strongest point since August 31, when price peaked at $27,576.
 
 
Bitcoin chart by TradingView
 

 
 

 
Despite the rise in momentum, bulls may not be satisfied, and are likely targeting a ceiling at the $28,000 mark.
 
Monday’s gain comes as the relative strength index (RSI) jumped past a ceiling of 53.00, and is now residing at 58.25.
 
A resistance level of 60.00 will likely be the next major target for bulls currently in the market.
 
 
Ethereum
 
Ethereum (ETH) also moved higher to start the week, as traders rejected a breakout below the $1,600 point.
 
Following a low of $1,609.96 on Sunday, ETH/USD rose to an intraday high of $1,653.07 earlier in the day.
 
This has resulted in ethereum surging to its highest point in the past ten days, closing in on a recent resistance of $1,660 in the process.
 
 
Ethereum chart by TradingView
 

 
 
Although price strength in ETH has also surpassed an obstacle of its own, it is on the cusp of colliding with another at the 50.00 mark. The index currently sits at a reading of 49.61.
 
It is likely that a breakout above this mark could lead ETH back above $1,700.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
How would an interest rate hike impact crypto prices? Leave your thoughts in the comments below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Analyst Hints at Possible Collapse of Crypto Exchange Binance]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18910768/Crypto-Analyst-Hints-at-Possible-Collapse-of-Crypto-Exchange-Binance</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18910768/Crypto-Analyst-Hints-at-Possible-Collapse-of-Crypto-Exchange-Binance"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T12:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Twitter analyst and Fintech Executive Adam Cochran, in a recent post on X, once again hinted at a possible imminent collapse of crypto exchange giant Binance. According to Cochran, the cracks at the company are starting to show, and the effects will be “nasty when this dam (Binance)...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BTC price hits $27.4K as Bitcoin open interest matches Grayscale peak]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18910743/BTC-price-hits-274K-as-Bitcoin-open-interest-matches-Grayscale-peak</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18910743/BTC-price-hits-274K-as-Bitcoin-open-interest-matches-Grayscale-peak"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T12:51:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC price gains more than 3% as the week begins, but concerns over open interest “ramping up” almost $1 billion in hours offer a sense of Grayscale deja vu.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amplifying Cryptocurrency Returns: The Power Of Compounding With Seasonal Tokens]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18910798/Amplifying-Cryptocurrency-Returns-The-Power-Of-Compounding-With-Seasonal-Tokens</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18910798/Amplifying-Cryptocurrency-Returns-The-Power-Of-Compounding-With-Seasonal-Tokens"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T12:47:20.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Six F1 Crypto Sponsors Jump Ship Ahead of Singapore Grand Prix]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18910735/Six-F1-Crypto-Sponsors-Jump-Ship-Ahead-of-Singapore-Grand-Prix</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18910735/Six-F1-Crypto-Sponsors-Jump-Ship-Ahead-of-Singapore-Grand-Prix"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T12:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fewer crypto logos on cars and racetracks alike dominate the Singapore Formula One (F1) Grand Prix.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get Ready For Bitcoin’s Next Surge: Analyst Believes ‘This Is The Beginning’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7540e1655b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/get-ready-for-bitcoins-next-surge-analyst/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T12:40:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) aficionados have something to smile about as crypto expert Jason Pizzino shares his optimistic outlook on the cryptocurrency’s future trajectory. Pizzino, known for his insightful analysis, recently took to YouTube to voice his conviction that Bitcoin is currently in the early stages of a bull market. His insights are setting the crypto community abuzz.
 
In his latest YouTube video, Pizzino emphasized that the cryptocurrency market is displaying compelling signs of strength and the potential for significant growth. While crypto markets can be notoriously unpredictable, Pizzino believes that the alpha coin is primed for an impressive uptrend. 
 
However, he cautions that the beginnings of a bull market are not always crystal clear. As Pizzino puts it:
 
 
 “Once things become…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hut 8 receives green light from Canadian Supreme Court for USBTC merger]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18910717/Hut-8-receives-green-light-from-Canadian-Supreme-Court-for-USBTC-merger</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18910717/Hut-8-receives-green-light-from-Canadian-Supreme-Court-for-USBTC-merger"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T12:37:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Supreme Court of British Columbia has given Hut 8 final clearance to complete a proposed merger with USBTC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jordan Peterson: Scrap the Banks, Adopt Bitcoin | EP 825]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18910739/Jordan-Peterson-Scrap-the-Banks-Adopt-Bitcoin-EP-825</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18910739/Jordan-Peterson-Scrap-the-Banks-Adopt-Bitcoin-EP-825"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T12:36:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jordan Peterson suggests it’s time to scrap banks and use Bitcoin - Finbold✓ SUBSCRIBE - https://bit.ly/3QbgqTQ✓ LEAVE A LIKE & COMMENT LIMITED MERCH DROP:► https://simplybitcoin.com/collections/allSPONSORS:► Foundation Passport: https://foundationdevices.com/simply► Swan:...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jim Cramer Warns of Market Volatility Ahead of the Fed’s September 20th FOMC Press Conference]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18910718/Jim-Cramer-Warns-of-Market-Volatility-Ahead-of-the-Feds-September-20th-FOMC-Press-Conference</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18910718/Jim-Cramer-Warns-of-Market-Volatility-Ahead-of-the-Feds-September-20th-FOMC-Press-Conference"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T12:31:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jim Cramer, the host of CNBC’s “Mad Money,” recently discussed various topics affecting the stock market, from the Federal Reserve’s upcoming FOMC meeting to earnings reports and IPOs. He emphasized that while the market has seen rallies, several factors could introduce turbulence. The Federal...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon Labs Details MATIC to POL Transition in New Proposals]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18910699/Polygon-Labs-Details-MATIC-to-POL-Transition-in-New-Proposals</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18910699/Polygon-Labs-Details-MATIC-to-POL-Transition-in-New-Proposals"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Thursday, September 14, 2023, Polygon Labs officially announced the release of three Polygon Improvement Proposals (PIPs) as part of the proposed Polygon 2.0 upgrade. Prominently featured among them is the replacement of MATIC with POL as the new native coin in the Polygon ecosystem. Last...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Billionaire Investor Mark Cuban’s Crypto Wallet Hacked]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18910700/Billionaire-Investor-Mark-Cubans-Crypto-Wallet-Hacked</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18910700/Billionaire-Investor-Mark-Cubans-Crypto-Wallet-Hacked"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T12:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Approximately $900,000 worth of cryptocurrency has reportedly been siphoned from a hot wallet owned by...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New York State of the USA Is Bringing New Rules for Bitcoin Exchanges to List and Delist Coins!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18910701/New-York-State-of-the-USA-Is-Bringing-New-Rules-for-Bitcoin-Exchanges-to-List-and-Delist-Coins</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18910701/New-York-State-of-the-USA-Is-Bringing-New-Rules-for-Bitcoin-Exchanges-to-List-and-Delist-Coins"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T12:22:06.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Marks 8th Year of US Commodity Status]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7540eca440</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/legal/bitcoin-marks-8th-year-us-commodity-sec-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T12:18:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On September 17, 2015, the U.S. Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) officially declared Bitcoin a commodity, a distinction that eight years later continues to set it apart from other cryptocurrencies that have yet to earn this status.
While regulatory uncertainty still looms over other more centralized, digital assets, the CFTC's classification of Bitcoin as a commodity established a regulatory framework for Bitcoin, one that allows it to be treated like other classical commodities including gold and precious metals.
In its ruling, the CFTC stated that Section 1a(9) of the CEA defines commodity to include "all services, rights, and interests in which contracts for future delivery are presently or in the future dealt in."
"The definition of a 'commodity' is broad... Bitcoin and othe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reed Macdonald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IPO Market Remains Sluggish as Instacart Set to Go Public]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18910655/IPO-Market-Remains-Sluggish-as-Instacart-Set-to-Go-Public</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18910655/IPO-Market-Remains-Sluggish-as-Instacart-Set-to-Go-Public"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T12:12:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite Arm successful debut, experts believe the IPO market is still sluggish.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk's $258 Billion Dogecoin Lawsuit: DOGE Architects Reject Allegations]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18910650/Elon-Musks-258-Billion-Dogecoin-Lawsuit-DOGE-Architects-Reject-Allegations</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18910650/Elon-Musks-258-Billion-Dogecoin-Lawsuit-DOGE-Architects-Reject-Allegations"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T12:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin creator and lead contributor reject allegations of assisting Elon Musk as lawsuit worth $258 billion progresses]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto prediction of the author of Rich Dad Poor Dad]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18910753/The-crypto-prediction-of-the-author-of-Rich-Dad-Poor-Dad</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18910753/The-crypto-prediction-of-the-author-of-Rich-Dad-Poor-Dad"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T12:10:12.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Mover Americas: Friend.tech Drives Up Coinbase’s Base Blockchain Activity]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18910660/First-Mover-Americas-Friendtech-Drives-Up-Coinbases-Base-Blockchain-Activity</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18910660/First-Mover-Americas-Friendtech-Drives-Up-Coinbases-Base-Blockchain-Activity"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest price moves in bitcoin (BTC) and crypto markets in context for Sept. 18, 2023. First Mover is CoinDesk’s daily newsletter that contextualizes the latest actions in the crypto markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Tops $27K a Week After Death Cross Formation With Fed Likely to Extend Rate Pause]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7540ee6879</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/09/18/bitcoin-tops-27k-a-week-after-death-cross-formation-with-fed-likely-to-extend-rate-pause/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T12:06:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. rates traders do not see the Fed raising rates for the rest of the year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arm’s Shares Continue to Fall in Premarket, Bernstein Sets $46 Target]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18910654/Arms-Shares-Continue-to-Fall-in-Premarket-Bernstein-Sets-46-Target</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18910654/Arms-Shares-Continue-to-Fall-in-Premarket-Bernstein-Sets-46-Target"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T12:02:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shares of Arm fell in premarket trading Monday following a successful debut day that valued the company at over $65 billion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain's Unseen Backbone Securing Billions of Dollars in Value]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154993</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154993/blockchains-unseen-backbone-securing-billions-of-dollars-in-value"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T12:01:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chronicle Protocol aims to redefine the oracle space with Scribe, when it launches to the public this month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Punches Above $27K, But Analysts Have Bearish Price Predictions]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7540e86e34</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/09/18/bitcoin-ether-remain-steady-but-analysts-have-bearish-price-predictions/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T11:52:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin traded just under $26,700 and ether exchanged hands at $1,630 as of Asian afternoon hours Monday, adding just 0.5% in the past 24 hours.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFTs in Adtech and Digital Art - Everything You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7540e9de9e</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/nfts-in-adtech-and-digital-art-everything-you-need-to-know/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T11:42:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The  
intersection between Non-Fungible Tokens (NFTs) with the worlds of advertising  
technology (adtech) and digital art is changing how we view and interact with  
digital material. NFTs have grown in popularity, capturing the attention of  
artists, advertisers, and collectors alike. 
Understanding  
Non-Financial Transactions
Non-fungible  
Tokens (NFTs) are indivisible and irreplaceable digital assets. Unlike fungible  
and interchangeable cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin or Ethereum, each NFT has  
a unique value and ownership record maintained on a blockchain. NFTs are  
perfect for demonstrating ownership and provenance in the digital environment  
due to their uniqueness and immutability.
The NFT  
Expansion
The NFT market  
has grown rapidly, with high-profile sales capturing at…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Ferreira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Bitcoin To Crypto: Weekly Guide To Key Market Events]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7540ea03e5</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-crypto-weekly-guide-key-market-events/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T11:41:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bitcoin and crypto market is holding its breath in anticipation of the week ahead, particularly due to a singular, critical event: the US Federal Reserve’s interest rate decision followed by the FOMC press conference featuring Fed Chairman Jerome Powell. This looming decision has the potential to ripple through all financial markets, from Wall Street to the decentralized corridors of Bitcoin and crypto.
 
Other events that could have a potential impact on the market are rather rare this week. Only the already last week approved liquidation of the FTX holdings (maximum $100 million, $200 million per week under certain circumstances) could be news-worthy. However, since the liquidations do not require any announcements, there will be no big headlines.
 
FOMC And Interest Rate Decision On…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Latam Insights: Crypto Adoption Booms in Latam Nations, Milei Bashes Socialism]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7540eafd07</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/latam-insights-crypto-adoption-booms-in-latam-nations-milei-bashes-socialism/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T11:34:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Latam Insights, a compendium of Latin America’s most relevant crypto and economic news during the last week. In this issue: Brazil, Argentina, and Mexico are present in Chainalysis’ 2023 Global Crypto Adoption Index; Argentine presidential candidate Javier Milei blames socialism for Argentina’s economic decline, and Bull Bitcoin expands to Costa Rica.
Brazil, Argentina, and Mexico Among the Countries With Most Crypto Adoption
Brazil, Argentina, and Mexico are among the 20 countries in the world where cryptocurrencies are used most, according to the Chainalysis 2023 Global Crypto Adoption Index, a yearly report that seeks to estimate the countries where the most grassroots crypto adoption is located.
According to several metrics, Chainalysis estimated that India, Nigeria, and Vie…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malta Seeks to Change Its Crypto Rulebook to Get Ready for MiCA]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7540d42979</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/09/18/malta-seeks-to-change-its-crypto-rulebook-to-get-ready-for-mica/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T11:26:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The country's financial watchdog wants to align its framework with EU-wide rules set to take effect in 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camomile Shumba, Jack Schickler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Cryptocurrency Exchange Case: Trevor Lawrence and Influencers Settle Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7540d4c967</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/ftx-cryptocurrency-exchange-case-trevor-lawrence-and-influencers-settle-lawsuit/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T11:22:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NFL  
quarterback Trevor Lawrence, along with popular YouTube influencers Kevin  
Paffrath and Tom Nash, have reached a settlement in a lawsuit related to their  
endorsements of the now-defunct FTX cryptocurrency exchange. 
High-Profile  
Figures Face Similar Lawsuits
According  
to Bloomberg's report on September 16, the terms of the settlement have not  
been disclosed. This development marks the first resolution among more than a  
dozen celebrities and firms accused of assisting Sam Bankman-Fried, the Founder of FTX, in  
alleged investor deception. He is set to face a criminal trial in Manhattan  
next month.
Other  
high-profile individuals, including Tom Brady, Gisele Bundchen, Steph Curry,  
Shaquille O’Neal, and Larry David, who had endorsed FTX, are also facing similar  
lawsuit…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tareq Sikder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether Co-Founder Sizes Up PayPal’s Stablecoin Ambitions]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7540d7426b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/09/18/tether-co-founder-sizes-up-paypals-stablecoin-ambitions/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T11:05:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tether pioneer William Quigley, who was also an early investor in PayPal, said he doubts the payments giant will bring much innovation to the stablecoin space.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Presearch: The Decentralized Search Engine]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7540d78949</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/introducing-presearch-the-decentralized-search-engine/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T11:03:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. La Jolla, California – September 18th, 2023 – Presearch is a revolutionary platform that is changing the way people search the internet. Presearch is a decentralized search engine designed to empower users, respect their privacy, and provide a better search experience. It is powered by almost 70,000 user computers (nodes) in more than 100 countries.
 
In a world where Big Tech search engines dominate the web with monolithic force, Presearch stands apart as a user-centric, privacy-focused, and community-driven alternative.
 
Why Presearch Matters
 
Traditional search engines are subject to censorship, collecting vast amounts of user data, invading privacy, tracking and profiling users for profit, while controlling the world’s access to information.
 
“The world needs a search…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elizabeth Warren's Digital Asset Anti-Money Laundering Act Gets Nine New Sponsors]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197565</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197565/elizabeth-warrens-digital-asset-anti-money-laundering-act-gets-nine-new-sponsors"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T10:53:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Warren's controversial Digital Asset Anti-Money Laundering Act has received support from nine more U.S. senators.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple CEO: The Billion-Dollar Problem That Will Make XRP The Next Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7540d2b770</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ripple-ceo-xrp-bitcoin/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T10:42:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple’s XRP token is believed to boast huge potential, but many have wondered how valuable the token can become. Ripple’s CEO Brad Garlinghouse seems to have an answer as he claims the token could become the next Bitcoin.
 
How XRP Can Become The Next Bitcoin
 
A prominent figure in the XRP community, JackTheRippler, shared a clip from an interview that Garlinghouse had with Bloomberg. In the interview, the CEO mentioned that the token could become the next bitcoin if his company, using the XRP token, could solve a huge financial problem, especially at a large scale running into “trillions of dollars.”
 
 
His statement likely stems from his company’s vision to disrupt the global financial system and become a viable alternative to the traditional system, such as the SWIFT payment system. …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Co-Founder Insists ETH Is a Commodity Amid SEC Crackdown on Crypto Securities]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7540d82415</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ethereum-co-founder-insists-eth-is-a-commodity-amid-sec-crackdown-on-crypto-securities/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T10:04:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum co-founder Joseph Lubin says he stands by his conviction that ether is a commodity despite the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and its chairman, Gary Gensler, trying to assert authority over all crypto tokens, except bitcoin. “I anticipate that, with previous technologies like the internet, the web and cryptography, clear heads will prevail,” said Lubin.
 
Lubin Insists Ether Is a Commodity
 

 
Ethereum co-founder and the CEO of blockchain technology company Consensys, Joseph Lubin, is confident that ETH is a commodity despite the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) increasing its efforts to crack down on crypto securities. He said in an interview with CNBC on Thursday:
 

I stand by my conviction that ether is a commodity.
 

 
The securities regulator ha…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robert Kiyosaki Again Champions Crypto, Labels Fiat ‘FAKE’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7540db0964</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/robert-kiyosaki-champions-crypto/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T09:43:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Renowned author Robert Kiyosaki, best known for his personal finance book ‘Rich Dad, Poor Dad,’ has once again underlined his conviction that traditional fiat currencies are on the path to obsolescence, while cryptocurrencies are poised to become the future of money. 
 
Kiyosaki’s outspoken endorsement of cryptocurrencies has been a recurring theme in his public statements, and his recent comments on social media have reignited the debate on the future of money.
 
Robert Kiyosaki took to the social media platform X to share his thoughts while he was coincidentally in Singapore during the TOKEN2049 conference, one of the largest annual gatherings for crypto enthusiasts and experts. 
 
 
 
In Singapore at same time massive crypto conference is on. Very exciting. Crypto is the future. Fiat…a.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Softbank Looking to Invest Billions in AI After Pausing Crypto Investments]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7540c34d57</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/softbank-looking-to-invest-billions-in-ai-after-pausing-crypto-investments/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T08:40:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Softbank, one of the largest investment management conglomerates in the world, is reportedly eyeing several investments in the artificial intelligence (AI) field after having paused its crypto investments. According to the Financial Times, Softbank founder and chief executive officer Masayoshi Son is prepared to put tens of billions of dollars into AI, with Microsoft-backed Openai being one of these potential opportunities.
Softbank Reportedly Prepared to Invest Billions in AI Initiatives
Softbank, the Japanese investment management conglomerate, is considering entering the field of artificial intelligence (AI) investments, according to reports from the Financial Times. According to two people familiar with the matter, Softbank’s founder and chief executive officer Masayoshi Son is conside…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Whale Takes $150M Bullish Bet on Ether, Trading Data Tracker Shows]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7540cc08c5</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/09/18/crypto-whale-takes-150m-bullish-bet-on-ether-trading-data-tracker-shows/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T08:34:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The large flow was concentrated in the so-called out-of-the-money calls, indicating a bullish outlook on the second-largest cryptocurrency by market volume, according to Greeks.Live]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX’s Crypto Liquidation Sales Unlikely to Cause Market Shock: Coinbase]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7540cc08ad</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/09/18/ftxs-crypto-liquidation-sales-unlikely-to-cause-market-shock-coinbase/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T08:34:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The sale of tokens won’t flood the market because liquidations are bound by sell limits, the report said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Canny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pro-XRP Lawyer Asserts ‘One Day Closer’ To Unveiling ETH Gate]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7540cd79a1</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/pro-xrp-lawyer-one-day-closer-unveiling-eth-gate/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T08:22:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a series of tweets that have captured the attention of the crypto community, John E Deaton, a lawyer known for his pro-XRP stance, alluded to the existence of damning information about ETH Gate that could be disclosed soon. His comments come in the wake of tweets from Steven Nerayoff, an early adviser to the Ethereum network, who recently had criminal extortion charges against him dismissed in May this year.
 
Deaton’s statement was a response to Nerayoff’s lawyer, Michael Scotto, who tweeted, “My client Steven Nerayoff fought and won the battle of a lifetime. Steve has been advised to follow proper procedures and is fully committed to making all his facts known at a time and manor that serves the interests of justice and the people. #staytuned.”
 
Deaton responded, “I’ve always said th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Europe is ‘Eating America’s Lunch’: U.S. Held Back by Bitcoin ETF Paralysis]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197538</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197538/europe-is-eating-americas-lunch-u-s-held-back-by-bitcoin-etf-paralysis"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T01:10:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Europe is probably a bit ahead of the game,” says a Swiss CEO. "The U.S. still has work to do.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nature, Not Humans, Should Be the Model for AI, Says Artist Collective]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197514</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197514/ai-agi-nature-fungi-plants-not-humans-theta-noir"/>
        <updated>2023-09-17T23:22:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Challenging conventional AI ethics, Theta Noir believes AI should mimic nature's sustainability rather than human excess.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Celebrities Settle Lawsuits Over FTX Deals]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197509</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197509/first-celebrities-settle-lawsuit-over-ftx-deals"/>
        <updated>2023-09-17T23:05:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Among those who agreed to settle were Jacksonville Jaguars quarterback Trevor Lawrence, and YouTube influencers Tom Nash and Kevin Paffrath.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PolkaWorld Hits Pause as Founder Faults Polkadot Governance Change]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197507</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197507/polkaworld-hits-pause-as-founder-faults-polkadot-governance-change"/>
        <updated>2023-09-17T22:42:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the center of the controversy is a new structure that grants every token holder a vote.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week on Crypto Twitter: Idris Elba Falls Flat, and Are We Near the End of Binance?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197480</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197480/this-week-on-crypto-twitter-idris-elba-stellar-binance-executive-turnover"/>
        <updated>2023-09-17T18:16:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several crypto Twitter heads remarked on the shifty personnel changes over at Binance this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prosecutors Say SBF’s Lawyers Are Trying to Taint Juror Pool]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197479</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197479/prosecutors-say-sbfs-lawyers-are-trying-to-taint-juror-pool"/>
        <updated>2023-09-17T17:56:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ahead of Sam Bankman-Fried's trial, the government objects to voir dire questions from the defense.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Steady Week for Bitcoin and Ethereum, Toncoin Balloons 23%]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197429</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197429/this-week-in-coins-bitcoin-steady-ethereum-invlationary-toncoin-rises"/>
        <updated>2023-09-16T19:16:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not even a big-budget Idris Elba commercial could save Stellar’s XLM from taking a nose dive.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Metaverse Token Coming From Animoca Game Studio]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197441</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197441/bitcoin-metaverse-token-coming-from-animoca-game-studio"/>
        <updated>2023-09-16T19:15:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animoca Brands' Darewise subsidiary will launch a metaverse token via Bitcoin Ordinals to power an ecosystem led by the game Life Beyond.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Billionaire Mark Cuban Loses $870,000 In Crypto Scam]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197439</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197439/mark-cuban-crypto-scam-metamask-hack"/>
        <updated>2023-09-16T19:01:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The owner of the Dallas Mavericks lost roughly $870,000, although the figures could have been much worse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Did Google Ban AI Artists from Running Stable Diffusion on Its Cloud?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197428</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197428/google-colab-stable-diffusion-web-ui-ban"/>
        <updated>2023-09-16T18:33:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Users have claimed that Google banned them from Colab after they tried to run Stable Diffusion with the famous WebUI popularized by A1111.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some Celebrities Are Embracing AI to Stay Ahead of Deepfake Makers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197412</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197412/celebrities-using-ai-to-get-ahead-of-deepfakes"/>
        <updated>2023-09-16T17:39:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prominent actors are reportedly using Metaphysic Pro to take ownership of the data needed to reproduce their likenesses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is KYC? How Crypto Exchanges Prevent Money Laundering]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=112290</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-kyc-how-crypto-exchanges-prevent-money-laundering"/>
        <updated>2023-09-16T09:51:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Know-your-customer (KYC) requirements are a growing part of Web3, as crypto becomes more integrated with the existing financial system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korea’s Lazarus Group Has Stolen $240M in Crypto in Just 104 Days: Elliptic]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197407</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197407/north-korea-lazarus-hacks-240m-crypto-just-104-days-elliptic"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T22:20:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adding to the tally is the $54 million hack of crypto exchange CoinEx, which blockchain sleuths at Elliptic now believe Lazarus was likely behind.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nouns Fork: Disgruntled NFT Holders Exit With $27 Million From Treasury]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197400</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197400/nouns-fork-disgruntled-nft-holders-exit-27-million-from-treasury"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T21:28:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Nouns NFT collective on Ethereum, which is building open-source IP by funding creative projects, fractures after a widely supported fork.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Judge Grants SEC’s Motion to Unseal Key Documents in Binance Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197396</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197396/judge-sec-unseal-key-documents-binance-lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T21:20:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The judge’s approval follows accusations that Binance US exhibited a “lack of transparency” in the SEC’s investigation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Gemini Poised to Take On AI Titans OpenAI and Microsoft]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197378</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197378/google-gemini-poised-to-take-on-ai-titans-openai-and-microsoft"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T19:58:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has reportedly started testing its most advanced AI model to date, Gemini, which it says has impressive multimodal capabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[London Design Museum Lets Visitors Test Iconic Runway Looks via AR]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197360</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197360/london-design-museum-lets-visitors-test-iconic-runway-looks-ar"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T19:41:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An augmented reality experience developed by Snapchat maker Snap is part of the museum's new "Rebel: 30 Years of London Fashion" exhibit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephanie Hirschmiller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Companies Aren't Banks, Hong Kong Warns Investors]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197359</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197359/crypto-companies-arent-banks-hong-kong-warns-investors"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T19:32:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Describing themselves as banks may mislead the public into entrusting the companies with their savings,” read the regulator's notice.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PUBG Creator Krafton Unveils 'Overdare' NFT Game With AI Creation Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197345</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197345/pubg-creator-krafton-unveils-overdare-nft-game-ai-creation-tools"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T18:19:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overdare looks to deliver a Roblox-like game creation experience within an open-world metaverse, built on top of the Settlus blockchain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[One Year After the Merge: Where Does Ethereum Stand?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197341</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197341/one-year-after-the-merge-where-does-ethereum-stand"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T18:17:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In terms of price, Ethereum is trading at approximately the same price it was when the merge happened in 2022. But that's just part of the story.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Bitcoin Mining Really Greener? Here's What's Going On]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197344</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197344/is-bitcoin-mining-really-greener-heres-whats-going-on"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T17:58:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new report says Bitcoin mining is mostly sustainable, and that environmental FUD is "overstated."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Yieldflow: the DeFi Protocol for Passive Growth of Digital Assets]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155780</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/how-to-use-yieldflow-the-defi-protocol-for-passive-growth-of-digital-assets"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T16:17:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While centralized exchanges expose customers to security risk in the event that they collapse, and to unpredictable liquidity, inflexible staking rules, and more, YieldFlow aims for a smooth user experience governed by trust, security, and decentralization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Reiff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Toncoin, the Cryptocurrency Conceived by Telegram?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197320</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-toncoin-the-cryptocurrency-conceived-by-telegram"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T16:12:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TON uses a sharded, proof of stake consensus mechanism, meaning it can process transactions in parallel, improving transaction speed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Hussey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arnault Family LVMH Succession Saga: Will Pro-Crypto Sons Prevail?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156798</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156798/arnault-family-lvmh-succession-saga-will-pro-crypto-sons-prevail"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T15:47:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bernard Arnault is preparing to choose which child will inherit his $400 billion luxury empire. The decision could have major implications for crypto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Are Wrapped Tokens? How They Work and What They’re Used For]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=99801</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-are-wrapped-tokens"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T14:54:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wrapped tokens such as WBTC help move assets across blockchains. Here’s why they matter to the crypto ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph O'Neill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried: 'There’s Nothing I Can Do to Make My Lifetime Impact Net Positive']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197291</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197291/sam-bankman-fried-theres-nothing-i-can-do-to-make-my-lifetime-impact-net-positive"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T12:25:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 250 pages of leaked writings about the collapse of FTX, its co-founder Sam Bankman-Fried laments that he feels "broke" and "hated."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celsius Exec Pleads Guilty, Agrees to Cooperate in Case Against CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197292</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197292/celsius-exec-pleads-guilty-agrees-to-cooperate-in-case-against-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T11:44:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former chief revenue officer Roni Cohen-Pavon reached an agreement with the U.S. Attorney’s office along with his guilty plea.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Accuses Binance US of ‘Numerous Discovery Failures’ in Court Filing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197285</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197285/sec-accuses-binance-us-of-numerous-discovery-failures-in-court-filing"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T11:04:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The regulator claimed that the exchange had produced just 220 documents during discovery, including “unintelligible screenshots.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Cast It Into the Fire': GOP Moves to Advance Bills That Ban CBDC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156790</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156790/cast-it-into-the-fire-gop-bills-ban-cbdc"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T22:59:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Republicans argue a CBDC would undermine existing stablecoins, and usher Americans down a slippery slope toward mass government surveillance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Defense Startup Helsing Raises $223 Million to 'Protect Democracies']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156787</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156787/ai-defense-startup-helsing-raises-223-million-protect-democracies"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T22:59:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With backing from Saab and General Catalyst, Helsing will focus on AI enhancements for the NATO Eurofighter and Future Combat Air System.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SoftBank's Arm Stock Soars 25% as AI Chip Designer's IPO Nets $65 Billion Valuation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156772</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156772/softbank-arm-stock-soars-25-ai-chip-designer-ipo-nets-65-billion-valuation"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T22:10:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apparently fueled by AI hype, semiconductor technology company Arm Holdings had a sensational Nasdaq return on Thursday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Christie's Turns Keith Haring Digital Art Into NFC-Equipped Patch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156777</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156777/christies-turns-keith-haring-digital-art-nfc-equipped-patch"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T21:15:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MNTGE and the auction house transformed one of Keith Haring's works—currently on sale as an NFT—into a patch with its own proof of ownership.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephanie Hirschmiller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gods Unchained's Daniel Paez on the Future of NFT Gaming Interoperability]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/obt7FGYr/gods-unchaineds-daniel-paez-on-the-future-of-nft-gaming-interoperability</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/obt7FGYr/gods-unchaineds-daniel-paez-on-the-future-of-nft-gaming-interoperability"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T20:27:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daniel Paez, executive producer on NFT card-battling game Gods Unchained, speaks with Decrypt Culture Editor Andrew Hayward about what the future of NFT game interoperability will really look like—and what it won't.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LaLiga NFT Fantasy Soccer Games Coming to North America]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156757</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156757/laliga-nft-fantasy-soccer-games-coming-north-america"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T20:17:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spanish soccer league LaLiga has tapped gaming startup GameOn to develop fantasy games built around NFTs for the U.S. and Canada.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Cohen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bull Bitcoin Exchange Expands From Canada to Costa Rica]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156750</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156750/bull-bitcoin-exchange-expands-canada-costa-rica"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T19:29:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company announced that it will tap into Costa Rica's widely used payment infrastructure SINPE Movil for Bitcoin swaps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Princess Peach to Pikachu: 6 Biggest Reveals From Nintendo Direct]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156719</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156719/from-princess-peach-to-pikachu-6-biggest-reveals-from-nintendo-direct"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T18:58:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Nintendo Direct stream offered fans a look at loads of upcoming Switch games. Here's a look at the biggest announcements and trailers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Mino Games is Using Artificial Intelligence]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/SrT1Afj7/how-mino-games-is-using-artificial-intelligence</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/SrT1Afj7/how-mino-games-is-using-artificial-intelligence"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T22:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mino Games CEO Sasha McKinnon tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about how the studio's upcoming game Dimensionals will use real-time AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INTERVIEW: How Will Aurory Use NFTs and Crypto?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qv3VwNmM/interview-how-will-aurory-use-nfts-and-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qv3VwNmM/interview-how-will-aurory-use-nfts-and-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T15:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Natoli, Aurory's Head of Marketing and Business Development, tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how the Aurory games will use NFTs and crypto and shares the studio's broader stance on the tech.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Cloud's James Tromans on the Intersection of AI and Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OeD4uoLj/google-clouds-james-tromans-on-the-intersection-of-ai-and-web3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OeD4uoLj/google-clouds-james-tromans-on-the-intersection-of-ai-and-web3"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google's Global Head of Google Cloud for Web3 James Tromans sat down with Decrypt's Jason Nelson to discuss how AI can help Web3 companies come to market faster and the real value of Web3 tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastering NFT Trading - Degen U]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/HQGt1Vrq/mastering-nft-trading-degen-u</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/HQGt1Vrq/mastering-nft-trading-degen-u"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T07:08:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Take Degen U's new course, Mastering NFT Trading, and earn an on-chain certificate. A top instructor will help you identify trends, seize the right moment to trade, weed out scams—and have fun while doing it!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Space Nation CEO on Working With 'Independence Day' Director Roland Emmerich]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LpznLhtx/space-nation-ceo-on-working-with-independence-day-director-roland-emmerich</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LpznLhtx/space-nation-ceo-on-working-with-independence-day-director-roland-emmerich"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T17:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jerome Wu, CEO of Space Nation, tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the upcoming Space Nation Online game in development and shares details on Space Nation Cofounder Roland Emmerich's role in the project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GAME REVIEW: Champions Arena from Gala Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qUE1RlDx/game-review-champions-arena-from-gala-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qUE1RlDx/game-review-champions-arena-from-gala-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Champions Arena is a turn-based fantasy RPG from Gala Games, where characters can become NFTs and crypto can be used to purchase gems, one of the game's synthetic currencies. Decrypt's Kate Irwin takes us inside the game for her thoughts on the fun, mobile-first title.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apex Legends Voice Actor Ben Prendergast on the Future of Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/X3RKdsaG/apex-legends-voice-actor-ben-prendergast-on-the-future-of-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/X3RKdsaG/apex-legends-voice-actor-ben-prendergast-on-the-future-of-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T18:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Voice actor Ben Prendergast, who's voiced characters in games like Apex Legends and God of War Ragnarok, shares his opinions on the tech space's history of "bubbles" and whether blockchain gaming has a future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Future of AI Stardom and Robotics With SingularityNET COO Janet Adams and Desdemona]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yVQaZI71/the-future-of-ai-stardom-and-robotics-with-singularitynet-coo-janet-adams-and-desdemona</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yVQaZI71/the-future-of-ai-stardom-and-robotics-with-singularitynet-coo-janet-adams-and-desdemona"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T16:45:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this interview, SingularityNET COO Janet Adams explains the intricate details that went into creating the Desdemona robot AI from Hanson Robotics and future plans for the AI Diva.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto a 'No-Brainer' for Video Games, Says Mino Games CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rdynom8C/crypto-a-no-brainer-for-video-games-says-mino-games-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rdynom8C/crypto-a-no-brainer-for-video-games-says-mino-games-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T18:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mino Games CEO Sasha MacKinnon, developer of the upcoming Dimensionals game, tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the studio's approach to digital collectibles.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Wagner's 'Controversial Take' on Crypto in Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tc2nKeqA/michael-wagners-controversial-take-on-crypto-in-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tc2nKeqA/michael-wagners-controversial-take-on-crypto-in-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T16:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Solana's PlayGG, Star Atlas CEO Michael Wagner shares his "controversial take" on crypto in games, shares the challenges of developing the upcoming scifi game, and how crypto's volatility has changed his perspective with Decrypt's Jason Nelson.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>