<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-05-14T05:15:38.757Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-05-14T05:15:38.757Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin and Ethereum ETFs saw sharp outflows in Hong Kong market]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19485276/Bitcoin-and-Ethereum-ETFs-saw-sharp-outflows-in-Hong-Kong-market</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19485276/Bitcoin-and-Ethereum-ETFs-saw-sharp-outflows-in-Hong-Kong-market"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T05:08:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong's spot Bitcoin and Ethereum exchange-traded funds (ETFs) recorded massive outflows in the latest trading session, according to data from Farside.On Monday, three Bitcoin fundsBorsera, AMC, and Harvestexperienced outflows totaling $32.7 million, marking the largest since their launch....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OKX Enters Australia: Launches Spot and Derivatives Crypto Exchange]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74239a2d2d</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/okx-enters-australia-launches-spot-and-derivatives-crypto-exchange/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T05:08:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OKX has officially launched its cryptocurrency exchange in Australia with spot and derivatives trading services, the company announced today (Tuesday). Although spot trading is available for all users in the country, only verified wholesale clients will be able to trade derivatives.
Crypto Exchange in the Land Down Under
The spot crypto exchange service of OKX listed 85 tokens, with a total of 170 crypto pairs. It also promised to expand the number of tokens offered “on an ongoing basis.”
The cryptocurrency exchange further highlighted that the launch of local services in Australia would allow users from the country to deposit and withdraw AUD using local banks. Aussies can further access peer-to-peer and convert functions for cryptocurrencies. Furthermore, the crypto exchange also allows …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arnab Shome</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK Crypto Advisory Firm Shuts Down Over Investor Losses, Accounting Neglect]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19485249/UK-Crypto-Advisory-Firm-Shuts-Down-Over-Investor-Losses-Accounting-Neglect</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19485249/UK-Crypto-Advisory-Firm-Shuts-Down-Over-Investor-Losses-Accounting-Neglect"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T04:57:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The UK government’s Insolvency Service has shut down a London-based crypto advisory firm that claimed to offer investment advice in cryptocurrencies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase confirms system-wide outage: Assures ‘funds are safe’]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19485247/Coinbase-confirms-system-wide-outage-Assures-funds-are-safe</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19485247/Coinbase-confirms-system-wide-outage-Assures-funds-are-safe"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T04:51:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto exchange Coinbase has suffered a 'system wide' outage, rendering platform unusable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Falcon Labs Settles with CFTC in Landmark Case Over Unregistered Status]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19485226/Falcon-Labs-Settles-with-CFTC-in-Landmark-Case-Over-Unregistered-Status</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19485226/Falcon-Labs-Settles-with-CFTC-in-Landmark-Case-Over-Unregistered-Status"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T04:44:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CFTC has reached a settlement with Falcon Labs, Ltd., a Seychelles-based entity, for operating as an unregistered futures commission merchant (FCM) and facilitating access to digital asset exchanges without proper registration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USDT-TON Hits $200M Circulation in Less Than a Month]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19485210/USDT-TON-Hits-200M-Circulation-in-Less-Than-a-Month</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19485210/USDT-TON-Hits-200M-Circulation-in-Less-Than-a-Month"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T04:19:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[USDt-TON has hit an adoption milestone, hitting a circulation of $200 million within a month of issuance. This growth sets a new record for the fastest token circulation in Tether’s USDt’s history and highlights the growing demand for USDT within the TON ecosystem. TON announced this achievement...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mark Cuban Says SEC Didn't Learn A Thing After Mt. Gox, Applauds Japan's Response: 'They Are Still So Stupid']]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19485223/Mark-Cuban-Says-SEC-Didnt-Learn-A-Thing-After-Mt-Gox-Applauds-Japans-Response-They-Are-Still-So-Stupid</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19485223/Mark-Cuban-Says-SEC-Didnt-Learn-A-Thing-After-Mt-Gox-Applauds-Japans-Response-They-Are-Still-So-Stupid"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T04:18:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mark Cuban, the billionaire investor and television personality, criticized the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission for its inaction following the Mt. Gox debacle. Cuban also lauded Japan’s regulatory response to the incident. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Crypto Regulations Tighten as Joe Biden Blocks Chinese-Owned Mining Site]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19485240/US-Crypto-Regulations-Tighten-as-Joe-Biden-Blocks-Chinese-Owned-Mining-Site</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19485240/US-Crypto-Regulations-Tighten-as-Joe-Biden-Blocks-Chinese-Owned-Mining-Site"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T04:14:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On May 13, The President of the United States, Joe Biden, issued a directive prohibiting MineOne from acquiring real estate near a strategic missile base. The US government found that MineOne, mainly owned by Chinese nationals, aimed to use the property for crypto mining. This decision stems...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto exchange OKX launches local regulated entity in Australia]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19485207/Crypto-exchange-OKX-launches-local-regulated-entity-in-Australia</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19485207/Crypto-exchange-OKX-launches-local-regulated-entity-in-Australia"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T04:14:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The expansion comes 12 months after the firm announced its intention to expand down under.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Firm Falcon Labs Settles ‘Unregistered Activities’ Case With CFTC For $1.7M]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7423811dc0</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-firm-falcon-labs-settles-with-cftc/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T04:06:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) has taken action against crypto brokerage firm Falcon Labs, a company based in the Seychelles, for failing to register as a futures commission merchant (FCM) in the US. 
 
Interestingly, this marks the CFTC’s first enforcement action against an unregistered futures commission merchant involved in providing “unauthorized access” to crypto exchanges.
 
Falcon Labs Faces CFTC Crypto Crackdown
 
Under the CFTC order, Falcon Labs is required to immediately cease acting as an unregistered FCM, specifically by facilitating US individuals’ access to digital asset derivatives trading platforms. 
 
In addition, Falcon Labs was ordered to pay a disgorgement of $1.7 million and a civil penalty of $589,000, the latter in recognition of the company’s coope…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin dominance tops 50% amidst market volatility: What’s next?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19485186/Bitcoin-dominance-tops-50-amidst-market-volatility-Whats-next</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19485186/Bitcoin-dominance-tops-50-amidst-market-volatility-Whats-next"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T04:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin has dominated the crypto market over the years. Its dominance could increase further.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Firm Falcon Labs Settles ‘Unregistered Activities’ Case With CFTC For $1.7M]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19485187/Crypto-Firm-Falcon-Labs-Settles-Unregistered-Activities-Case-With-CFTC-For-17M</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19485187/Crypto-Firm-Falcon-Labs-Settles-Unregistered-Activities-Case-With-CFTC-For-17M"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T04:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) has taken action against crypto brokerage firm Falcon Labs, a company based in the Seychelles, for failing to register as a futures commission merchant (FCM) in the US. Interestingly, this marks the CFTC’s first enforcement action against an...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New daily Runes etched on Bitcoin falls 99% from post-halving peak]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19485151/New-daily-Runes-etched-on-Bitcoin-falls-99-from-post-halving-peak</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19485151/New-daily-Runes-etched-on-Bitcoin-falls-99-from-post-halving-peak"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T03:34:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Only 157 new Runes were etched on Bitcoin on May 13, which contributed to just $3,835 in transaction fees paid to Bitcoin miners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Russian Authorities Propose Steep Fines for Crypto Miners Operating in Residential Apartments]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74238d0bea</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/report-russian-authorities-propose-steep-fines-for-crypto-miners-operating-in-residential-apartments/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T03:23:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Russian authorities have reportedly proposed to impose hefty fines on suspected crypto miners operating from residential properties. Authorities may also consider including amendments to the Code of Administrative Offenses which imposes liability on those misusing electricity. Proposed Measures Aimed at Curbing Rising Power Outage Cases Authorities in Russia have signaled their intention to pursue private […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop sparked the 2021 memecoin bull run — will history repeat itself?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19485133/GameStop-sparked-the-2021-memecoin-bull-run-will-history-repeat-itself</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19485133/GameStop-sparked-the-2021-memecoin-bull-run-will-history-repeat-itself"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T03:11:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following the return of Keith Gill — also known as “Roaring Kitty” — traders are keeping their eyes peeled for the next big stock or crypto rally — but analysts aren’t so sure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Motion Application Submitted To Seal Materials Related to SEC Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19485279/Ripple-Motion-Application-Submitted-To-Seal-Materials-Related-to-SEC-Lawsuit</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19485279/Ripple-Motion-Application-Submitted-To-Seal-Materials-Related-to-SEC-Lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T03:11:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Labs and the SEC's legal clash intensifies as Ripple motion application to seal materials has been submitted.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop Stock Price Surges As Meme-Stock Frenzy Returns: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19485277/GameStop-Stock-Price-Surges-As-Meme-Stock-Frenzy-Returns-Report</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19485277/GameStop-Stock-Price-Surges-As-Meme-Stock-Frenzy-Returns-Report"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T03:09:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop stock price surged, doubling due to a post by "Roaring Kitty". Yet, the increase doesn't match the 2021 frenzy due to changes in the trading landscape and economic context.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoin Exchange Inflows See Severe Drop: Why This Is Bad For Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74238ecd45</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/stablecoin-exchange-inflows-drop-why-bad-bitcoin/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T03:04:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data shows that stablecoin exchange inflows have seen a sharp drop recently. This could be bearish for the Bitcoin price.
 
Ethereum-Based Stablecoins Have Seen Low Exchange Deposits Recently
 
As CryptoQuant author Axel Adler Jr. pointed out in a post on X, the exchange inflows of Ethereum-based stablecoins have recently dropped below the 90-day average.
 
The “exchange inflow” here refers to an on-chain indicator that tracks the total amount of any given cryptocurrency being transferred to the wallets associated with centralized exchanges.
 
 
When the value of this metric is high, investors are now depositing large amounts of the asset into these platforms. Generally, holders send their coins to the exchanges for trading purposes, so this trend can show high demand for exchangi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Historical cycle data suggests Bitcoin has left the ‘danger zone’ — Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19485121/Historical-cycle-data-suggests-Bitcoin-has-left-the-danger-zone-Analyst</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19485121/Historical-cycle-data-suggests-Bitcoin-has-left-the-danger-zone-Analyst"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T03:03:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following a 23% correction, Bitcoin may have just entered a post-halving reaccumulation zone, according to one analyst.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is The Crypto Winter Thawing? US Bitcoin ETFs Record First Inflows In Weeks – Coinshares]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19485100/Is-The-Crypto-Winter-Thawing-US-Bitcoin-ETFs-Record-First-Inflows-In-Weeks-Coinshares</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19485100/Is-The-Crypto-Winter-Thawing-US-Bitcoin-ETFs-Record-First-Inflows-In-Weeks-Coinshares"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T03:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After experiencing outflows for four consecutive weeks, US spot Bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) have marked a notable shift in momentum, witnessing net inflows once again. According to recent data from CoinShares, digital asset investment products have seen inflows totaling $130 million for...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Korean Bithumb Airdrop Recipients Hit With Tax Bills, Exchange Responds]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19485115/South-Korean-Bithumb-Airdrop-Recipients-Hit-With-Tax-Bills-Exchange-Responds</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19485115/South-Korean-Bithumb-Airdrop-Recipients-Hit-With-Tax-Bills-Exchange-Responds"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T03:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[South Koreans who received airdrop tokens and prizes from the Bithumb crypto exchange from 2018 to 2021 could face unexpected tax bills.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoin Exchange Inflows See Severe Drop: Why This Is Bad For Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19485113/Stablecoin-Exchange-Inflows-See-Severe-Drop-Why-This-Is-Bad-For-Bitcoin</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19485113/Stablecoin-Exchange-Inflows-See-Severe-Drop-Why-This-Is-Bad-For-Bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T03:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data shows that stablecoin exchange inflows have seen a sharp drop recently. This could be bearish for the Bitcoin price. Ethereum-Based Stablecoins Have Seen Low Exchange Deposits Recently As CryptoQuant author Axel Adler Jr. pointed out in a post on X, the exchange inflows of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum: What does ETH’s future hold as investors continue to leave?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19485112/Ethereum-What-does-ETHs-future-hold-as-investors-continue-to-leave</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19485112/Ethereum-What-does-ETHs-future-hold-as-investors-continue-to-leave"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T03:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum's recent price decline seems to be turning investors away. Where does ETH go from here?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Black Donald Trump Surges 600% Before Consolidating, As Shiba Inu and Dogecoin Lag]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19485099/Black-Donald-Trump-Surges-600-Before-Consolidating-As-Shiba-Inu-and-Dogecoin-Lag</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19485099/Black-Donald-Trump-Surges-600-Before-Consolidating-As-Shiba-Inu-and-Dogecoin-Lag"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T02:54:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Black Donald Trump (BLATRUMP) could become a viral memecoin, like Shiba Inu (SHIB) and Dogecoin...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Tether Next? CEO Responds To Brad Garlinghouse’s Claims Of US Gov’t Persecution]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7423746e4f</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/is-tether-next-ceo-responds-to-brad-garlinghouses-claims-of-us-govt-persecution/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T02:01:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent podcast interview, Ripple’s CEO Brad Garlinghouse stated that Tether, the largest Stablecoin issuer by market share, is next on the US government’s target list. Tether’s CEO, Paolo Ardoino, refuted Garlinghouse’s comments and accused him of spreading fear.
 
 
Is Tether Next In Line?
 
Ripple’s CEO joined Quantum’s founder, Chris Vasquez, for his World Class podcast on May 10. During the interview, he discussed his outlook for the future of crypto and his thoughts on the US government’s crackdown on the industry.
 
 
New Episode with Brad Garlinghouse @bgarlinghouse, CEO of @Ripple is live!
 
We Cover:– Brad's wild journey scaling Ripple– Fighting SEC Lawsuits, the importance of taking risk & being courageous– Invaluable CEO lessons on building culture, hiring A+ players & endu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rubmar Garcia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who Is Roaring Kitty, and What Does His Return Mean for Crypto?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230566</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230566/who-is-roaring-kitty-keith-gill-deepfuckingvalue-back-on-twitter"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T01:38:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Keith Gill's Twitter account came back to life after more than two years, leading GameStop stock to more than double in value and a Solana-based tribute coin to spike 1,900%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Latam Powerhouse Crypto Exchange Bitso Launches Web3 Wallet]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742377f1b6</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/latam-powerhouse-crypto-exchange-bitso-launches-web3-wallet/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T01:22:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitso, the Mexico-based, Latam-focused cryptocurrency exchange, recently launched its own Web3 wallet, targeting the decentralized finance (defi) ecosystem. The idea behind this new product is to ease the onboarding of Bitso’s customers into this landscape, allowing them to dabble in non-fungible tokens (NFTs), decentralized exchange, and other services from a trustable platform. Bitso Launches Web3 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining Giant Bitfarms Axes CEO Amidst $27 Million Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742371d2b0</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-mining-giant-bitfarms-axes-ceo/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T01:02:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Toronto-based Bitcoin mining company Bitfarms has announced the termination of its interim president and chief executive officer (CEO), Geoffrey Morphy after he filed a $27 million lawsuit against the company. 
 
According to Bloomberg, the lawsuit alleges breach of contract and “wrongful termination” and seeks compensatory and punitive damages. Bitfarm believes the claims are without merit and intends to defend itself.
 
Bitfarms Shifts Leadership
 
Geoffrey Morphy, who assumed both leadership positions in late 2022, was initially slated to leave the company pending the appointment of his successor. However, following the lawsuit, Bitfarms immediately terminated Morphy’s employment, and he no longer serves as a company director.
 
 
Bitfarms has named Nicolas Bonta, the company’s chairman…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Kazakhstan Secures ISO Certifications for Security and Privacy]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74237d7d6d</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/binance-kazakhstan-secures-iso-certifications-for-security-and-privacy/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T00:23:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Kazakhstan has been awarded the ISO 27001 and ISO 27701 certifications, marking significant recognition for its robust information security and privacy management systems. These certifications, issued by the British Standards Institution after a thorough audit, affirm Binance’s compliance with the highest industry standards. The achievement emphasizes the platform’s dedication to maintaining a secure and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China Takes Down $295M Crypto Underground Bank: Beginning Of A Bigger Crackdown?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74237fa15d</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/china-takes-down-295m-crypto-underground-bank/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T00:01:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese law enforcement has disrupted a covert banking network that leveraged cryptocurrencies to execute unauthorized foreign exchange transactions totaling around 2.14 billion yuan ($295.8 million).
 
This illicit operation mainly converted the Chinese yuan into the South Korean won, evading the established legal frameworks for currency exchange.
 
 
Uncovering The Shadow Crypto Banking Network 
 
In Jilin province, police apprehended six people connected to this operation, underscoring the growing role of digital currencies in bypassing standard financial regulations.
 
According to official statements, this clandestine banking entity utilized cryptocurrencies’ inherent “anonymity and decentralization” to carry out these unlawful transactions.
 
It was reported that the accused managed …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether CEO and Ripple CEO Clash Over USDT — Brad Garlinghouse Says ‘I Wasn’t Attacking Tether’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74236442f2</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/tether-ceo-and-ripple-ceo-clash-over-usdt-brad-garlinghouse-says-i-wasnt-attacking-tether/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T23:14:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tether CEO Paolo Ardoino has responded to remarks made by Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse, branding him as an “uninformed CEO” and accusing him of fostering uncertainty about stablecoin USDT amid a U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) investigation into his company. In reply, Garlinghouse clarified that his comments were not an attack on Tether but […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Analyst Predicts 3,000% Surge For Shiba Inu – Here’s The Timeline]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74236571f6</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/3000-surge-for-shiba-inu/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T23:03:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto analyst Davie Satoshi has dropped a bullish prediction for Shiba Inu as part of what might be the future outlook for major meme coins. According to the analyst, SHIB is one of the meme coins with the potential to go on a 1,000% to 3,000% price surge amidst a flurry of cryptocurrencies in the meme coin niche. SHIB, on the other hand, is currently struggling with bearish price action as the bulls find themselves outnumbered by the bears.  
 
Surge Potential For Shiba Inu
 
The crypto market is full of different meme coins, each with its own community. Particularly, meme coin demand has shot up this year, with many new meme coins shooting up in value. However, investing in meme coins has its own demerits. This is because the value of these cryptocurrencies is driven by hype and sentime…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[President Biden Blocks Chinese-backed Bitcoin Mining Firm From Owning Land Near a Wyoming Nuclear Missile Base]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742362890c</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/legal/president-biden-blocks-chinese-backed-bitcoin-mining-firm-from-owning-land-near-a-wyoming-nuclear-missile-base"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T22:16:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[United States President Joe Biden has issued an order prohibiting the acquisition of certain real property by MineOne Cloud Computing Investment I L.P., citing national security concerns. The order, based on findings outlined by the President, aims to safeguard critical assets near Francis E. Warren Air Force Base (Warren AFB) in Cheyenne, Wyoming.
The President's order stems from evidence indicating that MineOne Partners Limited, a British Virgin Islands company majority owned by Chinese nationals, and related entities planned to acquire real estate within one mile of Warren AFB. This real estate, specifically described as Lot 1, Block 10 North Range Business Park 3rd Filing, and the nature of operations conducted by MineOne, poses potential national security risks due to its close proxim…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nik Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden Orders Chinese-Backed Crypto Mining Firm to Divest Land Near US Missile Base]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742363df24</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/biden-orders-chinese-backed-crypto-mining-firm-to-divest-land-near-us-missile-base/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T22:04:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[President Joe Biden has issued an order that blocks Mineone Partners Ltd., a Chinese-backed cryptocurrency mining company, from owning land near Wyoming’s Francis E. Warren Air Force Base, which is a strategic missile base. This measure requires the divestment of land used for crypto mining and the removal of surveillance-capable equipment, citing national security risks. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Deja Vu: Indicator Mirrors Pattern That Led To 2021 Top]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74236c0028</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-deja-vu-mirrors-pattern-led-2021-top/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T22:03:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data suggests a Bitcoin indicator is currently mirroring the same trend that led to the top of the bull run in 2021.
 
Bitcoin Long-Term Holder Distribution Appears To Be Ending
 
As explained by CryptoQuant community manager Maartunn in a post on X, the BTC long-term holders are currently showcasing a trend that’s reminiscent of 2021.
 
The “long-term holders” (LTHs) are Bitcoin investors who have been keeping their coins dormant (that is, not transferring or selling them from their wallet) for more than 155 days.
 
 
Generally, the longer a holder keeps their coins still, the less likely they are to move them at any point. As such, the LTHs, with their long holding times, are considered the market’s resolute hands.
 
These investors usually don’t react to events in the wider mar…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Steven Nerayoff Calls out Joseph Lubin for Damaging Crypto Market]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74236e2e55</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/steven-nerayoff-calls-out-joseph-lubin-for-damaging-crypto-market/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T21:44:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Steven Nerayoff, a former adviser to the Ethereum network, has publicly denounced Joseph Lubin, co-founder of the Ethereum Project and the founder of Consensys, and other “bad actors” for their detrimental actions in the cryptocurrency market. In a tweet, Nerayoff clarifies that his dispute is not with Ethereum as a whole, but specifically with Lubin […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop Meme Coins Are Taking Over Solana as Pump.fun Sets Record]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230546</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230546/gamestop-meme-coins-are-taking-over-solana-as-pump-fun-sets-record"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T21:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Among the 14,500 tokens deployed on Solana through pump.fun were more than a few GameStop-themed tokens.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Middle East-Focused Crypto Exchange, Rain, ‘Likely Exploited’ for $14.8 Million, Says Zachxbt]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742369e8b3</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/middle-east-focused-crypto-exchange-rain-likely-exploited-for-14-8-million-says-zachxbt/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T21:13:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cryptocurrency exchange Rain, which focuses on the Middle East, was likely exploited for $14.8 million on April 29, according to online crypto investigator Zachxbt. Zachxbt says he traced the stolen funds to a bitcoin address with 137.9 bitcoins and an ethereum address holding 1,881 ether. Crypto Exchange Yet to Confirm Attack According to online […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bracebridge Capital Becomes Largest Bitcoin ETF Holder, Investing $380 Million In All-In Bet]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74236af0da</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bracebridge-cap-becomes-largest-bitcoin-etf-holder/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T21:05:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week, the US spot Bitcoin ETF market experienced a notable shift in investor sentiment. Positive inflows were reported, breaking a streak of outflows that had persisted for almost a month. The week concluded with a significant $116 million positive inflows, indicative of growing interest in the newly approved index funds.
 
Notably, a new player entered the market and made substantial investments, quickly becoming one of the largest holders of Bitcoin ETFs.
 
Bracebridge Capital Nets Major ETF Holdings
 
Bracebridge Capital, a Boston-based hedge fund, reported owning $262 million worth of Ark Invest’s ARKB ETF. Additionally, they emerged as the largest owner of Blackrock’s IBIT with an investment of $81 million. 
 
 
Bracebridge Capital also holds $20 million of Grayscale’s Bitcoin Tr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Blocks China-Tied Crypto Miners as 'National Security Risk' Near Nuke Base]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74236b0358</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/05/13/us-blocks-china-tied-crypto-miners-as-national-security-risk-near-nuke-base/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T21:04:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[President Joe Biden ordered a cryptocurrency mining facility near Warren Air Force Base in Wyoming to halt operations on Monday, calling it a threat to national security.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why, for Some, Crypto Is the Defining Political Issue of Our Times]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7423554671</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/opinion/2024/05/13/why-for-some-crypto-is-the-defining-political-issue-of-our-times/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T20:45:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’d be foolish for people to vote against their own interests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Kuhn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lightspark CEO David Marcus: Lightning Network Will Become the World’s ‘Interoperability Neutral Settlement Layer’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742356dfa4</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/lightspark-ceo-david-marcus-lightning-network-will-become-the-worlds-interoperability-neutral-settlement-layer/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T20:33:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Marcus, CEO of Lightspark, a company that offers lightning network (LN) related services, has stated that LN will become the “interoperability neutral settlement layer” for the world. Marcus declared that only Bitcoin is “neutral enough” to be implemented as the enabler between national payment systems, granting companies and institutions adopting it an edge for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Andrew Tate Says He’s Cashed $500K in Bitcoin to Go ‘All In’ on GameStop]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230538</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230538/andrew-tate-bitcoin-gamestop-gme-taking-down-wall-street"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T19:20:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The controversial influencer says he’s “taking down Wall Street” through meme coin stocks, with GME short sellers out $1.4 billion in its revival.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF Weekly Investments Grow For First Time In Over a Month]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230520</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230520/bitcoin-etf-130-million-inflows-ethereum-etf-hope-dims"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T19:08:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Investor sentiment may be shifting, CoinShares says, as Grayscale’s GBTC outflows were the lowest since January.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI Shows Off Voice Chatbot, Touts New GPT-4o AI Model]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230460</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230460/openai-chatgpt-4-o-voice-chatbot"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T18:24:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The live demonstration of new conversational capabilities fueled comparisons to the virtual companion depicted in the movie “Her.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF Bonanza: Largest Holder of BlackRock, Ark Funds Revealed]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230512</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230512/bitcoin-etf-bonanza-largest-holder-blackrock-ark-revealed"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T17:37:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A little-known hedge fund in Boston has a massive stake in spot Bitcoin ETFs from BlackRock and ARK Invest/21Shares.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Pumps as GameStop Rally Kickstarts Memes Frenzy]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230509</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230509/dogecoin-pumps-gamestop-rally-memes-frenzy"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T16:54:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin and political meme coins are booking significant gains amid the GameStop stock resurgence, with some Donald Trump coins up 30% or more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop Tribute Meme Coin on Solana Surges 1,900% as GME Fever Returns]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230508</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230508/gamestop-meme-coin-solana-surges-gme-fever-returns"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T16:16:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The GME tribute meme coin on Solana is blasting off Monday, delivering sizable returns outpacing those of GameStop shares.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop Trading Paused Nine Times as Roaring Kitty Return Drives Meme Rally]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230459</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230459/gamestop-trading-paused-nine-times-roaring-kitty-meme-rally"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T15:22:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meme stocks and cryptocurrencies boomed Monday after Roaring Kitty, the internet figure behind the 2021 GameStop saga, posted online.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fantasy Top Volume Jumps as Crypto Twitter NFT Game Adds 40 New Heroes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230444</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230444/fantasy-top-volume-jumps-as-crypto-twitter-nft-game-adds-40-new-heroes"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T13:40:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The game's latest update adds tweaked mechanics and new heroes to Fantasy Top, while two big competitions have been announced.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Filing Hits Back at Coinbase 'Power Grab' Accusations]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230437</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230437/sec-filing-hits-back-at-coinbase-power-grab-accusations"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T11:42:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a court filing, the SEC argued that Coinbase can't demand that the regulator write new rules for crypto "from the ground up."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Leads The Bounce]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QoXLhFzb/solana-leads-the-bounce</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QoXLhFzb/solana-leads-the-bounce"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T11:06:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto up despite ETF outflow, SOL outperforms. HK ETFs also see another net daily outflow. SOL flips ETH again in 24hr DEX volume. SOL revenue now 50% of ETH. Bitcoin above $1m by 2030: Dorsey. Bitcoin & Kucoin get license in India. Kraken tries to get SEC case dismissed. Stand with Crypto sets up election war chest. VIP customers make up two thirds of Binance volume. NOT to launch on Binance & OKX. TON up 20%, speculation it will be listed after NOT. Securitize & BlackRock look to launch on ARB. Franklin Templeton calls for ‘Base season’. EIGEN claims go live today, will be un-transferable. Eclipse founder leaves after harassment claims.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To AI: Fine Tune Your Chatbot Privacy Settings]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230311</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230311/how-to-ai-chatbot-privacy-history-settings-training"/>
        <updated>2024-05-12T18:08:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Privacy is a huge concern amid the widespread deployment of artificial intelligence. Here's how you can take (some) control of your information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Crypto Games: 'Notcoin' Token Launch Date, 'Fantasy Top' Takes Over, and Rugging for Fun]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230404</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230404/this-week-crypto-games-notcoin-token-launch-date-fantasy-top-rugging-fun"/>
        <updated>2024-05-12T17:27:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Catch up on this week’s biggest crypto and NFT gaming news and find some weekend reads in our latest roundup.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week on Crypto Twitter: Fantasy Top Tops the Charts, Trump Courts Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230285</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230285/this-week-on-crypto-twitter-fantasy-top-donald-trump-crypto-election"/>
        <updated>2024-05-12T17:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tom Brady also reentered the crypto conversation, albeit likely against his will.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Bitcoin Is Boring But Bizarre Meme Coin Antics Continue]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230265</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230265/this-week-in-coins-bitcoin-boring-meme-coins-down"/>
        <updated>2024-05-11T16:49:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top cryptocurrencies Bitcoin and Ethereum are down and meme coins followed—but they at least kept things interesting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Crypto Startup Founder’s Diary]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230365</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230365/crypto-startup-founder-diary"/>
        <updated>2024-05-11T15:58:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this occasional series, Brother Bing takes us inside “MegaETH,” a company she co-founded that aims to make Ethereum more user friendly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shuyao Kong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum ETFs: Here Are All the Applications Awaiting SEC Approval]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230228</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230228/ethereum-etfs-all-applications-awaiting-sec-approval"/>
        <updated>2024-05-11T12:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many major investment firms hope to get the green light from the SEC to list spot Ethereum ETFs in the U.S. Here's the running list.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why ShapeShift Founder Erik Voorhees Is Pivoting to a Privacy-Centric AI Startup]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230281</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230281/venice-ai-shapeshift-founder-erik-voorhees-morpheus-open-source"/>
        <updated>2024-05-11T00:25:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new decentralized, open-source Venice AI tool has a less-censored premium tier that is free for Morpheus token holders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will OpenAI Let ChatGPT Make Porn? AI Maker Says It Depends]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230145</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230145/openai-chatgpt-porn-erotica-gore-depends-on-definition-of-porn"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T22:15:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[”We are not in it for creating AI deepfakes or AI porn,” a company product lead says, noting the announcement could have been “more precise.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Vitalik Buterin’s Gas Fee Proposal Make Ethereum More Like Solana?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230223</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230223/vitalik-fee-proposal-ethereum-solana"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T21:25:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ethereum co-founder is proposing some significant changes to the network’s gas fee structure. Would it make it more like its chief competitor?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Banking Giant Wells Fargo Reveals Investments in Bitcoin ETFs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230234</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230234/banking-giant-wells-fargo-reveals-investments-bitcoin-etfs"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T20:03:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wells Fargo has disclosed exposure to Bitcoin via several crypto product investments, a filing with the SEC shows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Is Approaching a Golden Cross: What Does It Mean for Traders?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230242</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230242/dogecoin-price-golden-cross-what-mean"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T19:18:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The meme-inspired cryptocurrency is showing signs of a potential bullish trend. What should traders expect?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Commencement Speaker Defends Ayahuasca-Fueled Speech, Praises Satoshi]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230222</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230222/bitcoin-commencement-speaker-defends-ayahuasca-fueled-speech-praises-satoshi"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T18:57:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From an "embarrassing" paper-hands trade in 2020 to spreading the word in a controversial speech, Christopher Pan recalls his Bitcoin journey.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lightning Labs Is Bringing Stablecoins to the Bitcoin Blockchain: CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230216</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230216/lightning-labs-stablecoins-on-bitcoin-blockchain-ceo"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T18:17:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CEO Elizabeth Stark said that Lightning Labs just ran a test transaction with an asset created using its Taproot Assets protocol.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Is Again Dictated By Fed Policy: Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230233</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230233/bitcoin-price-federal-reserve-interest-rates-alignment-coinshares"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T18:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Fed will likely cut rates later this year, which will bolster Bitcoin’s price, predicts CoinShares.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin and Ethereum Tank as Crypto Liquidations Top $150 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230199</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230199/bitcoin-and-ethereum-tank-as-crypto-liquidations-top-150-million"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T15:13:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Both Bitcoin and Ethereum plunged early Friday, prompting a wave of crypto long positions to be liquidated.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Week in Polkadot: Monthly Active Accounts Hit All-Time High]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230182</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230182/the-week-in-polkadot-monthly-active-accounts-hit-all-time-high"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T14:50:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Polkadot network reached a landmark in terms of active accounts, while the Relay Chain gets an important technical update.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will McCurdy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friend.tech Price Bounces Back 23% After Chaotic V2 Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230170</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230170/friend-tech-price-bounces-back-23-after-chaotic-v2-launch"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T13:10:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Social media platform Friend.tech endured a challenging launch last week, but its FRIEND token has shown signs of recovering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Blockchain and AI Are Recasting Ancient Occult Practices]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230135</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230135/how-blockchain-and-ai-are-recasting-ancient-occult-practices"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T12:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chaweon Koo, futurist and witch, combines AI and 17th century occult tomes to create vivid, digital demons.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rug.fun Turns Minting Ethereum Meme Coins Into a Competitive Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230157</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230157/rug-fun-turns-minting-ethereum-meme-coins-into-a-competitive-game"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T11:31:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new game on layer-2 network Base has gamified getting rug pulled by middling meme coins. Create, buy, and swap your way to the top… or bottom.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jack Dorsey: Bitcoin Price to Hit $1 Million in 2030]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230155</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230155/jack-dorsey-bitcoin-price-to-hit-1-million-in-2030"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T10:28:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twitter and Block co-founder Jack Dorsey argued that Bitcoin could hit $1 million and "beyond" in 2030, in a recent interview.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining Difficulty Is Plummeting—Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230133</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230133/bitcoin-mining-difficulty-plummeting-why"/>
        <updated>2024-05-09T22:16:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A drop in the price of Bitcoin coupled with reduced mining rewards means fewer miners and a less robust network—for now, at least.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Toncoin Spikes on Notcoin Rollout as Bitcoin, Ethereum Trade Flat]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230129</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230129/toncoin-spikes-notcoin-rollout-bitcoin-ethereum-trade-flat"/>
        <updated>2024-05-09T20:48:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With a Notcoin token launch set and Binance and OKX rewards revealed, Toncoin (TON) is flying high.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consensys Lawsuit Over Ethereum Won’t Deter SEC, Former Regulator Says]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230118</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230118/ethereum-lawsuit-consensys-sec-texas-jurisdiction"/>
        <updated>2024-05-09T20:21:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A legal salvo in Texas put the Securities and Exchange Commission on the defensive, but the agency could bring a lawsuit of its own.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Manhattan’s Newest On-Chain Fashion Store: 9dcc]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Oyjyb2JX/inside-manhattans-newest-on-chain-fashion-store-9dcc</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Oyjyb2JX/inside-manhattans-newest-on-chain-fashion-store-9dcc"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T20:25:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At NFT NYC, Decrypt’s Sander Lutz explored the on-chain fashion brand’s latest pop-up, and spoke to its founder Gmoney about 9dcc’s future expansion plans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BTC Sinks Lower]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rUBpJmbc/btc-sinks-lower</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rUBpJmbc/btc-sinks-lower"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T19:54:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HK ETF volumes disappoint at $11M, crypto sinks. US ETFs see another $52M outflow, 4th straight day. EigenLayer FUD after 5% non-transferable airdrop. EigenLayer also geoblocks USA for claims. 5K+ withdrawals after EigenLayer announcement. Microstrategy bought another $8M BTC in April. Miner revenue drops to 2023 lows. Consensys vs SEC litigation will take years: Cowen. SEC had been investigating ETH for a year. Gensler may have misled Congress with ETH stance.KMNO hits $363M on launch. Decentralised Rune airdrop opens at $102M. Friend Tech airdrop delayed until Thursday. NFTfi airdrop claim today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Very Red Week For Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XVGCQVOH/a-very-red-week-for-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XVGCQVOH/a-very-red-week-for-crypto"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T19:54:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Majors hit locals lows, break key support levels. Liquidations hit $420M, funding remains neutral. ETFs saw $344M withdrawals in April. CZ gets 4-month jail sentence. FTX sells $232M locked SOL at ‘around $100’. Final integration of SOL Firedancer ‘well underway’. SOL, DOGE, XRP open interest down 51% in a month. BlackRock BUIDL largest tokenised treasury fund. Uniswap integrates with Robinhood connect. Stablecoin bill may be coming very soon. Gensler lied to Congress: McHenry. KSI steps back from crypto trading. Coinbase supports Lightning network. BCH creator arrested in Spain. EigenLayer sees 12K queued withdrawals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Full Send]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zCrCMabk/solana-full-send</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zCrCMabk/solana-full-send"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T19:51:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SOL leads majors higher, DEX volume flips ETH. ETH burn rate hits yearly low. BTC needs to reach $67k for a ‘higher high’. Robinhood receives Wells Notice from SEC. Only 10% of stablecoin transactions are real: Visa. May 15th will see corporate filings of BTC purchases. Hayes continues to OTC buy PENDLE. Cartier arrested for USDT money laundering. ENA up 20% on rumours of integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Memecoin Bounce]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yw5MtFvY/memecoin-bounce</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yw5MtFvY/memecoin-bounce"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T19:38:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto volatile but bounces after dovish Fed speech. ETFs see record $563m outflow. BlackRock ETF sees first outflow in 77 days. BlackRock expects more institutions to buy BTC. BNP bank buys BlackRock ETF. BTC continues to sit below STH average cost. Coinbase earnings today. Tether made $4.5bn profit in Q1. MicroStrategy building identity protocol on Ordinals. Dorsey’s Block Inc investigated in US. BlackRock leads investment in RWA firm. STX Nakamoto upgrade delayed by 8 weeks. LayerZero 1st snapshot taken ahead of airdrop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Do A Little With Mike Demarais]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ajrh0oiK/we-do-a-little-with-mike-demarais</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ajrh0oiK/we-do-a-little-with-mike-demarais"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T15:11:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mike dropped knowledge bombs from years of building in the trenches alongside some deep cuts on the early Williamsburg crypto mafia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eth Rally Fails]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Gj7TMrbP/eth-rally-fails</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Gj7TMrbP/eth-rally-fails"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T12:45:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto falls, ETH/BTC rally again marks mini sell-off. Yen carry-trade implosion linked to worries. ETH gas fees hit 6-month lows. 3rd straight week of institutional outflows. Slowing BTC ETF flows are just a pause: Bernstein. BTC now on track for 5 red weeks in a row. BTC may have topped, could hit $35k: Brandt. ETFs may become big sellers: Bianco. Consensys list 4 reasons ETH isn’t a security. Rumours continue to grow of EigenLayer airdrop. Perp DEX volumes continue fall, GMX underperforms. Wallets begin to block US users after Samourai case. WLD in reported partnership talks with OpenAI. Large unlocks this week for SUI, PYTH & MEME.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Sasha Stiles’ Experiential, AI-Infused NFT Drop with Bang & Olufsen]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/6Vi2IgYj/inside-sasha-stiles-experiential-ai-infused-nft-drop-with-bang-olufsen</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/6Vi2IgYj/inside-sasha-stiles-experiential-ai-infused-nft-drop-with-bang-olufsen"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T22:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At a launch party for the collection in New York’s SoHo neighborhood, the artist broke down her latest art experiment, “Four Core Texts,” with Decrypt’s Sander Lutz.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interview: How 'Notcoin' Will Evolve After the NOT Token Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PprnGP14/interview-how-notcoin-will-evolve-after-the-not-token-launch</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PprnGP14/interview-how-notcoin-will-evolve-after-the-not-token-launch"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Open Builders founder Sasha Plotvinov speaks with Decrypt's Sander Lutz at Token 2049 Dubai about how he envisions Notcoin's expansion and evolution after the token drop—into something akin to the "Netflix of social, viral games."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Magic Runes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IGWg0R64/magic-runes</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IGWg0R64/magic-runes"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T13:59:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC stables at $66k, liquidations in narrow range. BTC funding again turns negative in bullish sign. ETFs net inflow after Grayscale moves to lower fees. BTC demand 5x vs supply post-halving: Bitfinex. SOL congestion issue now largely solved. Two SEC lawyers resign after ‘gross abuse of power’. Ripple fights to lower $2bn SEC fine. SAFE trades at $2.8bn FDV after OKX lists. MANEKI hits $150m on first day, China memes pump. Memecoins are ‘black hole you can’t ignore’. DeGods up 20%, may switch back to SOL. Magic Eden launches Runes platform ahead of time.  Louis Vuitton gifts Pharrell jacket to NFT holders. Melania Trump launches necklace with SOL NFTs. Hoodie Punk trades for $620K.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Luxury Watches, Designer Shoes Will Soon Trade Like NFTs: Arianee CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/CSNQG2md/luxury-watches-designer-shoes-will-soon-trade-like-nfts-arianee-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/CSNQG2md/luxury-watches-designer-shoes-will-soon-trade-like-nfts-arianee-ceo"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arianee CEO Pierre-Nicolas Hurstel sat down with Rug Radio founder Farokh and Decrypt’s Sander Lutz at NFT Paris to discuss everything from the future of on-chain luxury to the secret hack to finding the best restaurants in France.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notcoin's Co-Creator Explains the Game's Token Delay—And When to Expect NOT Now]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/7Zx33xo5/notcoins-co-creator-explains-the-games-token-delayand-when-to-expect-not-now</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/7Zx33xo5/notcoins-co-creator-explains-the-games-token-delayand-when-to-expect-not-now"/>
        <updated>2024-04-22T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Notcoin co-creator Sasha Plotvinov spoke with Decrypt's Sander Lutz at Token 2049 Dubai to discuss why the NOT token launch was pushed back from the original 4/20 target, when to expect the listing, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TON’s Justin Hyun Breaks Down The Importance of USDT Coming to Telegram]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ODQI6ACA/tons-justin-hyun-breaks-down-the-importance-of-usdt-coming-to-telegram</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ODQI6ACA/tons-justin-hyun-breaks-down-the-importance-of-usdt-coming-to-telegram"/>
        <updated>2024-04-19T10:14:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Token 2049 in Dubai, The Open Network’s director of investments sat down with Decrypt’s Sander Lutz to discuss what he sees as the game-changing integration of USDT onto TON, and his plans for getting Telegram’s 900 million users to start using crypto in the immediate future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Influencer Ansem Explains His Meme Coin Thesis and Why He’s Bullish on Bitcoin Runes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/u9DHFoK0/crypto-influencer-ansem-explains-his-meme-coin-thesis-and-why-hes-bullish-on-bitcoin-runes</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/u9DHFoK0/crypto-influencer-ansem-explains-his-meme-coin-thesis-and-why-hes-bullish-on-bitcoin-runes"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T21:56:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ansem, the crypto trader who's amassed a sizable following on the back of meme coin Dogwifhat (WIF) and other calls, chats with Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz at Token 2049 Dubai about his meme coin thesis, why he's bullish on Bitcoin Runes, and what he sees ahead for the crypto markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Sander Lutz Braves the Dubai Floods for a Crypto Conference]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/mtjVHGa3/decrypts-sander-lutz-braves-the-dubai-floods-for-a-crypto-conference</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/mtjVHGa3/decrypts-sander-lutz-braves-the-dubai-floods-for-a-crypto-conference"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T21:33:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz reports from Dubai amid a historic storm that flooded the famed city, trudging through the streets to complete his essential task: Attending the Token 2049 crypto conference.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gold Beats Its All Time High]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/6ULgUKVk/gold-beats-its-all-time-high</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/6ULgUKVk/gold-beats-its-all-time-high"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T09:53:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) maintains its trend of reaching higher lows amidst choppy market conditions. Exchange-traded funds (ETFs) witness another influx of $125 million. There's anticipation of Hong Kong approving ETFs for both Bitcoin and Ethereum (ETH) come Monday. Notable institutional investor BlackRock shows interest in Bitcoin. Recent filings reveal increased Bitcoin purchases by banks. A Bitcoin-friendly political party secures victory in the South Korean election. Analyst Kang predicts Bitcoin could surge to $80-100k by May. Meanwhile, Ethereum sees accumulation by stablecoin whales on the rise. A new Ethereum Improvement Proposal (EIP) aims to streamline signing requests. Solana (SOL) experiences a resurgence in activity, reaching yearly highs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>