<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-12-08T14:14:13.759Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-12-08T14:14:13.759Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Spot ETF Approval: Fidelity ETF Listed On DTCC Website And Assigned A Ticker]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7494d50e79</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-spot-etf-fidelity-dtcc/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T14:09:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spot Bitcoin ETF filers continue to make necessary preparations and adjustments in hopes of imminent approval by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). As part of these preparations, asset manager Fidelity Investments has gotten its fund listed on the Depository Trust & Clearing Corporation (DTCC) website.
 
Fidelity’s Spot Bitcoin ETF Ticker Also Revealed
 
Crypto outlet Bitcoin Magazine first made this development of the DTCC listing known in an X (formerly Twitter) post. Fidelity’s ticker for its Spot Bitcoin ETF was also revealed as it will be trading with the ‘FBTC’ ticker. Commenting on this development, Bloomberg analyst Eric Balchunas noted that almost all the issuers have now revealed their tickers. 
 
 
With that almost out of the way, Balchunas mentioned that the next thi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cook Up Magic in Disney Dreamlight Valley with These Recipes]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19095665/Cook-Up-Magic-in-Disney-Dreamlight-Valley-with-These-Recipes</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19095665/Cook-Up-Magic-in-Disney-Dreamlight-Valley-with-These-Recipes"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T14:04:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Disney Dreamlight Valley players, get ready to elevate your culinary skills as we delve into the delectable world of cooking within this enchanting game. Whether you’re looking to make your crops more valuable or strengthen your bonds with the beloved Disney characters of Dreamlight Valley,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Dips as U.S. November Job Growth of 199K Tops Estimates]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7494d609c8</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/12/08/bitcoin-dips-as-us-november-job-growth-of-199k-tops-estimates/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T14:02:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anticipating a slowdown in the economy and easier Fed monetary policy, investors have sharply bid down interest rates in the weeks leading up to this morning's numbers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen  Alpher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin miner revenue per exahash spikes, nearing yearly high]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19095664/Bitcoin-miner-revenue-per-exahash-spikes-nearing-yearly-high</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19095664/Bitcoin-miner-revenue-per-exahash-spikes-nearing-yearly-high"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T14:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quick Take In a notable development in the Bitcoin mining arena, an uptick in miner fees was observed by CryptoSlate yesterday. Miner revenue per Exahash, a metric applied to estimate the daily income of miners in relation to their network hash-power contribution, has experienced a significant...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morph secures multi-million investment from Bitget]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19095630/Morph-secures-multi-million-investment-from-Bitget</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19095630/Morph-secures-multi-million-investment-from-Bitget"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto spot and futures trading platform Bitget announced on Dec 11 a multimillion-dollar investment in Morph, a Layer 2 … Continued]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[L2 Crypto Project Blast Crosses $822M in TVL Ahead of Next Year’s Mainnet Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19095622/L2-Crypto-Project-Blast-Crosses-822M-in-TVL-Ahead-of-Next-Years-Mainnet-Launch</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19095622/L2-Crypto-Project-Blast-Crosses-822M-in-TVL-Ahead-of-Next-Years-Mainnet-Launch"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T13:59:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinspeaker L2 Crypto Project Blast Crosses $822M in TVL Ahead of Next Year’s Mainnet Launch Blast has announced that it is hiring for senior DevOps engineer and senior protocol engineer to ensure a timely mainnet launch in February 2024. L2 Crypto Project Blast Crosses $822M in TVL Ahead of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Preston Pysh: How To Actually Get Free Speech]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7494d657b9</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/technical/preston-pysh-how-to-actually-get-free-speech"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T13:59:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like most things, it’s hard to talk about the solution if we don’t properly define the problem first. So, let’s start there. Last week, Elon Musk and Andrew Ross Sorkin conducted an hour-long interview full of awkward and strange moments. For people not familiar with the battle for free speech taking place. Please take a moment to watch this curated clip to see what I’m talking about.
https://primal.net/e/note1zllssevk93a894tjx9v2e0kfj3m4f28vnr26qjvr3sg5rllnxkaq57h4nw
What in the world is this all about? Well, as you’ll see, it’s about control, legacy string-pullers trying to maintain order, and ultimately it’s about a desire to control your free speech.
The Problem
The current social media landscape is not just a battleground for public opinion but also a complex web of influence and cont…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preston Pysh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BBVA partners with Ripple’s Metaco to expand its crypto services in Switzerland]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19095621/BBVA-partners-with-Ripples-Metaco-to-expand-its-crypto-services-in-Switzerland</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19095621/BBVA-partners-with-Ripples-Metaco-to-expand-its-crypto-services-in-Switzerland"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T13:51:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BBVA in Switzerland will migrate its crypto custody service to Metaco’s Harmonize platform. It also plans to expand its crypto trading services beyond Bitcoin and Ethereum. Ripple acquired Swiss-based Metaco in May 2023. BBVA in Switzerland, the Swiss arm of the Spanish banking giant BBVA,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana liquid staking token JTO surges 85% post-exchange debut, following unique airdrop event]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19095624/Solana-liquid-staking-token-JTO-surges-85-post-exchange-debut-following-unique-airdrop-event</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19095624/Solana-liquid-staking-token-JTO-surges-85-post-exchange-debut-following-unique-airdrop-event"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T13:50:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana-based liquid staking project Jito’s JTO token price soared more than 80% following its trading debut across multiple major exchanges like Coinbase and Binance. Data from CoinMarketCap shows that JTO’s value surged to more than $3 during the past day, representing an 85% growth for the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[India signals potential veto on Pakistan’s BRICS membership bid]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19095608/India-signals-potential-veto-on-Pakistans-BRICS-membership-bid</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19095608/India-signals-potential-veto-on-Pakistans-BRICS-membership-bid"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T13:45:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[India has recently articulated its stance regarding Pakistan’s aspiration to join the BRICS (Brazil, Russia, India, China, South Africa) alliance. Arindam Bagchi, the spokesperson for India’s Ministry of External Affairs (MEA), addressed this topic during a press conference. While responding to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Whopping $880 Million in Bitcoin Shoveled to Exchanges – Will BTC Price Hold?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19095614/Whopping-880-Million-in-Bitcoin-Shoveled-to-Exchanges-Will-BTC-Price-Hold</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19095614/Whopping-880-Million-in-Bitcoin-Shoveled-to-Exchanges-Will-BTC-Price-Hold"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T13:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recent on-chain data shows that staggering hunk of Bitcoins deposited to various crypto exchanges over last week]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s Share Price Surges 5% on Gemini AI Model Announcement]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19095567/Googles-Share-Price-Surges-5-on-Gemini-AI-Model-Announcement</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19095567/Googles-Share-Price-Surges-5-on-Gemini-AI-Model-Announcement"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T13:40:21.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FCA too slow on crypto enforcement, says UK’s spending watchdog]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19095576/FCA-too-slow-on-crypto-enforcement-says-UKs-spending-watchdog</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19095576/FCA-too-slow-on-crypto-enforcement-says-UKs-spending-watchdog"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T13:39:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The UK's Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) has been criticized by the National Audit Office for acting too slow to enforce crypto laws.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Mover Americas: Binance Withdraws an Abu Dhabi License Application]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7494d11765</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/12/08/first-mover-americas-binance-withdraws-an-abu-dhabi-license-application/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T13:39:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest price moves in bitcoin [BTC] and crypto markets in context for Dec. 8, 2023. First Mover is CoinDesk’s daily newsletter that contextualizes the latest actions in the crypto markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley, Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin remains stable as US unemployment drops to 3.7%]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19095564/Bitcoin-remains-stable-as-US-unemployment-drops-to-37</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19095564/Bitcoin-remains-stable-as-US-unemployment-drops-to-37"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T13:38:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quick Take The current US labor market data exhibits an intriguing dynamic, with the unemployment rate settling at 3.7%, notably lower than the consensus of 3.9%. This unexpected decrease signifies an improving job market, potentially indicating a more robust economy. Concurrently, non-farm...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Dips as U.S. November Job Growth of 199K Tops Estimates]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19095606/Bitcoin-Dips-as-US-November-Job-Growth-of-199K-Tops-Estimates</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19095606/Bitcoin-Dips-as-US-November-Job-Growth-of-199K-Tops-Estimates"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T13:37:37.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[El Salvador offers ‘Freedom Visa’ for $1 million crypto investment]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19095578/El-Salvador-offers-Freedom-Visa-for-1-million-crypto-investment</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19095578/El-Salvador-offers-Freedom-Visa-for-1-million-crypto-investment"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T13:34:51.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Technical Analysis: A Lull in Bullish Activity as BTC Enters Consolidation]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7494d1bb04</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-technical-analysis-a-lull-in-bullish-activity-as-btc-enters-consolidation/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T13:34:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As bitcoin stabilizes near $43,654, its market dynamics reveal a mixture of optimism and caution. Oscillators are currently in a neutral to bearish state, and moving averages are indicating a robust buying trend, creating a complex scenario for investors.
 
Bitcoin
 
Presently, bitcoin’s price steadies at $43,654, fluctuating between $43,049 and $43,840. This stability suggests a balanced market, but underlying elements hint at potential fluctuations ahead. With a market capitalization of $854 billion and a 24-hour trading volume of $25.31 billion, bitcoin’s impact on the crypto market is unmistakable.
 
The relative strength index (RSI) positioned at 63, alongside the Stochastic at 37, and the commodity channel index (CCI) at 17, collectively point towards a neutral to a slightly bearish …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BREAKING: US Non-Farm Payrolls Data Released – Bitcoin Reacts]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19095582/BREAKING-US-Non-Farm-Payrolls-Data-Released-Bitcoin-Reacts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19095582/BREAKING-US-Non-Farm-Payrolls-Data-Released-Bitcoin-Reacts"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T13:34:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to the latest information, Non-Farm Employment Data in the USA was announced as 199,000, above the expectation of 183,000. The previous non-farm employment data was at 150,000. Unemployment data was announced as 3.7%, lower than the last data and expectation of 3.9%. US November...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bonk Rally Continues as Galaxy Fox Presale Flies Past $600,000]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19095604/Bonk-Rally-Continues-as-Galaxy-Fox-Presale-Flies-Past-600000</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19095604/Bonk-Rally-Continues-as-Galaxy-Fox-Presale-Flies-Past-600000"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana meme coin BONK is still surging with a vengeance, rising 130% over the past two weeks as Galaxy Fox soars past $600,000 in its presale. Let’s take a closer look at these two projects and see what’s driving the upward momentum.  Bonk Price Soars 1,100% in Past Month October saw Bonk making...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fidelity Investments’ Jurrien Timmer: “Bitcoin Is a Form of Digital Gold, With a Venture Twist”]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19095563/Fidelity-Investments-Jurrien-Timmer-Bitcoin-Is-a-Form-of-Digital-Gold-With-a-Venture-Twist</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19095563/Fidelity-Investments-Jurrien-Timmer-Bitcoin-Is-a-Form-of-Digital-Gold-With-a-Venture-Twist"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T13:27:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On December 7, 2023, Jurrien Timmer, the Director of Global Macro at Fidelity Investments, shared his perspective on Bitcoin’s current state and future prospects in a thread on social media platform X (formerly, known as Twitter). His analysis draws parallels between Bitcoin and traditional...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Breaks Barriers: Crypto Exchanges Volumes Soar to 8-Month High]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7494d3b989</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/bitcoin-breaks-barriers-crypto-exchanges-volumes-soar-to-8-month-high/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T13:20:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin's  
(BTC) rise to 19-month highs in November caused retail investors to trade  
cryptocurrencies much more eagerly last month. This translated into the spot  
volumes of major crypto exchanges, which grew by 58% to the highest levels in  
eight months.
Data from Finance  
Magnates Intelligence shows a month-over-month (MoM) jump in total trading  
volume from $424 billion to $671 billion. Despite this robust monthly  
performance, the figures fell short by 15% compared to the $787 billion  
reported in November 2022.
Crypto Volumes Soar in  
November
Following  
an above-average October for cryptocurrencies, expectations were high for  
November, and the market did not disappoint. Bitcoin climbed an additional 9%,  
closing the month at $38,000, its highest since May 2022. 
The upb…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Damian Chmiel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia CEO Sees Southeast Asia as a Promising AI Market]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19095512/Nvidia-CEO-Sees-Southeast-Asia-as-a-Promising-AI-Market</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19095512/Nvidia-CEO-Sees-Southeast-Asia-as-a-Promising-AI-Market"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T13:20:22.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu: BONE Jumps 20%, Two Reasons for Sudden Rise]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19095518/Shiba-Inu-BONE-Jumps-20-Two-Reasons-for-Sudden-Rise</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19095518/Shiba-Inu-BONE-Jumps-20-Two-Reasons-for-Sudden-Rise"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T13:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Popular Analyst Predicts XRP Price to Rally Over 2000% Based on Golden Cross Pattern]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19095508/Popular-Analyst-Predicts-XRP-Price-to-Rally-Over-2000-Based-on-Golden-Cross-Pattern</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19095508/Popular-Analyst-Predicts-XRP-Price-to-Rally-Over-2000-Based-on-Golden-Cross-Pattern"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T13:18:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinspeaker Popular Analyst Predicts XRP Price to Rally Over 2000% Based on Golden Cross Pattern XRP has shown little or no action of late but its luck may just be about to change, according to popular crypto analyst JD. Popular Analyst Predicts XRP Price to Rally Over 2000% Based on Golden Cross Pattern]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Animoca Brands Fronts $3 Million Funding Round for  Gaming Startup, Gacha Monsters]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19095513/Animoca-Brands-Fronts-3-Million-Funding-Round-for-Gaming-Startup-Gacha-Monsters</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19095513/Animoca-Brands-Fronts-3-Million-Funding-Round-for-Gaming-Startup-Gacha-Monsters"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T13:12:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animoca Brands has spearheaded a $3 million funding round for Gacha Monsters, a burgeoning Japanese gaming startup led by industry veteran Jia Shen. With a noteworthy background in developing titles such as Pokémon Medallion and Battle Cats, alongside contributing to the international version of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terra Classic Price Climbs 77% Amid Do Kwon Extradition Drama]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7494dd3d8f</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/terra-classic-up-77-amid-do-kwon-extradition-drama/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T13:09:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following Do Kwon’s arrest in Montenegro and subsequent legal issues, the price of Terra Classic (LUNC) demonstrated its durability.
 
Do Kwon’s legal representatives will not be able to stop his extradition to the United States. To be more precise, the attorneys had challenged a ruling from late November that permitted this kind of transfer.
 
In the aftermath of the arrest, Terra Classic (LUNC) held its ground with a sustained 77% increase in the last seven days, data from Coingecko shows.
 
 
LUNC Resilience Amid Legal Woes: Kwon Faces Extradition For TerraUSD Manipulation
 
Despite a losing 3.4% in the last 24 hours following the news, LUNC was able to brush off the negative vibes surrounding Kwon’s legal nightmares.
 
A Wall Street Journal report claims that a senior Montenegrin judic…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samourai Wallet Calls out Ocean Pool for Censoring Whirlpool Privacy Transactions]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7494ddd6fc</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/samourai-wallet-calls-out-ocean-pool-for-censoring-whirlpool-privacy-transactions/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T13:04:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samourai, a privacy-focused bitcoin wallet, revealed the changes in the recent Bitcoin Knots software used by Ocean, a Bitcoin mining pool, censor Whirlpool transactions, a kind of coinjoin operation. The wallet explained that Ocean is pursuing a “very slippery slope” by filtering these types of transactions.
 
Samourai Wallet Reveals Ocean Is Censoring Privacy Transactions
 
Samourai Wallet is alerting people about an anti-privacy movement in Ocean, a bitcoin mining pool. The organization recently revealed that the recent changes in Knots, a full Bitcoin node software used by Ocean, have resulted in the censorship of Whirlpool transactions, a kind of privacy operation used by wallet users.
 
Samourai denounced this behavior on X, stating that the actions carried by Ocean operator and Bitc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Starknet Foundation to Allocate 1.8B STRK Tokens 'Soon']]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7494de1caa</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/12/08/starknet-foundation-to-allocate-18b-strk-tokens-soon/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T13:03:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starknet said 900 million STRK are earmarked for the foundation’s Provisions Committee, and 900 million will be dedicated to user rebates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Withdraws Abu Dhabi Investment Fund Licence Application]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209069</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209069/binance-withdraws-abu-dhabi-investment-fund-licence-application"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T12:30:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The license, which Binance voluntarily canceled, would have permitted the exchange to manage a collective investment fund in the country.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Halving Is Poised to Unleash Darwinism on Miners]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7494db9829</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/12/08/bitcoin-halving-is-poised-to-unleash-darwinism-on-miners/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T12:21:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Strong miners might be about to eat the weak ones as the reward for mining BTC gets cut in half, experts say.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aoyon Ashraf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mentioned 40x By New Hampshire’s Nuclear Energy Study]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7494c580b5</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-40x-new-hampshire-nuclear-energy-study/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T12:07:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The New Hampshire Commission on Nuclear Energy’s latest report has highlighted a significant intersection between nuclear energy and Bitcoin mining, underscoring its potential to revolutionize energy utilization and demand in the sector. Bitcoin mining is mentioned 40 times in the report.
 
 
BREAKING: New Hampshire Commission on Nuclear Energy produces a report on “Next-Generation Nuclear Reactor Technology” which mentions #Bitcoin over 40 times. pic.twitter.com/mTlN5T1hY7
 
— Dennis Porter (@Dennis_Porter_) December 7, 2023
 

 
US State New Hampshire Hails Bitcoin Mining
 
Ryan McLeod, a chemical technologist at Canadian Nuclear Laboratories, emphasized the synergy between these two fields in his presentation. “Utilizing nuclear reactors, especially small modular reactors, for Bitcoin m…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nigerian Crypto Firm Bitmama to Pay $1 Million for Startup That Raised $3 Million in February]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7494c1c06e</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/nigerian-crypto-firm-bitmama-to-pay-1-million-for-startup-that-raised-3-million-in-february/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T11:35:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Nigerian crypto platform Bitmama is reportedly set to acquire the African remittances startup Payday for $1 million. Reports of Payday’s acquisition come almost a year after the startup raised $3 million in a funding round. 
 
Bitmama’s Pivot From Crypto
 
The Nigerian crypto platform Bitmama is set to acquire the cross-border payment startup Payday for a reported sum of $1 million. The acquisition deal, which puts Payday’s value at $30 million, allows Bitmama to broaden its product offering to include cross-border remittances without having to start this service from scratch.
 
According to a Dec. 5 Techcabal report, Bitmama’s yet-to-be-consumated acquisition deal comes nearly a year after the previously high-flying Payday successfully raised $3 million in a funding round. Commenting on the deal, Favour Ori, founder and CEO of Payday, said:
 
“The deal is a work in progress. If the deal goes through, the result will be a strong team with much more efficiency.”
 

 
When the deal is finalized, Bitmama is expected to take over Payday’s customer deposits and the remittance firm’s liabilities.
 
Ruth Iselema, who founded Bitmama in 2019, explained how her platform’s pivot away from its crypto-only approach convinced Ori to approach. She also suggested that Bitmama’s desire to become a leading remittance service provider made the deal to buy Payday even more lucrative.
 
Meanwhile, Payday’s downfall may be linked to the founder’s extravagance and brash management style as well as the company’s failure to effectively deal with customer complaints, according to reports.
 
What are your thoughts on this story? Let us know what you think in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[93% Of All Bitcoin Has Now Been Mined, How Much BTC Is Left?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7494cd5aab</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/93-bitcoin-mined-btc/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T11:09:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The total Bitcoin supply which is pegged at 21 million has been continuously mined since the coin was first introduced back in 2009. Now, 14 years later, the mined percentage of this total supply sits at 93%, so how much BTC is left to mine?
 
93% Of Bitcoin Supply Already Mined
 
The total mined Bitcoin crossed 19 million back in 2022 and the figure has continually risen since then. Then in December 2023, the total percentage of the total BTC supply that has been mined crossed the 93% threshold, and Binance, the largest crypto exchange in the world, took to Twitter to share this milestone.
 
 
According to data from Blockchain.com, a total of 19,560,877.158 BTC has been mined as of December 5. This means that between April 2022 and December 2023, less than 600 BTC were brought into circul…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elizabeth Warren: Update Bank Secrecy Act to Address Crypto 'Threat']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209068</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209068/elizabeth-warren-update-bank-secrecy-act-to-address-crypto-threat"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T11:02:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Senator linked crypto to terrorist financing, drug trafficking, and North Korea's nuclear weapons programme.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Economics of On-Chain Governance: Incentives, Rewards, and Financial Sustainability]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7494cfa5c5</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/the-economics-of-on-chain-governance-incentives-rewards-and-financial-sustainability/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T10:51:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain governance changes how decisions are made in decentralized systems. Unlike traditional ways involving discussions off the blockchain, on-chain governance uses the blockchain for decision-making. This process is done through smart contracts, which are self-executing agreements. 
 In on-chain governance, decisions and voting are programmed into smart contracts, making the entire process transparent and recorded on the unchangeable blockchain. This method aligns with decentralization, where power isn't held by a few individuals but distributed among the participants. This decentralization reduces the risks of central control and strengthens the security of blockchain networks. 
 A crucial aspect of on-chain governance is the role of economic incentives. Token holders actively partici…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Clarke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Balancing Risk and Opportunity: Can Institutions Afford to Ignore Crypto Any Longer?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7494b4cf7d</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/balancing-risk-and-opportunity-can-institutions-afford-to-ignore-crypto-any-longer/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T10:13:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When institutions larger than the cryptocurrency ecosystem begin to wake up to the potential of crypto, it’s certainly food for thought. Can the ever-evolving world of crypto remain outside of mainstream adoption for much longer?  
 Larry Fink, the CEO of BlackRock, the largest asset management firm in the world with around $9.4 trillion in AUM, doesn’t appear to pull any punches when it comes to speaking his mind.  In 2017, Fink dismissed crypto as an “index of money laundering.” But just three years later the BlackRock CEO admitted that assets like Bitcoin had caught his attention.  
 “I do believe the role of crypto is it’s digitizing gold in many ways,” Fink said in a recent interview with Fox Business, while also referring to BTC as an “international asset.”  Today, BlackRock is geari…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dmytro Spilka</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Institutional Traders’ BTC Holding Percentage Increased ‘Almost Twofold’ Between January and September — Study]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7494b61dc2</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/institutional-traders-btc-holding-percentage-increased-almost-twofold-between-january-and-september-study/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T10:03:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bitcoin held by institutional traders (INS) in their respective crypto portfolios saw an “almost twofold” increase in the initial three quarters of 2023. Institutional traders’ BTC allocation shifted from under 40% in January to nearly 50% by the end of September.
 
The Spot Bitcoin ETF Factor
 
According to a study conducted by the crypto platform Bybit, the bitcoin held by INS saw an “almost twofold increase in their Bitcoin holding percentage” during the initial three quarters of 2023. The study report suggests that the accumulation trends by these traders depict a pattern which is distinct from that of VIP and retail traders.
 
For context, the BTC holding percentages for the VIP and retail traders at the start of 2023 and the end of Q3 are almost identical. Even after the June BTC…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Senator Labels Cryptocurrency As A New Threat, Calls For Regulation]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7494b1485e</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/us-senator-labels-cryptocurrency-as-a-new-threat/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T09:38:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elizabeth Warren, a United States Senator has voiced her concerns about the role of cryptocurrency at large and the threat it poses in the global landscape while stressing the need for a better regulation.
 
US Senator Calls Cryptocurrency A Rising Threat
 
A pseudomynous user on X (formerly Twitter) recently took to the social media platform to share the US senator’s opposition to cryptocurrency. The X post was accompanied by a short video of Warren’s interview on CNBC’s Squawkbox Newsmaker.
 
In the interview, Warren stated that “there is a new threat out there, and it is crypto.” The senator’s assertion is apparently due to the risk of criminal activities that cryptocurrency poses.
 
 
Senator Warren’s viewpoint is consistent with the more general concern regarding the unregulated natur…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Godspower Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Withdraws Bid for Abu Dhabi License: Reuters]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7494b188d7</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/12/08/binance-withdraws-bid-for-abu-dhabi-license-reuters/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T09:37:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance determined the application was not necessary "when assessing [its] global needs." The move is unrelated to the exchange's legal settlement in the U.S.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bipartisan Anti-Crypto Terror Financing Bill Heads to U.S. Senate]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7494bd5e84</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/12/08/bipartisan-anti-crypto-terror-financing-bill-heads-to-us-senate/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T09:07:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Legislation will crack down on terrorist organizations like Hamas by applying sanctions to foreign parties that facilitate financial transactions with terrorists.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[El Salvador Could Rake In $1B Bitcoin Investment per Year With New ‘Freedom VISA’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7494bd6bdc</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/12/08/el-salvador-could-rake-in-1b-bitcoin-per-year-with-new-freedom-visa/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T09:07:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The country’s treasury owns just over 2,700 bitcoin (BTC), which has yielded over $3 million in unrealized profit so far.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Judge Bans Changpeng ‘CZ’ Zhao from Leaving the Country]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209060</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209060/us-judge-bans-changpeng-cz-zhao-from-leaving-the-country"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T02:51:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["The defendant has enormous wealth and property abroad," wrote Judge Richard Jones, "and no ties to the United States."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Early Bitcoin Ordinals Art Sells for Record $450,000]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209032</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209032/early-bitcoin-ordinals-art-sells-for-record-450000"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T02:21:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Honey Badger inscription number eight, created on Jan. 15, sold on Magic Eden on Thursday for 10.4 BTC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft May Be Working On an AI Edition of Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209025</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209025/microsoft-ai-windows-2024-germanium-copilot"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T02:06:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 Windows release is rumored to have AI in everything from its graphical user interface to its command line.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jito Airdrop Hands Out $225 Million to Solana Users]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209010</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209010/jito-airdrop-hands-out-225-million-solana-users"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T23:22:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana DeFi users are celebrating after Jito launched JTO, with 90 million tokens up for grabs for eligible users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INTERVIEW: Ember Sword CEO Says NFT Games Are More 'Transparent']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/M9OHCVpA/interview-ember-sword-ceo-says-nft-games-are-more-transparent</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/M9OHCVpA/interview-ember-sword-ceo-says-nft-games-are-more-transparent"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T21:58:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ember Sword CEO Mark Laursen shares why some big game studios "irk" him—and why he got into game development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Unveils Open-Source Path for AI Development on Its Silicon Chips]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209003</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209003/apple-ai-ml-development-mlx-silicon"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T21:07:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MLX speeds AI development on Apple hardware, connecting its users with the broader AI development community on other platforms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What the Bitcoin Halving Means for Investors]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208164</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208164/bitcoin-halving-what-it-means-investors"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T19:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The next Bitcoin halving takes place in April—but this time is different, insiders say. Here's what retail investors should know.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reebok Follows Nike Into Digital Fashion and Gaming, With an AI Twist]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208993</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208993/reebok-follows-nike-into-digital-wearables-gaming-with-ai-twist"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T19:31:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Footwear brand Reebok will debut an on-chain gaming experience next year that it promises will be “mind-bending.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meme Coins Dogecoin, SHIB Slip—But Solana's BONK Continues to Soar]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208973</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208973/meme-coin-dogecoin-shib-solana-bonk"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T18:38:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bullish traders are once again eyeing up risky assets for quick gains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ronin and Beam Gaming Tokens Surge, Outpacing Bitcoin and Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208986</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208986/ronin-beam-gaming-tokens-surge-outpacing-bitcoin-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T18:16:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gaming tokens remain hot, with RON and BEAM the biggest winners this week with huge double-digit weekly percentage jumps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gamers Can Now Livestream to Twitter via Streamlabs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208972</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208972/gamers-can-now-livestream-twitter-streamlabs"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T17:01:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Streamlabs’ new X feature allows gamers to go live on Twitter from a phone or computer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Montenegro Set to Extradite Terra Co-Founder Do Kwon to US: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208983</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208983/montenegro-extradite-terra-co-founder-do-kwon-us"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T17:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Terraform Labs co-founder has been caught in a jurisdictional tug-of-war between the U.S. and his native South Korea.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These Are the High-Profile Spot Bitcoin ETF Applications Currently in Play]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=62912</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/62912/high-profile-bitcoin-etf-applications"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T15:06:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. SEC has dragged its heels on approval of a Bitcoin spot ETF—but analysts are optimistic that there's light at the end of the tunnel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Auction House Sotheby's Announces First Sale of Bitcoin Ordinals Collection]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208961</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208961/auction-house-sothebys-announces-first-sale-of-bitcoin-ordinals-collection"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T13:22:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The sale marks the first occasion on which works from the BitcoinShrooms collection will be made available to the public, Sotheby's said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood Crypto Launches in EU With 'Crypto Back' Bitcoin Rewards Program]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208954</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208954/robinhood-crypto-launches-in-eu-with-crypto-back-bitcoin-rewards-program"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T10:06:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood Crypto's EU users will receive a percentage of trading volume back in Bitcoin, as well as Bitcoin rewards for referrals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rising Bitcoin Fees Prompt Renewed Battle Over Ordinals, BRC-20 Tokens]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208945</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208945/rising-bitcoin-fees-prompt-renewed-battle-over-ordinals-brc-20-tokens"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T02:01:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While some call for purging the NFT-like inscriptions, others say they are good for the network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t ‘AI Wash’ Investment Pitches: SEC Chair Gary Gensler]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208944</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208944/dont-ai-wash-investment-pitches-sec-chair-gary-gensler"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T01:33:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While excited by AI technology, Gensler highlighted its potential biases and conflicts of interest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Adds AI Across Its Apps, Launches Standalone Image Generator]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208935</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208935/meta-adds-ai-across-its-apps-launches-standalone-image-generator"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T01:02:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Facebook, Instagram, Messenger, and WhatsApp get new AI features, and the Meta Imagine tool lets users create AI art.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Set to List Jito Following Airdrop of Solana Token]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208923</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208923/coinbase-set-list-jito-following-airdrop-solana-token"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T00:07:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase has announced it will list Solana-based DeFi project Jito's token on its platform following the JTO airdrop Thursday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Merit Circle Brings Immutable zkEVM Into Beam Crypto Gaming Ecosystem]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208912</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208912/merit-circle-brings-immutable-zkevm-into-beam-crypto-gaming-ecosystem"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T23:31:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Merit Circle’s Beam tech is expanding beyond Avalanche to the Immutable zkEVM as a part of the DAO's "chain agnostic" approach.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Stock Short Sellers Have Lost $2.6 Billion Since Bitcoin Bull Run Began]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208921</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208921/crypto-stock-short-sellers-lost-2-6-billion-since-bitcoin-bull-run-began"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T23:07:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Short sellers are playing with fire and getting burned as Bitcoin's boom boosts crypto stocks. Experts say it's about to get worse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To AI: Best AI Tools for Image Generation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208752</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208752/which-ai-art-generator-should-you-use-comparison-dalle-midjourney-stable-diffusion-sdxl-adobe-firefly-amazon-titan-leonardo"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T22:05:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Which AI image generator fits your needs? From Dall-E and MidJourney to Stable Diffusion, we've got a comprehensive guide to help you choose.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Buy BTC': Viral Leaked GTA 6 Game Trailer Shills Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208899</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208899/buy-btc-viral-leaked-gta-6-game-trailer-shills-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T21:20:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The much-anticipated Grand Theft Auto 6 trailer came with a Bitcoin-buying plug, thanks to an anonymous leaker.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JP Morgan CEO Jamie Dimon Says Feds Should 'Close Down' Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208890</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208890/jp-morgan-ceo-jamie-dimon-close-down-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T20:15:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JP Morgan CEO has again slammed crypto and Bitcoin, saying he'd "close it down" if he were in charge of making laws.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FaZe Clan Founder Banks Says Ethereum Is 'Large Percentage' of His Net Worth]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208876</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208876/faze-clan-founder-banks-says-ethereum-large-percentage-net-worth"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T19:12:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Richard "FaZe Banks" Bengtson took to Instagram to boast that he recently dropped $200,000 on altcoins like Pepe, among other claims.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Flips Tesla, Meta, and BTC Hater Buffett's Berkshire Hathaway]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208854</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208854/btc-flip-tesla-meta-bitcoin-hater-buffetts-berkshire-hathaway"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T18:25:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin now ranks among the top 7 most valuable traded assets in the world—topping a financial giant led by BTC skeptic Warren Buffett.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Is Surging—Is It Up Only From Here?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208844</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208844/bitcoin-surging-up-only-from-here"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T17:21:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Analysts say that Bitcoin could just continue to go up in price as institutions and excitement surround a spot Bitcoin ETF have caused a rally.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond Bard: Google Launches Gemini, a Multimodal AI to Challenge ChatGPT]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208845</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208845/beyond-bard-google-launches-gemini-a-multimodal-ai-to-challenge-chatgpt"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T16:58:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At first glance, Gemini demonstrates unprecedented capabilities in understanding and integrating text, image, audio, and video.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Gaming Platform Portal Adds Rockstar Co-Founder Amid Airdrop Frenzy]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208747</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208747/portal-foundation-adds-rockstar-games-cofounder-amid-airdrop-push"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Exclusive: One of the original minds behind the Grand Theft Auto franchise has joined Portal, a cross-platform gaming token project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Marks 10th Anniversary, Hits $0.10 For First Time in a Year]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208813</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208813/dogecoin-marks-10th-anniversary-hits-0-10-for-first-time-in-a-year"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T09:43:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dog-themed meme coin Dogecoin marked its 10th anniversary with a double-digit surge that carried its price to a yearly high over $0.10.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tech Titans Assemble: IBM and Meta Lead 50+ Organizations in New AI Alliance]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208762</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208762/tech-titans-assemble-ibm-and-meta-lead-50-organizations-in-new-ai-alliance"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T01:36:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tech giants form yet another coalition to champion open source AI innovation and development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GTA 6 Preview: Everything You Need to Know About the New Grand Theft Auto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154049</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154049/grand-theft-auto-6-release-date-rumors-leaks-news"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T00:44:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATE: The first Grand Theft Auto 6 trailer is officially live, confirming a number of the GTA leaks and rumors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Flying High: Why Bitcoin Fans Are Buzzing About Hitting $42,069]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208727</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208727/flying-high-why-bitcoin-fans-buzzing-hitting-42069"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T23:54:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin broke past the fabled meme number this week, sparking hopes that the cryptocurrency might soon ascend to the promised land of $69,420.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Wonderful Afterlife? AI Recreates Jimmy Stewart's Voice for Holiday Story]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208728</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208728/jimmy-stewart-ai-voice-recreation-calm-app-wonderful-life"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T23:11:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The distinctive vocals of the Hollywood legend have been brought back to narrate a new bedtime track in the Calm app.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Send a Selfie to See Porn? UK Ponders Ways to Age-Gate Adult Sites]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208719</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208719/uk-ofcom-age-gate-porn-ai-selfie-evaluation"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T21:56:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A European telecom regulator floats using AI to analyze selfies of web surfers to determine if they’re old enough to see stuff.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Is Talking to Bitcoin ETF Contenders—Here’s What It's Likely Saying]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208717</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208717/sec-talking-bitcoin-etf-contenders-what-its-saying"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T21:56:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What has the SEC been saying in discussions with Bitcoin ETF applicants? Recent changes in amended filings provide a few clues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Director Jordan Bayne on the State of Film3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZLoEDkL9/director-jordan-bayne-on-the-state-of-film3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZLoEDkL9/director-jordan-bayne-on-the-state-of-film3"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T00:11:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the 2023 Film3 Summit, Jordan Bayne—director and founder of The Squad—spoke with Decrypt's Sander Lutz about how the Film3 world has progressed over the last year and what decentralized technologies can offer to creators that want to buck the Hollywood system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Questions With SCENE: Phil Mohun]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TwOjXfOR/5-questions-with-scene-phil-mohun</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TwOjXfOR/5-questions-with-scene-phil-mohun"/>
        <updated>2023-12-01T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bright Moments co-founder Phil Mohun joins 5 Questions With SCENE to recount some favorite moments from the road, including negotiating with Patagonian gauchos, falling in love with Tokyo, and gaining a newfound appreciation for shrooms chocolate bars.

Shot and edited by Vincent Roazzi Jr.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are NFTs Ever Coming Back?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qLmFpNKE/are-nfts-ever-coming-back</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qLmFpNKE/are-nfts-ever-coming-back"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T18:38:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this weeks episode we sit down with Cashtro from Arcade.xyz to discuss NFTs, shitcoins, what collections have held onto their floor prices, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Summit: Will Web3 Gaming Ever be Mainstream?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OvVWhGbW/web-summit-will-web3-gaming-ever-be-mainstream</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OvVWhGbW/web-summit-will-web3-gaming-ever-be-mainstream"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T19:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animoca Brands CEO Robby Yung, EndeavorXR CEO Amy Peck and Gamee co-founder CEO Bozena Rezab joined Decrypt's Stephen Graves on stage at Web Summit to talk about the future of Web3 gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Allie Eve Knox on Spankchain and the life of a Crypto Financial Dominatrix]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/16rVeg6o/allie-eve-knox-on-spankchain-and-the-life-of-a-crypto-financial-dominatrix</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/16rVeg6o/allie-eve-knox-on-spankchain-and-the-life-of-a-crypto-financial-dominatrix"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T21:20:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the first IRL episode of This Time Will Be Different!

In this week's episode, our host, Reza Jafery, is joined by Allie Eve Knox, the Spankchain Chief of Staff and FinDomme. 

They discuss
- How to sell feet pics
- If crypto is really as permissionless as it seems
- the intersections between crypto and sex work]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Questions With SCENE: Jeff Davis]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PChJu1R8/5-questions-with-scene-jeff-davis</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PChJu1R8/5-questions-with-scene-jeff-davis"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artist Jeff Davis joins 5 Questions with SCENE to answer burning questions about his artistic practice, the path that brought him to Art Blocks, and his quietly sophisticated DJ abilities.

Video shot and edited by Vincent Roazzi Jr.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Heatbit Founder Alex Busarov on the Bitcoin Miner That Heats Your Home]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DJuHqcGT/heatbit-founder-alex-busarov-on-the-bitcoin-miner-that-heats-your-home</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DJuHqcGT/heatbit-founder-alex-busarov-on-the-bitcoin-miner-that-heats-your-home"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T18:12:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt joined Heatbit founder Alex Busarov at Web Summit for a walkthrough of the firm's flagship product, a Bitcoin miner that acts as a domestic space heater—aimed at the casual user.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nym CEO Harry Halpin on Privacy, Decentralized VPNs and Tornado Cash]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/aLTtY2aq/nym-ceo-harry-halpin-on-privacy-decentralized-vpns-and-tornado-cash</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/aLTtY2aq/nym-ceo-harry-halpin-on-privacy-decentralized-vpns-and-tornado-cash"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T18:08:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The founder of privacy-preserving mixnet Nym sat down with Decrypt at Web Summit to talk about its new decentralized VPN, the Web3 privacy landscape and why "devs should be defended" in the wake of the Tornado Cash crackdown.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pat Felder - The worst is over [Macro Deep Dive Episode]]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MdcKPVo0/pat-felder-the-worst-is-over-macro-deep-dive-episode</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MdcKPVo0/pat-felder-the-worst-is-over-macro-deep-dive-episode"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T17:10:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the first Markets Edition of This Time Will Be Different! In this episode we dive into the current macroeconomic conditions around crypto and look at the data behind the price action. 


Reza sits down with Pat Felder, founder of Prismatic Capital to discuss the current macro environment, and to answer the question on everyone's mind-- is the bear market really over?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Sandbox Co-Founder Sebastien Borget: 'We're Already Integrating AI']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/HlARjhG1/the-sandbox-co-founder-sebastien-borget-were-already-integrating-ai</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/HlARjhG1/the-sandbox-co-founder-sebastien-borget-were-already-integrating-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T16:09:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt sat down with The Sandbox co-founder Sebastien Borget at Web Summit to talk about AI, the open metaverse and the creative challenges of interoperability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dacoco CEO Saro McKenna: How Alien Worlds is Creating an AI-Powered 'Lore DAO' with Kevin J Anderson]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QrQTrsjH/dacoco-ceo-saro-mckenna-how-alien-worlds-is-creating-an-ai-powered-lore-dao-with-kevin-j-anderson</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QrQTrsjH/dacoco-ceo-saro-mckenna-how-alien-worlds-is-creating-an-ai-powered-lore-dao-with-kevin-j-anderson"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T16:06:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt joined Dacoco CEO Sarojini McKenna at Web Summit 2023 to talk about Alien Worlds' new Lore DAO and its AI-powered collaboration with sci-fi author Kevin J Anderson.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avalon's Jeffrey Butler on Designing a Metaverse MMO That Lets Players Co-Create]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XDz9vsvT/avalons-jeffrey-butler-on-designing-a-metaverse-mmo-that-lets-players-co-create</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XDz9vsvT/avalons-jeffrey-butler-on-designing-a-metaverse-mmo-that-lets-players-co-create"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T00:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avalon Chief Product Officer Jeffrey Butler speaks with Decrypt reporter Jason Nelson and details his studio's new MMO game with interoperable assets—and how it will enable players to create and monetize their own content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Gen Z Is Different: OTK Chief Strategy Officer Talks Creator Economy Shift and Rise of Kick]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PieshbpH/how-gen-z-is-different-otk-chief-strategy-officer-talks-creator-economy-shift-and-rise-of-kick</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PieshbpH/how-gen-z-is-different-otk-chief-strategy-officer-talks-creator-economy-shift-and-rise-of-kick"/>
        <updated>2023-11-10T18:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One True King, an esports and gaming lifestyle brand and media company, was founded by creators like Asmongold and Mizkif. OTK's Chief Strategy Officer Zachary Diaz, who previously worked at TikTok and Twitch, shares with Decrypt's Kate Irwin about how the creator economy is changing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moisés Zamora on Videomart and Bucking the Hollywood System]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kyjQCle8/moises-zamora-on-videomart-and-bucking-the-hollywood-system</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kyjQCle8/moises-zamora-on-videomart-and-bucking-the-hollywood-system"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T17:11:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Selena: The Series" creator and co-showrunner Moisés Zamora joins Decrypt's Sander Lutz at the Film3 Summit 2023 to discuss why the Hollywood system is broken and why he founded the Videomart NFT digital film marketplace to give creators more power.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why OTK Is Making Video Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/1NCV4Fk0/why-otk-is-making-video-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/1NCV4Fk0/why-otk-is-making-video-games"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One True King (OTK) Chief Strategy Officer Zachary Diaz tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about OTK's long-term strategy and vision to become a content creator-powered media and video games company.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>