<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-03-19T15:15:55.261Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-03-19T15:15:55.261Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Others Continue to Live Your Dreams! An Investor Earned $3.34 Million in 3 Days: Here is the List of Altcoins He Bought!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19339587/Others-Continue-to-Live-Your-Dreams-An-Investor-Earned-334-Million-in-3-Days-Here-is-the-List-of-Altcoins-He-Bought</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19339587/Others-Continue-to-Live-Your-Dreams-An-Investor-Earned-334-Million-in-3-Days-Here-is-the-List-of-Altcoins-He-Bought"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T15:09:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lookonchain shared the Solana-based mem token investment strategy of the investor, who made his money 704x and earned $ 3.34 million. Continue Reading: Others Continue to Live Your Dreams! An Investor Earned $3.34 Million in 3 Days: Here is the List of Altcoins He Bought!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Signal Points To End Of Bull Phase For Bitcoin, Quant Says]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74c9083581</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/signal-points-end-bull-phase-bitcoin-quant-says/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T15:05:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A quant has pointed out a pattern in a Bitcoin on-chain indicator that may imply the bull phase may be close to ending for now.
 
Bitcoin NUPL Has Been At Overheated Levels For Weeks Now
 
In a CryptoQuant Quicktake post, an analyst has talked about a bearish development that has recently occurred in the Bitcoin “Net Unrealized Profit/Loss” (NUPL) indicator.
 
As its name already suggests, the NUPL keeps track of the net amount of unrealized profit or loss that the investors of the cryptocurrency as a whole are holding right now. This metric works by going through the on-chain history of each token in circulation to see what price it was last moved at.
 
 
With the assumption that the previous transfer for any coin was the last point it changed hands, the metric subtracts the price at its …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Signal Points To End Of Bull Phase For Bitcoin, Quant Says]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19339564/This-Signal-Points-To-End-Of-Bull-Phase-For-Bitcoin-Quant-Says</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19339564/This-Signal-Points-To-End-Of-Bull-Phase-For-Bitcoin-Quant-Says"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T15:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A quant has pointed out a pattern in a Bitcoin on-chain indicator that may imply the bull phase may be close to ending for now. Bitcoin NUPL Has Been At Overheated Levels For Weeks Now In a CryptoQuant Quicktake post, an analyst has talked about a bearish development that has recently occurred...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche Price Prediction: AVAX $80 Dreams Fold as New Exchange Token Option2Trade Completes 98% Stage 4]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19339581/Avalanche-Price-Prediction-AVAX-80-Dreams-Fold-as-New-Exchange-Token-Option2Trade-Completes-98-Stage-4</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19339581/Avalanche-Price-Prediction-AVAX-80-Dreams-Fold-as-New-Exchange-Token-Option2Trade-Completes-98-Stage-4"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cryptocurrency market is once again at the cusp of a significant transformation, this time brought about by the meteoric rise of Option2Trade (O2T), a new exchange token that has just completed 98% of its Stage 4 presale. This remarkable achievement has not only solidified O2T’s position as...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Semiconductor Slump: A Day of Losses for AMD, NVDA, and SMCI]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19339551/Semiconductor-Slump-A-Day-of-Losses-for-AMD-NVDA-and-SMCI</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19339551/Semiconductor-Slump-A-Day-of-Losses-for-AMD-NVDA-and-SMCI"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T14:59:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a rough day for the semiconductor industry, Advanced Micro Devices (AMD), Nvidia (NVDA), and Super Micro Computer (SMCI) saw notable declines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Surges with Record Token Burns and Whale Moves, Sparking New Investor Enthusiasm]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19339534/Shiba-Inu-Surges-with-Record-Token-Burns-and-Whale-Moves-Sparking-New-Investor-Enthusiasm</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19339534/Shiba-Inu-Surges-with-Record-Token-Burns-and-Whale-Moves-Sparking-New-Investor-Enthusiasm"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T14:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu, often referred to as the ‘Dogecoin Killer,’ is experiencing a significant resurgence, evidenced...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Macro Index Surge Signals Double Pump, Says Top Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19339576/Bitcoin-BTC-Macro-Index-Surge-Signals-Double-Pump-Says-Top-Analyst</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19339576/Bitcoin-BTC-Macro-Index-Surge-Signals-Double-Pump-Says-Top-Analyst"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T14:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto analyst Willy Woo has predicted double-pump cycle for Bitcoin]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy Amasses 1% of Bitcoin Supply After Latest Buy]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19339523/MicroStrategy-Amasses-1-of-Bitcoin-Supply-After-Latest-Buy</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19339523/MicroStrategy-Amasses-1-of-Bitcoin-Supply-After-Latest-Buy"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T14:49:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy goes on another Bitcoin buying spree after raising funds in a private offering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Goldman Sachs head of digital assets: The future is on public blockchains]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19339535/Goldman-Sachs-head-of-digital-assets-The-future-is-on-public-blockchains</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19339535/Goldman-Sachs-head-of-digital-assets-The-future-is-on-public-blockchains"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T14:37:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[But Goldman’s Mathew McDermott says the bank wants to see public blockchains “mature” before expanding in that arena]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Centrifuge Introduces New Platform for Streamlined On-Chain Fund Management]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19339492/Centrifuge-Introduces-New-Platform-for-Streamlined-On-Chain-Fund-Management</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19339492/Centrifuge-Introduces-New-Platform-for-Streamlined-On-Chain-Fund-Management"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T14:37:36.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Genesis agrees to $21M SEC settlement over Gemini Earn]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19339487/Genesis-agrees-to-21M-SEC-settlement-over-Gemini-Earn</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19339487/Genesis-agrees-to-21M-SEC-settlement-over-Gemini-Earn"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T14:36:06.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analysts See Gold Reaching $2,600 per Ounce Amid Strong Market Demand]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74caf65e9e</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/analysts-see-gold-reaching-2600-per-ounce-amid-strong-market-demand/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T14:32:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While bitcoin experienced a 12% decrease following its all-time high last week, gold has shown relative stability over the past five days, with only a slight 1% decline in the same period. In a similar vein to crypto enthusiasts, advocates for gold predict that the metal will continue its upward trajectory, potentially reaching the $2,600 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Human Rights Foundation Grants $500,000 To 14 Bitcoin Projects Worldwide]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74caf67501</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/human-rights-foundation-grants-500000-to-14-bitcoin-projects-worldwide"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T14:31:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, the Human Rights Foundation (HRF) announced its most recent round of Bitcoin Development Fund grants, according to a press release sent to Bitcoin Magazine. 
$500,000 is being granted across 14 different projects around the world focusing on global education, Lightning Network development, decentralized communications, and providing nonprofits and human rights groups with an easier onramp to "financial freedom tools," per the release. The main areas of focus for these grants center around Latin America, Asia, and Africa.
This announcement comes only a few months after their last round of grants in December, also donating $500,000 to worldwide Bitcoin projects. While the HRF did not disclose exactly how much money each project is receiving, the following 14 projects are the recipient…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nik Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 Reasons to use a Bitcoin Hardware Wallet]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74caf674ef</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/sponsored/8-reasons-to-use-a-bitcoin-hardware-wallet"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T14:31:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the value of your bitcoin grows, so does your need for secure key storage. One such solution is a hardware wallet, a physical device that allows you to securely hold the keys to your bitcoin. But hardware wallets aren’t the only option for storing your bitcoin keys—there are also software wallets, paper wallets, and even “brain wallets.” So why specifically choose a hardware wallet?
1. Keep your keys offline, protected from remote attacks
 
                         
                         
                         
                     
                    
Hardware wallets enable you to generate and hold the keys to your bitcoin entirely offline, known as cold storage. This stands in contrast to hot wallets, which are more susceptible to remote attacks such as malware and SIM swap at…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Unchained</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Palladium and Botanix Labs Launches Bitcoin-native Stablecoin on Bitcoin’s First EVM Layer 2]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74caf674d4</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/palladium-and-botanix-labs-launches-bitcoin-native-stablecoin-on-bitcoins-first-evm-layer-2"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T14:31:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Palladium and Botanix Labs have announced the launch of a new stablecoin, PUSD, on Bitcoin's first EVM-equivalent Layer 2 network, according to a press release sent to Bitcoin Magazine.
The PUSD stablecoin, developed by Palladium Labs, boasts a unique feature of being over-collateralized by 110%, a strategic measure aimed at enhancing its resilience against potential risks inherent in DeFi infrastructure. Importantly, the stablecoin's algorithmic monetary policy attempts to remain immune to governance changes or manipulation by administrator keys, aiming to ensure its integrity and reliability.
“To realize the true value of decentralized finance, crypto needs to break free from infrastructure that is susceptible to exploits and manipulation,” stated Palladium Labs CEO Akash Gaurav. “At Palladium, we designed this stablecoin for resilience and reliability. By leveraging the unique capabilities of the Botanix EVM, we can radically increase the security and reliability of stablecoin access for millions of people using Bitcoin.”
Operating on the Botanix EVM, which has been in development since early 2023, Palladium leverages the capabilities of this platform to enhance the security and accessibility of stablecoin transactions for Bitcoin users. The Botanix EVM's underlying sidechain protocol, known as the Spiderchain, plays a pivotal role in safeguarding funds transferred from the Bitcoin base layer to the EVM network.
“The importance of native stablecoins to the technological renaissance happening on Bitcoin cannot be overstated,” said Willem Schroe, inventor of the Spiderchain and co-founder of Botanix Labs. “We are thrilled to support the Palladium team in launching their over-collateralized stablecoin on our EVM network.”
With the launch of PUSD on Bitcoin's first EVM Layer 2 network, Palladium and Botanix Labs aim to meet the growing demand for secure and efficient DeFi solutions, seeking to pave the way for a new era of financial innovation on the Bitcoin blockchain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nik Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Luxor and Bitnomial Launch First Ever Bitcoin Hashrate Futures]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74caf674cc</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/markets/luxor-and-bitnomial-launch-first-ever-bitcoin-hashrate-futures"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T14:31:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Luxor Technology Corporation (Luxor) and Bitnomial, Inc. have announced the launch of the first US exchange-traded Hashrate Futures, according to a press release sent to Bitcoin Magazine. Set to debut on Bitnomial’s derivatives exchange by the end of this month, these futures contracts are specifically tailored to cater to Bitcoin miners and institutional investors alike.
“Hashrate has one of the highest volatilities of major commodities, and the April 2024 Bitcoin Halving will exacerbate this volatility,” said Luxor’s Head of Derivatives, Matt Williams. “Bitcoin miners need additional methods to mitigate this price risk to ensure the longevity of their businesses. Exchange-traded hashrate futures will allow them to quickly move in and out of hedging positions to de-risk their revenue stre…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nik Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Saylor's MicroStrategy Acquired an Additional 9,245 BTC]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74caf674c4</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/michael-saylors-microstrategy-9245-btc-620-million"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T14:31:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy has continued expanding its bitcoin holdings, announcing the purchase of approximately 9,245 bitcoins for around $623 million in cash today.
According to the company's new press release, it acquired the bitcoin between March 11 and 18, using proceeds from its recent convertible senior notes offering and excess company cash. The average purchase price was approximately $67,382 per bitcoin.
This latest acquisition comes just after MicroStrategy raised $603.75 million through a private offering of 0.875% convertible senior notes due in 2031. The company upsized the planned offering from $500 million after seeing strong demand.
With the new 9,245 BTC purchase, MicroStrategy now holds an aggregate total of approximately 214,246 bitcoins acquired at an average price of $35,160 per bitcoin. The company has spent $7.53 billion to accumulate its Bitcoin treasury reserves.
Led by CEO Michael Saylor, MicroStrategy continues to aggressively execute its bitcoin strategy even amid Bitcoin market volatility. 
The company aims to hold Bitcoin as its primary corporate treasury asset, taking on debt and issuing equity to raise funds for further accumulation. MicroStrategy now own more than 1% of Bitcoin total supply.
While sceptics argue that bitcoin-backed loans introduce balance sheet risk, Saylor remains staunchly confident in bitcoin's long-term trajectory. With its latest buy enabled by the upsized note offering, MicroStrategy is doubling down on its Bitcoin play.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vivek Sen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exec claims Bitcoin to $125K is coming, IF BTC goes through these phases first]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19339482/Exec-claims-Bitcoin-to-125K-is-coming-IF-BTC-goes-through-these-phases-first</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19339482/Exec-claims-Bitcoin-to-125K-is-coming-IF-BTC-goes-through-these-phases-first"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T14:30:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Galaxy Digital's Head of Trading Jason Urban believes that BTC could hit $125K by end of 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ‘Danger Zone’ Imminent As BTC Reaches Point of Market Cycle Historically Correlated With Correction: Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19339471/Bitcoin-Danger-Zone-Imminent-As-BTC-Reaches-Point-of-Market-Cycle-Historically-Correlated-With-Correction-Analyst</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19339471/Bitcoin-Danger-Zone-Imminent-As-BTC-Reaches-Point-of-Market-Cycle-Historically-Correlated-With-Correction-Analyst"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T14:30:40.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nomura Bank launches Libre with Polygon for on-chain tokenization of alternative assets]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19339468/Nomura-Bank-launches-Libre-with-Polygon-for-on-chain-tokenization-of-alternative-assets</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19339468/Nomura-Bank-launches-Libre-with-Polygon-for-on-chain-tokenization-of-alternative-assets"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T14:30:11.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Libre Launches Tokenization Platform for Institutional Investors]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19339458/Libre-Launches-Tokenization-Platform-for-Institutional-Investors</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19339458/Libre-Launches-Tokenization-Platform-for-Institutional-Investors"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T14:25:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Libre, a cutting-edge tokenization platform designed for the issuance and distribution of tokenized alternative assets, has officially launched for eligible investors. The platform, which leverages Polygon technology, aims to revolutionize the way institutional investors access and manage...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EU lawmakers pass legislation extending anti-money laundering controls to crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19339457/EU-lawmakers-pass-legislation-extending-anti-money-laundering-controls-to-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19339457/EU-lawmakers-pass-legislation-extending-anti-money-laundering-controls-to-crypto"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T14:24:47.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Machine learning algorithm predicts SHIB price for April 1, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19339460/Machine-learning-algorithm-predicts-SHIB-price-for-April-1-2024</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19339460/Machine-learning-algorithm-predicts-SHIB-price-for-April-1-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T14:24:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the cryptocurrency sector switching its previous gains for trading in the red and wiping $230 billion in a day … Continue reading]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale Announces Fee Reduction for Bitcoin ETF Amidst $12 Billion Outflows]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19339450/Grayscale-Announces-Fee-Reduction-for-Bitcoin-ETF-Amidst-12-Billion-Outflows</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19339450/Grayscale-Announces-Fee-Reduction-for-Bitcoin-ETF-Amidst-12-Billion-Outflows"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T14:24:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale, a leading digital asset management firm, has signaled a strategic shift in its fee structure for the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust ETF (GBTC), following a significant $12 billion in outflows. Michael Sonnenshein, CEO of Grayscale, in a recent interview with CNBC, confirmed that the firm...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Empower Oversight Challenges SEC Over Cryptocurrency Documents]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19339449/Empower-Oversight-Challenges-SEC-Over-Cryptocurrency-Documents</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19339449/Empower-Oversight-Challenges-SEC-Over-Cryptocurrency-Documents"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T14:23:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a significant legal move, Empower Oversight has initiated a lawsuit against the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), accusing the agency of failing to adequately respond to a Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) request.  The request was centered around obtaining documents that could...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These Crypto Exchanges Will Support the SLERF Community Following Presale Fund Mishap]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19339446/These-Crypto-Exchanges-Will-Support-the-SLERF-Community-Following-Presale-Fund-Mishap</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19339446/These-Crypto-Exchanges-Will-Support-the-SLERF-Community-Following-Presale-Fund-Mishap"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T14:18:32.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The institutions are paying attention. Now comes the hard part.]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19339456/The-institutions-are-paying-attention-Now-comes-the-hard-part</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19339456/The-institutions-are-paying-attention-Now-comes-the-hard-part"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T14:16:53.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fidelity Adjusts Ethereum ETF Application, Optimistic About Regulatory Approval]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74caf3543b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/fidelity-adjusts-ethereum-etf-application/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T14:05:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spot Ethereum Exchange-Traded Funds (ETFs) may be witnessing a decline in approval odds, but there is still a wave of optimism among several financial management firms applying for the products.
 
Fidelity Amends Its Ethereum Spot ETF Application
 
Amid the anticipation encompassing the Ethereum spot ETFs, financial management giant Fidelity has recently amended its application for the exchange products, demonstrating confidence toward approval by the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).
 
 
 
 
Chairman and President of The ETF Store, Nate Geraci, took to the social media platform X to share the update with the crypto community today. According to Nate Geraci, the amendment contains a “more thorough examination” of the connection between the spot and futures markets.
 
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Godspower Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Lender Genesis Agrees to $21 Million SEC Fine, Funds to Await Bankruptcy Claim Settlements]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74cafd732e</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/crypto-lender-genesis-agrees-to-21-million-sec-fine-funds-to-await-bankruptcy-claim-settlements/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T13:53:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Genesis Global Capital has settled with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and agreed to pay a $21 million civil penalty. The SEC further disclosed that the regulator will “not receive any portion of the penalty until after payment of all other allowed claims by the bankruptcy court, including claims by retail investors in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase's Allies Join Crypto Firm's Case Against SEC]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74cafd81a7</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/03/19/coinbases-allies-join-crypto-firms-case-against-sec/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T13:52:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several allies joined Coinbase Inc. (COIN) in its court fight against the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to force the agency to rethink its refusal to write specific rules to govern the crypto industry, with Paradigm, the Crypto Council for Innovation and others filing outside arguments with the circuit court.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Luxor Looks to Help Bitcoin Miners Hedge Halving Risk With New Hashrate Futures]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74caff43b7</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2024/03/19/luxor-looks-to-help-bitcoin-miners-hedge-halving-risk-with-new-hashrate-futures/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T13:42:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bitcoin mining software and services company partnered with Bitnomial to offer cash-settled hashrate futures.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aoyon Ashraf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Hits Genesis with $21 Million Penalty over Unregistered Crypto Lending Program]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74caffd9c2</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/sec-hits-genesis-with-21-million-penalty-over-unregistered-crypto-lending-program/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T13:39:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Genesis Global Capital, LLC has agreed to a $21  
million penalty to settle charges brought against the firm by the Securities  
and Exchange Commission (SEC). This matter involves allegations by the  
regulator that the crypto lending platform offered unregistered securities to  
the public. 
The SEC accused Genesis of failing to register the  
Gemini Earn program, a crypto lending product jointly managed with the  
cryptocurrency exchange Gemini. The regulator maintains that the offering  
breached the disclosure requirements designed to safeguard investors. 
Unregistered Lending Program
The SEC's Chair, Gary Gensler, mentioned: "We  
charged Genesis with failing to register its retail crypto lending product  
before offering it to the public, bypassing essential disclosure requirements …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin.com Announces Integration of VERSE Token With BitPay for Expanded Payment Options]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74cafa7300</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-com-announces-integration-of-verse-token-with-bitpay-for-expanded-payment-options/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T13:24:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin.com, a leading figure in the world of cryptocurrency and blockchain technology, is thrilled to announce a significant enhancement to the utility of its ecosystem token, VERSE. In a groundbreaking collaboration, VERSE has now been integrated with BitPay, the world’s largest provider of Bitcoin and cryptocurrency payment services. This integration heralds a new era of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Flash Crash Below $9K on BitMEX Prompts 'Unusual Activity' Investigation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=222328</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/222328/bitcoin-flash-crash-bitmex-investigation"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T13:14:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crash lasted a few minutes, but was followed by a short panic episode that cause BTC to drop near 7% on the global markets after the news spread.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Is The Shiba Inu Price Down Today?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74cae5f4a9</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-price-down-today/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T13:04:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Shiba Inu price has seen a massive drawdown in the last day as the Bitcoin price lost its support at $65,000. As a result, the SHIB price is down more than 10% in a single day, with what is arguably one of the worst crypto trading days in crypto so far this year. But what is behind this market crash?
 
Crypto Market Fumbles On FOMC
 
The crypto market seems to be already reacting to the Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC) meeting which is scheduled to take place on Wednesday, March 20. Expectations are quite lax for the outcome of the meeting. Nevertheless, investors and traders are looking toward the outcome as something that could significantly impact the crypto market.
 
 
Alongside this, Bitcoin is also going through an expected correction after what has been a green year, moving …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microstrategy Expands Bitcoin Holdings: Acquires 9,245 BTC After Successful Convertible Note Sale]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74cae5ee5a</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/microstrategy-expands-bitcoin-holdings-acquires-9245-btc-after-successful-convertible-note-sale/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T13:04:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Tuesday, the business intelligence firm Microstrategy announced it completed a $603.75 million offering of convertible senior notes due 2031. After the announcement, Microstrategy’s founder Michael Saylor announced the company acquired 9,245 bitcoin for $623 million using the proceeds and excess cash. Microstrategy Now Holds 214,246 Bitcoin After Microstrategy announced its convertible note sale, the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Saylor's MicroStrategy Acquired Another 9,245 BTC For $623M]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74cae67451</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/03/19/michael-saylors-microstrategy-acquired-another-9245-btc-for-623m/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T13:01:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy now holds approximately 214,246 BTC ($13.5 billion), which is more than 1% of all the 21 million bitcoin that will ever exist.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MANTRA Chain Raises $11M for RWA Tokenization with Middle East Tint]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74cae06e81</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2024/03/19/mantra-chain-raises-11m-for-rwa-tokenization-with-middle-east-tint/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T12:50:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The project seeks to be a hub for RWAs in the Cosmos ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EU Lawmakers Vote for Three Major Texts in Anti-Money Laundering Package That Also Targets Crypto]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74caed598b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/03/19/eu-lawmakers-vote-for-three-major-texts-in-anti-money-laundering-package-that-also-targets-crypto/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T12:22:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The broad package sets up an anti-money laundering authority, a single rulebook for all 27 member states, and tough rules for crypto service providers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandali Handagama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoin Project Gyroscope to Conduct Points Program, Launch High-Yield Liquidity Pools]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74caee3597</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2024/03/19/stablecoin-project-gyroscope-to-conduct-points-program-launch-high-yield-liquidity-pools/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T12:17:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gyroscope seeks to boost its GYD stablecoin with new products servicing airdrop farmers and yield seekers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Mover Americas: Bitcoin Slumps, Liquidations Surge]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74caee358c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/03/19/first-mover-americas-bitcoin-slumps-liquidations-surge/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T12:17:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest price moves in crypto markets in context for March 19, 2024. First Mover is CoinDesk’s daily newsletter that contextualizes the latest actions in the crypto markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lyllah Ledesma, Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin and Ethereum See Red as Crypto Market Boom Turns to Gloom]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=222321</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/222321/bitcoin-ethereum-crypto-market-boom-to-gloom"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T11:24:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the past day, more than $500 million worth of long and $100 million worth of short positions have been liquidated.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Square Enix Brings Ethereum NFT Game Symbiogenesis to HyperPlay Amid Investment]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=222281</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/222281/square-enix-ethereum-nft-game-symbiogenesis-hyperplay-amid-investment"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T11:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Final Fantasy maker has made a strategic investment in HyperPlay and is extending its Symbiogenesis game to the launcher.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jupiter Founder Says DEX Will Donate Fees to Slerf Presale Buyers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=222307</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/222307/jupiter-founder-dex-donate-fees-slerf-solana-meme-coin"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T10:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana DEX Jupiter said it "will be donating current and ongoing SLERF limit order & DCA fees to the SLERF presale participants."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Weekend Madness]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/RGxNjELq/the-weekend-madness</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/RGxNjELq/the-weekend-madness"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T09:59:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin rebounds as users withdraw funds from exchanges. Solana breaks $200, surpassing Binance Coin to claim the 4th spot in crypto rankings. Ethereum's supply drops to a two-year low. Over $100 million raised by new coin presales in just two days. A dog NFT sells for a staggering $4.3 million. PRIME emerges as the leader in gaming coins, while NodeMonkes flips Bored Ape Yacht Club (BAYC).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Embattled Binance Founder Changpeng Zhao Launches ‘Giggle Academy’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=222297</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/222297/embattled-binance-founder-changpeng-zhao-pitches-giggle-academy"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T02:27:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even as he awaits sentencing in federal court, CZ announces "the most impactful thing I could do for the next chapter of my life."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Kawailani Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NVIDIA Unveils Project Gr00t for Robotic AI, Apple Vision Pro Integration]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=222282</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/222282/nvidia-project-groot-ai-robots-blackwell-gpu-apple-vision-pro"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T01:44:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CEO Jensen Huang showed off the "very, very big" Blackwell AI GPU and real-world AI use cases from Mercedes and Siemens.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Could Top $14,000 Next Year Alongside Bitcoin Boom: Standard Chartered]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=222258</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/222258/ethereum-headed-for-14000-in-2025-alongside-bitcoin-boom-standard-chartered"/>
        <updated>2024-03-18T22:12:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spot Ethereum ETFs should get the green light by May, and the bank says the asset will only go up from there.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adam Back Wants ‘Prodigal Son’ Roger Ver to Come Home to Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=222206</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/222206/adam-back-roger-ver-come-home-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2024-03-18T21:25:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In his new book, Ver claims Bitcoin was “hijacked” and corrupted—Back says Ver should let it go and return to BTC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Ordinals Buzz Pushes NodeMonkes Market Cap Above Bored Ape NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=222219</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/222219/bitcoin-ordinals-buzz-pushes-nodemonkes-above-bored-ape-nfts"/>
        <updated>2024-03-18T21:01:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top Ordinals collections are challenging their Ethereum NFT counterparts as demand for Bitcoin assets skyrockets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Was Solana Meme Coin BOME's Boom Aided by a Binance Insider?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=222237</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/222237/bome-solana-coin-binance-insider-trading-claims"/>
        <updated>2024-03-18T21:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance offered a multi-million dollar bounty for information on corruption within the exchange after an insider trading accusations went viral.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bill Gates Says AI Will Bring 'Free Work'—But We'll Need to Be Careful]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=222094</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/222094/bill-gates-ai-will-bring-free-work-need-be-careful"/>
        <updated>2024-03-18T20:38:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Co-founder Bill Gates said he's still included in conversations about AI at Microsoft—and he has thoughts about the big shift ahead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Kawailani Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin May Be Down—But Demand Isn't Slowing From Crypto Fund Investors]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=222208</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/222208/bitcoin-may-be-down-but-demand-isnt-slowing-from-crypto-fund-investors"/>
        <updated>2024-03-18T20:20:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A record $2.9 billion flowed into crypto funds, says CoinShares, the vast majority backing Bitcoin ETFs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Meme Coin Slerf Racks Up $2 Billion in Volume Despite Dev Burning Presale Funds]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=222207</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/222207/solana-meme-coin-slerf-racks-up-2-billion-in-volume-despite-dev-burning-presale-funds"/>
        <updated>2024-03-18T20:15:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An anonymous Solana developer accidentally burned $10 million worth of tokens after raising that amount in a presale. Degens bought in anyway.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Charges Investment Advisors for ‘AI Washing’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=222205</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/222205/ai-investment-sec-charges-400000-fine"/>
        <updated>2024-03-18T19:44:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An advisor lying about using AI is like ”recommending investments they hallucinated while on mushrooms,” says SEC head Gary Gensler.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Will Hit $150,000 This Year, Standard Chartered Analysts Say]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=222155</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/222155/bitcoin-150000-2024-standard-chartered-forecast"/>
        <updated>2024-03-18T18:30:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Continued success of the new Bitcoin exchange-traded funds will push the price of the cryptocurrency higher, the bank said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Memes Have a New Top Dog: Dogwifhat Ethereum NFT Sells for $4.3 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=222198</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/222198/dogwifhat-ethereum-nft-sells-4-3-million"/>
        <updated>2024-03-18T18:13:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The South Korean parents of the pup featured in the Dogwifhat meme, Achi, will take home some $4.1 million from the NFT sale.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bull Run Among 'Most Robust' In History, Says Glassnode Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=222180</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/222180/bitcoin-bull-run-most-robust-history-glassnode"/>
        <updated>2024-03-18T17:34:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin's weekend pullback was remarkably predictable and completely healthy for an ongoing bull market, on-chain analysis suggests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Is Soaring—You Can Earn More by Playing These Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207766</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207766/solana-soaring-earn-more-playing-these-games"/>
        <updated>2024-03-18T16:56:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATED: Want to stack SOL? These Solana games let you earn tokens while you play. Here are seven games to get started with.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche (AVAX) and DogWifHat (WIF) Defy Gravity Amidst a Flat to Bearish Crypto Market]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=222146</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/222146/avalanche-avax-dogwifhat-wif-defy-gravity"/>
        <updated>2024-03-18T15:32:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche (AVAX) and DogWifHat (WIF) don't like the slow pace of today's market and have spiked more than 10% in the last 24 hours.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BOME Blast off]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/wiIrxdqG/bome-blast-off</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/wiIrxdqG/bome-blast-off"/>
        <updated>2024-03-18T14:11:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC experiences a 9% drop, resulting in $700 million liquidations, with funding and open interest hitting their lowest levels in weeks. The sell-off appears more sustained compared to previous brief dips, with most BTC downside liquidations concentrated around $66,000. ETFs witness $132 million inflows, sparking predictions of a potential liquidity crisis within six months. VanEck suggests that an ETH ETF could surpass BTC in size. Grayscale's ETH discount doubles within a week. Meanwhile, SOL's market cap reaches an all-time high amid a frenzy surrounding memecoins. Additionally, rumors circulate about a fund losing $1 billion on the BTC-MicroStrategy basis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Soars Into Top Four Amid SLERF Meme Coin Snafu]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=222113</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/222113/solana-top-4-market-cap-slerf-meme-coin"/>
        <updated>2024-03-18T12:12:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While Solana has been rallying, the ecosystem has been reeling from an issue with the SLERF meme coin launch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Crypto Games: PRIME Pumps on 'Parallel' Maker’s Solana Game News, Airdrop Mania Continues]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=222088</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/222088/this-week-crypto-games-prime-parallel-solana-game-airdrop-mania"/>
        <updated>2024-03-17T20:01:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Catch up on this week’s biggest crypto and NFT gaming news and find some weekend reads in our latest roundup.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week on Crypto Twitter: Dencun Goes Live, Dogwifhat Goes Vegas, Craig Wright Goes Down]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=221988</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/221988/this-week-on-crypto-twitter-dencun-dogwifhat-craig-wright-not-satoshi"/>
        <updated>2024-03-17T11:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was a jubilant week for many reasons, despite crypto prices dipping in the end.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reddit Discloses FTC Probe into AI Data Licensing Ahead of IPO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=222039</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/222039/reddit-ai-ftc-investigation-ipo"/>
        <updated>2024-03-16T20:04:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The social media platform's $60 million deal with Google draws regulatory scrutiny as it orepares to go public.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Kawailani Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Game On: The Hottest Upcoming Gaming Token Airdrops]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211029</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211029/game-on-hottest-upcoming-gaming-token-airdrops"/>
        <updated>2024-03-16T19:14:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATED: Crypto gamers can still get in on airdrops for Notcoin, BlockGames, Upland, Nyan Heroes, and more. Here's what you need to know.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Bitcoin Hits All-Time High, Then Gets Battered, While Solana Soars]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=221983</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/221983/this-week-in-coins-bitcoin-falls-after-all-time-high-solana-soars"/>
        <updated>2024-03-16T17:32:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin soared above $73,600 per coin before dropping below $69,000. But Solana made gains, with its market cap hitting an all-time high.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mercedes-Benz to Put AI in Its Assembly Line Robots]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=222004</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/222004/ai-automotive-factory-robots-ai-apptronik"/>
        <updated>2024-03-16T00:44:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The seven-year-old robotics firm says the deal with the automaker is a ”dream scenario.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Parallel’ Creator Details ‘Colony’ AI Game on Solana, Pushing PRIME to All-Time High Price]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=221992</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/221992/parallel-creator-colony-ai-game-solana-prime-all-time-high-price"/>
        <updated>2024-03-15T22:58:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The makers of hot Ethereum NFT game Parallel are shifting to Solana for their next game, an AI-driven “survival sim” called Colony.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogwifhat Spat? Ethereum NFT Auction Reveals Tensions Between Dog’s Owners and Solana Community]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=221974</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/221974/dogwifhat-spat-ethereum-nft-auction-tensions-dog-owners-solana-community"/>
        <updated>2024-03-15T21:35:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The owners of the actual "Dogwifhat" meme canine are trying to get a piece of the $3 billion phenomenon that they started. So why are people upset?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Shooter 'Nyan Heroes' Nearing Early Access With Airdrop Rewards]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=221979</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/221979/solana-shooter-nyan-heroes-early-access-airdrop-rewards"/>
        <updated>2024-03-15T20:36:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nyan Heroes developer 9 Lives Interactive revealed the early access timeline this week alongside word of a new funding round.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Runes Launch at the Halving: Here's Everything You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=221962</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/221962/bitcoin-runes-launch-at-the-halving-heres-everything-you-need-to-know"/>
        <updated>2024-03-15T19:55:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The creator of Bitcoin’s Ordinals protocol is debuting a new fungible token standard to rival BRC-20. Here’s everything we know about Runes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Founder Sam Bankman-Fried Should Get Up to 50 Years in Prison, $11 Billion Fine: DOJ]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=221971</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/221971/ftx-founder-sam-bankman-fried-sentencing-50-years-prison"/>
        <updated>2024-03-15T19:28:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Department of Justice set out its sentencing recommendations Friday after FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried was found guilty last year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Starbucks Is Shutting Down Its Odyssey Beta NFT Rewards Program—Will It Return?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=221967</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/221967/starbucks-shutting-down-odyssey-nft-rewards-program"/>
        <updated>2024-03-15T19:05:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starbucks Odyssey is shutting down this month, and it's unclear whether the Polygon-based NFT rewards program will be revived.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This is The Time of SOL]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DIZFtR67/this-is-the-time-of-sol</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DIZFtR67/this-is-the-time-of-sol"/>
        <updated>2024-03-14T23:10:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETFs match last week’s inflows in just 3 days. ETH Dencun upgrade goes, ETH coins broadly fall. ETH L2 costs for trading decrease dramatically. SOL nears $100bn FDV as activity soars. SOL DEX volume now 3x ETH mainnet. MicroStrategy plans $500m raise to buy more BTC. Franklin Templeton releases memecoin paper. AEVO faces FUD about tokenomics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Hits ATH Again]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/a7WwOWdu/bitcoin-hits-ath-again</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/a7WwOWdu/bitcoin-hits-ath-again"/>
        <updated>2024-03-14T20:22:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin hits a new high at $73.1k with a 2% increase, while Ethereum remains steady at $4050 and Solana sees a similar surge to $154. TON, RBN, RUNE, and QNT emerge as top gainers, capturing market attention. BTC's unprecedented rise is fueled by a record $1 billion in ETF inflows, coinciding with Ethereum's Dencun upgrade promising significant changes for Layer 2 solutions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CPI COMES IN, BTC HOLDS 72]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9A8FE6VE/cpi-comes-in-btc-holds-72</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9A8FE6VE/cpi-comes-in-btc-holds-72"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T13:28:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) at $72k and Ethereum (ETH) at $4035, both up 1%. Solana (SOL) rises 3% to $152. Leading gains: TON, XRP, IOTA, FLOW. Bitcoin nears record high with significant ETF investments. Solana sees spike in new users. TON surges 30% with Telegram IPO rumors. Ark Invest offloads $69m in Coinbase stock. Predictions: Bitcoin could outdo gold, potentially reaching $150k. Blast platform's value hits $3bn with higher yields. Biden proposes crypto miner tax. El Salvador profits $84m from Bitcoin. Monad plans $200m raise led by Paradigm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BITCOIN HITS $72,000!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/W6z0S2OZ/bitcoin-hits-72-000</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/W6z0S2OZ/bitcoin-hits-72-000"/>
        <updated>2024-03-12T10:04:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC hits new ATH of $72k, flips Silver market cap. Wick lower then higher causes $350m liquidations. London Stock Exchange to consider crypto ETNs. Funding again soars before ETF buying begins. Crypto saw record $2.7bn inflows last week. MicroStrategy buys another $821m of BTC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BTC HITS 70K!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/CoPpmqhC/btc-hits-70k</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/CoPpmqhC/btc-hits-70k"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T14:25:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETF net inflows hit $472m in strong week. GBTC outflows hit $10bn, nearly overtaken by new 9. BlackRock to allow more funds to buy BTC ETFs. Rumours still of Qatar buying amid Bukele meeting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Live With Raoul Pal]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mDLO9pe3/live-with-raoul-pal</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mDLO9pe3/live-with-raoul-pal"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T12:59:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SOL up 10%, Pantera raising $250m to buy from FTX. Market flat but spot buyers begin to drive volumes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Streamlining Blockchain: Demystifying Real-Time Insights & Simplifying Data Management]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/z4ol8A6J/streamlining-blockchain-demystifying-real-time-insights-simplifying-data-management</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/z4ol8A6J/streamlining-blockchain-demystifying-real-time-insights-simplifying-data-management"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T09:02:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover how to navigate and overcome the complexities of blockchain data management with QuickNode’s Streams. This webinar, guided by our seasoned experts Nick Yushkevich and Carl DiClementi, provides you with actionable insights into tackling common challenges faced by businesses in the blockchain space. From real-time data streaming that ensures timely decision-making to robust error handling mechanisms that guarantee data integrity, and comprehensive observability features that offer deep insights into your blockchain operations, we’ll cover how QuickNode’s infrastructure is tailored to enhance operational efficiency, scalability, and innovation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOGS ON TOP!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/jB64PVcH/dogs-on-top</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/jB64PVcH/dogs-on-top"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T18:46:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETFs see another $562m net inflow. Fear & Greed hits 90, was above for months in 2021. ETH leads majors, beta-plays take lead in altcoins. BlackRock to start buying BTC in its largest fund. MicroStrategy plans $600m capital raise to buy BTC. BTC flips market cap of Silver. WIF to be listed on Binance, rises 20%. PEPE & WIF mentioned on Bloomberg. Alien Punk sells for $16m, ‘NFTs not dead’. 3 more large NFT sales for $500K.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interview: How SocialFi Will Transform Crypto Farming Game 'Pixels']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pDipznta/interview-how-socialfi-will-transform-crypto-farming-game-pixels</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pDipznta/interview-how-socialfi-will-transform-crypto-farming-game-pixels"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pixels founder Luke Barwikowski joins Decrypt's Andrew Hayward to discuss how the Ronin-based farming game will be transformed through the addition of guilds and changes to resource generation. They also discuss his ultimate vision for Pixels and his team. Note: This interview was recorded shortly before the PIXEL token launch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Orangie Plays the 'Otherside' Apes Come Home Game Event With His Bored Ape]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IdyVeqvK/orangie-plays-the-otherside-apes-come-home-game-event-with-his-bored-ape</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IdyVeqvK/orangie-plays-the-otherside-apes-come-home-game-event-with-his-bored-ape"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T23:03:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rug Radio creator Orangie checked out the limited-time "Apes Come Home" event in Otherside, the Bored Ape metaverse game, and got to use his own Ape avatar. Was it worth the $75K he spent for the NFT? Check out his impressions of the experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['This is the Age of Creators': How DASTAN is Fixing the 'Broken' Media Industry]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/UeOWvV0c/this-is-the-age-of-creators-how-dastan-is-fixing-the-broken-media-industry</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/UeOWvV0c/this-is-the-age-of-creators-how-dastan-is-fixing-the-broken-media-industry"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T15:33:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following the launch of decentralized media publishing company DASTAN, its President Farokh Sarmad, CEO Loxley Fernandes, and COO Quinn Button, Ph. D joined Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz and The Nifty & BoDoggos Founder and Partner Easy to talk about the future of media.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside The Mind Of a Web3 Gamer]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/0Wx2bcVa/inside-the-mind-of-a-web3-gamer</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/0Wx2bcVa/inside-the-mind-of-a-web3-gamer"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T13:39:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Saro McKenna, Co-Founder of Alien Worlds, Linda Ang, Head of Strategy at Aelf, and Sami Chlagou, CEO of Cross the Ages joined Stephen Graves at NFT Paris to explore the profile of the Web3 gamer, the evolving landscape of Web3 gaming and the transition between Web2 and Web3 gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Casper Network: Opening a 'New World of Possibilities' Beyond Enterprise Users]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/xz9F8Lct/casper-network-opening-a-new-world-of-possibilities-beyond-enterprise-users</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/xz9F8Lct/casper-network-opening-a-new-world-of-possibilities-beyond-enterprise-users"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T15:44:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Casper Network's Director of Ecosystem Alizee Carli and Head of Content Joe Benso join Stephen Graves at NFT Paris to talk about how the Layer 1 blockchain is expanding beyond its enterprise user base to Web3-native projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VanEck Web3 Lead: Tokenized Real Estate the 'Holy Grail']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/HHwsvcei/vaneck-web3-lead-tokenized-real-estate-the-holy-grail</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/HHwsvcei/vaneck-web3-lead-tokenized-real-estate-the-holy-grail"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T13:05:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VanEck's Head of NFT Community and Web3, Matt Bartlett, joined Stephen Graves at NFT Paris to discuss the launch of its new NFT platform Segment.io, and the need for regulatory clarity in the NFT space.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Orangie Plays 'Dookey Dash: Unclogged,' the Bored Ape Game With Over $1 Million in Prizes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/uY3bIt1R/orangie-plays-dookey-dash-unclogged-the-bored-ape-game-with-over-1-million-in-prizes</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/uY3bIt1R/orangie-plays-dookey-dash-unclogged-the-bored-ape-game-with-over-1-million-in-prizes"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T22:37:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rug Radio creator Orangie shares a first look at an early version of Dookey Dash: Unclogged, the new free-to-play version of 2023's crypto gaming sensation. Yuga Labs is releasing the new version of the game this spring with over $1 million in prizes up for grabs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Paris Saint-Germain FC Joined Chiliz as a Validator]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/spD1tCwb/how-paris-saint-germain-fc-joined-chiliz-as-a-validator</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/spD1tCwb/how-paris-saint-germain-fc-joined-chiliz-as-a-validator"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T15:16:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chiliz Chief Strategy Officer Max Rabinovitch joined Decrypt's Stephen Graves at NFT Paris to discuss Paris Saint-Germain FC joining its network as a validator, and how consequential Web3 adoption in sport will come from the grassroots.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Sandbox Co-Founder Sébastien Borget: 'The Future of Gaming is User-Generated Content']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Vf77nhXF/the-sandbox-co-founder-sebastien-borget-the-future-of-gaming-is-user-generated-content</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Vf77nhXF/the-sandbox-co-founder-sebastien-borget-the-future-of-gaming-is-user-generated-content"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T13:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sébastien Borget, COO and co-founder of The Sandbox, joined Decrypt's Stephen Graves at NFT Paris to talk about the metaverse platform's launch of user-generated content, AI in gaming, and open metaverse standards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Calladita' Director Miguel Faus: How Web3 Filmmaking is 'Taking the Castle']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IDoFDfZy/calladita-director-miguel-faus-how-web3-filmmaking-is-taking-the-castle</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IDoFDfZy/calladita-director-miguel-faus-how-web3-filmmaking-is-taking-the-castle"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T16:18:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Miguel Faus, director of NFT-funded feature film "Calladita," joined Decrypt's Stephen Graves at NFT Paris to talk about the film's recent premiere and how the "radically independent" decentralized Film3 movement is evolving.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>