<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-09-03T02:20:23.853Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-09-03T02:20:23.853Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Lawyer, Coinbase CLO Believe SEC’s Interlocutory Appeal Will Get Rejected]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754990a95b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/coinbase-clo-believe-secs-interlocutory-appeal/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T01:42:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The battle between the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and Ripple Labs over the regulatory status of XRP took a dramatic turn last week. The latest powerplay? A Hail Mary interlocutory appeal from the authority. The agency tried appealing a past court decision allowing Ripple to use a “fair notice” defense. However, prominent lawyers vehemently oppose this, predicting its inevitable rejection.
 
Ripple’s chief counsel, James K. Filan, and Coinbase CLO Paul Grewal already called the SEC’s bluff. In their view, the rigid standards for an interlocutory appeal still need to be met. These mid-case appeals only proceed if waiting for a final verdict would cause “irreparable harm.” According to Filan, the agency has yet to prove this harm exists. 
 
 
The lawyer forecasted a quick reject…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kent Glory</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robert Kennedy Jr: China Doesn’t Want War With US — They Want to ‘Bury’ Us Economically]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754990ebb5</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/robert-kennedy-jr-china-doesnt-want-war-with-us-they-want-to-bury-us-economically/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T01:37:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. presidential candidate Robert F. Kennedy Jr. (RFK Jr.) has explained that China does not want a war with the U.S. However, he warned that China wants to “bury” the U.S. economically. “I’m not afraid of the United States competing with China head to head and countries around the world. I think that’s good for us. I think we win that competition,” the presidential hopeful stated.
 
RFK Jr on China and BRICS Competing With US
 
U.S. presidential candidate Robert F. Kennedy Jr. (RFK Jr.) shared his views on several topics in an interview with CNBC on Wednesday. RFK Jr. is a son of former U.S. Attorney General and Senator Robert F. Kennedy and nephew of former U.S. President John F. Kennedy.
 
Among the topics RFK Jr. delved into were China’s global influence and the expansion of the BRICS…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto's Future Under Biden Presidency, Dogecoin's Potential Surge And More: This Week In Cryptocurrency]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18876359/Cryptos-Future-Under-Biden-Presidency-Dogecoins-Potential-Surge-And-More-This-Week-In-Cryptocurrency</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18876359/Cryptos-Future-Under-Biden-Presidency-Dogecoins-Potential-Surge-And-More-This-Week-In-Cryptocurrency"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T01:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week in the world of cryptocurrency was nothing short of eventful. From concerns about the future of crypto in the U.S. under President Joe Biden to the potential of Dogecoin (CRYPTO: DOGE) skyrocketing due to Elon Musk‘s influence, the sector was abuzz with news. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Billion-Dollar Bank Says It May Freeze, Terminate Accounts Sending ‘Unacceptable’ Transactions – Here’s What It Means]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18876341/Billion-Dollar-Bank-Says-It-May-Freeze-Terminate-Accounts-Sending-Unacceptable-Transactions-Heres-What-It-Means</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18876341/Billion-Dollar-Bank-Says-It-May-Freeze-Terminate-Accounts-Sending-Unacceptable-Transactions-Heres-What-It-Means"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T00:04:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the largest banks in Australia says it may freeze and terminate customer accounts that engage in certain types of “unacceptable account conduct.” National Australia Bank says a new policy launching in November is designed to protect people from harm by automatically flagging customer...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Files Opposition to SEC’s Motion to Certify Interlocutory Appeal of XRP Ruling]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75499f7b6c</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ripple-files-opposition-to-secs-motion-to-certify-interlocutory-appeal-of-xrp-ruling/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T23:36:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Labs has filed its opposition to the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission’s request for Judge Analisa Torres to certify an interlocutory appeal of her ruling regarding XRP. The crypto firm has argued that “the exceptional circumstances required for interlocutory appeal are absent.”
 
Ripple Says Court Should Deny SEC’s Motion
 
On Friday, Ripple Labs filed its response to the motion by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to certify an interlocutory appeal. The securities watchdog is seeking to appeal the ruling by District Judge Analisa Torres regarding the “programmatic” offers and sales of XRP over crypto trading platforms and Ripple’s “other distributions.” The regulator also seeks to stay the district court proceedings.
 
The Ripple legal team wrote:
 

The cour…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Study Shows Fastest Growing L2 Blockchains Adopt Users in Weeks, Not Months]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7549872892</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/study-shows-fastest-growing-l2-blockchains-adopt-users-in-weeks-not-months/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T21:31:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The newest layer two (L2) blockchains are being adopted at record speeds, with some reaching one million users within weeks rather than months, according to a study by Coingecko.
 
L2 Blockchains Hit One Million Users Faster Than Ever, Coingecko Study Shows
 
A layer two (L2) blockchain runs alongside an existing blockchain like Ethereum to improve transaction speeds and reduce fees. The Ethereum network now has several popular L2 solutions, but they haven’t always seen rapid adoption. Coingecko recently published a report on the subject which highlights the growth of today’s top L2s.
 
Arbitrum, an ETH-based L2, took 303 days to reach one million unique addresses after its mainnet launch on August 31, 2021, according to Coingecko’s contributor Shaun Paul Lee. The L2 solution Optimism, lau…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[If you Bought $100 of LiteCoin LTC… #shorts]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18876268/If-you-Bought-100-of-LiteCoin-LTC-shorts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18876268/If-you-Bought-100-of-LiteCoin-LTC-shorts"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T21:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you Bought $100 of LiteCoin in 2015, here's how much money you would have made! Litecoin hit a low of $1.15 in 2015 and a high of $410 a few years after!Enjoy smoother trading journey with our new trading campaign with BYDFi. You'll get:✔️ No KYC with up to 0.5 BTC daily withdrawals (even for...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Vanishing OFF Exchanges!! | The Great Bitcoin Houdini!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18876266/Bitcoin-Vanishing-OFF-Exchanges-The-Great-Bitcoin-Houdini</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18876266/Bitcoin-Vanishing-OFF-Exchanges-The-Great-Bitcoin-Houdini"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T20:58:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin is playing hard-to-get, vanishing off exchanges, and throwing its own party! Sprinkle in some Bullish Bitcoin forecasts, a side of U.S. debt dilemmas, and impending Bitcoin ETF approval from giants like BlackRock, and you've got a recipe for the ultimate Bitcoin Bull Run in 2024! Bon...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Startup Wants to Use AI to Improve Your Morning Commute]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154729</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154729/oxa-startup-using-ai-to-improve-morning-commute"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T20:53:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following a successful $140 million Series C fundraise, Oxa is set to debut its driverless shuttles in Florida.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Startup Wants to Use AI to Improve Your Morning Commute]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18876261/This-Startup-Wants-to-Use-AI-to-Improve-Your-Morning-Commute</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18876261/This-Startup-Wants-to-Use-AI-to-Improve-Your-Morning-Commute"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T20:53:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following a successful $140 million Series C fundraise, Oxa is set to debut its driverless shuttles in Florida.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bloomberg on NFT Market: Plummeting Sales and Waning Investor Interest Signal a Bleak Future]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18876260/Bloomberg-on-NFT-Market-Plummeting-Sales-and-Waning-Investor-Interest-Signal-a-Bleak-Future</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18876260/Bloomberg-on-NFT-Market-Plummeting-Sales-and-Waning-Investor-Interest-Signal-a-Bleak-Future"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T20:41:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to a report by Olga Kharif and James Tarmy for Bloomberg, the Non-Fungible Token (NFT) market is undergoing a severe downturn characterized by plummeting trading volumes and dwindling investor enthusiasm. Daniel Maegaard, a prominent NFT collector known by the pseudonym Seedphrase, has...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Half of the People in Turkey Now Own Crypto: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154724</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154724/republic-of-turkey-crypto-adoption-half-kucoin"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T20:32:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KuCoin says crypto adoption is high in Turkey, as observed in other nations struggling with rapid inflation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alyssa Hertig</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Half of the People in Turkey Now Own Crypto: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18876242/Half-of-the-People-in-Turkey-Now-Own-Crypto-Report</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18876242/Half-of-the-People-in-Turkey-Now-Own-Crypto-Report"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T20:32:30.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$114,500,000,000 in US Treasuries Dumped By China and New BRICS Member Saudi Arabia]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18876225/114500000000-in-US-Treasuries-Dumped-By-China-and-New-BRICS-Member-Saudi-Arabia</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18876225/114500000000-in-US-Treasuries-Dumped-By-China-and-New-BRICS-Member-Saudi-Arabia"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T20:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRICS members China and Saudi Arabia are unloading hundreds of billions of dollars worth of US treasuries. New numbers from the Treasury Department show that China trimmed its US treasury holdings from $938.8 billion in June 2022 to $835.4 billion in June 2023 – a decrease of about $103.4...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 Social Network Altcoin Skyrockets by More Than 308% This Week, Defying Sideways Crypto Market]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18876217/Web3-Social-Network-Altcoin-Skyrockets-by-More-Than-308-This-Week-Defying-Sideways-Crypto-Market</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18876217/Web3-Social-Network-Altcoin-Skyrockets-by-More-Than-308-This-Week-Defying-Sideways-Crypto-Market"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T20:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A web3 decentralized social network altcoin printed a new all-time high on Friday, defying the ongoing crypto market doldrums. CyberConnect (CYBER) aims to enable developers to create social apps where users own their digital identities and data. The project’s native asset, CYBER, ripped to a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOGE Founder Says His X App Paycheck Shrinks, He Reveals Why]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18876226/DOGE-Founder-Says-His-X-App-Paycheck-Shrinks-He-Reveals-Why</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18876226/DOGE-Founder-Says-His-X-App-Paycheck-Shrinks-He-Reveals-Why"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Colorado Enables Crypto Payments via PayPal for Driver’s License and Vehicle Registration Renewals]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18876216/Colorado-Enables-Crypto-Payments-via-PayPal-for-Drivers-License-and-Vehicle-Registration-Renewals</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18876216/Colorado-Enables-Crypto-Payments-via-PayPal-for-Drivers-License-and-Vehicle-Registration-Renewals"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T19:55:28.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defi Sector Navigates an Extended Crypto Winter: TVL Dips to February 2021 Levels]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75498e9618</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/defi-sector-navigates-an-extended-crypto-winter-tvl-dips-to-february-2021-levels/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T19:40:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The realm of decentralized finance (defi) is grappling with the aftermath of the sweeping crypto market slump that marked the close of August. As it stands, the total value locked (TVL) in defi, pegged at $37.59 billion, has plummeted to a low last witnessed in the second week of February 2021.
 
Crypto Winter’s Grip on Defi: TVL Stumbles to $37 Billion
 
The total value locked in defi is on a steady decline, and as of September 1, 2023, it’s teetering at roughly $37.59 billion. Rewinding to February 9, 2021, this was the last time the TVL stood at such a level, right before it surged to its record peak.
 
By May 11, 2021, it swelled to an impressive $121 billion, and by November 8, 2021, it soared to a staggering $178 billion. Although there was a brief resurgence to $161 billion on April…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Community Joins Forces with Oprah and The Rock]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18876200/Crypto-Community-Joins-Forces-with-Oprah-and-The-Rock</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18876200/Crypto-Community-Joins-Forces-with-Oprah-and-The-Rock"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T19:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto community has united in solidarity with the Maui community, rallying behind a relief...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Youtuber Loses $60,000 In Crypto and NFTs After Exposing His Private Key While Live Streaming]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18876208/Youtuber-Loses-60000-In-Crypto-and-NFTs-After-Exposing-His-Private-Key-While-Live-Streaming</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18876208/Youtuber-Loses-60000-In-Crypto-and-NFTs-After-Exposing-His-Private-Key-While-Live-Streaming"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T19:26:22.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John Deaton Says Jim Cramer Should Be ‘Ashamed’ for Misleading the Public on XRP]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18876191/John-Deaton-Says-Jim-Cramer-Should-Be-Ashamed-for-Misleading-the-Public-on-XRP</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18876191/John-Deaton-Says-Jim-Cramer-Should-Be-Ashamed-for-Misleading-the-Public-on-XRP"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T19:21:13.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pressure Mounts on Worldcoin as More People Sign Up to Get Iris Scanned]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18876198/Pressure-Mounts-on-Worldcoin-as-More-People-Sign-Up-to-Get-Iris-Scanned</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18876198/Pressure-Mounts-on-Worldcoin-as-More-People-Sign-Up-to-Get-Iris-Scanned"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T19:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin, the controversial project created by OpenAI CEO Sam Altman and launched in July, has attracted over 2.3 million global users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Are The AI Celebrities You Can Date Right Now]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154705</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154705/here-are-the-ai-celebrities-you-can-date-right-now"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T19:12:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The modern twist on the 900 numbers of the past, AI chatbots provide interactive conversations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Are The AI Celebrities You Can Date Right Now]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18876189/Here-Are-The-AI-Celebrities-You-Can-Date-Right-Now</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18876189/Here-Are-The-AI-Celebrities-You-Can-Date-Right-Now"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T19:12:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The modern twist on the 900 numbers of the past, AI chatbots provide interactive conversations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Total Market Capitalization of Stablecoins Declined in August: What’s the Cause?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18876177/The-Total-Market-Capitalization-of-Stablecoins-Declined-in-August-Whats-the-Cause</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18876177/The-Total-Market-Capitalization-of-Stablecoins-Declined-in-August-Whats-the-Cause"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T19:01:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoin market cap experienced a decline in August. So, what are the reasons for the partial decline? Continue Reading: The Total Market Capitalization of Stablecoins Declined in August: What’s the Cause?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[German Airline Lufthansa to Launch NFT Loyalty Program on Polygon]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18876168/German-Airline-Lufthansa-to-Launch-NFT-Loyalty-Program-on-Polygon</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18876168/German-Airline-Lufthansa-to-Launch-NFT-Loyalty-Program-on-Polygon"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T18:56:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lufthansa and Polygon are taking off together, quite literally, it seems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. SEC Punts on Bitcoin (BTC) Spot Exchange-Traded Fund Approvals, Delays Decisions Until October]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18876155/US-SEC-Punts-on-Bitcoin-BTC-Spot-Exchange-Traded-Fund-Approvals-Delays-Decisions-Until-October</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18876155/US-SEC-Punts-on-Bitcoin-BTC-Spot-Exchange-Traded-Fund-Approvals-Delays-Decisions-Until-October"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T18:45:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) is delaying its decision on the approval of spot-based Bitcoin (BTC) exchange-traded funds (ETFs) until October. In new filings, the regulatory agency announces that it will be pushing back its decision to approve or deny numerous bids to create...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top BTC Whales Set Three-Year Record: Details]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18876156/Top-BTC-Whales-Set-Three-Year-Record-Details</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18876156/Top-BTC-Whales-Set-Three-Year-Record-Details"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T18:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s Largest Accounts: Peering Into the Top 10 Wallets on the ‘BTC Rich List’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754977715e</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoins-largest-accounts-peering-into-the-top-10-wallets-on-the-btc-rich-list/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T17:40:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In recent weeks, buzz within the crypto sphere has centered on prominent bitcoin and ethereum holders. Some addresses are awash with speculation, while others have earned distinct labels. Interestingly, a handful have purportedly been unmasked, leading to many of the top ten BTC addresses being tagged. The following is a closer peek at the top ten bitcoin wallets featured in ‘Bitcoin’s Rich List’ of addresses.
 
From Exchanges to the U.S. Government — Shining a Light on the Largest Bitcoin Wallets in 2023
 
Recently, chatter in the crypto world zeroed in on the identity of the third-largest bitcoin (BTC) wallet. Both OXT researcher Ergo and crypto data analytics firm Arkham Intelligence believe it’s likely affiliated with Robinhood — a sentiment echoed on Arkham’s dashboard. However, as cu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Bitcoin and Ethereum Unmoved in Slow Market Week]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154695</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154695/this-week-in-coins-bitcoin-ethereum-toncoin-ton-polygon-matic"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T17:08:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Also, the SEC was ordered to review its denial of crypto asset manager Grayscale’s ETF proposal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biggest Video Games Releasing in September 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154658</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154658/biggest-video-games-releasing-september-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T17:03:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Summer is over, but the games are still coming. From Starfield to Final Fantasy, here are the biggest video games releasing in September.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China’s Cryptocurrency Verdict: Legal Property Or Trouble Ahead?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75497a1b70</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/chinas-cryptocurrency-decision-legal-property/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T15:39:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency has long been a contentious subject in China, with the government imposing strict regulations and outright bans on various aspects of the industry. However, a recent report from China’s People’s Court challenges this historical stance, offering newfound recognition to virtual assets as legal property.
 
In a significant departure from conventional policy, the report titled “Identification of the Property Attributes of Virtual Currency and Disposal of Property Involved in the Case” asserts that virtual assets possess economic attributes that categorize them as property. 
 
This revelation cited in a report from a local publication is a remarkable departure from China’s blanket ban on foreign digital assets, asserting that individual-held virtual assets should enjoy legal prot…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFT Sales Slide for Third Consecutive Week Amid Crypto Downturn]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75497a3d4e</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/nft-sales-slide-for-third-consecutive-week-amid-crypto-downturn/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T15:37:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sales of non-fungible tokens (NFTs) have taken another hit, declining over 10% from the previous week, with transactions totaling $85,046,840 since Saturday, August 26, 2023. This marks the third consecutive week of falling NFT sales, reflecting the broader crypto economy’s downturn and its significant impact on the NFT marketplace.
 
Can NFTs Rally in September? Recent 3-Week Sales Trend Casts Doubt
 
Cryptoslam.io reports that in the past week, NFT sales have seen a 10.71% decline, while the volume of NFT transactions has fallen by 17.15% compared to the previous week. Interestingly, the number of NFT purchasers surged, showing a 20.35% increase from the week before. Data compiled on September 2, 2023, at 9 a.m. (ET), spanning the last seven days since August 26, reveals that Ethereum-ba…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Pushes Back Against SEC’s Appeal Request With New Court Filing]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7549675008</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ripple-pushes-back-against-secs-appeal-request/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T14:38:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In its latest court filing, the legal team representing Ripple Labs – the company behind the XRP token – argued that the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) doesn’t have the grounds to request an appeal.
 
This comes as the SEC looks to dispute Ripple’s partial victory after Judge Annalisa Torres ruled – in July – that XRP doesn’t classify as a security when sold to retail investors. 
 
In its interlocutory appeal, the commission stated that an appeal was merited “because they involved controlling questions of law as to which there are substantial grounds for difference of opinion.”
 
Ripple Calls For Denial Of SEC’s Request To Appeal Or Stay
 
On Friday, September 1, Ripple’s lawyers stated in a new filing to the US District Court for the Southern District of New York t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Opeyemi Sule</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biggest Movers: Ton 10% Higher on Saturday, Hitting Highest Level Since May]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754963ae33</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/biggest-movers-ton-10-higher-on-saturday-hitting-highest-level-since-may/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T13:46:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Toncoin was easily one of the biggest movers in crypto markets to start the weekend, as price rose by over 10%. Saturday’s surge comes despite the global market cap mostly trending lower, having fallen by 0.43% as of writing. XRP was one of the tokens to fall, dropping below a key price floor.
 
Toncoin (TON)
 
Toncoin (TON) was a notable mover in today’s session, as the token rose by as much as 10% on Saturday.
 
After a low of $1.74 on Friday, TON/USD surged to an intraday peak of $1.95 to start the weekend.
 
As a result of the move, toncoin climbed to its strongest point since May 24, which was the last time price traded above $2.00.
 
 
Today’s rally comes as the 14-day relative strength index (RSI) rebounded at a floor of 75.00, following a surge above 83.00.
 
Price strength is deeply overbought, however this has not stopped bulls from continuing to send TON even higher.
 
This could be a recipe for a bear trap however, with a change in direction almost certainly on the cards in the not too distant future.
 
 
XRP
 
XRP, formerly ripple, was in the red to start the weekend, as the token marginally dropped below a key support point.
 
XRP/USD fell to a bottom at $0.4886 on Saturday, which comes following a peak at $0.5081 the day prior.
 
This downturn comes as bears pushed price below a price floor of $0.5100 earlier in the week, with momentum continuing to slip since then.
 
 
Ever since the ripple ruling, which saw XRP price spike to an almost two-year high, the token has mostly moved lower.
 
The RSI is now tracking around a floor of 29.00, which is in the midst of a bear zone. However, should this level hold firm, there could be a reversal next week.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
Could XRP jump back above $0.5100 in the coming days? Let us know your thoughts in the comments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MakerDAO Could Utilize Solana Codebase For ‘NewChain’ Project – Details]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75496c5d2f</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/makerdao-could-utilize-solana-codebase-for-newchain/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T13:38:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MakerDAO Co-founder Rune Christensen has suggested the DeFi project utilize a fork of Solana’s codebase to build its proposed “NewChain.”
 
Back in May, the MakerDAO announced its “Endgame” network update aimed at improving the protocol’s “efficiency, resilience and participation” via the formation of a “strong governance equilibrium.” 
 
The “NewChain” is a vital part of the Endgame’s fifth and final phase, in which the MakerDAO protocol will be fully rebuilt on its own new, native layer-one blockchain. 
 
Christensen has described this final phase as a long-term project set to run for over three years. However, in easing the team’s effort, the MakerDAO Co-founder believes they can explore the fork of existing open-source blockchain rather than building a new protocol from scratch. 
 
 
S…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Semilore Faleti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mysterious Owner Of Second-Largest Ethereum Wallet Exposed By DeFi Protocol]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7549695cf0</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/second-largest-ethereum-wallet-exposed/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T12:38:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale is known to be one of the largest holders of the flagship cryptocurrency, Bitcoin. However, a recent report by crypto analytics platform Arkham Intelligence suggests that the asset manager could also be the entity with the second-largest Ethereum holdings.
 
 
Grayscale Holds Close To $5 Billion In ETH
 
Arkham tweeted that it “identified” the Grayscale Ethereum Trust on-chain. According to the platform, this discovery places Grayscale as the “second largest ETH entity,” with the asset manager holding close to $5 billion (around $4.88 billion at the time of writing) in Ether.
 
 
Breaking: Arkham has identified the Grayscale Ethereum Trust on chain.
 
It is now the second largest ETH entity globally with $5B in ETH.
 
This had not been previously reported or publicly identified. …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Technical Analysis: BTC Starts Weekend Trading Close to $25,000]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7549699140</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-ethereum-technical-analysis-btc-starts-weekend-trading-close-to-25000/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T12:36:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin started the weekend trading below the $26,000 level, as bears seized market momentum to end the week. Price surged during the early part of the week, climbing over the $28,000 mark. However in the days that followed, sentiment has mostly trended lower. Ethereum remains in the red.
 
Bitcoin
 
Bitcoin continued to trend lower on Saturday, as the bears were once again in control of crypto market sentiment.
 
Following a high of $28,148 on Tuesday, BTC/USD started the weekend falling to a low of $25,362.61.
 
The decline has come as a result of profit taking, and also the changing economic climate in the United States.
 
 
Consumer spending is slowing, whilst the labor market remains tight as a result of increasing interest rates.
 
Looking at the chart, today’s decline pushed bitcoin below a key support point of $25,600, however bulls have since reentered.
 
At the time of writing, BTC is now trading at $25,818.66, with a target of $26,000 likely to be present throughout the weekend.
 
 
Ethereum
 
After almost falling below $1,600 on Friday, ethereum (ETH) was mostly higher to start the weekend’s session.
 
ETH/USD peaked at $1,650.71 earlier in the day, but momentum has since dropped, with the price now at $1,635.02.
 
The world’s second largest cryptocurrency has not been able to move back above $1,650, which has been a point of price support.
 
 
From the chart it appears that ETH managed to avoid dropping under $1,600 due to the relative strength index (RSI) colliding with a floor at 36.00.
 
As of writing, price strength is now tracking at a reading of 37.04, with the next visible ceiling at 49.00.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
Do you expect ethereum to move beyond $1,700 next week? Leave your thoughts in the comments below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top BRICS Diplomats Approached Indonesia With Proposal to Join, Foreign Minister Says]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75495384bc</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/top-brics-diplomats-approached-indonesia-with-proposal-to-join-foreign-minister-says/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T10:35:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The foreign ministers of the BRICS states have reached out to invite Indonesia to become a member of the group, their Indonesian counterpart unveiled. The government in Jakarta is still weighing the benefits of joining the organization and is yet to decide whether to apply formally.
 
BRICS Nations Sought to Induct Indonesia Into Their Expanding Bloc of Emerging Economies
 
Indonesia has been contacted by the top diplomats of the BRICS member states (Brazil, Russia, India, China, and South Africa) with a proposal to join the grouping, the country’s Minister of Foreign Affairs, Retno Marsudi, told a parliamentary committee.
 
“All BRICS foreign ministers made an approach to Indonesia to invite it to join,” she was quoted by the Antara news agency as saying during a meeting of the First Comm…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lubomir Tassev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Base Network Rakes in the Fees Riding Crypto's Favorite Memes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154566</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154566/base-network-rakes-fees-riding-cryptos-favorite-memes"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T10:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With more than $3.3 million in profit generated since its mainnet launch on August 9, the Base network is firing on all cylinders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DC Circuit Court of Appeals Chastises SEC for Grayscale Denial]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75495ad7d2</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/dc-circuit-court-of-appeals-chastises-sec-for-grayscale-denial/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T09:06:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Tuesday, August 29, 2023, The U.S. Court of Appeals, District of Columbia Circuit (Court) unanimously granted Grayscale’s petition for review of the Securities Exchange Commission’s (SEC) denial of Grayscale’s Bitcoin Exchange Traded Product (Grayscale ETP) and vacated the SEC denial order. The Court chastised the SEC for its “arbitrary and capricious” treatment of Grayscale’s ETP and its inconsistent treatment of substantially identical cases where it approved bitcoin futures ETPs from Teucrium and Valkyrie.
 
The following editorial was written by guest authors Wyatt Noble and Michael Handelsman for Kelman.Law
 
Brief Spot and Futures Markets Explainer
 
Those unfamiliar with spot and futures markets keep reading. However, feel free to skip ahead if you are already familiar with tradi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Guest Author</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Colorado DMV Accepts Crypto Payments Through Paypal]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754941934e</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/colorado-dmv-accepts-crypto-payments-through-paypal/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T07:36:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Colorado Department of Motor Vehicles (DMV) has announced it accepts cryptocurrency for its online services via the payment processor Paypal. Besides paying local taxes with coins, residents of the crypto-friendly state will be able to use their digital cash to renew driver’s licenses and plates.
 
Colorado Introduces Online Payments With Crypto at the DMV
 
People in Colorado who use the online services of the state’s Department of Motor Vehicles, like renewing a driver’s license or vehicle registration, can now pay with cryptocurrency through the popular payment platform Paypal, the Denver 7 TV channel reported.
 
Those who chose to pay with crypto will be directed to Paypal, where they can select the digital currency they want to use which will then be converted to U.S. dollars and eventually transferred to the department, DMV officials explained.
 
 
“At the DMV, we’re always looking for ways to better serve Coloradans and leverage technology to offer our services,” Senior Director Electra Bustle emphasized in a statement quoted on Thursday. The executive further elaborated:
 

This new online cryptocurrency payment option is yet another way the DMV is providing innovative and convenient service delivery to our customers.
 
A service fee of $1 plus 1.83% of the DMV total will be applicable to payments made with cryptocurrencies, the department noted. The DMV is currently accepting crypto transactions only through Paypal which can apply its own fees.
 
Colorado has been open towards cryptocurrency adoption. Under Governor Jared Polis, it started accepting crypto as payment of state taxes and fees in the summer of 2020. The Colorado Digital Token Act, which allows certain cryptocurrencies to have securities exemptions, was passed the previous year.
 
 Do you expect other states to introduce crypto payments for taxes and services? Tell us in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lubomir Tassev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dollar Share in Reserves Drops Below 60%, Yuan Rises, Russian Diplomat Says]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7549481050</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/dollar-share-in-reserves-drops-below-60-yuan-rises-russian-diplomat-says/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T06:05:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The share of currencies other than the U.S. dollar and the euro in international reserves is on the rise, according to a Russian representative. The trend is being observed as a growing number of countries try to use their national currencies in foreign trade settlements, the official noted. 
 
Russia Sees Alternative Currencies Like Chinese Yuan Replacing U.S. Dollar in Reserves and Settlements
 
The share of the U.S. dollar in international reserves has dropped below 60% amid increasing use of alternative currencies in international settlements, the Spokeswoman of Russia’s Ministry of Foreign Affairs, Maria Zakharova, pointed out on Wednesday, quoted by the official Russian Tass news agency.
 
The Russian diplomat remarked that this indicator for the status of the greenback was at 72% in…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lubomir Tassev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta’s Metaverse Is Finding Its Legs — In Avatars]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754937fd8a</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/metas-metaverse-is-finding-its-legs-in-avatars/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T04:04:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meta’s Horizon Worlds, the metaverse flagship app of the company formerly known as Facebook, is reportedly getting legs as part of users’ avatars in the coming weeks. The functionality is already present in a public test version of the app, but it is only present in Horizon Home, the default space of each user.
 
Meta’s Metaverse Gets Legs for Avatars
 
Horizon Worlds, Meta’s metaverse app, has reached a goal proposed almost a year ago: to give legs to its avatars. According to Uploadvr’s reports, the feature will be included in Horizon Worlds in the coming weeks, with the functionality being present in a public test version of Horizon Home, the default room in which all Quest headset users enter when logging on.
 
The legs donned by the virtual avatars will only be visible in third-person…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Economist Peter Schiff Warns Bidenomics Will Soon Be Exposed for Fraud]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75493d71ae</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/economist-peter-schiff-warns-bidenomics-will-soon-be-exposed-for-fraud/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T02:35:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Economist Peter Schiff has warned that Bidenomics “will soon be exposed for the fraud that it is, as inflation and unemployment heat up while the economy cools down.” He cautioned: “If Americans think the economy is bad now, just wait until they see what’s coming. Once the dollar cracks, both inflation and interest rates will rise sharply. This will send the economy deeper into recession, causing many people to lose their jobs. That’s the real Bidenomics.” 
 
Peter Schiff Calls Bidenomics Fraud
 
Gold bug and economist Peter Schiff slammed President Joe Biden’s economic policy, known as Bidenomics, in a series of posts on social media platform X this week.
 
“If Americans think the economy is bad now, just wait until they see what’s coming. Once the dollar cracks, both inflation and intere…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Yuan Not Ready to Topple US Dollar as World Reserve Currency, Says Strategist]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75493b22a0</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/chinese-yuan-not-ready-to-topple-us-dollar-as-world-reserve-currency-says-strategist/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T01:01:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A global macro strategist has explained that the Chinese yuan is unlikely to replace the U.S. dollar as the global reserve currency. She emphasized that the “weaponization” of the USD is one of the top reasons why Russia, China, and other BRICS nations have been seeking an alternative to the dollar.
 
US Dollar v Chinese Yuan
 
Skylar Montgomery, senior global macro strategist at Globaldata TS Lombard, an independent investment research group focusing on global macro and strategy, explained in a note on Wednesday that the Chinese yuan is unlikely to replace the U.S. dollar as the world’s reserve currency.
 
She detailed that the U.S. dollar’s global reserve currency status “is a privilege that gives the U.S. significant political, economic, and market influence.” However, she cautioned tha…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Co-Founder Says FTX's SOL Should Be Distributed to Customers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154663</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154663/solana-cofounder-says-ftx-sol-should-distributed-customers"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T22:32:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FTX’s new management is starting to move its holdings around. Amid fears of an impending dump, a Solana co-founder has an idea.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Just One Dose of Magic Mushroom Psychedelic Can Ease Depression for Weeks, Study Finds]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154664</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154664/depression-treatment-psychedelic-psilocybin-mushrooms"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T21:35:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Psilocybin is having a magical effect on major depression disorders, but more study is needed, new research suggests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood Buys Back Sam Bankman-Fried’s Seized Shares Worth $600 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154656</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154656/robinhood-buys-back-sam-bankman-fried-seized-shares"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T18:42:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood shares jumped 3% following news of the buy back.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uniswap Ruling Creates Regulatory 'Anomaly' for DeFi: Legal Scholar]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154651</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154651/uniswap-ruling-creates-regulatory-anomaly-defi-legal-scholar"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T18:19:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A district judge's recent decision in a class action lawsuit against Uniswap demarcates DeFi from centralized exchanges like Coinbase.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Two Most Popular Stable Diffusion UIs Just Got Major Upgrades]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154618</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154618/the-two-most-popular-stable-diffusion-uis-just-got-major-upgrades"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T17:20:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With new features in Automatic 1111 and InvokeAI's latest versions, the Stable Diffusion platforms are easier and more powerful.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NYC Seaport Scavenger Hunt Brings NFTs Into the Real World]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=153493</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/153493/nyc-seaport-scavenger-hunt-brings-nfts-real-world"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T17:19:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manhattan's Seaport neighborhood is hosting a scavenger hunt driven by NFTs and QR codes, but it wasn't all smooth sailing at first.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Incredible Shrinking Market Share of Circle’s USDC Stablecoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154608</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154608/shinking-market-share-circle-usdc-stablecoin"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T17:07:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For most of 2022, USDC was close to catching its rival Tether. But that figure has been shrinking—and fast.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tennis Meets Tech as Tiffany, Amex, Wilson Descend Upon US Open]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154542</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154542/tennis-meets-tech-tiffany-amex-wilson-us-open"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T15:49:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Major brands are using the U.S. Open tennis tournament to show off how they're embracing tech like augmented reality, NFTs, and VR.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INTERVIEW: How Will Aurory Use NFTs and Crypto?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qv3VwNmM/interview-how-will-aurory-use-nfts-and-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qv3VwNmM/interview-how-will-aurory-use-nfts-and-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T15:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Natoli, Aurory's Head of Marketing and Business Development, tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how the Aurory games will use NFTs and crypto and shares the studio's broader stance on the tech.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cambridge Updates Bitcoin Mining Index to Reveal True Power Consumption]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154593</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154593/cambridge-updates-bitcoin-mining-index-reveal-true-power-consumption"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T14:58:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Experts say there’s still room for improvement, but that Cambridge’s new model is a big step forward.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Cloud's James Tromans on the Intersection of AI and Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OeD4uoLj/google-clouds-james-tromans-on-the-intersection-of-ai-and-web3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OeD4uoLj/google-clouds-james-tromans-on-the-intersection-of-ai-and-web3"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google's Global Head of Google Cloud for Web3 James Tromans sat down with Decrypt's Jason Nelson to discuss how AI can help Web3 companies come to market faster and the real value of Web3 tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether's Stablecoin USDT 'Has a Peg Stability Problem', Claims Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154580</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154580/tethers-stablecoin-usdt-has-a-peg-stability-problem-claims-analyst"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T12:15:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One possible solution would be for Tether to reconsider its redemption fee and minimum redeemable amount, says a Kaiko analyst.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Trading Volumes Headed for Worst Quarter Since 2019]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154583</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154583/bitcoin-ethereum-trading-volumes-headed-worst-quarter-since-2019"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T12:05:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trading volumes for the largest cryptocurrencies in Bitcoin and Ethereum are on track for their worst quarter in four years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who’s Who in Global Crypto Regulation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=153195</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/whos-who-in-global-crypto-regulation"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T10:50:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is difficult to properly assess cryptocurrencies through the lenses of traditional finance—it is even challenging to determine which agencies may be responsible for their oversight.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Reiff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Determines the Price of Bitcoin?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=121725</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-determines-the-price-of-bitcoin-2"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T10:38:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Considered by some to be a currency without a state, the price of Bitcoin (BTC) has rapidly ascended and descended. What determines the current Bitcoin price?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kade Garrett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Drop After SEC Delays ETF Decision]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154565</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154565/bitcoin-ethereum-drop-sec-delays-etf-decision"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T09:31:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin puked gains from earlier this week after Grayscale's legal victory, as the SEC again punted on several spot Bitcoin ETF applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Otherside: Legends of the Mara Open Beta Launching in September]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154526</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154526/otherside-legends-mara-open-beta-launching-september"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T00:03:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bored Ape Yacht Club creator's Otherside: Legends of the Mara game experience is about to open up, letting players evolve egg-like NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[YouTuber Loses $60K Worth of Crypto After Showing Seed Phrases on Stream]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154522</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154522/youtuber-loses-60k-worth-crypto-after-showing-seed-phrase-stream"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T23:42:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Brazilian YouTuber went on an emotional rollercoaster this week—but there's a mostly happy ending to his tale.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vivek Ramaswamy Is Changing Presidential Campaign Discourse on Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154504</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154504/vivek-ramaswamy-changing-presidential-campaign-discourse-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T22:23:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By casting the SEC as a villainous deep state entity situated above politics, presidential candidate Vivek Ramaswamy is reshaping the calculus on what has often been a partisan issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google's Generative AI Tools Now Turn Text Into Online Worlds]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154510</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154510/google-generative-ai-tools-turn-text-online-worlds"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T20:54:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hiber3D has integrated Google's AI tools to give creators the ability to type what they want to see—and generate an immersive world.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No Internet? You Could Still Use Bitcoin on the Lightning Network]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154499</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154499/no-internet-you-could-still-use-bitcoin-on-the-lightning-network"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T20:05:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers found a way to use a local "mesh network" to connect nodes via Bluetooth and WiFi, building a local Lightning Network they call LNMesh.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alyssa Hertig</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Punts on Bitcoin ETFs, Including BlackRock, Fidelity and More]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154505</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154505/sec-bitcoin-etfs-more-delays"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T19:50:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wisdom Tree, Fidelity, and BlackRock Bitcoin ETF applications have all been delayed until October at the earliest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott,André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale Bitcoin Trust Investors Who Bought December Dip Are Up 137%]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154494</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154494/grayscale-bitcoin-trust-investors-who-bought-december-dip-are-up-137"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T19:24:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GBTC’s shrinking discount relative to its Bitcoin holdings was nearly 50% last December. Traders who bought the dip are sitting on big gains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adidas Creates Residency for NFT Artists With Plans for Physical Collabs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154469</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154469/adidas-creates-residency-nft-artists-plans-physical-collabs"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T18:29:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sportswear and lifestyle giant Adidas is partnering with artists on NFT drops and other products, kicking off during Korea Blockchain Week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephanie Hirschmiller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Argent, Starknet Foundation Tag 'Several Millions' for New Startup Studio]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154450</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154450/argent-starknet-foundation-tag-several-millions-new-startup-studio"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T17:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With infrastructure and UX solved, Argent and the Starknet Foundation are teaming up again to fund builders looking to launch on Starknet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Earn Bitcoin by Playing Mobile Bubble Shooters—Here's How Much]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154449</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154449/earn-bitcoin-playing-mobile-bubble-shooters-heres-how-much"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T16:58:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How much Bitcoin can you really earn from these iOS and Android games? After a few hours of Bitcoin Pop and Bitcoin Bay: Not much.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Worldcoin? Sam Altman's Eye-Scanning Global ID 'Orb' Project Hits Regulatory Roadblocks]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150832</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-worldcoin-the-app-and-token-that-protects-your-personhood"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T13:44:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin has introduced a concept called “proof of personhood" to keep AI bots out of its global financial network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Reiff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PancakeSwap Expands to Coinbase-Incubated Base Network]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154426</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154426/pancakeswap-expands-coinbase-incubated-base-network"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T13:01:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PancakeSwap joins DeFi heavyweights like Uniswap, SushiSwap, and 1inch launching on the buzzy layer-2 network Base.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nexo Rolls Out 'Dual Mode' for its Flagship Crypto Card]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154428</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154428/nexo-rolls-out-dual-mode-flagship-crypto-card"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nexo's new functionality is now available to Europeans, enabling users to instantly toggle between debit and credit modes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chainlink, Swift Complete Tokenization Tests With Citi Bank, BNY Mellon, and Others]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154434</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154434/chainlink-swift-complete-tokenization-tests-with-citi-bank-bny-mellon-others"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T12:19:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Swift, Chainlink, and 10 banks teamed up to test the ability to move financial assets across traditional rails and blockchain networks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance to Phase Out BUSD Support, ‘Encourages’ Users To Convert Into Other Stablecoins]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154427</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154427/binance-to-phase-out-busd-support-encourages-users-to-convert-into-other-stablecoins"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T12:06:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto exchange will gradually end support for its native stablecoin, after Paxos halted the minting of new BUSD.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Judge Mulls Delaying Bankman-Fried's Court Date Amidst Defense Pleas]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154425</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154425/judge-mulls-delaying-bankman-fried-court-date-amidst-defense-pleas"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T11:17:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The defense for the disgraced crypto founder Sam Bankman-Fried has until September 7 to appeal for a trial postponement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi Deposits on Base Soar as Yield Farmers Plant Aerodrome Harvest]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154421</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154421/base-defi-deposits-soar-yield-farmers-plant-aerodrome-harvest"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T10:50:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi deposits on the Base network hit a new all-time high thanks to liquidity mining incentives from the decentralized exchange Aerodrome.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are Staking and Lending? The Crypto Investment That Can Earn Interest]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=55615</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/how-to-invest-in-cryptocurrencies-staking-and-lending"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T09:13:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this guide we explain how staking and lending works in cryptocurrencies, their benefits, but also their potential downsides.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Hussey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood Wallet Expands Crypto Offering to Add Bitcoin, Dogecoin, and Ethereum Swaps]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154418</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154418/robinhood-wallet-expands-crypto-offering-add-bitcoin-dogecoin-ethereum-swaps"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T09:08:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood's self-custodial crypto wallet now lets users dive deep into the world of decentralized finance via Ethereum swaps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastering NFT Trading - Degen U]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/HQGt1Vrq/mastering-nft-trading-degen-u</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/HQGt1Vrq/mastering-nft-trading-degen-u"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T07:08:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Take Degen U's new course, Mastering NFT Trading, and earn an on-chain certificate. A top instructor will help you identify trends, seize the right moment to trade, weed out scams—and have fun while doing it!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Space Nation CEO on Working With 'Independence Day' Director Roland Emmerich]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LpznLhtx/space-nation-ceo-on-working-with-independence-day-director-roland-emmerich</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LpznLhtx/space-nation-ceo-on-working-with-independence-day-director-roland-emmerich"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T17:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jerome Wu, CEO of Space Nation, tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the upcoming Space Nation Online game in development and shares details on Space Nation Cofounder Roland Emmerich's role in the project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GAME REVIEW: Champions Arena from Gala Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qUE1RlDx/game-review-champions-arena-from-gala-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qUE1RlDx/game-review-champions-arena-from-gala-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Champions Arena is a turn-based fantasy RPG from Gala Games, where characters can become NFTs and crypto can be used to purchase gems, one of the game's synthetic currencies. Decrypt's Kate Irwin takes us inside the game for her thoughts on the fun, mobile-first title.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apex Legends Voice Actor Ben Prendergast on the Future of Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/X3RKdsaG/apex-legends-voice-actor-ben-prendergast-on-the-future-of-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/X3RKdsaG/apex-legends-voice-actor-ben-prendergast-on-the-future-of-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T18:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Voice actor Ben Prendergast, who's voiced characters in games like Apex Legends and God of War Ragnarok, shares his opinions on the tech space's history of "bubbles" and whether blockchain gaming has a future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The future of AI Stardom and Robotics with SingularityNET COO Janet Adams and Desdemona]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yVQaZI71/the-future-of-ai-stardom-and-robotics-with-singularitynet-coo-janet-adams-and-desdemona</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yVQaZI71/the-future-of-ai-stardom-and-robotics-with-singularitynet-coo-janet-adams-and-desdemona"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T16:45:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this interview, SingularityNET COO Janet Adams explains the intricate details that went into creating the Desdemona robot AI from Hanson Robotics and future plans for the AI Diva.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto a 'No-Brainer' for Video Games, Says Mino Games CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rdynom8C/crypto-a-no-brainer-for-video-games-says-mino-games-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rdynom8C/crypto-a-no-brainer-for-video-games-says-mino-games-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T18:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mino Games CEO Sasha MacKinnon, developer of the upcoming Dimensionals game, tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the studio's approach to digital collectibles.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Wagner's 'Controversial Take' on Crypto in Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tc2nKeqA/michael-wagners-controversial-take-on-crypto-in-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tc2nKeqA/michael-wagners-controversial-take-on-crypto-in-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T16:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Solana's PlayGG, Star Atlas CEO Michael Wagner shares his "controversial take" on crypto in games, shares the challenges of developing the upcoming scifi game, and how crypto's volatility has changed his perspective with Decrypt's Jason Nelson.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interview: Angelic CEO on Building the Sci-Fi RPG on Solana and Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/uCzW3K7P/interview-angelic-ceo-on-building-the-sci-fi-rpg-on-solana-and-ethereum</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/uCzW3K7P/interview-angelic-ceo-on-building-the-sci-fi-rpg-on-solana-and-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T15:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Angelic is a sci-fi roleplay game in development that will be free-to-play and offer optional, opt-in crypto features on Solana and Ethereum and a governance token. Metaverse Game Studios CEO and Founder Erkan Bayol tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how he sees AAA traditional games as Angelic's main competitors and shares his vision for the game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apex Legends Voice Actor on AI's Impact on Video Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IOIrmb0N/apex-legends-voice-actor-on-ais-impact-on-video-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IOIrmb0N/apex-legends-voice-actor-on-ais-impact-on-video-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T17:28:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ben Prendergast is an actor who has voiced characters like Apex Legends' Fuse, God of War Ragnarok's Tyr, and Patroclus in Hades. But as debates swirl around the use of artificial intelligence in entertainment in light of the SAG-AFTRA and WGA strikes, Prendergast gives Decrypt's Kate Irwin his honest take on the potential use of AI actors in games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Star Atlas CEO on Developing an MMO Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/WQCaahmH/star-atlas-ceo-on-developing-an-mmo-game</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/WQCaahmH/star-atlas-ceo-on-developing-an-mmo-game"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T13:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Jason Nelson speaks with Star Atlas Founder and CEO Michael Wagner about the MMO game's approach to development, marketing, and blockchain integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aurory's Origin Story: How JRPGs Inspired the Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/O0S201TB/aurorys-origin-story-how-jrpgs-inspired-the-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/O0S201TB/aurorys-origin-story-how-jrpgs-inspired-the-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T16:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Jason Nelson talks to Aurory's Head of Marketing and Business Development Michael Natoli about the origins of the Aurory crypto games at the Solana PlayGG event.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Parallel TCG: Inside the Sci-Fi Card Game’s Closed Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/q8YVWJh4/parallel-tcg-inside-the-sci-fi-card-games-closed-beta</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/q8YVWJh4/parallel-tcg-inside-the-sci-fi-card-games-closed-beta"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T15:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin goes hands-on with Parallel’s closed beta on Windows PC to find out what sets it apart from other crypto card-battlers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 Games Need to Compete with All Games, Says Solana Foundation GM]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ud9wTd4s/web3-games-need-to-compete-with-all-games-says-solana-foundation-gm</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ud9wTd4s/web3-games-need-to-compete-with-all-games-says-solana-foundation-gm"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T19:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Foundation's General Manager of Games Johnny Lee tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about Solana's PlayGG conference and shares his take on crypto gaming and the "play-to-earn" concept.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Many Early Blockchain Games Were 'Cash Grabs,' Says Twitch Streamer Alliestrasza]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BA4yE45A/many-early-blockchain-games-were-cash-grabs-says-twitch-streamer-alliestrasza</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BA4yE45A/many-early-blockchain-games-were-cash-grabs-says-twitch-streamer-alliestrasza"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T16:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["I wrote them off," Twitch streamer Alliestrasza said of her initial thoughts on many early blockchain games. She tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how her perspective on Web3 games has evolved over time and now sees blockchain games getting significantly better.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['MetalCore' Game Preview: Hands-on With the 'Titanfall' Meets 'Destiny' NFT Mashup]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/tjK6i7lv/metalcore-game-preview-hands-on-with-the-titanfall-meets-destiny-nft-mashup</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/tjK6i7lv/metalcore-game-preview-hands-on-with-the-titanfall-meets-destiny-nft-mashup"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T19:46:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MetalCore is an upcoming mech shooter developed by Studio 369, and it's being developed on Ethereum scaling network Immutable zkEVM. Decrypt contributor Ryan Gladwin played through the prologue and tested out the recent Alpha 3 online experience to get a sense of the NFT-infused mashup of Titanfall and Destiny.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>