<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-09-02T03:13:58.888Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-09-02T03:13:58.888Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A US Bank Says Sensitive Customer Data Has Been Compromised in Global Cybersecurity Breach]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18875332/A-US-Bank-Says-Sensitive-Customer-Data-Has-Been-Compromised-in-Global-Cybersecurity-Breach</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18875332/A-US-Bank-Says-Sensitive-Customer-Data-Has-Been-Compromised-in-Global-Cybersecurity-Breach"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T03:08:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A New York-based bank says a global cybersecurity incident has exposed sensitive customer data. In a letter to customers, M&T Bank says the exploit involves the file transfer tool MOVEit, which is used to securely send and receive confidential information. According to the bank, the attacker was...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Economist Peter Schiff Warns Bidenomics Will Soon Be Exposed for Fraud]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75493d71ae</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/economist-peter-schiff-warns-bidenomics-will-soon-be-exposed-for-fraud/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T02:35:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Economist Peter Schiff has warned that Bidenomics “will soon be exposed for the fraud that it is, as inflation and unemployment heat up while the economy cools down.” He cautioned: “If Americans think the economy is bad now, just wait until they see what’s coming. Once the dollar cracks, both inflation and interest rates will rise sharply. This will send the economy deeper into recession, causing many people to lose their jobs. That’s the real Bidenomics.” 
 
Peter Schiff Calls Bidenomics Fraud
 
Gold bug and economist Peter Schiff slammed President Joe Biden’s economic policy, known as Bidenomics, in a series of posts on social media platform X this week.
 
“If Americans think the economy is bad now, just wait until they see what’s coming. Once the dollar cracks, both inflation and intere…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PEPE tops weekly search charts: Is a potential pivot on the horizon?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18875318/PEPE-tops-weekly-search-charts-Is-a-potential-pivot-on-the-horizon</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18875318/PEPE-tops-weekly-search-charts-Is-a-potential-pivot-on-the-horizon"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T02:30:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The supply of PEPE held by top addresses has been growing since mid-August. This could be an indication that PEPE is still centralized and will drop to fresh lows if whales decided to dump the memecoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How does FDUSD measure against BUSD? A market analysis]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18875290/How-does-FDUSD-measure-against-BUSD-A-market-analysis</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18875290/How-does-FDUSD-measure-against-BUSD-A-market-analysis"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T01:30:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance's BUSD journey nears its end while FDUSD takes flight. Can this new stablecoin soar to rival giants USDT and USDC? The crypto battle begins.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Yuan Not Ready to Topple US Dollar as World Reserve Currency, Says Strategist]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75493b22a0</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/chinese-yuan-not-ready-to-topple-us-dollar-as-world-reserve-currency-says-strategist/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T01:01:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A global macro strategist has explained that the Chinese yuan is unlikely to replace the U.S. dollar as the global reserve currency. She emphasized that the “weaponization” of the USD is one of the top reasons why Russia, China, and other BRICS nations have been seeking an alternative to the dollar.
 
US Dollar v Chinese Yuan
 
Skylar Montgomery, senior global macro strategist at Globaldata TS Lombard, an independent investment research group focusing on global macro and strategy, explained in a note on Wednesday that the Chinese yuan is unlikely to replace the U.S. dollar as the world’s reserve currency.
 
She detailed that the U.S. dollar’s global reserve currency status “is a privilege that gives the U.S. significant political, economic, and market influence.” However, she cautioned tha…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA) Breaks Bearish Trend, But Not in Expected Way]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18875282/Cardano-ADA-Breaks-Bearish-Trend-But-Not-in-Expected-Way</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18875282/Cardano-ADA-Breaks-Bearish-Trend-But-Not-in-Expected-Way"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T01:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ADA showing some resilience on market following break of destructive trend]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former SEC Chair Guarantees Bitcoin Spot ETFs: Inevitable Approval]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754924a6e3</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/former-sec-chair-bitcoin-spot-etfs-inevitable/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T00:36:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Chair, Jay Clayton, has weighed in on the ongoing applications for Bitcoin (BTC) spot Exchange-Traded Funds (ETFs) by various asset managers, including BlackRock, WisdomTree, and Ark Invest. 
 
Despite the SEC’s cautious approach and the applications facing repeated delays, Clayton is confident that the approval of a Bitcoin ETF is inevitable. 
 
In a recent interview with CNBC, Clayton emphasized the demand from retail investors and the willingness of trusted providers to offer this investment product to the public.
 
‘BTC Clearly Not A Security’
 
Several major asset managers have submitted applications for Bitcoin spot ETFs, seeking approval from the SEC. However, the regulatory body has yet to greenlight any of these proposals, resulti…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anti-Crypto Senator Seeks Financial Aid, Faces Backlash from Coinbase CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18875258/Anti-Crypto-Senator-Seeks-Financial-Aid-Faces-Backlash-from-Coinbase-CEO</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18875258/Anti-Crypto-Senator-Seeks-Financial-Aid-Faces-Backlash-from-Coinbase-CEO"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T00:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rerunning U.S. Senator Jon Tester, co-sponsor of anti-crypto legislation, faces financial trouble. The senator faces backlash from the crypto community after seeking financial aid on social media. Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong questions Tester’s stance on crypto. U.S. Senator Jon Tester, known...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Punts ETF Applications Till October]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18875259/SEC-Punts-ETF-Applications-Till-October</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18875259/SEC-Punts-ETF-Applications-Till-October"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T00:12:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NLW catches up on the late week news including the SEC punting 7 ETF applications, the JOLTS and nonfarm payroll reports, and revised GDP estimates. Enjoying this content?SUBSCRIBE to the Podcast: https://pod.link/1438693620Watch on YouTube:...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JPMorgan Chase Rejects Customer’s Plea for Reimbursement After Criminal With Chase Bank Account Steals $24,000]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18875256/JPMorgan-Chase-Rejects-Customers-Plea-for-Reimbursement-After-Criminal-With-Chase-Bank-Account-Steals-24000</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18875256/JPMorgan-Chase-Rejects-Customers-Plea-for-Reimbursement-After-Criminal-With-Chase-Bank-Account-Steals-24000"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T00:04:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JPMorgan Chase says a customer who lost $24,000 in a sophisticated scam is out of luck – even though the funds were sent directly to a Chase bank account used by the scammer. New Jersey resident Todd Kirby says he received a text message on June 6th that appeared to be from Chase, asking if […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top US Crypto Exchange Coinbase Officially Rolls Out Trading Support for New PayPal Stablecoin PYUSD]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18875241/Top-US-Crypto-Exchange-Coinbase-Officially-Rolls-Out-Trading-Support-for-New-PayPal-Stablecoin-PYUSD</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18875241/Top-US-Crypto-Exchange-Coinbase-Officially-Rolls-Out-Trading-Support-for-New-PayPal-Stablecoin-PYUSD"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T00:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase customers can now buy and sell PayPal’s new US dollar-pegged stablecoin on the exchange’s website and mobile apps. The top US crypto exchange officially rolled out trading support on Thursday for PayPal USD (PYUSD), which aims to maintain a 1:1 peg with the US dollar. Coinbase first...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former SEC Chair Guarantees Bitcoin Spot ETFs: Inevitable Approval]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18875228/Former-SEC-Chair-Guarantees-Bitcoin-Spot-ETFs-Inevitable-Approval</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18875228/Former-SEC-Chair-Guarantees-Bitcoin-Spot-ETFs-Inevitable-Approval"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Chair, Jay Clayton, has weighed in on the ongoing applications for Bitcoin (BTC) spot Exchange-Traded Funds (ETFs) by various asset managers, including BlackRock, WisdomTree, and Ark Invest. Despite the SEC’s cautious approach and the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don't Buy Polygon MATIC Until You Watch This | BIG OPPORTUNITY OR...]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18875226/Dont-Buy-Polygon-MATIC-Until-You-Watch-This-BIG-OPPORTUNITY-OR</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18875226/Dont-Buy-Polygon-MATIC-Until-You-Watch-This-BIG-OPPORTUNITY-OR"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T23:52:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon's token MATIC is being upgraded to POL. We discuss all the implications of this major change to one of the crypto space's best altcoins.Manage Your Crypto Portfolio with Regular Updates and Top Insights for only $15/ month.Sign up for Altcoin Buzz Alpha:Youtube:...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[URGENT!! CHINA LEGALIZES BITCOIN AND CRYPTO!! (Biggest Bull Market of ALL TIME Beginning)]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18875224/URGENT-CHINA-LEGALIZES-BITCOIN-AND-CRYPTO-Biggest-Bull-Market-of-ALL-TIME-Beginning</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18875224/URGENT-CHINA-LEGALIZES-BITCOIN-AND-CRYPTO-Biggest-Bull-Market-of-ALL-TIME-Beginning"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T23:39:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[🔥 Activate NordVPN FOR JUST $3 PER MONTH and get access to Threat Protection: https://nordvpn.com/ellio#nft #ethereum #defi #blockchain #crypto #cryptocurrency #bitcoin #btc #eth #news #protocols #sidechain #altcoin #nftmarketplace #opensea #cryptoart #protocol #altcoins #nonfungibletoken #dao...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What X’s (Twitter) Daring Expansion Could Mean For Dogecoin]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7549209b37</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/x-twitter-dogecoin/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T23:35:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk’s X (formerly Twitter) has been going through an interesting phase since the billionaire took over and crypto enthusiasts can’t help but hope that Dogecoin is in the grand plan of things. This is because the social media platform has undergone some daring changes so far, so speculations that Dogecoin could fit into all of this abound.
 
X Steps Up Its Game With Audio/Video Call Addition
 
Since its founding in 2006 by Jack Dorsey and three others, the Twitter (as it was known before) platform stuck very close to its original mission of being a micro-blogging site. This meant that the social media giant was not looking toward shiny bells and whistles like audio and video calling features. That is until Elon Musk made good on his promise and bought the site for $44 billion in Octob…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Best Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arkham Intelligence Reveals Grayscale’s Ethereum Holdings Across 500 Addresses]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754920e5ac</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/arkham-intelligence-reveals-grayscales-ethereum-holdings-across-500-addresses/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T23:31:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On September 1, Arkham Intelligence, a crypto analytics and data tracking agency, reportedly pinpointed the ethereum (ETH) holdings of Grayscale for its Ethereum Trust. Arkham reveals that Grayscale’s ether stash is spread across 500 distinct addresses.
 
Grayscale’s Ethereum Holdings Mapped by Arkham
 
According to Arkham, the firm has identified the ethereum owned by Grayscale for the Ethereum Trust fund. The fund’s shares are based on a fraction of ether, and each share represents 0.00963214 ETH on September 1, according to Grayscale’s web portal. Grayscale’s Ethereum Trust was initially introduced in December 2017, and Arkham believes the company is now the second-largest holder of ETH.
 
“Arkham has identified the Grayscale Ethereum Trust onchain,” the firm posted to the social media …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What X’s (Twitter) Daring Expansion Could Mean For Dogecoin]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18875186/What-Xs-Twitter-Daring-Expansion-Could-Mean-For-Dogecoin</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18875186/What-Xs-Twitter-Daring-Expansion-Could-Mean-For-Dogecoin"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T23:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk’s X (formerly Twitter) has been going through an interesting phase since the billionaire took over and crypto enthusiasts can’t help but hope that Dogecoin is in the grand plan of things. This is because the social media platform has undergone some daring changes so far, so...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoin Surge: Over $11 Trillion in Payments Rival Visa’s Dominance]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18875180/Stablecoin-Surge-Over-11-Trillion-in-Payments-Rival-Visas-Dominance</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18875180/Stablecoin-Surge-Over-11-Trillion-in-Payments-Rival-Visas-Dominance"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T22:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The stablecoin market is growing fast as adoption in the crypto market increases overall, according to a report by hedge fund manager Brevan Howard Digital.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood Billion-Dollar Reversal: $600 Million Deal Sees Bankman-Fried Stake Return Home]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75492cf4e8</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/robinhood-600-million-bankman-fried-stake-return/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T22:35:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood, the popular online brokerage platform, has successfully executed a significant share repurchase agreement, acquiring $605 million worth of shares from Emergent Fidelity Technologies, owned by Sam Bankman-Fried, former CEO of the bankrupt crypto exchange FTX. 
 
The company filed an 8-K form with the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to officially announce the agreement, which had been previously disclosed earlier this year. 
 
Robinhood CFO Anticipates Dynamic Growth Ahead
 
Robinhood’s Board of Directors authorized the pursuit of repurchasing the remaining 55 million shares that Emergent Fidelity Technologies had acquired in May 2022. 
 
 
This share repurchase initiative underscored the board’s belief in the company’s future success and the value it could deliver to …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Co-Founder Says FTX's SOL Should Be Distributed to Customers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154663</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154663/solana-cofounder-says-ftx-sol-should-distributed-customers"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T22:32:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FTX’s new management is starting to move its holdings around. Amid fears of an impending dump, a Solana co-founder has an idea.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitter To Collect Biometric Data From Users; Will This Policy Affect DOGE?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18875149/Twitter-To-Collect-Biometric-Data-From-Users-Will-This-Policy-Affect-DOGE</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18875149/Twitter-To-Collect-Biometric-Data-From-Users-Will-This-Policy-Affect-DOGE"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T22:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twitter (X) is now planning to collect biometric data, such as photo IDs, from its user base. This new development would only apply to premium users and is set to come into effect from 29 September. Meanwhile, DOGE is priced at $0.06395 registering a surge of 2.63% over the past week. According...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin Claims Signups Soar in Argentina: 9.5K Users Verified in a Single Day]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75492f02fa</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/worldcoin-claims-signups-soar-in-argentina-9-5k-users-verified-in-a-single-day/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T22:09:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The number of verifications for Worldcoin, the biometric digital ID and wallet project, has soared recently in Argentina, reaching a daily signup record in August. According to data provided by the project, Worldcoin verified 9,500 Argentine users in a single day, with only four verification stations in the country.
Wordcoin Popularity Peaks in Argentina; Project Reaches 9.5K Verifications in a Day
Worldcoin, the biometric ID and digital wallet project, has recently experienced a surge in popularity in Argentina. According to data provided by the project, Argentina reached a record for signups during August, registering more than 9,500 verifications in a single day.
Worldcoin project co-founder and CEO of Tools for Humanity Alex Blania attributed this high demand to the interest Argentine …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Whales Move Over $730,000,000 in Bitcoin, Ethereum and XRP – Here’s Where the Crypto’s Headed]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18875134/Whales-Move-Over-730000000-in-Bitcoin-Ethereum-and-XRP-Heres-Where-the-Cryptos-Headed</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18875134/Whales-Move-Over-730000000-in-Bitcoin-Ethereum-and-XRP-Heres-Where-the-Cryptos-Headed"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T22:01:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deep-pocketed crypto investors are moving hundreds of millions of dollars worth of digital assets into and from centralized crypto exchange platforms as the king crypto falls below $26,000. New data from whale-surveying platform Whale Alert reveals that high-net-worth traders have abruptly...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock Bitcoin ETF Delayed?! | What’s Next?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18875133/BlackRock-Bitcoin-ETF-Delayed-Whats-Next</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18875133/BlackRock-Bitcoin-ETF-Delayed-Whats-Next"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T21:55:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We dive deep into the much-anticipated approval of the Spot Bitcoin ETFs! Hear from Jay Clayton, former SEC chair, on Bitcoin's classification and what's stalling the official nod. Discover why BlackRock's iShares Bitcoin Trust is making headlines and the significance of the October 17th...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple legal team opposes SEC appeal over XRP decision]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18875116/Ripple-legal-team-opposes-SEC-appeal-over-XRP-decision</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18875116/Ripple-legal-team-opposes-SEC-appeal-over-XRP-decision"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T21:53:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lawyers argued the SEC’s grounds for an appeal was based on “dissatisfaction” with a July court decision that the XRP token did not largely qualify as a security.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The story of a crypto influencer’s attempt to bend reality]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18875115/The-story-of-a-crypto-influencers-attempt-to-bend-reality</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18875115/The-story-of-a-crypto-influencers-attempt-to-bend-reality"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T21:50:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A bizarre tale about Carl ‘The Moon” Runefelt asking Cointelegraph to revise history on his behalf by concealing old claims that he co-founded a crypto app.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto’s Newest Threat: Android Devices At Risk As US And UK Intel Agencies Raise Alarm]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754929d7f7</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-newest-threat-android-devices-at-risk-us-uk/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T21:35:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto space, long viewed as particularly vulnerable to cyber criminals due to its nascent stage, faces fresh malware threats. A recent joint report from top intelligence agencies in the United States and the United Kingdom underscores this ongoing cyber tug-of-war.
 
The joint advisory, which encompasses a significant international collaboration, alarms the emergence of a newly identified malware, “Infamous Chisel,” that threatens Android device users in the crypto user base.
 
 
Unmasking The ‘Infamous Chisel’
 
Piercing deeper into the report’s findings, the roots of this malware can be traced back to the clandestine activities of Sandworm. This cyber warfare unit, believed to function under the aegis of the GRU – Russia’s military intelligence agency- has previously gained notoriet…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Just One Dose of Magic Mushroom Psychedelic Can Ease Depression for Weeks, Study Finds]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154664</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154664/depression-treatment-psychedelic-psilocybin-mushrooms"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T21:35:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Psilocybin is having a magical effect on major depression disorders, but more study is needed, new research suggests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Just One Dose of Magic Mushroom Psychedelic Can Ease Depression for Weeks, Study Finds]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18875110/Just-One-Dose-of-Magic-Mushroom-Psychedelic-Can-Ease-Depression-for-Weeks-Study-Finds</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18875110/Just-One-Dose-of-Magic-Mushroom-Psychedelic-Can-Ease-Depression-for-Weeks-Study-Finds"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T21:35:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Psilocybin is having a magical effect on major depression disorders, but more study is needed, new research suggests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Digital rupee gets big usability boost through Yes Bank integration with UPI]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18875092/Digital-rupee-gets-big-usability-boost-through-Yes-Bank-integration-with-UPI</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18875092/Digital-rupee-gets-big-usability-boost-through-Yes-Bank-integration-with-UPI"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T21:30:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Yes Bank app’s UPI integration is the first for the Indian retail CBDC, which has seen a variety of projects since its pilot launch in December.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Hasn't Met Requirements to Argue for an Appeal, Ripple Says]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754914a6e0</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/09/01/sec-hasnt-met-requirements-to-argue-for-an-appeal-ripple-says/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T21:03:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple made its case to a federal judge for why the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission shouldn't be able to appeal her ruling on its programmatic sales of XRP on Friday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Thefts in 2023: Nearly $1 Billion Lost to Scams and Exploits, Reports Certik]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754916f551</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/crypto-thefts-in-2023-nearly-1-billion-lost-to-scams-and-exploits-reports-certik/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T20:36:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to cybersecurity firm Certik, nearly $1 billion in cryptocurrency has been pilfered due to scams, rug pulls, and exploits throughout 2023. The company highlighted that the combined incidents in August alone led to a loss of $45.8 million.
 
Certik Analysis: Cryptocurrency Losses Near $1 Billion
 
The digital security and smart contract auditing firm Certik disclosed that $45.8 million was purloined last month from various exploits, hacks, and deceptions. The PEPE token exit scam took the lead in August with a staggering $13.2 million, followed closely by the Exactly Protocol incident at $7.3 million.
 

 
Certik pointed out that exit scams led to $26 million in losses, flash loans were responsible for $6.4 million, and general exploits amounted to $13.5 million in August. Additionally, Certik’s analysis states that almost $1 billion, or approximately $997,345,346 was misappropriated in 2023 via scams, exploits, rug pulls, and flash loans. July emerged as the year’s leader thus far in terms of the amount pilfered through exploits during 2023.
 
Exit scams’ peak month was May, but August came dangerously close with the recent PEPE incident. Regarding flash loan attacks, there’s been a modest number all year; however, a significant spike occurred in March when more than $200 million was snatched that month through flash loan attacks. In total, flash loan attacks accounted for $261 million this year.
 
Exploits reached a total of $596 million in 2023, with $137 million linked to exit scams as per Certik’s findings. Although PEPE was August’s most colossal exit scam, the Zunami Protocol attack emerged as the largest flash loan issue during that month. Meanwhile, the Exactly Protocol incident turned out to be August’s most significant exploit.
 
What do you think about Certik’s report on the crypto scam, hack, and exploit incidents in 2023? Share your thoughts and opinions about this subject in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What The New Ethereum Stakers Self-Limit Rule Means For The Network]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75491712af</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-stakers-self-limit/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T20:35:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an effort to maintain decentralization and promote responsible and sustainable blockchain growth, a group of large Ethereum stakers have voluntarily agreed to devote themselves to a self-limit rule that would restrict the scope of their staking activities on the network to a certain threshold.
 
Ethereum Stakers Commit to 22% Self-Limit Rule
 
Ethereum Beacon Chain community health consultant, Superphiz.eth announced in an X (formerly Twitter) post on Thursday, August 31, that four major Ethereum staking providers have dedicated or are working on dedicating themselves to a self-limit rule. This self-limit rule would see the staking provider’s staking limit reduced to less than 22%. 
 
 
Among the staking service providers that have agreed to the self-limit rule are Rocket Pool, Stader L…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Large Bitcoin Holders Accumulate $1.5B Worth of BTC as Price Wavers]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7549174d7a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/09/01/large-bitcoin-holders-accumulate-15b-worth-of-btc-as-price-wavers/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T20:33:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The accumulation by BTC whales suggests optimism among large investors, IntoTheBlock’s head of research noted.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cambridge Revises Bitcoin Mining Index, Lowers BTC’s Estimated Power Use]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75491fb7cd</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/cambridge-revises-bitcoin-mining-index-lowers-btcs-estimated-power-use/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T19:04:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cambridge Centre for Alternative Finance has significantly revised its Bitcoin Electricity Consumption Index, lowering its estimates of the cryptocurrency’s energy use after finding its previous model greatly overstated power consumption.
 
Cambridge Centre Revises Bitcoin Energy Estimates Downward: Corrected Index Reflects More Accurate Power Consumption
 

 
In a report published this week, the research center said its prior methodology, in place since 2019, worked well during periods of low mining profitability but exhibited “shortcomings” when profits surged, particularly in 2021. The previous index equally weighted all profitable mining machines in use, which led to an overrepresentation of older, less efficient models when mining was highly lucrative.
 

 
“Evidence suggests this bot…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bitcoin Maximalist’s Ode To Ordinals]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754918d668</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/a-bitcoin-maximalists-ode-to-ordinals"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T18:53:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is an opinion editorial by L. Asher Corson, a partner at UTXO Management.
As a Bitcoin Maximalist, I love Ordinals. Other Maximalists should also consider loving Ordinals, as they demonstrate Bitcoin's superiority in ways not previously possible. Ordinals enable functionalities that undermine the need for other blockchains to even exist. The use cases that were demonstrated on other blockchains are now possible natively on Bitcoin. Despite Bitcoin’s strengthening position, some self-proclaimed Maximalists on X (formerly Twitter) bizarrely celebrated decreased network fees and declared Ordinals to have failed. This seemingly implies that Bitcoin might somehow benefit from a failure of the Ordinals protocol and lower miner earnings. But Ordinals haven’t failed and the interest isn’t nea…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>L. Asher Corson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood Buys Back Sam Bankman-Fried’s Seized Shares Worth $600 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154656</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154656/robinhood-buys-back-sam-bankman-fried-seized-shares"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T18:42:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood shares jumped 3% following news of the buy back.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chainlink Exchange Supply Plummets, Is This Bullish?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75491ac998</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/chainlink-exchange-supply-plummets-is-this-bullish/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T18:34:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data shows the Chainlink exchange supply has observed a plummet, something that could turn out to be bullish for the asset’s price.
 
Chainlink Supply On Exchanges Has Registered A Drawdown Recently
 
According to data from the on-chain analytics firm Santiment, the LINK supply on exchanges could be forming a bullish divergence right now. The “supply on exchanges” here refers to the percentage of the total Chainlink circulating supply that’s currently being stored in the wallets of all centralized exchanges.
 
When the value of this metric rises, it means that the investors are depositing a net amount of their coins to these platforms currently. As one of the main reasons why they may transfer their coins to exchanges is for selling-related purposes, this kind of trend can have be…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hououin Kyouma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uniswap Ruling Creates Regulatory 'Anomaly' for DeFi: Legal Scholar]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154651</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154651/uniswap-ruling-creates-regulatory-anomaly-defi-legal-scholar"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T18:19:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A district judge's recent decision in a class action lawsuit against Uniswap demarcates DeFi from centralized exchanges like Coinbase.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Twist in Bankman-Fried Saga: Robinhood Strikes $600M Deal to Reclaim Shares]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7549052023</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/a-twist-in-bankman-fried-saga-robinhood-strikes-600m-deal-to-reclaim-shares/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T18:13:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood has announced a share repurchase agreement  
worth $605.7 million with the US Marshal Service (USMS) to regain control of  
shares previously held by Same Bankman-Fried (SBF)’s Emergent Fidelity  
Technologies. This move comes after a series of legal events that began when  
SBF, just six months before his empire collapsed, disclosed a 7.6% stake in  
Robinhood.
The shares in question  
had been seized and subsequently transferred into the custody of the US  
government after Bankman-Fried's cryptocurrency exchange, FTX, and Emergent  
filed for bankruptcy protection in 2022. Reacting to the latest development,  
Robinhood's shares surged by more than 3% in pre-market trading as news of the  
buyback broke.
Robinhood  
Announces Completion of the Share Buyback       
Jason Warnic…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MakerDAO Should Use Solana’s Code to Build Its New Blockchain, Co-Founder Says]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7549062046</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/09/01/makerdao-should-use-solanas-code-to-build-its-new-blockchain-co-founder-says/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T18:04:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some community members have already pushed back against the idea.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Is XRP Price Down Today?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754901b9fa</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/why-is-xrp-price-down-today/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T17:34:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The XRP price is down today after seeing an encouraging start to the week. This decline has now seen the altcoin wipe out the vast majority of its gains from Ripple’s triumph over the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) back in July. So the question now is, what is driving the XRP price down today?
 
XRP Price Falls To Pre-Victory Levels
 
The XRP price is down 4.08% in the last day, as shown by data from coin tracker CoinMarketCap. This decline makes XRP one of the highest losers in the top 10 over the last day, suggesting that there could be unique drivers behind the price decline.
 
One of the most prominent factors in the decline of XRP though is the general bearish market. For example, the top 10 cryptocurrencies by market cap closely mirror the movement of Bitcoin,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Infamous Chisel’ Malware Targets Crypto Wallets and Exchanges: A Joint Warning by FBI and GCHQ]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754901bcfa</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/infamous-chisel-malware-targets-crypto-wallets-and-exchanges-a-joint-warning-by-fbi-and-gchq/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T17:34:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The “Infamous Chisel,” a new sophisticated malware, has been targeting crypto wallets and exchanges, as revealed in a joint report by the U.S. Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) and the U.K.’s Government Communications Headquarters (GCHQ). 
 
Multi-Agency Alert Over ‘Infamous Chisel’ Malware Threat Targeting Android Crypto Infrastructure
 
The malware, named “Infamous Chisel,” has been designed specifically to target Android devices. Unlike many of its counterparts, this malware is associated with the notorious Sandworm’s activity, a group known for its complex cyber-espionage campaigns. The report notes that the malware can target specific crypto wallets and digital currency exchanges.
 
One of the alarming features of the “Infamous Chisel” is its ability to perform periodic scans of b…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Two Most Popular Stable Diffusion UIs Just Got Major Upgrades]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154618</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154618/the-two-most-popular-stable-diffusion-uis-just-got-major-upgrades"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T17:20:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With new features in Automatic 1111 and InvokeAI's latest versions, the Stable Diffusion platforms are easier and more powerful.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NYC Seaport Scavenger Hunt Brings NFTs Into the Real World]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=153493</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/153493/nyc-seaport-scavenger-hunt-brings-nfts-real-world"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T17:19:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manhattan's Seaport neighborhood is hosting a scavenger hunt driven by NFTs and QR codes, but it wasn't all smooth sailing at first.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Incredible Shrinking Market Share of Circle’s USDC Stablecoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154608</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154608/shinking-market-share-circle-usdc-stablecoin"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T17:07:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For most of 2022, USDC was close to catching its rival Tether. But that figure has been shrinking—and fast.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Road Ahead: What Bitcoin Traders Can Expect In The ‘Longest’ Crypto Bear Market]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7549098d76</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/what-bitcoin-traders-can-expect-in-bear-market/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T16:33:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) and the entire cryptocurrency market are currently caught in a sideways trading pattern, leaving investors grappling with uncertainty. In a market where prices can swing dramatically in a matter of minutes, such stability can be unsettling for traders. 
 
However, renowned crypto analyst Michaël van de Poppe, known for his insightful predictions, offers a glimmer of hope to those who have been “hodling” through these turbulent times. He anticipates a substantial payoff for patient investors in the next one to two years.
 
Bitcoin Bear Market Blues
 
Van de Poppe points out that the ongoing market conditions constitute the longest bear market in Bitcoin’s relatively short history. But what exactly is a bear market? 
 
 
A bear market is characterized by a prolonged period of d…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tennis Meets Tech as Tiffany, Amex, Wilson Descend Upon US Open]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154542</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154542/tennis-meets-tech-tiffany-amex-wilson-us-open"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T15:49:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Major brands are using the U.S. Open tennis tournament to show off how they're embracing tech like augmented reality, NFTs, and VR.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INTERVIEW: How Will Aurory Use NFTs and Crypto?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qv3VwNmM/interview-how-will-aurory-use-nfts-and-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qv3VwNmM/interview-how-will-aurory-use-nfts-and-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T15:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Natoli, Aurory's Head of Marketing and Business Development, tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how the Aurory games will use NFTs and crypto and shares the studio's broader stance on the tech.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cambridge Updates Bitcoin Mining Index to Reveal True Power Consumption]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154593</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154593/cambridge-updates-bitcoin-mining-index-reveal-true-power-consumption"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T14:58:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Experts say there’s still room for improvement, but that Cambridge’s new model is a big step forward.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Cloud's James Tromans on the Intersection of AI and Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OeD4uoLj/google-clouds-james-tromans-on-the-intersection-of-ai-and-web3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OeD4uoLj/google-clouds-james-tromans-on-the-intersection-of-ai-and-web3"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google's Global Head of Google Cloud for Web3 James Tromans sat down with Decrypt's Jason Nelson to discuss how AI can help Web3 companies come to market faster and the real value of Web3 tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether's Stablecoin USDT 'Has a Peg Stability Problem', Claims Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154580</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154580/tethers-stablecoin-usdt-has-a-peg-stability-problem-claims-analyst"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T12:15:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One possible solution would be for Tether to reconsider its redemption fee and minimum redeemable amount, says a Kaiko analyst.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Trading Volumes Headed for Worst Quarter Since 2019]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154583</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154583/bitcoin-ethereum-trading-volumes-headed-worst-quarter-since-2019"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T12:05:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trading volumes for the largest cryptocurrencies in Bitcoin and Ethereum are on track for their worst quarter in four years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who’s Who in Global Crypto Regulation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=153195</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/whos-who-in-global-crypto-regulation"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T10:50:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is difficult to properly assess cryptocurrencies through the lenses of traditional finance—it is even challenging to determine which agencies may be responsible for their oversight.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Reiff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Determines the Price of Bitcoin?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=121725</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-determines-the-price-of-bitcoin-2"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T10:38:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Considered by some to be a currency without a state, the price of Bitcoin (BTC) has rapidly ascended and descended. What determines the current Bitcoin price?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kade Garrett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Drop After SEC Delays ETF Decision]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154565</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154565/bitcoin-ethereum-drop-sec-delays-etf-decision"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T09:31:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin puked gains from earlier this week after Grayscale's legal victory, as the SEC again punted on several spot Bitcoin ETF applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Otherside: Legends of the Mara Open Beta Launching in September]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154526</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154526/otherside-legends-mara-open-beta-launching-september"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T00:03:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bored Ape Yacht Club creator's Otherside: Legends of the Mara game experience is about to open up, letting players evolve egg-like NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[YouTuber Loses $60K Worth of Crypto After Showing Seed Phrases on Stream]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154522</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154522/youtuber-loses-60k-worth-crypto-after-showing-seed-phrase-stream"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T23:42:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Brazilian YouTuber went on an emotional rollercoaster this week—but there's a mostly happy ending to his tale.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vivek Ramaswamy Is Changing Presidential Campaign Discourse on Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154504</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154504/vivek-ramaswamy-changing-presidential-campaign-discourse-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T22:23:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By casting the SEC as a villainous deep state entity situated above politics, presidential candidate Vivek Ramaswamy is reshaping the calculus on what has often been a partisan issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google's Generative AI Tools Now Turn Text Into Online Worlds]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154510</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154510/google-generative-ai-tools-turn-text-online-worlds"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T20:54:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hiber3D has integrated Google's AI tools to give creators the ability to type what they want to see—and generate an immersive world.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No Internet? You Could Still Use Bitcoin on the Lightning Network]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154499</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154499/no-internet-you-could-still-use-bitcoin-on-the-lightning-network"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T20:05:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers found a way to use a local "mesh network" to connect nodes via Bluetooth and WiFi, building a local Lightning Network they call LNMesh.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alyssa Hertig</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Punts on Bitcoin ETFs, Including BlackRock, Fidelity and More]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154505</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154505/sec-bitcoin-etfs-more-delays"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T19:50:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wisdom Tree, Fidelity, and BlackRock Bitcoin ETF applications have all been delayed until October at the earliest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott,André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale Bitcoin Trust Investors Who Bought December Dip Are Up 137%]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154494</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154494/grayscale-bitcoin-trust-investors-who-bought-december-dip-are-up-137"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T19:24:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GBTC’s shrinking discount relative to its Bitcoin holdings was nearly 50% last December. Traders who bought the dip are sitting on big gains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adidas Creates Residency for NFT Artists With Plans for Physical Collabs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154469</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154469/adidas-creates-residency-nft-artists-plans-physical-collabs"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T18:29:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sportswear and lifestyle giant Adidas is partnering with artists on NFT drops and other products, kicking off during Korea Blockchain Week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephanie Hirschmiller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Argent, Starknet Foundation Tag 'Several Millions' for New Startup Studio]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154450</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154450/argent-starknet-foundation-tag-several-millions-new-startup-studio"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T17:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With infrastructure and UX solved, Argent and the Starknet Foundation are teaming up again to fund builders looking to launch on Starknet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Earn Bitcoin by Playing Mobile Bubble Shooters—Here's How Much]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154449</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154449/earn-bitcoin-playing-mobile-bubble-shooters-heres-how-much"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T16:58:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How much Bitcoin can you really earn from these iOS and Android games? After a few hours of Bitcoin Pop and Bitcoin Bay: Not much.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Worldcoin? Sam Altman's Eye-Scanning Global ID 'Orb' Project Hits Regulatory Roadblocks]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150832</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-worldcoin-the-app-and-token-that-protects-your-personhood"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T13:44:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin has introduced a concept called “proof of personhood" to keep AI bots out of its global financial network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Reiff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PancakeSwap Expands to Coinbase-Incubated Base Network]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154426</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154426/pancakeswap-expands-coinbase-incubated-base-network"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T13:01:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PancakeSwap joins DeFi heavyweights like Uniswap, SushiSwap, and 1inch launching on the buzzy layer-2 network Base.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nexo Rolls Out 'Dual Mode' for its Flagship Crypto Card]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154428</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154428/nexo-rolls-out-dual-mode-flagship-crypto-card"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nexo's new functionality is now available to Europeans, enabling users to instantly toggle between debit and credit modes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chainlink, Swift Complete Tokenization Tests With Citi Bank, BNY Mellon, and Others]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154434</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154434/chainlink-swift-complete-tokenization-tests-with-citi-bank-bny-mellon-others"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T12:19:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Swift, Chainlink, and 10 banks teamed up to test the ability to move financial assets across traditional rails and blockchain networks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance to Phase Out BUSD Support, ‘Encourages’ Users To Convert Into Other Stablecoins]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154427</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154427/binance-to-phase-out-busd-support-encourages-users-to-convert-into-other-stablecoins"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T12:06:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto exchange will gradually end support for its native stablecoin, after Paxos halted the minting of new BUSD.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Judge Mulls Delaying Bankman-Fried's Court Date Amidst Defense Pleas]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154425</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154425/judge-mulls-delaying-bankman-fried-court-date-amidst-defense-pleas"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T11:17:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The defense for the disgraced crypto founder Sam Bankman-Fried has until September 7 to appeal for a trial postponement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi Deposits on Base Soar as Yield Farmers Plant Aerodrome Harvest]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154421</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154421/base-defi-deposits-soar-yield-farmers-plant-aerodrome-harvest"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T10:50:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi deposits on the Base network hit a new all-time high thanks to liquidity mining incentives from the decentralized exchange Aerodrome.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are Staking and Lending? The Crypto Investment That Can Earn Interest]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=55615</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/how-to-invest-in-cryptocurrencies-staking-and-lending"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T09:13:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this guide we explain how staking and lending works in cryptocurrencies, their benefits, but also their potential downsides.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Hussey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood Wallet Expands Crypto Offering to Add Bitcoin, Dogecoin, and Ethereum Swaps]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154418</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154418/robinhood-wallet-expands-crypto-offering-add-bitcoin-dogecoin-ethereum-swaps"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T09:08:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood's self-custodial crypto wallet now lets users dive deep into the world of decentralized finance via Ethereum swaps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Airline Giant Lufthansa Launches NFT Loyalty Program on Polygon]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154390</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154390/lufthansa-airline-travel-nft-polygon-uptrip"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T08:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lufthansa’s Uptrip loyalty program offers special perks for passengers who collect sets of NFT-based trading cards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stroom Raises $3.5M to Bring Liquid Staking to Bitcoin Lightning Network]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154264</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154264/stroom-raises-3-5m-bring-liquid-staking-bitcoin-lightning-network"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T07:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bringing liquid staking to Bitcoin will help solve Lightning Network’s liquidity challenges, argues the team behind the Stroom Network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Can Shrink 'Time to Market' for Web3 Startups: Google Cloud Executive]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154412</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154412/ai-can-shrink-web3-startup-time-to-market-google-cloud"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T01:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s James Tromans is bullish on the role AI can play in accelerating tasks like smart contract writing and auditing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[India Opens a 3D Printed Post Office, Boosting Hopes for Housing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154399</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154399/india-opens-a-3d-printed-post-office-boosting-hopes-for-housing"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T01:02:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fast-evolving technology means building faster, cheaper, and more efficient structures, and offers hope for housing shortages worldwide.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong Reveals His 10 Favorite Crypto Innovations]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154398</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154398/coinbase-ceo-brian-armstrong-shares-favorite-crypto-innovations"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T00:55:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Messari CEO Ryan Selkis quickly chimed in with his own take on each idea.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt AI, Edited by Ryan Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can AI Make 'Call of Duty' Matches Less Toxic? We're About to Find Out]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154375</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154375/ai-make-call-duty-matches-less-toxic-about-find-out"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T22:50:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Activision has introduced AI chat moderation in Call of Duty games in an effort to curtail toxic behavior in real time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastering NFT Trading - Degen U]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/HQGt1Vrq/mastering-nft-trading-degen-u</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/HQGt1Vrq/mastering-nft-trading-degen-u"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T07:08:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Take Degen U's new course, Mastering NFT Trading, and earn an on-chain certificate. A top instructor will help you identify trends, seize the right moment to trade, weed out scams—and have fun while doing it!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Space Nation CEO on Working With 'Independence Day' Director Roland Emmerich]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LpznLhtx/space-nation-ceo-on-working-with-independence-day-director-roland-emmerich</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LpznLhtx/space-nation-ceo-on-working-with-independence-day-director-roland-emmerich"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T17:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jerome Wu, CEO of Space Nation, tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the upcoming Space Nation Online game in development and shares details on Space Nation Cofounder Roland Emmerich's role in the project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GAME REVIEW: Champions Arena from Gala Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qUE1RlDx/game-review-champions-arena-from-gala-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qUE1RlDx/game-review-champions-arena-from-gala-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Champions Arena is a turn-based fantasy RPG from Gala Games, where characters can become NFTs and crypto can be used to purchase gems, one of the game's synthetic currencies. Decrypt's Kate Irwin takes us inside the game for her thoughts on the fun, mobile-first title.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apex Legends Voice Actor Ben Prendergast on the Future of Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/X3RKdsaG/apex-legends-voice-actor-ben-prendergast-on-the-future-of-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/X3RKdsaG/apex-legends-voice-actor-ben-prendergast-on-the-future-of-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T18:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Voice actor Ben Prendergast, who's voiced characters in games like Apex Legends and God of War Ragnarok, shares his opinions on the tech space's history of "bubbles" and whether blockchain gaming has a future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The future of AI Stardom and Robotics with SingularityNET COO Janet Adams and Desdemona]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yVQaZI71/the-future-of-ai-stardom-and-robotics-with-singularitynet-coo-janet-adams-and-desdemona</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yVQaZI71/the-future-of-ai-stardom-and-robotics-with-singularitynet-coo-janet-adams-and-desdemona"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T16:45:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this interview, SingularityNET COO Janet Adams explains the intricate details that went into creating the Desdemona robot AI from Hanson Robotics and future plans for the AI Diva.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto a 'No-Brainer' for Video Games, Says Mino Games CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rdynom8C/crypto-a-no-brainer-for-video-games-says-mino-games-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rdynom8C/crypto-a-no-brainer-for-video-games-says-mino-games-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T18:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mino Games CEO Sasha MacKinnon, developer of the upcoming Dimensionals game, tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the studio's approach to digital collectibles.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Wagner's 'Controversial Take' on Crypto in Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tc2nKeqA/michael-wagners-controversial-take-on-crypto-in-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tc2nKeqA/michael-wagners-controversial-take-on-crypto-in-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T16:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Solana's PlayGG, Star Atlas CEO Michael Wagner shares his "controversial take" on crypto in games, shares the challenges of developing the upcoming scifi game, and how crypto's volatility has changed his perspective with Decrypt's Jason Nelson.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interview: Angelic CEO on Building the Sci-Fi RPG on Solana and Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/uCzW3K7P/interview-angelic-ceo-on-building-the-sci-fi-rpg-on-solana-and-ethereum</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/uCzW3K7P/interview-angelic-ceo-on-building-the-sci-fi-rpg-on-solana-and-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T15:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Angelic is a sci-fi roleplay game in development that will be free-to-play and offer optional, opt-in crypto features on Solana and Ethereum and a governance token. Metaverse Game Studios CEO and Founder Erkan Bayol tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how he sees AAA traditional games as Angelic's main competitors and shares his vision for the game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apex Legends Voice Actor on AI's Impact on Video Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IOIrmb0N/apex-legends-voice-actor-on-ais-impact-on-video-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IOIrmb0N/apex-legends-voice-actor-on-ais-impact-on-video-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T17:28:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ben Prendergast is an actor who has voiced characters like Apex Legends' Fuse, God of War Ragnarok's Tyr, and Patroclus in Hades. But as debates swirl around the use of artificial intelligence in entertainment in light of the SAG-AFTRA and WGA strikes, Prendergast gives Decrypt's Kate Irwin his honest take on the potential use of AI actors in games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Star Atlas CEO on Developing an MMO Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/WQCaahmH/star-atlas-ceo-on-developing-an-mmo-game</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/WQCaahmH/star-atlas-ceo-on-developing-an-mmo-game"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T13:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Jason Nelson speaks with Star Atlas Founder and CEO Michael Wagner about the MMO game's approach to development, marketing, and blockchain integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aurory's Origin Story: How JRPGs Inspired the Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/O0S201TB/aurorys-origin-story-how-jrpgs-inspired-the-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/O0S201TB/aurorys-origin-story-how-jrpgs-inspired-the-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T16:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Jason Nelson talks to Aurory's Head of Marketing and Business Development Michael Natoli about the origins of the Aurory crypto games at the Solana PlayGG event.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Parallel TCG: Inside the Sci-Fi Card Game’s Closed Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/q8YVWJh4/parallel-tcg-inside-the-sci-fi-card-games-closed-beta</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/q8YVWJh4/parallel-tcg-inside-the-sci-fi-card-games-closed-beta"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T15:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin goes hands-on with Parallel’s closed beta on Windows PC to find out what sets it apart from other crypto card-battlers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 Games Need to Compete with All Games, Says Solana Foundation GM]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ud9wTd4s/web3-games-need-to-compete-with-all-games-says-solana-foundation-gm</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ud9wTd4s/web3-games-need-to-compete-with-all-games-says-solana-foundation-gm"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T19:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Foundation's General Manager of Games Johnny Lee tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about Solana's PlayGG conference and shares his take on crypto gaming and the "play-to-earn" concept.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Many Early Blockchain Games Were 'Cash Grabs,' Says Twitch Streamer Alliestrasza]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BA4yE45A/many-early-blockchain-games-were-cash-grabs-says-twitch-streamer-alliestrasza</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BA4yE45A/many-early-blockchain-games-were-cash-grabs-says-twitch-streamer-alliestrasza"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T16:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["I wrote them off," Twitch streamer Alliestrasza said of her initial thoughts on many early blockchain games. She tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how her perspective on Web3 games has evolved over time and now sees blockchain games getting significantly better.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['MetalCore' Game Preview: Hands-on With the 'Titanfall' Meets 'Destiny' NFT Mashup]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/tjK6i7lv/metalcore-game-preview-hands-on-with-the-titanfall-meets-destiny-nft-mashup</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/tjK6i7lv/metalcore-game-preview-hands-on-with-the-titanfall-meets-destiny-nft-mashup"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T19:46:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MetalCore is an upcoming mech shooter developed by Studio 369, and it's being developed on Ethereum scaling network Immutable zkEVM. Decrypt contributor Ryan Gladwin played through the prologue and tested out the recent Alpha 3 online experience to get a sense of the NFT-infused mashup of Titanfall and Destiny.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>