<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-05-12T17:12:39.400Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-05-12T17:12:39.400Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DigiToads utility sets itself apart from Shiba Inu and Pepe as meme coins demand grows]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328089/DigiToads-utility-sets-itself-apart-from-Shiba-Inu-and-Pepe-as-meme-coins-demand-grows</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328089/DigiToads-utility-sets-itself-apart-from-Shiba-Inu-and-Pepe-as-meme-coins-demand-grows"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T17:10:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Digitoads is currently in the presale stage. PEPE has been the talk of the town over the last couple of after it got listed by Binance. 2023 has seen newly launched meme coins register staggering price movements. Many analysts are calling 2023 the year of meme coins. The market has seen new meme...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Price analysis 5/12: BTC, ETH, BNB, XRP, ADA, DOGE, MATIC, SOL, DOT, LTC]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328091/Price-analysis-512-BTC-ETH-BNB-XRP-ADA-DOGE-MATIC-SOL-DOT-LTC</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328091/Price-analysis-512-BTC-ETH-BNB-XRP-ADA-DOGE-MATIC-SOL-DOT-LTC"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T17:04:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin and most major altcoins are slumping, but the charts suggest that a recovery could be around the corner.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano’s hydra scaling solution goes live on mainnet as Ethereum gas fees surge]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328096/Cardanos-hydra-scaling-solution-goes-live-on-mainnet-as-Ethereum-gas-fees-surge</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328096/Cardanos-hydra-scaling-solution-goes-live-on-mainnet-as-Ethereum-gas-fees-surge"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T17:01:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first Hydra node compatible with the Cardano mainnet was launched on May 11, according to developer Sebastian Nagel. Hydra is a layer2 scaling solution designed to improve scalability on the Cardano blockchain. Its launch came after several months of testing. According to its technical...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Florida governor signs CBDC bill into law, restricting some uses of US and foreign CBDCs]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328090/Florida-governor-signs-CBDC-bill-into-law-restricting-some-uses-of-US-and-foreign-CBDCs</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328090/Florida-governor-signs-CBDC-bill-into-law-restricting-some-uses-of-US-and-foreign-CBDCs"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T16:58:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new law, signed by Governor Ron DeSantis, also urges other states to take action against the potential introduction of CBDCs through their commercial codes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Traders Choose Huobi and OKX After Binance Lifts Zero-Fee Trading]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328086/Traders-Choose-Huobi-and-OKX-After-Binance-Lifts-Zero-Fee-Trading</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328086/Traders-Choose-Huobi-and-OKX-After-Binance-Lifts-Zero-Fee-Trading"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T16:53:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance market share drops to low not seen since October 2022 as fees weigh on trading volumes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who said pro sports has cooled to crypto? Floki partners with ping pong]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328055/Who-said-pro-sports-has-cooled-to-crypto-Floki-partners-with-ping-pong</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328055/Who-said-pro-sports-has-cooled-to-crypto-Floki-partners-with-ping-pong"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T16:45:32.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The right to use digital assets to be added to Texas Bill of Rights]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328054/The-right-to-use-digital-assets-to-be-added-to-Texas-Bill-of-Rights</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328054/The-right-to-use-digital-assets-to-be-added-to-Texas-Bill-of-Rights"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T16:44:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The state of Texas has made a historic move by voting on an amendment that includes the possession, retainment and utilization of cryptocurrencies in its state Bill of Rights, signaling a major step toward digital-asset adoption. This new addition called House Joint Resolution 146 (HJR146) and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Imprisoned Ethereum Developer Virgil Griffith Faces 10-year Export Privilege Bar]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328046/Imprisoned-Ethereum-Developer-Virgil-Griffith-Faces-10-year-Export-Privilege-Bar</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328046/Imprisoned-Ethereum-Developer-Virgil-Griffith-Faces-10-year-Export-Privilege-Bar"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T16:43:51.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[yPredict Crypto Startup Enters Stage 5, Nears $1 Million Mark as Investors Scoop Up Tokens Ahead of 28.5% Price Increase]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328049/yPredict-Crypto-Startup-Enters-Stage-5-Nears-1-Million-Mark-as-Investors-Scoop-Up-Tokens-Ahead-of-285-Price-Increase</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328049/yPredict-Crypto-Startup-Enters-Stage-5-Nears-1-Million-Mark-as-Investors-Scoop-Up-Tokens-Ahead-of-285-Price-Increase"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T16:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Investors are rushing to secure ground-breaking AI-powered trading and market intelligence platform yPredict’s $YPRED crypto token, which continues to fly off the shelves in one of this year’s hottest crypto start-up fundraising presale rounds. yPredict’s viral presale, which has already scooped...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Congressman Brad Sherman Sends Letter To SEC Chair Calling Attention To Grayscale Bitcoin Trust Situation]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750b965643</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/legal/u-s-congressman-sends-letter-to-sec-chair-calling-attention-to-gbtc-situation"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T16:39:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Congressman Brad Sherman has sent a letter to Gary Gensler, Chair of the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), regarding the situation of Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC).



According to Sherman, as many as 850,000 retail investors, including some who used individual retirement account funds, are currently trapped in their GBTC investments due to the actions of GBTC and its parent company, Digital Currency Group (DCG). Sherman estimates that these investors' retirement security and in some cases, their life savings, may be at risk and that if the situation is not remedied, they could lose tens of billions of dollars of their savings.
Sherman's concerns regarding GBTC stem from the fact that GBTC shares currently trade at a ~42% discount to the bitcoins in the trust, and Graysc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BtcCasey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MetaCannes Ushers in Film3's Next Wave of Cinema at Cannes Film Festival]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139889</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139889/metacannes-ushers-in-film3s-next-wave-of-cinema-at-cannes-film-festival"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T16:31:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Web3 film festival will showcase Film3’s potential to transform the industry, with livestreamed talks and screenings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Traditional to Trending: The Unstoppable Shift to Web3 Marketing]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328023/From-Traditional-to-Trending-The-Unstoppable-Shift-to-Web3-Marketing</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328023/From-Traditional-to-Trending-The-Unstoppable-Shift-to-Web3-Marketing"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T16:31:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The marketing industry is witnessing a revolution with the shift from traditional to Web3 marketing. As brands leverage blockchain, NFTs, and decentralized platforms, customer engagement and loyalty are reaching new heights.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Markets Stll Dropping as Week Comes to a Close!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18327882/Markets-Stll-Dropping-as-Week-Comes-to-a-Close</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18327882/Markets-Stll-Dropping-as-Week-Comes-to-a-Close"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T16:29:31.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Musk’s Milady Meme, Opening Up Ordinals]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750b903d37</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/web3/2023/05/12/musks-milady-meme-opening-up-ordinals/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T16:26:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Miladys NFTs saw a brief pump after Elon Musk tweeted about them and Binance is making it easier for people to buy Bitcoin NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rosie Perper</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paradigm-Backed NFT Ownership Platform Tessera is Shutting Down]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328002/Paradigm-Backed-NFT-Ownership-Platform-Tessera-is-Shutting-Down</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328002/Paradigm-Backed-NFT-Ownership-Platform-Tessera-is-Shutting-Down"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T16:24:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Co-founder Andy Chorlian tweeted that the decision was made after "carefully analyzing possible market scenarios, our company structure and our financial situation."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Names NBCUniversal’s Linda Yaccarino New Twitter CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139905</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139905/elon-musk-names-nbcuniversals-linda-yaccarino-new-twitter-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T16:24:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Musk says Yaccarino will start in six weeks as he segues to “focus on product design and new technology” at the social media giant.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Leaders Turn to the UAE As Frustration Grows With US Regulators]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328008/Crypto-Leaders-Turn-to-the-UAE-As-Frustration-Grows-With-US-Regulators</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328008/Crypto-Leaders-Turn-to-the-UAE-As-Frustration-Grows-With-US-Regulators"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T16:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some cryptocurrency leaders are turning to the United Arab Emirates as others are showing irritation with US regulators. Saqr Ereiqat, co-founder of venture-building firm Crypto Oasis, told CoinTelegraph that the UAE checks all the boxes in terms of countries’ “regulatory infrastructure, digital...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biggest Movers: SHIB, DOGE Near Multi-Month Lows, as Musk Finds New Twitter CEO]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750b91715a</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/biggest-movers-shib-doge-near-multi-month-lows-as-musk-finds-new-twitter-ceo/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T16:18:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba inu moved close to a five-month low on Friday, as meme coins reacted to news that Elon Musk has found a new Twitter CEO. Musk tweeted, “Excited to announce that I’ve hired a new CEO for X/Twitter. She will be starting in ~6 weeks.” Dogecoin neared a two-month low today.
 
Shiba Inu (SHIB)
 
Shiba inu (SHIB) neared a five-month low on Friday, as markets reacted to the news that Elon Musk will be stepping down as CEO.
 
Musk, who acquired the social media company last year, has been at the helm since the takeover, but has now found a long-term replacement.
 
Following a high of $0.000008746 on Thursday, SHIB/USD dropped to a bottom of $0.000008549 earlier in the day.
 
 
As a result of this sell-off, shiba inu moved close to Monday’s low at $0.00000835, which was the weakest point the meme coin has hit since January.
 
Looking at the chart, this latest move occurred as the relative strength index (RSI) moved deep into oversold territory, with a current reading at 23.02.
 
This does give hope to longer-term bulls however, that a reversal could be on the cards.
 
 
Dogecoin (DOGE)
 
Dogecoin (DOGE) also moved lower in today’s session, as the meme coin neared a multi-month low of its own.
 
DOGE/USD fell to an intraday low of $0.06957 earlier on Friday, hours after trading at a peak of $0.07268.
 
Similar to SHIB, today’s decline almost led to dogecoin recapturing a low of $0.0692, which was its weakest level since March.
 
 
DOGE has since bounced back from this earlier low, after bulls rejected a full breakout of a support point of $0.07000.
 
As of writing, the price is now at $0.07127, which seems to have occurred as traders moved to buy the dip.
 
Should today’s low be the hard floor, there will likely be a stronger rebound in the coming days.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
Could DOGE climb towards $0.08000 next week? Let us know your thoughts in the comments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lawyers of Kwon, Chang-joon Request $400K+ Bail and House Arrest]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18327993/Lawyers-of-Kwon-Chang-joon-Request-400K-Bail-and-House-Arrest</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18327993/Lawyers-of-Kwon-Chang-joon-Request-400K-Bail-and-House-Arrest"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T16:16:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The attorneys representing co-founder of Terra Do Kwon and Terra executive Han Chang-joon proposed that they be put under house arrest upon posting bail of 400,000 euros each, approximately $436,000, according to a notice from the Basic Court in Podgorica, Montenegro on May 11. Under such...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Meme-Generating Platform AiDoge’s Presale Surges to $6.2 Million, The Next Dogecoin But With Utility?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328050/AI-Meme-Generating-Platform-AiDoges-Presale-Surges-to-62-Million-The-Next-Dogecoin-But-With-Utility</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328050/AI-Meme-Generating-Platform-AiDoges-Presale-Surges-to-62-Million-The-Next-Dogecoin-But-With-Utility"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T16:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Upstart artificial intelligence meme coin project AiDoge’s viral presale continues to surge. AiDoge is building a revolutionary new social platform that allows users to generate memes using AiDoge’s cutting-edge generative artificial intelligence (AI) technology and earn crypto if their memes...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LG Files Patent for TV That Lets Users Trade NFTs From Their Couches]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139899</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139899/lg-patents-tv-that-can-trade-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T16:14:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LG television would permit purchases through a user’s cryptocurrency wallet connected to the TV set, according to the patent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin: This Could Change Everything! [Big Crypto News]]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328011/Bitcoin-This-Could-Change-Everything-Big-Crypto-News</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18328011/Bitcoin-This-Could-Change-Everything-Big-Crypto-News"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T16:06:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Big things happening in markets that could affect bitcoin and all of crypto. 🔥 GET MY FREE NEWSLETTER 👉 https://cryptolark.co/WEALTHMASTERY💸 BYBIT $30,030 BONUS & FEE DISCOUNT 👉 https://cryptolark.co/BYBIT💡💡💡 ESSENTIAL CRYPTO KNOWLEDGE 💡💡💡🔥 GET MY FREE NEWSLETTER 👉...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Gains Recognition As Blockchain Leader by Dubai Government Media]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750b931eaf</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ripple-gains-recognition-as-blockchain-leader-by-dubai-government-media/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T16:06:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Dubai government’s official media has praised the blockchain company Ripple as a leader. The recent spotlighting is coming shortly after the firm launches its new business office in the country.
 
Dubai Government’s Media Office Spotlights Ripple
 
The official media Twitter page of the Dubai government spotlighted the blockchain company behind the crypto asset XRP. The tweet recognized the firm as a prominent player and a master in enterprise blockchain and crypto solutions.
 
The government’s media office praised while responding to the expansion move into the country. It further highlighted the country’s proactive decisions concerning innovative technologies and advancement. 
 
Related Reading: Michael Saylor Doubles Down On Bitcoin As ‘King’ Commodity, Warns ‘Money Is Dying’
 
Thes…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Dambel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Musk’s Milady Meme, Opening Up Ordinals]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18327965/Musks-Milady-Meme-Opening-Up-Ordinals</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18327965/Musks-Milady-Meme-Opening-Up-Ordinals"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T16:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Miladys NFTs saw a brief pump after Elon Musk tweeted about them and Binance is making it easier for people to buy Bitcoin NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shytoshi Kusama Issues Major Warning on Shibarium, Top Lawyer Reacts to Ripple CEO's Prediction on When XRP Case Ends: Crypto News Digest by U.Today]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18327978/Shytoshi-Kusama-Issues-Major-Warning-on-Shibarium-Top-Lawyer-Reacts-to-Ripple-CEOs-Prediction-on-When-XRP-Case-Ends-Crypto-News-Digest-by-UToday</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18327978/Shytoshi-Kusama-Issues-Major-Warning-on-Shibarium-Top-Lawyer-Reacts-to-Ripple-CEOs-Prediction-on-When-XRP-Case-Ends-Crypto-News-Digest-by-UToday"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T16:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Take a closer look at what’s happening in the world of crypto with U.Today’s news digest!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinGecko hit 100k subscribers]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18327966/CoinGecko-hit-100k-subscribers</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18327966/CoinGecko-hit-100k-subscribers"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T16:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meme Coin Chill: Shiba Inu (SHIB) Price Eyes Correction Amid Cooling Trend]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18327960/Meme-Coin-Chill-Shiba-Inu-SHIB-Price-Eyes-Correction-Amid-Cooling-Trend</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18327960/Meme-Coin-Chill-Shiba-Inu-SHIB-Price-Eyes-Correction-Amid-Cooling-Trend"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Latest Trends and Innovations in Loyalty and Reward Programs Tied to Payments]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750b99605d</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/education-centre/the-latest-trends-and-innovations-in-loyalty-and-reward-programs-tied-to-payments/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T15:24:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Businesses have  
traditionally used loyalty and reward programs to encourage consumer loyalty  
and encourage repeat business. These programs have developed and advanced in  
recent years, with payment integration being a crucial factor. This article  
will examine the newest developments and trends in payment-related loyalty and  
reward programs. 
Understanding  
and utilizing these developments can assist organizations in developing  
effective and engaging loyalty programs that increase customer retention and  
generate income, from tailored offers to blockchain-based loyalty tokens.
Personalization  
and Targeted Offers 
Personalization  
is one of the major developments in loyalty programs. Businesses are utilizing  
customer insights and data analytics to develop personalized offer…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Finance Magnates Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Exchange Supply At New All-Time Low, Investors Accumulating?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750b9bef81</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-exchange-supply-all-time-low-accumulating/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T15:07:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data shows the Ethereum exchange supply has declined to an all-time low recently, suggesting that investors may be accumulating.
 
Ethereum Supply On Exchanges Has Continued Its Downtrend Recently
 
According to data from the on-chain analytics firm Santiment, ETH on exchanges is now at its lowest since the cryptocurrency started trading publicly in July 2015. The “ETH supply on exchanges” is an indicator that measures the percentage of the total Ethereum circulating supply that’s currently sitting in the wallets of all centralized exchanges.
 
When the value of this metric goes up, it means the investors are depositing their coins in the wallets of exchanges currently. Since one of the main reasons why holders may transfer their ETH to these platforms is for selling-related purpo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hououin Kyouma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Among Bitcoin Developers, Debate Is Raging Over Whether to Censor Ordinals BRC-20s]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750b844c37</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/05/12/among-bitcoin-developers-debate-is-raging-over-whether-to-censor-ordinals-brc-20s/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T15:05:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite calls for censorship, many developers agree that maintaining the status quo is the right thing to do for now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Frederick  Munawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The State Of Web3 Gaming On Hedera]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/7TTEckkZ/the-state-of-web3-gaming-on-hedera</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/7TTEckkZ/the-state-of-web3-gaming-on-hedera"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T14:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hedera VP Alex Russman tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about Hedera's Web3 gaming ecosystem and shares a game he's particularly excited about.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Temporary Transaction Finality Glitch Disrupts Ethereum Network for 25 Minutes, Developers Investigate the Cause]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750b8376ee</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/temporary-transaction-finality-glitch-disrupts-ethereum-network-for-25-minutes-developers-investigate-the-cause/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T14:17:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum had issues processing transactions on May 11, 2023, at around 4:13 p.m. Eastern Time on Thursday, and transaction finality issues lasted for roughly 25 minutes. Currently, developers do not know what caused the issue and the blockchain is now running normally. 
 
Ethereum Network Experiences Temporary Transaction Processing Issue
 
The Ethereum blockchain was unable to process ETH transactions and reach consensus for approximately 25 minutes on Thursday, just after 4 p.m. (ET). Ansgar Dietrichs, a researcher at the Ethereum Foundation said: “The beacon chain had a brief period of non-finalization just now. Good illustration for the robustness of the chain — while there was some slowdown of blocks, transactions continued to be processed as usual. We are back to normal now.”
 
Prysm…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Crypto Dominance Declines, Empowering Rivals Huobi And OKX]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750b8d1466</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/binance-crypto-dominance-declines/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T14:06:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance is now facing another major challenge as a recent study by research firm Kaiko revealed that rival exchanges Huobi and OKX benefited from Binance’s decision to curtail its zero-fee promotion. Subsequently, the crypto exchange saw its market share drop in the spot trading of digital assets.
 
The study highlights the impact of Binance’s decision on the wider crypto exchange market, as Huobi and OKX were able to capitalize on the exchange’s loss and increase their own market share. 
 
 
This news comes at a time when the crypto exchange is already facing mounting controversies regarding its operations and regulatory compliance, as well as recent issues faced by its CEO Changpeng Zhao.
 

 
Despite being one of the largest and most successful crypto exchanges in the world, Binance’s r…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Liquidity on Binance Has More Than Halved Since February: Kaiko]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139877</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139877/bitcoin-liquidity-binance-has-more-than-halved-since-february-kaiko"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T13:57:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Low liquidity and volumes on Binance have led to a serious uptick in volatility in the price action for Bitcoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly,Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Casinos Not On Gamstop 2023]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750b88161d</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/best-casinos-not-on-gamstop-uk/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T13:46:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you looking for non-Gamstop casinos in the UK? Do you want to find great bonuses and experience fantastic games without the restrictions found on UK Gambling Commission-regulated sites? Look no further than our updated guide for the best casinos in 2023.
 
 
Seven.Casino – Best Casino Overall
 
NonstopCasino – Premium New Casino
 
Superb.bet – Excellent Casino and Sports
 
Betti.com – Best Gambling Site 2023
 
BloodMoonCasino – Huge UK Favorite
 
Goldenbet – Great for Mobile Play
 
AllwinsCasino – Big Welcome Offer
 
Goldwin – Top Casino 2023
 
Slotsdreamer – Best For Bonuses
 
Gxmble – Quick Payments
 
 
Our Top Non-Gamstop Casino Sites Review 2023
 
We’ve researched and compiled a list of the top non-Gamstop casino sites and we’re excited to share our findings with you. These sites, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stella Jackson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Mother’s Day, Try Explaining Bitcoin To Your Mom]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750b8bdccf</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/give-bitcoin-for-mothers-day"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T13:21:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is an opinion editorial by Hector Alvero, a Bitcoin educator who serves as co-host of the Broward County Bitcoiners meetup.
 
         
         
         
        Source 
    
As Bitcoiners, we love the exhilarating feeling of bringing a new person into the Bitcoin lifeboat. Many of us constantly work to orange pill our friends, our coworkers and our neighbors, trying to save as many as we can before the fiat ship sinks. We'll even try to orange pill the waiter at our favorite local restaurant, helping them download a Lightning wallet and offering to give them a bigger tip to help them "get off zero."
But what about your mom? Have you given her the same gift that you’ve given to the Uber driver who took you home from your last conference or meetup? Have you taken the time to help her…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hector Alvero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Technical Analysis: BTC Plunges Under $27,000, Hitting 7-Week Low]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750b7467b7</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-ethereum-technical-analysis-btc-plunges-under-27000-hitting-7-week-low/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T13:18:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin fell to a seven-week low on May 12, as prices dropped below the $27,000 level in today’s session. Friday’s decline came as a red wave swept through cryptocurrencies, with the market cap down 2.75% as of writing. Ethereum also slipped to its weakest point since March. 
 
Bitcoin
 
Bitcoin (BTC) dropped below the $27,000 level in today’s session, pushing prices to a seven-week low.
 
Following a high of $27,589.92 on Thursday, BTC/USD slipped to an intraday bottom at $26,166.87.
 
As a result of this drop, bitcoin fell to its lowest level since March 17, when price was below the $25,000 mark.
 
 
Bitcoin chart by TradingView
 

 
 

 
Overall, this latest sell-off coincided with the 14-day relative strength index (RSI) breaking out of yesterday’s floor of 43.00.
 
At the time of writing, price strength is tracking at 35.07, which is its lowest point in over two months.
 
Should momentum continue in this current trajectory, there is a possibility that BTC could move toward $25,000 this weekend.
 
 
Ethereum
 
In addition to BTC, ethereum (ETH) was also in the red on Friday, as bears continued to control market sentiment.
 
ETH/USD slipped to a low at $1,742.40 on Thursday, following an earlier peak of $1,835.62 the day prior.
 
Similar to bitcoin, today’s drop in price saw the world’s second largest cryptocurrency hit its lowest point since March.
 
 
Ethereum chart by TradingView
 

 
 

 
A major catalyst to the move was also a breakout on the RSI, which fell out of a support point at the 44.00 zone.
 
Currently, the index is at a reading of 39.04, which is its weakest level since March 11, when ETH traded below $1,500.
 
Ultimately, this could be a long-term positive for bulls, who may move to buy the current dip in price.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
 What is behind today’s red wave? Leave your thoughts in the comments below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terra Founder Do Kwon Buys His Way Out Of Jail In Montenegro]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750b74e3f7</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/terra-do-kwon-buys-his-way-out-of-jail/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T13:14:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What an unexpected development: Terra Luna founder Do Kwon has bought his way out of jail in Montenegro, using his own assets to do so. According to local media, Do Kwon accepted the offered bail of 400,000 euros (about $435,000) each for himself and his relative Hon Chand Jun. Both are accused of forging documents in Montenegro.
 
According to the news report, the defendants explained their financial situation to the court, stating that they have assets worth several million and that the bail could be paid in full by their wives.
 
In addition, the Terra Luna founder and his companion reportedly assured the court that if they were released on bail until the conclusion of the criminal proceedings, they would not hide, would regularly respond to court summonses, and would be reachable at th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform CEO Do Kwon to Be Released on Bail in Montenegro]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139873</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139873/terraform-ceo-do-kwon-be-released-bail-montenegro"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T13:09:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Basic Court in Montenegro has agreed to a $436,000 bail for Terraform Labs’ co-founder and CEO Do Kwon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EU Crypto Tax Plans Include NFTs, Foreign Companies, Draft Text Shows]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750b70acc0</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/05/12/eu-crypto-tax-plans-include-nfts-foreign-companies-draft-text-shows/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T12:50:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Laws set to be agreed next week would require crypto companies to register with tax authorities, even if they’re based outside the bloc or offering non-fungible tokens.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack Schickler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LG Electronics Seeks Patent for TV Which Lets Users Trade NFTs]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750b70aca0</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/05/12/lg-electronics-seeks-patent-for-tv-which-lets-users-trade-nfts/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T12:50:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LG has been a node operator on the Hedera Network since 2020.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Mover Americas: Bitcoin Falls to 2-Month Low]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750b70ac8e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/05/12/first-mover-americas-memecoin-pepe-hits-1b-market-cap/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T12:50:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest price moves in bitcoin (BTC) and crypto markets in context for May 12, 2023. First Mover is CoinDesk’s daily newsletter that contextualizes the latest actions in the crypto markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do Kwon Set To Be Released on Bail in Montenegro Travel Document Forgery Case]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750b7366d8</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/05/12/do-kwon-set-to-be-released-on-bail-in-montenegro-travel-document-forgery-case/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T12:32:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bail conditions restrict Kwon from leaving his apartment in the country as the trial continues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandali Handagama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Saylor Doubles Down On Bitcoin As ‘King’ Commodity, Warns ‘Money Is Dying’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750b7ca072</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/michael-saylor-warns-money-is-dying/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T12:23:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin still commands respect and popularity despite the current gloomy economic climate. Michael Saylor, MicroStrategy co-founder, has been particularly vocal in his support for the cryptocurrency, and in a recent interview, he reiterated his optimism for Bitcoin’s potential as a solution to economic instability. 
 
Saylor has been a well-known advocate for Bitcoin since MicroStrategy announced its $425 million investment in the cryptocurrency in 2020, and his views on the digital asset are highly regarded by investors around the world.
 
In an interview with financial journalist David Lin, Michael Saylor highlighted the shortcomings of traditional currencies, pointing out that their value is subject to inflation and instability. 
 
He emphasized how “money is dying,” and explained how B…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance.US Considers Reducing Founder Changpeng Zhao’s Control Amid Regulatory Scrutiny]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750b7ac817</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/binance-considers-reducing-changpeng-zhaos-control/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T11:42:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amid the continuous regulatory scrutiny, Binance.US, the American arm of the world’s largest cryptocurrency exchange, has disclosed it is now contemplating cutting down founder Changpeng Zhao’s (CZ) majority stake in the company.
 
This move comes in response to regulators targeting the exchange. And according to the report, this latest move is in the favor of the company as it will remove any challenges regarding the obtaining of any future regulatory license. 
 
Cutting Down Control
 
On Thursday, The Information reported that Binance.US executives have been in discussions with Zhao about reducing his stake in the company. The move is said to be aimed at addressing concerns over regulatory compliance and bolstering the exchange’s standing with US regulators.
 
Binance.US is currently in …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ATPBot Launched a Real AI Quantitative Trading Bot]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750b600b0d</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/atpbot-launched-a-real-ai-quantitative-trading-bot/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T11:07:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. Recently, ATPBot, the first truly quantitative trading bot, announced that it can now connect to the Binance API for trading, providing users with more opportunities to trade cryptocurrencies. By registering ATPBot, connect to Binance Exchange, enter your investment amount and earn income. Users can experience an unparalleled trading experience, delivering results through mature trading strategies and professional investment management.
 
Have you ever heard about ChatGPT? It has been a hot topic this year, for it’s changing the way we live and work. It provides personalized and accurate responses, while continuously improving its understanding through machine learning, offering unparalleled convenience and accessibility. As one of the most advanced language models, the capa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former FTX Exec Cooperating in Lawsuit Against Celebrity Promoters]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139866</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139866/former-ftx-exec-cooperating-lawsuit-against-celebrity-promoters"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T10:48:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FTX's former compliance chief shared evidence in support of a lawsuit alleging that celebrities promoted the now-bankrupt crypto exchange.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CZ Looking to Offload Some of Majority Stake in Binance US: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139867</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139867/cz-looking-to-offload-majority-stake-binance-us-report"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T10:18:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao is reportedly looking to hand over some of his majority stake in Binance.US to appease American regulators.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Own a Share of a Famed Andy Warhol Print for Just $20—Kinda]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139850</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139850/you-can-own-share-famed-andy-warhol-print-just-23-kinda"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T10:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New fractionalized art platform Freeport is offering Ethereum-based tokenized shares of original Warhol screen prints.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Hits Two-Month Low Amid Dollar Strength, Cooling Ordinals Activity]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139861</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139861/bitcoin-hits-two-month-low-dollar-strength-cooling-ordinals-activity"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T09:45:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin took a hit this morning amid rising economic uncertainty around the U.S. debt limit crisis and a slowdown in Ordinals hype.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Chamber of Commerce Slams SEC, Backs Coinbase in Legal Fight]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139843</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139843/chamber-commerce-slams-sec-coinbase-lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T22:53:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A heavyweight in the business world, the organization says the SEC's "regulatory chaos is by design, not happenstance."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your Crypto Mining Chips Are No Good for AI—Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139825</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139825/crypto-mining-chips-ai-heres-why"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T21:07:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mining and AI have different tastes when it comes to GPUs, and crypto miners can’t satisfy them both.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Is Hot—But Meta Is Still ‘Really Interested in the Metaverse,’ Exec Claims]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139826</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139826/ai-is-hot-but-meta-is-still-really-interested-in-the-metaverse-exec-claims"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T21:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meta’s short-term focus has shifted towards AI, but an exec says that such tools will actually help its metaverse vision come to life.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Cohen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Heavy Metal Band Avenged Sevenfold Keeps Betting on NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139832</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139832/avenged-sevenfold-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T20:59:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avenged Sevenfold frontman M. Shadows appeared on Decrypt’s gm podcast to discuss why he thinks NFTs give fans a better experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Mirandus is Innovating Video Game Audio]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kLHZIUsl/how-mirandus-is-innovating-video-game-audio</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kLHZIUsl/how-mirandus-is-innovating-video-game-audio"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T20:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mirandus' Lead Developer and Gala Games Cofounder Michael McCarthy tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the game's thoughtful approach to audio design and the technologies being built to support the MMORPG's immersive world.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IRS Trains Ukraine Law Enforcement to Track and Trace Russia's Cryptocurrency Moves]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139812</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139812/irs-chainalysis-train-urkaine-law-enforcement"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T17:58:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["We resist the aggressor state not only on the battlefield, but also on the economic front," said the head of Ukraine's Economic Security Bureau.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘We Screwed Up’: Coinbase Apologizes for Pepe Comments as #DeleteCoinbase Trends]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139805</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139805/we-screwed-up-coinbase-apologizes-for-pepe-comments-as-deletecoinbase-trends"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T17:14:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The move comes after the hashtag trended on Twitter, as PEPE holders bristled over Coinbase's description of Pepe's past alt-right history.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Labs Opening 25,000-Square-Foot Office Space in NYC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139795</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139795/solana-labs-opens-nyc-coworking-space"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T16:47:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite shuttering stores earlier this year, the company behind the 10th biggest cryptocurrency is opening co-working space.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Silvergate Lays Off 230 Workers as Crypto-Friendly Bank Continues Wind Down]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139791</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139791/silvergate-lays-off-230-as-it-continues-wind-down"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T15:28:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The banked shuttered in March after its deposits were rocked in the wake of FTX’s collapse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do Gamers Hate NFTs?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/X0FtIw0j/do-gamers-hate-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/X0FtIw0j/do-gamers-hate-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin asks the InfiniGods developers Damon Gura and Owen O’Donoghue about gamers and NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking Boundaries: YuYu's Personal Journey as a Queer Artist in the NFT World]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139737</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139737/breaking-boundaries-yuyu-personal-journey-queer-artist-nft-world"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T15:03:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[YuYu’s first NFT-powered exhibit “GAG” merges a variety of artforms—including traditional art and photography—all on the blockchain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gaming Dominates On-Chain Transactions in April as Arbitrum Users Surge]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139695</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139695/gaming-dominates-on-chain-transactions-in-april-as-arbitrum-users-surge"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T15:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The meme token craze might be impacting Web3 gaming activity, DappRadar suggests, but Arbitrum users are up and Sui is gaining steam.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miners Earning $40M Daily Revenue as Ordinals Debate Splits Devs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139679</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139679/bitcoin-miners-earning-40m-daily-revenue-as-ordinals-debate-splits-devs"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T14:51:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Miners have struggled as of late, but the Ordinals craze is creating a windfall for a fortunate few.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin and Ethereum Down 3%, Top Altcoins Fall as Market Sees Red]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139747</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139747/bitcoin-and-ethereum-down-3-percent"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T14:45:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now that Bitcoin fees have subsided, delayed selling has dragged down BTC, ETH, and altcoin prices a day after the U.S. CPI report.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Artizen Fund Raises $2.2 Million to Create NFT Cultural Artifacts]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139682</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139682/artizen-fund-raises-2-2-million-to-create-nft-cultural-artifacts"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The platform leverages tokenization and gamification to crowdfund niche projects in the arts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Texas Lawmakers Vote to Include Use of Digital Currencies in State's Bill of Rights]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139729</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139729/texas-lawmakers-vote-include-use-digital-currencies-states-bill-rights"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T12:55:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The people of Texas may soon be guaranteed the right to use cryptocurrencies if lawmakers enshrine it into the state’s Bill of Rights.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Crypto Rules ‘Will Bite’ Firms That Market to Consumers, Says Financial Regulator]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139730</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139730/new-crypto-rules-will-bite-firms-marketing-consumers-says-financial-regulator"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T12:35:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Financial Conduct Authority said the UK is looking to protect consumers with upcoming crypto regulatory framework changes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Crypto Bros Are Certainly a Problem': Ripple Managing Director]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139724</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139724/crypto-bros-are-certainly-problem-ripple-managing-director"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T09:54:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solving the long-standing issue of diversity in the crypto industry demands more than just “one magic bullet,” says Ripple’s Sendi Young.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Serves Bitcoin Mining Firm Marathon Digital With Subpoena, Again]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139722</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139722/sec-serves-bitcoin-mining-firm-marathon-digital-subpoena-again"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T09:17:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marathon Digital revealed the company has received a new subpoena from the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CleanSpark Eyes Expansion Plans Ahead of Bitcoin Halving]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139713</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139713/cleanspark-eyes-expansion-plans-ahead-bitcoin-halving"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T08:14:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CleanSpark assured investors during its Q2 earnings call that that it is both growing rapidly and focusing on efficiency.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Krantz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why DeFi Cybersecurity Can Never Sleep]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139573</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139573/why-defi-cybersecurity-can-never-sleep"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T22:41:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["You can't know if the report is that serious hack, or if it's just spam," said Immunefi CEO Mitchell Amador.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonah Elkowitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Barbie and Boss Beauties Make Joint Bid to Bring More Women into Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139666</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139666/barbie-boss-beauties-digital-collectibles-nfts-women-web3"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T21:50:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The two brands have created a crossover NFT collection featuring a variety of rarity levels and real-world perks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can New York AG’s Crypto Proposal Offer Investors Greater Protection?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139659</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139659/new-york-crypto-crpto-act-law-regulation-investor-protection"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T21:06:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CRPTO Act focuses on transparency and conflicts of interest in an already crypto-savvy state.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This 23-Year Old Snapchat Star Can Be Your AI Girlfriend—For a Price]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139633</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139633/snapchat-star-caryn-marjorie-ai-girlfriend-carynai"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T20:21:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You too can now be social media influencer Caryn Marjorie’s virtual boyfriend, for just $1 per minute.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOJ: Crypto Assets 'Touch Every Aspect of Criminal Activity We Investigate']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139653</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139653/doj-crypto-assets-touch-every-aspect-of-crime"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T20:05:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Law enforcement can freeze conventional transactions, but they can’t do that with digital asset transactions," said the DOJ's Eun Young Choi.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano,Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: Avenged Sevenfold's M. Shadows on Deathbats, Fandom, and AI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JEgr9COw/gm-avenged-sevenfolds-m-shadows-on-deathbats-fandom-and-ai</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JEgr9COw/gm-avenged-sevenfolds-m-shadows-on-deathbats-fandom-and-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T20:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avenged Sevenfold lead singer Matt Sanders, aka M. Shadows, is rehearsing for the band's upcoming tour. He's also figuring out how to upend what it means to be a music fan. The band launched a Deathbats Club NFT collection in 2021. That is to say: They were early. The lead singer said it was timed to give fans a chance to get comfortable with Web3 technology ahead of the group's 2023 tour, when the NFT holders can use their Deathbats for early access to tickets. M. Shadows also talked to hosts Andrew Hayward and Stephen Graves about AI and bringing Web3 into gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lawmakers Say Crypto Turf War Between SEC and CFTC Is an 'Industry-Fueled Narrative']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139630</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139630/lawmakers-say-crypto-turf-war-between-sec-and-cftc-is-an-industry-fueled-narrative"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T19:43:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How a token could go from a commodity to a security—and where to draw the line—remains unclear as ever on Capitol Hill.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alo Yoga Retail Chain Debuts In-Store NFT Claim With MoonPay]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139613</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139613/alo-yoga-in-store-nft-moonpay"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T18:21:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The brick-and-mortar brand is offering customers free “daily affirmation” NFTs minted on Ethereum scaling network Polygon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roblox Users Surge 22% to New Peak Despite Fading Metaverse Hype]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139606</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139606/roblox-users-surge-22-to-new-peak-despite-fading-metaverse-hype"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T18:09:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The game company saw over $655 million in quarterly revenue and hit a new all-time high in daily active users (DAU), but losses were sharper than expected.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether Posts Massive First Quarter Profits of $1.48 Billion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139604</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139604/tether-posts-massive-first-quarter-profits-of-1-48-billion"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T17:45:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In its latest assurance report, the company behind the USDT stablecoin says it has seen “tremendous success.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Tweets Miladys NFT Meme—Price Predictably Pumps]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139593</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139593/elon-musk-tweets-miladys-nft-meme-price-predictably-pumps"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T16:39:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As it has for Dogecoin, Twitter owner Elon Musk's tweet has sent the price of Milady Maker NFTs flying, now up 57% over the past day.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Mojo Melee's Lore with Creator Mike Levine and Art Director Eric Campanella]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BfIB2H5e/inside-mojo-melees-lore-with-creator-mike-levine-and-art-director-eric-campanella</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BfIB2H5e/inside-mojo-melees-lore-with-creator-mike-levine-and-art-director-eric-campanella"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T22:29:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the Game Developers' Conference, Mojo Melee Creator Mike Levine and Art Director Eric Campanella tell Decrypt's Kate Irwin about their autobattler game and its unique characters, which are also NFTs on Polygon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why 'Blair Witch' Exec Producer Kevin Foxe Is '1,000% In' on Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZXj16C8r/why-blair-witch-exec-producer-kevin-foxe-is-1-000-in-on-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZXj16C8r/why-blair-witch-exec-producer-kevin-foxe-is-1-000-in-on-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T23:02:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["The Blair Witch Project" Executive Producer Kevin Foxe wants to avoid corporate overlords and enlighten fans of the dark "Mandala" graphic novel with a video game adaptation and NFTs across multiple blockchains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gala Games Co-Founder on the Aesthetic of Mirandus]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/1bQV1R6l/gala-games-co-founder-on-the-aesthetic-of-mirandus</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/1bQV1R6l/gala-games-co-founder-on-the-aesthetic-of-mirandus"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T14:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["When assets are overdone, they just feel a little dirty. It's not pretty to look at," shared Mirandus' Lead Developer and Gala Games co-founder Michael McCarthy in an interview with Decrypt's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Games GM: Play-to-Earn Games Are DeFi Products, Not Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yp7btQtl/solana-games-gm-play-to-earn-games-are-defi-products-not-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yp7btQtl/solana-games-gm-play-to-earn-games-are-defi-products-not-games"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T16:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Games' General Manager Johnny Lee offers a hot take on the first generation of Web3 gaming with Decrypt's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brycent's Advice For Gaming Content Creators]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/o19nZCeN/brycents-advice-for-gaming-content-creators</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/o19nZCeN/brycents-advice-for-gaming-content-creators"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T20:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XSET's Brycent shares his advice for Web3 content creators with Decrypt's Kate Irwin, including which social media platform is best for posting content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Behind the Scenes of Jeremy Cowart's 'Auras' NFT Event]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/C0ZeidQg/behind-the-scenes-of-jeremy-cowarts-auras-nft-event</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/C0ZeidQg/behind-the-scenes-of-jeremy-cowarts-auras-nft-event"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T22:54:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A look at the preparation behind "Auras," an event in which photographer Jeremy Cowart produced and starred in 10,000 photo-based NFTs, captured in less than 30 minutes before a live audience. Credit: Brett Carlsen for Decrypt]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jeremy Cowart Discusses 'Auras' Event, Live-Shooting 10,000 Photo NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/E3ViHsPd/jeremy-cowart-discusses-auras-event-live-shooting-10-000-photo-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/E3ViHsPd/jeremy-cowart-discusses-auras-event-live-shooting-10-000-photo-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T18:32:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jeremy Cowart speaks with Decrypt's Sander Lutz in Nashville ahead of the "Auras" event, in which the noted photographer live-shot 10,000 unique photo-based NFTs in less than 30 minutes. The NFTs will be released through OpenSea on May 9. Video credit: Brett Carlsen for Decrypt]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azra Games CEO on Putting Fun Before Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/03W3KZjM/azra-games-ceo-on-putting-fun-before-web3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/03W3KZjM/azra-games-ceo-on-putting-fun-before-web3"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T14:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["The Web3 interfaces cannot be on the foreground of the player's initial experience," says Azra Games CEO Mark Otero.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: Meet Immunefi's White Hat Whisperer]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/2vTAgpTC/gm-meet-immunefis-white-hat-whisperer</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/2vTAgpTC/gm-meet-immunefis-white-hat-whisperer"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T17:30:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Web3 bug bounty platform Immunefi launched two years ago, CEO and founder Mitchell Amador says the bug bounties weren't great and adoption was slow. But the tides started to turn because even if exploiting a smart contract nets a bigger payday than a bounty, it comes with a huge drawback. "There's a ton of risk when you engage in this, you know, wantonly criminal behavior and steal $200 million from someone else," he said. "There's no way someone's not going to come looking."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gala Games Co-Founder on Why Mirandus Will Not Have NPCs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5pey6epR/gala-games-co-founder-on-why-mirandus-will-not-have-npcs</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5pey6epR/gala-games-co-founder-on-why-mirandus-will-not-have-npcs"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T17:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lead Mirandus Developer and Gala Games Cofounder Michael McCarthy tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the Web3 MMORPG Mirandus and what its world will be like.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFC Lisbon Founder John Karp Heralds 'Level 2' Content for 2023 Event]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cYaJ25qv/nfc-lisbon-founder-john-karp-heralds-level-2-content-for-2023-event</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cYaJ25qv/nfc-lisbon-founder-john-karp-heralds-level-2-content-for-2023-event"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T09:44:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No panels, no problem. This year's NFC Lisbon from June 7 to June 9 boasts a variety of alternative formats, catering to a decentralized (and sometimes pseudonymous) NFT community. The event also plans to take a closer look into one of the faster-growing niches in NFTs: Photography and what founder John Karp calls "level 2" content. Not to be missed, as NFC Lisbon's media partner, Decrypt will be on-site for all three days. Come say hi!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Does Magic Eden Vet Web3 Games?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ogci0VQ6/how-does-magic-eden-vet-web3-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ogci0VQ6/how-does-magic-eden-vet-web3-games"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Magic Eden Chief Gaming Officer Chris Akhavan tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about how the NFT marketplace vets potential Web3 games for its platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interview: Kevin Rose on the 'Weird Dynamic' of Building an NFT Project]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rb2MhkWH/interview-kevin-rose-on-the-weird-dynamic-of-building-an-nft-project</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rb2MhkWH/interview-kevin-rose-on-the-weird-dynamic-of-building-an-nft-project"/>
        <updated>2023-04-30T18:49:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Proof co-founder and CEO Kevin Rose chats with Decrypt Culture Editor Andrew Hayward during NFT NYC 2023 to discuss his startup's reaffirmed focus on digital art and collectors, the challenges of building in the NFT market, and what he's learned in the last year since the buzzy Moonbirds drop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How MMORPG Mirandus is Managing its Web3 Elements]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XETXOt0k/how-mmorpg-mirandus-is-managing-its-web3-elements</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XETXOt0k/how-mmorpg-mirandus-is-managing-its-web3-elements"/>
        <updated>2023-04-29T16:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gala Games Cofounder Michael McCarthy says an "unbelievable" amount of Mirandus conversations are about its approach to Web3 and crypto transactions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Azra Games's Creative Process?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zyYFJkg0/what-is-azra-gamess-creative-process</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zyYFJkg0/what-is-azra-gamess-creative-process"/>
        <updated>2023-04-28T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azra Games CEO Mark Otero tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about Azra's creative process to game development and storytelling.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aurory Is 'Pokemon Meets The Matrix,' Says Executive Producer]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/AotiTeMz/aurory-is-pokemon-meets-the-matrix-says-executive-producer</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/AotiTeMz/aurory-is-pokemon-meets-the-matrix-says-executive-producer"/>
        <updated>2023-04-27T20:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Aurory Web3 game's Executive Producer Jonathan Campeau tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin at the 2023 Game Developer's Conference about the game and what it's like to play.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>