<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-10-21T14:11:54.765Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-10-21T14:11:54.765Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biggest Movers: SOL Rallies Towards $30, Following 33% Surge in Price]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74abe156a7</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/biggest-movers-sol-rallies-towards-30-following-33-surge-in-price/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T14:05:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana has undoubtedly been one of this week’s biggest gainers, with price rallying by as much as 33% in recent days. The move comes as the global crypto market cap remained mostly in the green to start the weekend. Chainlink was another big mover, hitting a three-week high.
 
Solana (SOL)
 
Solana (SOL) was on the cusp of entering the $30.00 level on Saturday, as bullish momentum continued to intensify.
 
SOL/USD peaked at $29.74 to start the weekend, following a low at $26.39 the day prior.
 
Today’s move saw solana climb to its strongest point since July 14, when price hit a high of $32.40.
 
 
Overall, solana has risen by as much as 33% in the past seven-day period, with today’s surge leading to yet another breakout on the relative strength index (RSI).
 
Price strength climbed beyond a ceiling at 74.00 earlier in the day, and is now at a reading of 78.90.
 
As a result of SOL now being significantly overbought, there is a chance that bears could be looming waiting to send the price lower.
 
 
Chainlink (LINK)
 
Chainlink (LINK) also surged considerably higher to start the weekend, colliding with a key resistance level in the process.
 
After trading at a low of $7.54 on Friday, LINK/USD peaked at $8.15 earlier in Saturday’s session.
 
This level has acted as a price ceiling since late July, and today’s rally is the first time LINK has hit this point since October 1.
 
 
Saturday’s move came following a breakout of a resistance level at 59.00 on the RSI, with price strength now residing at 64.71.
 
70.00 is the likely target for current bulls, and should they reach this desired level, LINK could be trading around $8.50.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
How long do you expect chainlink to extend today’s gains? Let us know your thoughts in the comments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Clients Targeted in a Withdrawal Scam: Activist Alerts on X]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18985045/FTX-Clients-Targeted-in-a-Withdrawal-Scam-Activist-Alerts-on-X</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18985045/FTX-Clients-Targeted-in-a-Withdrawal-Scam-Activist-Alerts-on-X"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T14:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FTX users have been reportedly targeted in a withdrawal scam via fake emails. The debtors received emails falsely promising instant withdrawals of assets. Sunil, an FTX activist, alerted users of the phishing scam via a post on X. In the ever-fluctuating crypto space open to potential threats...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Saylor Shares Evidence His Bitcoin (BTC) Strategy Is Good Play]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18985042/Michael-Saylor-Shares-Evidence-His-Bitcoin-BTC-Strategy-Is-Good-Play</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18985042/Michael-Saylor-Shares-Evidence-His-Bitcoin-BTC-Strategy-Is-Good-Play"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T13:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy made great bet with Bitcoin as Michael Saylor shares evidence]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Rises as SPX Dumps!!!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18985018/Bitcoin-Rises-as-SPX-Dumps</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18985018/Bitcoin-Rises-as-SPX-Dumps"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T13:54:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get your ticket to https://Unconfiscatable.com before it Sells Out!!!The Financial Summit Dubai Nov 5-10: https://TheFinancialSummit.comPromo Video: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3rATkFrSTVsTestimonial Video: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PHvhtJXkjNsFor Momentum Reversal Indicator (MRI) See...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This is Bitcoin’s next price target as correction is ruled out]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18985031/This-is-Bitcoins-next-price-target-as-correction-is-ruled-out</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18985031/This-is-Bitcoins-next-price-target-as-correction-is-ruled-out"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T13:44:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) has regained market attention again, aiming to surpass the $30,000 level amid the ongoing short-term rally. In this … Continued]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are Central Banks Losing Control? With Lyn Alden & Natalie Smolenski]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18985049/Are-Central-Banks-Losing-Control-With-Lyn-Alden-Natalie-Smolenski</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18985049/Are-Central-Banks-Losing-Control-With-Lyn-Alden-Natalie-Smolenski"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T13:41:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SHOW NOTES:https://www.whatbitcoindid.com/podcast/are-central-banks-losing-controlLyn Alden is a macroeconomist and investment strategist, and Natalie Smolenski founded and leads the Texas Bitcoin Foundation. In this interview, we discuss the impact of digital currencies on government control,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin and Ethereum’s latest ‘exodus’ has this meaning for investors]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18985012/Bitcoin-and-Ethereums-latest-exodus-has-this-meaning-for-investors</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18985012/Bitcoin-and-Ethereums-latest-exodus-has-this-meaning-for-investors"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T13:30:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a whirlwind week, Bitcoin and Ethereum said goodbye to exchanges, saw surging volumes, and presented contrasting narratives for their holders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT picks 3 low-cap cryptocurrencies for the next bull run]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18984999/ChatGPT-picks-3-low-cap-cryptocurrencies-for-the-next-bull-run</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18984999/ChatGPT-picks-3-low-cap-cryptocurrencies-for-the-next-bull-run"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T13:24:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) is outperforming both traditional finance assets and the majority of the cryptocurrency market in 2023, more specifically due … Continued]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why This Renowned Finance Author Believes Bitcoin Is Headed To $135,000]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18984968/Why-This-Renowned-Finance-Author-Believes-Bitcoin-Is-Headed-To-135000</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18984968/Why-This-Renowned-Finance-Author-Believes-Bitcoin-Is-Headed-To-135000"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T13:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto community is buzzing with excitement after a renowned finance author predicts an impending Bullish outcome for Bitcoin. The words of the respected financial figure have raised questions and discussions across the crypto community.  Related Reading: Stacks (STX) Rockets 26% Higher In A...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Technical Analysis: BTC, ETH Marginally Lower as Traders Secure This Week’s Profits]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74abe84ad3</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-ethereum-technical-analysis-btc-eth-marginally-lower-as-traders-secure-this-weeks-profits/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T12:54:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin traded around the $30,000 region to start the weekend, as markets remained optimistic that an ETF approval could be looming. This has been the topic of the week, with many speculating how high crypto markets could surge on such potential news. Ethereum slipped from Friday’s peak.
 
Bitcoin
 
Bitcoin was hovering marginally below the $30,000 level on Saturday as a section of bulls looked to seize this week’s profits.
 
Following a peak at $30,104.09 on Friday, BTC/USD has fallen to a current low of $29,816.64 during today’s session.
 
Despite the decline, the world’s largest cryptocurrency remains higher than yesterday’s low at the $29,376.12 mark.
 
 
The easing of momentum comes as the relative strength index (RSI) continued its stay in overbought territory, with a present reading of 73.17.
 
This is the highest point the index has tracked at since February, giving some traders concerns of a potential pullback.
 
Should this occur in the coming days, bears will likely look to push bitcoin to the $29,000 level, which seems to be the next visible floor.
 
 
Ethereum
 
Ethereum (ETH) also edged lower to start the weekend, however remains above the $1,600 level.
 
ETH/USD dropped to a bottom at $1,593.45 earlier in the day, however bulls then pushed price to a high of $1,610.11.
 
Overall, ethereum traders appear to still be targeting its long-term floor of $1,650, with today’s decline a possible pitstop towards this point.
 
 
Unlike bitcoin above, ETH’s price strength has yet to climb into the overbought mark, and is currently tracking at 51.76.
 
This is slightly above a ceiling at 50.00, with the next firm resistance point around the 60.00 region.
 
In the event bulls push for this point, ethereum will almost certainly be trading above $1,650.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
Do you expect ethereum to end the month above $1,650? Leave your thoughts in the comments below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Victory in SEC Lawsuit: 4 Tailwinds and 3 Headwinds for XRP price]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18984950/Ripple-Victory-in-SEC-Lawsuit-4-Tailwinds-and-3-Headwinds-for-XRP-price</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18984950/Ripple-Victory-in-SEC-Lawsuit-4-Tailwinds-and-3-Headwinds-for-XRP-price"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T12:35:43.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Giant Cryptocurrency Whale Made the Wrong Move: Suffers $5 Million Loss]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18984945/Giant-Cryptocurrency-Whale-Made-the-Wrong-Move-Suffers-5-Million-Loss</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18984945/Giant-Cryptocurrency-Whale-Made-the-Wrong-Move-Suffers-5-Million-Loss"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T12:30:06.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FinCEN issues new alert about crypto-financed terrorism]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18984928/FinCEN-issues-new-alert-about-crypto-financed-terrorism</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18984928/FinCEN-issues-new-alert-about-crypto-financed-terrorism"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T12:30:02.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Etherium Co-founder Got Sued by Early ConsenSys Staff Over Equity!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18984976/Etherium-Co-founder-Got-Sued-by-Early-ConsenSys-Staff-Over-Equity</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18984976/Etherium-Co-founder-Got-Sued-by-Early-ConsenSys-Staff-Over-Equity"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Early ConsenSys Staff Sued Etherium Co-founder In a lawsuit filed by over two dozen of early ConsenSys employees, Ethereum co-founder, Joseph Lubin, finds himself in the middle of a legal storm in the world of Cryptocurrency where trust and integrity are top priority. “ He broke his word” was...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[xDay 2023 Day 3: Interview With Bogdan-Gruia Ivan, Romanian Minister of Research, Innovation and Digitalization]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74abd43014</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/xday-2023-day-3-interview-with-bogdan-gruia-ivan-romanian-minister-of-research-innovation-and-digitalization/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T12:13:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the next three days, our team at Bitcoinist will cover xDay 2023, an event organized by MultiversX in the Palace of Parliament, Romania. Formerly known as Elrond, the project rebranded in 2022 and focused on the Metaverse, scalability, and global adoption by simplifying users’ access to crypto.
 
 
 
 
xDay 2023: “No Time To Waste In Driving Innovation”
 
On the event’s third day, we sat down with Bogdan-Gruia Ivan, Romanian Minister of Research, Innovation and Digitalization. The Minister intends to support the crypto community and builders by attracting capital into the country, giving crypto companies tax exceptions, and implementing a new legal framework to provide them with clarity and security.
 
 
The Minister sees himself as a “true believer” in blockchain, artificial intelligen…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reynaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance To Terminate EEA Visa Debit Card Service – Here’s When]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74abd4300d</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/binance-to-terminate-eea-visa-debit-card-service/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T12:13:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The world’s largest crypto exchange, Binance, has revealed plans to shut down its crypto card services in the European Economic Area (EEA). This development comes amidst the heavy regulatory pressure on the prominent exchange in several nations across the world.
 
 
Binance Visa Debit Card Issuer To Shut Down Program In December
 
According to a post on October 20 via its official blog, Binance confirmed intentions to terminate its Visa Debit Card Services in the EEA, which includes all 27 member states of the European Union alongside Iceland, Lichtenstein, and Norway. 
 
The Seychelles-based exchange had previously communicated this development to all affected customers via email. It has been revealed by multiple sources that UAB “Finansines passages ‘Contis,'” the Binance Visa Debit card…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Semilore Faleti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[xDay 2023 Day 3: Interview With Bogdan-Gruia Ivan, Romanian Minister of Research, Innovation and Digitalization]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18984897/xDay-2023-Day-3-Interview-With-Bogdan-Gruia-Ivan-Romanian-Minister-of-Research-Innovation-and-Digitalization</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18984897/xDay-2023-Day-3-Interview-With-Bogdan-Gruia-Ivan-Romanian-Minister-of-Research-Innovation-and-Digitalization"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T12:03:06.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week on Crypto Twitter: Fake ETF News Pumps Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202616</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202616/this-week-crypto-twitter-fake-etf-news-pumps-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T12:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One mistaken tweet on Monday pumped the price of Bitcoin by 10% in 24 hours—but it's not the only buzz from a busy week on Crypto Twitter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week on Crypto Twitter: Fake ETF News Pumps Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18984901/This-Week-on-Crypto-Twitter-Fake-ETF-News-Pumps-Bitcoin</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18984901/This-Week-on-Crypto-Twitter-Fake-ETF-News-Pumps-Bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T12:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance To Terminate EEA Visa Debit Card Service – Here’s When]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18984898/Binance-To-Terminate-EEA-Visa-Debit-Card-Service-Heres-When</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18984898/Binance-To-Terminate-EEA-Visa-Debit-Card-Service-Heres-When"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T12:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[#1 Most Important Crypto Tech NO ONE Knows About [Axelar Explained]]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18984906/1-Most-Important-Crypto-Tech-NO-ONE-Knows-About-Axelar-Explained</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18984906/1-Most-Important-Crypto-Tech-NO-ONE-Knows-About-Axelar-Explained"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T12:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Delists Five ‘Non-Compliant’ Coins with $60M Combined Cap]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18984889/Coinbase-Delists-Five-Non-Compliant-Coins-with-60M-Combined-Cap</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18984889/Coinbase-Delists-Five-Non-Compliant-Coins-with-60M-Combined-Cap"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T11:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase announces the delisting of five tokens due to non-compliance with listing standards. Affected tokens include CRPT, MXC, QSP, REN, and TONE, with a combined market valuation of $60 million. Coinbase reassures investors that despite delisting, their funds remain safe and accessible for...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Analyst Tone Vays Issues Bitcoin Alert, Warns Traders Not To ‘Go Crazy’ As BTC Soars by 10% This Week]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18984873/Crypto-Analyst-Tone-Vays-Issues-Bitcoin-Alert-Warns-Traders-Not-To-Go-Crazy-As-BTC-Soars-by-10-This-Week</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18984873/Crypto-Analyst-Tone-Vays-Issues-Bitcoin-Alert-Warns-Traders-Not-To-Go-Crazy-As-BTC-Soars-by-10-This-Week"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T11:45:34.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Relai Integrates Lightning With Help of Breez SDK And Greenlight]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74abd7dc0b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/relai-integrates-lightning-with-help-of-breez-sdk-and-greenlight"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T11:35:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Relai, a European non-custodial Bitcoin wallet with broker services incorporated in the app, is announcing their integration of Lightning functionality today at the Plan B conference in Lugano. Lightning support will initially roll out as a closed invite-only beta program, slowly rolling out to full public access before the end of the year Q4 2023. Starting early 2024, Relai will expand the integration to direct purchases through their broker service directly into their Lightning wallets. 
This integration comes through a partnership with Breez, one of the earliest self custodial Lightning wallets still in operation today, making use of the Breez Software Development Kit (SDK). The SDK will allow Relai to seamlessly integrate Lightning functionality for their users while relying on Blockst…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shinobi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin skeptic Charles Schwab bank deposits down 30% YoY, while BTC is up 50%]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18984860/Bitcoin-skeptic-Charles-Schwab-bank-deposits-down-30-YoY-while-BTC-is-up-50</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18984860/Bitcoin-skeptic-Charles-Schwab-bank-deposits-down-30-YoY-while-BTC-is-up-50"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T11:32:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Charles Schwab Corp. (NYSE: SCHW) is among the most affected financial firms facing a drop in customer deposits due … Continued]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is USDC and how does it work? A guide to Circle’s stablecoin]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18984853/What-is-USDC-and-how-does-it-work-A-guide-to-Circles-stablecoin</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18984853/What-is-USDC-and-how-does-it-work-A-guide-to-Circles-stablecoin"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T11:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Vs. SEC: Pro-XRP Lawyer Weighs In On Possibility Of An Immediate Appeal]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74abd1f959</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ripple-pro-xrp-lawyer-weighs-in-on-immediate-appeal/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T11:14:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an interesting turn of events, the United States Securities and Exchange Securities (SEC) voluntarily dropped its case against Ripple executives Brad Garlinghouse and Christian Larsen on Thursday, October 19. While this move implies that the trial scheduled for April 2024 will no longer hold, the financial regulator is still pursuing other parts of the case against the payment company.
 
In the wake of the surprising dismissal, there has been a wide range of reactions from the crypto world, particularly the XRP community. John Deaton, a lawyer and popular XRP supporter, is the latest to offer an insight into the ongoing legal battle between Ripple and the SEC.
 
Will The SEC Bring An Immediate Appeal Against Ripple?
 
In a post on the X (formerly Twitter) platform, Deaton shared his opi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Opeyemi Sule</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bank of Russia Predicts Digital Ruble Won’t End Other Payment Methods]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74abdd226c</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bank-of-russia-predicts-digital-ruble-wont-end-other-payment-methods/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T10:40:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Central Bank of Russia does not expect the introduction of the digital ruble to end the popularity of other non-cash and cash payment options. According to statements offered by Alla Bakina, director of the bank’s national payment system department, other non-cash payment options have reached over 80% of the total payment transactions in Russia.
Bank of Russia: Digital Ruble Won’t Sideline Other Payment Options
The Central Bank of Russia does not expect individuals and institutions to suddenly drop their payment options in favor of the Russian central bank digital currency (CBDC), the digital ruble.
According to statements made on a recent webinar by Alla Bakina, director of the bank’s national payment system department, non-cash payments using instruments different from the digital ru…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Precious Rally: Bitcoin And Gold Revisit August Peaks]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74abdf9fbc</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-and-gold-revisit-august-peaks/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T10:13:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent intraday trading session on a Friday, both Bitcoin and gold reached their highest values since August. Bitcoin surpassed $29,000, while the precious metal breached the $1,950 level. These price surges garnered attention and indicated renewed interest in both assets.
 
The simultaneous rally of Bitcoin and gold showcased the diverse investment choices available in the financial market and led to discussions about the factors driving these gains. Market dynamics were shifting, prompting analysis and speculation about the future trajectories of these assets.
 
 
At the time of writing, Bitcoin was trading at $29,706, up 1.4% in the last 24 hours, and sustaining an impressive 10.6% rally in the last week, according to data by crypto market tracker Coingecko.
 
On Friday, gold reach…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Resumes Euro Transfers Through New Fiat Partners]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74abcdfcad</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/binance-resumes-euro-transfers-through-new-fiat-partners/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T07:35:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency exchange Binance is restoring fiat services for customers using the common European currency, the euro (EUR). The coin trading giant announced that users are already migrating to the new platforms it partnered with in the wake of losing the services of Paysafe.
 
Crypto Exchange Binance Offers Users New EUR Options for Deposits and Withdrawals
 

 
Binance, the global leader in digital assets exchange, has signed agreements with new fiat partners that will process EUR payments, deposits and withdrawals for traders. These are regulated and authorized providers of fiat services, the crypto company said.
 

 
Users have already started being migrated to the new platforms, Binance revealed in a blog post published Thursday, emphasizing the importance of accessible fiat channels …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lubomir Tassev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin In Peril? Is BTC ‘Fighting Crucial Levels’ Or Winning?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74abb1c85c</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/is-bitcoin-fighting-crucial-levels-or-winning/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T05:12:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) analyst Michaël Van de Poppe suggests potential paths for the world’s leading cryptocurrency as it grapples with significant price levels. Van de Poppe, a prominent figure in the crypto trading world known for his insightful market analyses, emphasized the critical nature of BTC’s current struggle. 
 
Taking to X, the renowned social media platform, he stated that BTC is currently engaged in a battle at crucial levels, hinting at the possibility of a downward retest around $27,700. 
 
 
Concurrently, the precious metal Gold continues its ascent, adding a layer of complexity to the current market dynamics.
 
 
#Bitcoin fighting crucial levels.
 
A retest around $27,700 would still be possible, while Gold is continuing the upwards run.
 
Above $28,800 and we’ll be eager towards…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roblox to End Remote Work Policies; Metaverse and Digital Workspaces ‘Still Not There’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74abbc301b</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/roblox-to-end-remote-work-policies-metaverse-and-digital-workspaces-still-not-there/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T04:41:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roblox, a metaverse gaming company, has recently announced the end of its remote work policies, calling all but a few workers to work from its headquarters in San Mateo, California. Roblox founder and CEO David Baszucki stated that the metaverse and digital workspaces were still not as “engaging, collaborative, and productive as physical spaces.”
Roblox Recalls Its Workers to Headquarters, Ends Remote Work Policies
Roblox, a gaming and metaverse company, has recently recalled its workers, requesting they work from its headquarters. The company, which had turned into a remote workforce in March 2020 amid the coronavirus pandemic, has required all but a few of its workers to be present in office on a three-day schedule (Tues.-Thurs.) or take a severance package.
David Baszucki, founder and C…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Exchange Coinbase Chooses Ireland as EU MiCA Hub]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74aba7e830</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/crypto-exchange-coinbase-chooses-ireland-as-eu-mica-hub/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T02:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase has selected Ireland as the main regulatory hub for its operations across the European Union. The company hopes to obtain a license in Ireland that will allow it to provide services in EU member states under the pan-European Markets in Crypto Assets (MiCA) law.
 
Coinbase Bets on EU Growth Amid Regulatory Uncertainty and Pressure in US
 
America’s leading crypto exchange, Coinbase, announced it has chosen Ireland as its “MiCA hub” in the European Union. The trading platform said the decision is part of the realization of the second phase of its “Go Broad, Go Deep” strategy for international expansion.
 
Coinbase currently holds an e-money institution license and a virtual asset service provider (VASP) registration in Ireland as well as licenses and reg…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lubomir Tassev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Is on a Winning Streak (but the Game Isn't Yet Won)]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74abacaafe</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/10/20/ripple-is-on-a-winning-streak-but-the-game-isnt-yet-won/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T00:53:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC threw out a lawsuit against Ripple executives Brad Garlinghouse and Chris Larson over what it had claimed was an “unregistered” offering of XRP tokens.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Kuhn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MultiversX's EGLD Token Rallies on Partnership With Google Cloud]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74abacaaf5</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/10/20/multiversxs-egld-token-rallies-on-partnership-with-google-cloud/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T00:53:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EGLD ticked up nearly 10% to just over $26 during European morning hours on Friday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Whale Moving Large Stash Of Ethereum To Kraken, Prices Bullish And Unmoved]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74abafe1c8</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/whale-moving-ethereum-kraken-prices-unmoved/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T00:10:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data from Lookonchain, a blockchain analytics platform, on October 20, shows that one Ethereum (ETH) whale is actively moving coins to Kraken, a crypto exchange, and appears to be selling. The unidentified whale deposited 35,176 ETH, worth over $56.5 million when writing, and withdrew $10 million in USDT hours later. USDT is the world’s most liquid stablecoin, tracking the value of the USD. 
 
Ethereum Whale Selling On Kraken
 
Still, it is not immediately clear whether the whale ended up selling the whole stash and only choosing to withdraw $10 million. What’s evident is that the unknown whale has been actively accumulating Ethereum for some years before deciding to take profit.
 
 
Looking at market trends, the whale appears to be taking profit and exiting. Often, when coins are moved to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dalmas Ngetich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Americans Have Their Say in Constitution for AI]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74aba876af</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/americans-have-their-say-in-constitution-for-ai/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T00:02:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic has acquired the views of a group of American citizens on the fundamental principles that should govern artificial intelligence (AI). The gathered opinions have formed the basis of a “constitution for AI” as part of an attempt to explore how democratic processes can influence the technology’s development.
 
Anthropic Prepares Constitution for AI Using Public Input
 
AI startup Anthropic, the creator of the Claude chatbot, has secured the help of around 1,000 Americans to draft a constitution for an AI system. The initiative is a joint effort with the Collective Intelligence Project (CIP), a non-profit organization that seeks to “direct technological development towards the collective good.”
 
Claude currently relies on a constitution curated by Anthropic employees using Constitut…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lubomir Tassev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thor Technologies Faces Legal Consequences In SEC’s $2.6 Million Crypto Sale Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74ab9512bd</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/thor-technologies-sec-2-6-million-crypto-lawsuit/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T23:08:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a win against the crypto industry, the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has obtained a default judgment against Thor Technologies and its founder David Chin. 
 
According to court documents, Thor Technologies and Chin were found guilty of conducting an unregistered offering of crypto asset securities amounting to $2.6 million. 
 
SEC Prevails In Unregistered Crypto Offering Lawsuit
 
The judgment was issued by a San Francisco district court, which permanently restrains and enjoins the defendants from violating Sections 5(a) and 5(c) of the Securities Act of 1933. 
 
These sections pertain to the sale and offering of what the SEC denominates as “crypto securities” without proper registration or exemption.
 
 
In the legal context, a default judgment is a judgment entered by a …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Is Like a Grocery Store Selling Oranges and SEC Should Leave It Alone, Says Crypto Lobby Group]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202626</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202626/binance-grocery-store-oranges-sec-crypto-lobby-group"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T22:10:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In its fight against Binance, "the SEC is suing the equivalent of a grocery store selling oranges and other fruit," says US Chamber of Digital Commerce in an amicus brief.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance to Sunset Visa Crypto Card as 2023 Sees Decline in Digital Debit Cards]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74ab925c4e</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/binance-to-sunset-visa-crypto-card-as-2023-sees-decline-in-digital-debit-cards/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T22:09:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several reports have revealed that Binance, which is recognized as the leading crypto exchange by trading volume, intends to discontinue its Visa crypto card on December 20, 2023. The enterprise emphasized that only a “small number of Binance users” would be affected by this development.
 
Binance to Discontinue Visa Offering by Year’s End
 
In 2023, crypto debit cards have been falling out of favor rapidly, triggered in part by a series of bankruptcies that ignited a crypto bear market. Back in March, Bitpay in the U.S. phased out its prepaid Mastercard program, although it assured users of a renewed card service on the horizon. However, this week, holders of the Binance Visa card were informed via email that the card would cease to be functional by the close of the year.
 
The email communicated that the Binance Visa card would become non-operational post-December 20, 2023. The Binance Visa, which was available to users in Europe, was utilized by individuals across various countries including Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, France, the Czech Republic, and Finland, among others. Binance has suggested that cardholders can switch to Binance Pay for their shopping needs, provided the service is accessible in their region.
 
The email also clarified that, despite the changes, Binance accounts would remain unaffected and continue to operate as usual. A lively discussion about the Binance Visa card issue has taken place on social media. “Binance shutting down their Visa card,” one person said. “The [Gnosis Pay] card cannot come soon enough! wen shipping?” Another user expressed indifference towards the shutdown, expressing a preference for the Crypto.com Visa card instead.
 
What do you think about Binance shutting down its Visa service? Share your thoughts and opinions about this subject in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Billion-Dollar Battle: Ethereum Co-Founder Hit With Lawsuit Over ConsenSys Shares]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74ab928a7b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-co-founder-hit-with-lawsuit-over-consensys/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T22:08:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent turn of events, Ethereum’s co-founder, Joseph Lubin, is under legal scrutiny over alleged issues in equity promises related to his blockchain technology company, ConsenSys.
 
ConsenSys, recently appraised at roughly $7 billion, is at the center of these allegations. The company, which has been instrumental in numerous blockchain innovations, is now caught in a maelstrom of accusations, primarily revolving around equity commitments and asset transfers.
 
 
Accusations And Alleged Equity Violations
 
A group of over twenty former employees has lodged a lawsuit against Lubin, suggesting that the Ethereum co-founder orchestrated a complex asset transfer within the holding structure of ConsenSys. 
 
The group particularly claimed that valuable assets, including the renowned web3 wal…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FinCEN Proposes Insane Special Measures]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74ab92b7ce</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/legal/fincen-proposes-insane-special-measures"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T22:06:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday’s FinCEN rule proposal is incredibly overbroad, comprehensive, and perfectly designed to allow arbitrary information collection at any scope they choose to enforce. It truly is a mind-blowingly large grab attempt at private information of anyone they can get their hands on. They want all regulated entities — VASPs, banks, financial institutions or entities like casinos, etc. — to by default submit reports of any transactions interacting with mixing within 30 days of noticing the relevant transaction and its association to mixing activity. Currently, most exchanges and businesses keep these records anyway, but they do not by default send copies of them to regulators unless deeper inspection actually merits a reason to do so. FinCEN wants that to change.
To really get a sense for t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shinobi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitch Will Let Users Stream Across Platforms—But They Better Act Right]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202617</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202617/twitch-let-users-stream-across-platforms-they-better-act-right"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T22:04:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Popular video game streaming site Twitch introduces big changes at TwitchCon 2023 as rivals new and old start to pose serious competition.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google and BlackRock Considered Investing in FTX as It Crumbled]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202583</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202583/google-blackrock-considered-investing-ftx-before-bankruptcy"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T20:12:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The exchange wanted to tap big names for its C1 funding, but FTX buckled before it closed the round.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI and Bitcoin Mining Meet in New Texas Data Center]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202590</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202590/ai-and-bitcoin-mining-meet-in-new-texas-data-center"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T20:09:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite the expansion, APLD shares fell 5.3% on Friday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Raini: The Lords of Light Review—SBF, CZ, and Satoshi Battle in This Crypto Card Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202585</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202585/raini-lords-light-review-sbf-cz-satoshi-battle-crypto-card-game"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T19:36:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[REVIEW: Putting an NFT spin on the Hearthstone formula, Raini: The Lords of Light goes even further with crypto memes and compelling card mechanics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Game Review: 'Raini: The Lords of Light' Brands Itself With Memes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/32YyJHCJ/game-review-raini-the-lords-of-light-brands-itself-with-memes</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/32YyJHCJ/game-review-raini-the-lords-of-light-brands-itself-with-memes"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T19:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Raini: Lords of Light is an NFT-optional card game bursting with crypto memes. From SBF to CZ and Elon, this free-to-play game has some truly wild animations. Decrypt contributor Ryan S. Gladwin shares his honest thoughts on the game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s Going On With Crypto Behemoth Digital Currency Group?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202551</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202551/whats-going-on-with-crypto-behemoth-digital-currency-group"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T18:31:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most important companies in the space has been steeped in legal woes. Here’s how it got to this point.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Model Transparency Is Getting Worse, Researchers Warn]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202555</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202555/ai-model-transparency-getting-worse-stanford-researchers"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T17:58:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Foundation models promise a new era in AI, but Stanford University researchers have flagged that they're becoming less transparent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Solana Explodes 25%, Bitcoin Reclaims $30K on ETF Hopes and Ripple Wins]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202554</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202554/week-in-coins-solana-bitcoin-xrp-ripple"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T16:59:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, usually the market pace-setter, was far outpaced by Solana, Bitcoin Cash and XRP.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Habbo Game Plans to Keep Using NFTs Without Uttering Dirty Crypto 'Jargon']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202553</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202553/habbo-game-keep-using-nfts-without-uttering-dirty-crypto-jargon"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T16:47:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The classic social web game will change the way it conveys its NFT push, but it’s still moving forward with the blockchain initiative.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vitalik's Biggest Worries? Crypto Stagnating and AI Risks, Says Ethereum Co-Founder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202548</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202548/vitaliks-biggest-worries-crypto-stagnating-ai-risks-says-ethereum-co-founder"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T15:07:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The co-founder believes that Ethereum can provide a potential solution to address AI-related challenges, such as digital impersonation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nintendo Switch 2 Preview: Everything You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197793</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197793/nintendo-switch-2-rumors-leaks-latest-news"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T14:47:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATE: How powerful will the Switch 2 be? The latest leaks point to some serious capabilities. Here's everything we know so far.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angry Birds, 'The Voice', Warner Music Artists to Launch Avatar Skins via Ready Player Me]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202484</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202484/angry-birds-voice-warner-music-artists-launch-avatar-skins-ready-player-me"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T13:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Multiplatform avatar startup Ready Player Me is unleashing a brand barrage, with licensed skins from major entertainment partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Game Upland Raises $7 Million Ahead of Ethereum Token Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202498</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202498/crypto-game-upland-raises-7-million-ahead-ethereum-token-launch"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T12:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The EOS-based metaverse game Upland expands its Series A raise, with plans to bridge its Spark utility token to Ethereum as Sparklet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maker Annualized Revenue Soars Past $200M to New All-Time High]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202515</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202515/maker-annualized-revenue-soars-past-200m-to-new-all-time-high"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T11:30:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The stablecoin issuer’s revenue is up on high U.S. treasury yields and increased yields for DAI holders through Gnosis chain integration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Hits $30,000 Amid Spot ETF Amendments From BlackRock, Fidelity]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202507</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202507/bitcoin-spot-etf-amendments-blackrock-fidelity"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T10:54:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With industry talking heads more bullish than ever of an ETF approval, Bitcoin has jumped 5% overnight, briefly hitting $30,000.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Soars 12% Overnight as Crypto Market Recoups $43 Billion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202505</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202505/solana-soars-overnight-crypto-market-recoups-billion"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T09:55:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the crypto market rebounds, the price of Solana's native token SOL has seen its price hit a 3-month high above $26.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Did an AI Hallucination Help Convict Fugees Rapper Pras?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202461</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202461/did-ai-hallucination-help-convict-fugees-rapper-pras"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T00:15:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pras Michel's new counsel filed for a fresh trial, claiming the AI tool and his previous legal team were ineffective in the Fugees star's conspiracy case.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoins on Bitcoin? Lightning Labs Aims to 'Bitcoinize the Dollar']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202474</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202474/stablecoins-bitcoin-lightning-labs-aims-bitcoinize-dollar"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T22:28:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lightning Labs launches Taproot Assets, enabling stablecoins and other assets to be tokenized on top of Bitcoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Dismisses Lawsuit Against Ripple Execs in 'Stunning Capitulation']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202471</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202471/sec-dismisses-lawsuit-against-ripple-execs-stunning-capitulation"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T21:51:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brad Garlinghouse and Chris Larsen are no longer facing charges from the U.S. regulator, which is still pursuing Ripple over securities violations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Human vs. AI-Generated Music: Indistinguishable, or Uncanny Valley?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202442</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/human-vs-ai-generated-music-indistinguishable-or-uncanny-valley"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T20:19:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some studies suggest that many listeners are already unable to tell the difference between music made by computers and music composed by humans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Reiff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Seeks to Label Crypto Mixers as National Security Threats Amid Money Laundering Concerns]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202428</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202428/us-seeks-label-crypto-mixers-national-security-threat"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T19:58:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The move comes amid an escalating narrative in D.C. that crypto was disproportionately responsible for triggering the escalating crisis in Israel and Palestine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SBF Asked Former FTX Lawyer to Find 'Legal Justifications' for Missing Customer Funds]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202417</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202417/sbf-asked-former-ftx-lawyer-for-legal-justifications-for-missing-funds"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T19:56:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Can Sun structured billions of dollars in personal loans to FTX insiders, but said he had "no idea that customer funds were being misused."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is a Bitcoin ETF, and Why Does Everyone from Blackrock to Grayscale Want One?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=12006</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-bitcoin-etf-explained-guide-learn-easy"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T19:54:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Bitcoin ETF creates a simple, legally compliant way to trade the price of Bitcoin, accessible on markets that investors are already familiar with.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Stevens,Ki Chong Tran,Daniel Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Art Blocks Marfa Weekend Recap]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/QaTBP6eO/art-blocks-marfa-weekend-recap</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/QaTBP6eO/art-blocks-marfa-weekend-recap"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T19:19:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Relive the Art Blocks Marfa Weekend 2023 event with this highlights video, produced by Vincent Roazzi Jr. for Decrypt Studios in partnership with Art Blocks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF Could Be Approved in Time for Christmas, Says JP Morgan]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202416</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202416/bitcoin-etf-could-be-approved-in-time-for-christmas-says-jp-morgan"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T19:17:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A report from the Wall Street bank estimates that the SEC will green light a Bitcoin ETF before January 10, 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Largest Broker in Brazil XP Shutters Its XTAGE Crypto Service]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202411</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202411/brazil-broker-xp-shutters-xtage-crypto-service"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T18:55:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Customers have until Dec. 15 to sell their digital assets, at which point XP will sell them and deposit the proceeds in a Banco XP account.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the Fashion Industry Uses Generative AI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202414</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/how-the-fashion-industry-uses-generative-ai-2"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T17:41:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Generative artificial intelligence (AI) has numerous applications in the world of fashion, including the creation of new designs, as a way of tailoring marketing campaigns, and as a tool to help personalize a customer’s shopping experience, among others.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Reiff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Horror Game 'The Evil Within' Is Free on PC—Here's How to Claim]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202402</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202402/horror-game-evil-within-free-pc-heres-how-claim"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T16:49:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The eerie survival horror game from the creator of Resident Evil is free right now, with the sequel available free come next week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Startup Ryder Raises $1.2 Million to Build Wallets With No Seed Phrases]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202323</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202323/ryder-raises-1-million-for-seed-phraseless-hardware-crypto-wallet"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T16:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["People just don’t like seed phrases,” said Ryder CEO Louise Ivan, who added that he considers Ledger the company's biggest competitor.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Clearinghouse DTCC Snaps Up Blockchain Startup Securrency]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202383</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202383/clearinghouse-dtcc-acquires-blockchain-startup-securrency"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T15:47:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The deal will see Securrency become a fully-owned subsidiary of DTCC and operate under the name DTCC Digital Assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock Amends Bitcoin ETF Prospectus, Acknowledges Fierce Competition]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202385</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202385/blackrock-amends-bitcoin-etf-acknowledges-fierce-competition"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T15:04:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock is the third company to make changes to its spot Bitcoin ETF filing with the SEC this past week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon Paves Way for Governance 2.0 with Introduction of Protocol Council]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202342</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202342/polygon-paves-way-for-governance-2-0-with-introduction-of-protocol-council"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T13:56:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon takes another step towards decentralized governance, unveiling a new proposal to form a new 13-person protocol council.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pantera Capital Leads $22 Million Investment in Derivatives Exchange SynFutures]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202334</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202334/pantera-capital-leads-22-million-investment-derivatives-exchange-synfutures"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T13:01:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SynFutures' innovative V3 release is aimed at ramping up DeFi's derivatives infrastructure and accommodating institutional players.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is MiCA? What the EU Crypto Governing Framework Means for You]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149193</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-mica-what-the-eu-crypto-governing-framework-means-for-you"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T12:39:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MiCA does not cover most NFTs (except fractionalized NFTs and NFTs released as collections). Similarly, it does not cover DeFi apps that exist without an intermediary.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Reiff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NYAG Sues Genesis, Gemini, DCG for Defrauding Crypto Investors of $1 Billion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202343</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202343/nyag-charges-genesis-gemini-dcg-defrauding-232000-investors"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T12:21:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["It was middle-class investors who suffered," said NYAG Letitia James of the charges that the three entities defrauded 232,000 investors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aptos Hit With 5-Hour Outage on Blockchain's First Birthday]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202340</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202340/aptos-hit-5-hour-outage-blockchains-first-birthday"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T09:32:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The speedy layer-1 network is back up and running but the event raised concerns about Aptos’ performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘MiCA Would Have a Different Scope If Negotiated Today’ Says EU Financial Watchdog]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202315</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202315/mica-would-have-a-different-scope-if-negotiated-today-says-eu-financial-watchdog"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T09:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto assets should not be considered “safe” by investors because of MiCA, ESMA said, adding that the rules don't go into effect until 2025.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Phantom Galaxies: A Look Inside the Mech Shooter NFT Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QI1uDwQv/phantom-galaxies-a-look-inside-the-mech-shooter-nft-game</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QI1uDwQv/phantom-galaxies-a-look-inside-the-mech-shooter-nft-game"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T21:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animoca Brands and game studio Blowfish are developing Phantom Galaxies, an upcoming sci-fi mech shooter game inspired by mech battlers like Transformers. Decrypt's Kate Irwin asks Blowfish Studios Cofounder and Managing Director Ben Lee about what it's like to play the game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Clip: DeepMedia's DeepID Deepfake Detection Tool at Work]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/m4Vy4vhC/clip-deepmedias-deepid-deepfake-detection-tool-at-work</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/m4Vy4vhC/clip-deepmedias-deepid-deepfake-detection-tool-at-work"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T16:48:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A clip showcasing how DeepMedia's DeepID deepfake detection tool works. Courtesy: DeepMedia]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentraland AI World Fair Trailer]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/3tUb56Fv/decentraland-ai-world-fair-trailer</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/3tUb56Fv/decentraland-ai-world-fair-trailer"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A trailer for the AI World Fair event in metaverse game Decentraland, taking place from October 25-27. Courtesy: Decentraland.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BackTheBunny - Money, Conspiracy, Milady]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BRoKZzer/backthebunny-money-conspiracy-milady</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BRoKZzer/backthebunny-money-conspiracy-milady"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T19:48:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our host Reza Jafery sits down with BackTheBunny to dive deep into money, the fight against crypto that we're witnessing in real-time, and milady culture. 

Our Host: https://twitter.com/rezajafery
Our Guest: https://twitter.com/BackTheBunny

Our Sponsors
https://decrypt.co/1000x]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['A Grand Experiment': Shrapnel Studio Head Don Norbury Talks Game Economics]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Z2OMMsC5/a-grand-experiment-shrapnel-studio-head-don-norbury-talks-game-economics</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Z2OMMsC5/a-grand-experiment-shrapnel-studio-head-don-norbury-talks-game-economics"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T17:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How much of Shrapnel's in-game items are tradeable NFTs? Don Norbury, Studio Head at Shrapnel and CTO at game studio NEON, tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about Shrapnel's approach to game economics, including different game pricing models and how NFT game economies create different challenges for developers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trezor Safe 3 and Trezor Keep Metal Unboxing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/IjqnO9pR/trezor-safe-3-and-trezor-keep-metal-unboxing</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/IjqnO9pR/trezor-safe-3-and-trezor-keep-metal-unboxing"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T14:45:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trezor has launched the Safe 3, a hardware wallet aimed at "new entrants to crypto," alongside the new Keep Metal recovery seed storage device. We take a first look at what comes in the box.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why AI Arena is Building on Arbitrum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Gl80TQOm/why-ai-arena-is-building-on-arbitrum</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Gl80TQOm/why-ai-arena-is-building-on-arbitrum"/>
        <updated>2023-10-12T14:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI Arena CEO Brandon Da Silva and COO Wei Xie discuss the challenges that come with building on Ethereum, ETH sidechains, and layer-two blockchains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pet3rPan_ on venture DAOs and blockchain games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DawNLI3O/pet3rpan-on-venture-daos-and-blockchain-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DawNLI3O/pet3rpan-on-venture-daos-and-blockchain-games"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T18:24:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the 4th episode of this time will be different.

Our guest for today's episode is Pet3rpan_ from Metacartel, 1kx, HydraVentures, and more!

https://twitter.com/pet3rpan_

This Time Will Be Different is sponsored by 1000x
https://decrypt.co/1000x]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Shrapnel's Marketplace, New Map, and 'AI Director' Feature]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/F5RQCmvH/inside-shrapnels-marketplace-new-map-and-ai-director-feature</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/F5RQCmvH/inside-shrapnels-marketplace-new-map-and-ai-director-feature"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T16:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin chats with Shrapnel's Head of Studio Don Norbury to get the latest updates on how the NFT-powered first-person sci-fi extraction shooter's development is progressing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Art of the Times': Art Blocks Founder Erick Calderon on the State of Generative Art]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zSjfRrl5/art-of-the-times-art-blocks-founder-erick-calderon-on-the-state-of-generative-art</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zSjfRrl5/art-of-the-times-art-blocks-founder-erick-calderon-on-the-state-of-generative-art"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T18:10:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Art Blocks founder and CEO Erick Calderon sat down with Sander Lutz, lead culture reporter at Decrypt's SCENE, at Art Blocks Marfa Weekend 2023. They discuss the evolution of the company and the generative art world, along with what draws art enthusiasts to be an active part of the community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt Learn: Digital Ownership Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/6udZCotB/decrypt-learn-digital-ownership-explained</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/6udZCotB/decrypt-learn-digital-ownership-explained"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T10:57:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most powerful aspects of blockchain technology is its ability to provide us genuine ownership of our digital assets. This is called digital ownership. In this video, we’ll deep dive into digital ownership, why it matters, and how web3 makes owning digital assets like our social networks, music libraries, personal data, and beyond possible. Author: Clarissa Watson, Senior Writer at Consensys.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Martin Shkreli on E/ACC and SBF in Prison]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QONaWXKZ/martin-shkreli-on-e-acc-and-sbf-in-prison</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QONaWXKZ/martin-shkreli-on-e-acc-and-sbf-in-prison"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T22:03:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reza Jafery and Martin Shkreli sit down for a casual conversation about the growing movement that is E/ACC, what songs they could recite at gunpoint, and whether or not SBF will thrive or just survive during his time in prison.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Can AI Do in Gaming?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JKuqCMao/what-can-ai-do-in-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JKuqCMao/what-can-ai-do-in-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T17:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI Arena CEO Brandon Da Silva and COO Wei Xie discuss how artificial intelligence can shape the video game experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['There Are No Real Standards': Ready Player Me CEO Timmu Tõke on Building for an Open Gaming Ecosystem]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TH3KEAI0/there-are-no-real-standards-ready-player-me-ceo-timmu-tke-on-building-for-an-open-gaming-ecosystem</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TH3KEAI0/there-are-no-real-standards-ready-player-me-ceo-timmu-tke-on-building-for-an-open-gaming-ecosystem"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T17:29:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Timmu Tõke, co-founder and CEO of Ready Player Me, joins Decrypt contributor Ryan Gladwin to discuss the startup's approach to powering avatars that are interoperable across games and metaverse platforms—and what's needed to convince the industry to adopt standards and open up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain Is 'Only Way' Forward for Gaming, Says Shrapnel Studio Head]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/fhoy7Z8f/blockchain-is-only-way-forward-for-gaming-says-shrapnel-studio-head</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/fhoy7Z8f/blockchain-is-only-way-forward-for-gaming-says-shrapnel-studio-head"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T21:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shrapnel Studio Head Don Norbury tells Kate Irwin the reasons why the upcoming first-person shooter game will offer a wide range of NFTs. He also reveals team-based gameplay plans and shares how game maps have already changed this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Social Media Sentiment Is Key to Crypto Price Discovery]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/981TBppa/social-media-sentiment-is-key-to-crypto-price-discovery</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/981TBppa/social-media-sentiment-is-key-to-crypto-price-discovery"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T23:47:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sacha Ghebali, Director of Strategy and Business Development at The TIE, says social media sentiment remains a key factor in price movements for major cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin and Ethereum. However, he notes that sentiment has turned more negative lately amid regulatory uncertainty. Ghebali believes events like the Ripple lawsuit ruling significantly impacted sentiment and prices. André Beganski interviewed him at Messari Mainnet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[500Altcoins discusses DeFi Summer and the Dubai Crypto Scene - This Time Will Be Different - Episode 2]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cI7p8AK3/500altcoins-discusses-defi-summer-and-the-dubai-crypto-scene-this-time-will-be-different-episode-2</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cI7p8AK3/500altcoins-discusses-defi-summer-and-the-dubai-crypto-scene-this-time-will-be-different-episode-2"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our host Reza Jafery is joined by Gareth Fenney aka 500Altcoins. They discuss the glory days of DeFi Summer and whether or not its a smart move for builders in the crypto space to relocate to Dubai.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralize Derivatives Trading with Custom Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/lfmwAjB9/decentralize-derivatives-trading-with-custom-blockchain</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/lfmwAjB9/decentralize-derivatives-trading-with-custom-blockchain"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T10:37:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Gogel of dYdX discusses how the decentralized exchange is building a custom blockchain to fully decentralize derivatives trading. He explained how the new dYdX chain will allow validators to run order books in memory, enabling decentralized order matching at scale. This shift aims to increase security and transparency for traders while maintaining the performance of centralized exchanges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>