<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-10-10T18:25:26.147Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-10-10T18:25:26.147Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Daily: Trump-linked DeFi project looks to raise $300 million, Uniswap Labs unveils Unichain Layer 2 and more]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19991292/The-Daily-Trump-linked-DeFi-project-looks-to-raise-300-million-Uniswap-Labs-unveils-Unichain-Layer-2-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19991292/The-Daily-Trump-linked-DeFi-project-looks-to-raise-300-million-Uniswap-Labs-unveils-Unichain-Layer-2-and-more"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T18:19:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The following article is adapted from The Block’s newsletter, The Daily, which comes out on weekday afternoons.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Drops Below $60,000 – What’s the Reason Behind the Decline?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19991290/Bitcoin-Drops-Below-60000-Whats-the-Reason-Behind-the-Decline</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19991290/Bitcoin-Drops-Below-60000-Whats-the-Reason-Behind-the-Decline"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T18:17:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, the leading cryptocurrency, failed to withhold the $60,000 support level and experienced a notable decline.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ZachXBT exposes scammer Faris Ali who stole $4.3m in crypto from a Twitter user]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19991278/ZachXBT-exposes-scammer-Faris-Ali-who-stole-43m-in-crypto-from-a-Twitter-user</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19991278/ZachXBT-exposes-scammer-Faris-Ali-who-stole-43m-in-crypto-from-a-Twitter-user"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T18:08:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto investigator ZachXBT is at it again. This time, he’s gone after a UK scammer named Faris Ali, also known as Zay or Tommy, for his alleged involvement in a home invasion that led to a $4.3 million crypto theft. The robbery happened in June when the victim, after suffering a crypto data...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Buy Bitcoin With Cash in 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19991275/How-to-Buy-Bitcoin-With-Cash-in-2024</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19991275/How-to-Buy-Bitcoin-With-Cash-in-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T18:07:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This guide explains how to buy Bitcoin with cash in 2024, outlining the steps and options available for transactions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Are 20 Crypto Assets With the ‘Best Chance’ of Rallying Based on Sentiment, According to Analytics Firm]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19991276/Here-Are-20-Crypto-Assets-With-the-Best-Chance-of-Rallying-Based-on-Sentiment-According-to-Analytics-Firm</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19991276/Here-Are-20-Crypto-Assets-With-the-Best-Chance-of-Rallying-Based-on-Sentiment-According-to-Analytics-Firm"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T18:05:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto analytics platform Santiment is naming 20 digital assets that may soon rally based upon one key metric. In a new thread on the social media platform X, the firm says 20 digital assets are standing out for the amount of negative public sentiment they are receiving on social media...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lombard Vault Shatters $100M Milestone, Triples Liquidity in Just a Month]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19991263/Lombard-Vault-Shatters-100M-Milestone-Triples-Liquidity-in-Just-a-Month</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19991263/Lombard-Vault-Shatters-100M-Milestone-Triples-Liquidity-in-Just-a-Month"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T18:01:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR Lombard Vault has nearly tripled its total value locked (TVL), reaching $114.5 million in less than a month since its launch. The platform allows users to deposit Wrapped Bitcoin (WBTC), LBTC, and other digital assets, offering an annual percentage yield (APY) exceeding 11%. On October 10,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Launches Custody Service to Compete in Growing Crypto Market]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19991256/Ripple-Launches-Custody-Service-to-Compete-in-Growing-Crypto-Market</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19991256/Ripple-Launches-Custody-Service-to-Compete-in-Growing-Crypto-Market"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T18:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple, based in San Francisco, has launched a crypto custody service for banks and fintech firms, coinciding with increased Federal Reserve scrutiny on traditional banks offering crypto custodial solutions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram wallet app enables law enforcement evidence collection]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19991248/Telegram-wallet-app-enables-law-enforcement-evidence-collection</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19991248/Telegram-wallet-app-enables-law-enforcement-evidence-collection"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T17:59:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Wallet app on Telegram now supports law enforcement evidence collection, according to its updated FAQ page. This page directs law enforcement agencies to submit requests via a designated email address, stating: “Wallet will carefully review each law enforcement request and cooperate on a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KYC: Ensuring Compliance and Security in Crypto Exchanges]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19991242/KYC-Ensuring-Compliance-and-Security-in-Crypto-Exchanges</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19991242/KYC-Ensuring-Compliance-and-Security-in-Crypto-Exchanges"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T17:57:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KYC, or Know Your Customer, is a regulatory process that crypto exchanges use to verify user identities to prevent fraud and comply with laws.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance’s CZ Set To Leave US: Insights Into His Upcoming Plans For October 30]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7443cee124</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/binances-cz-set-to-leave-us-insights-upcoming-plan/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T17:55:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Changpeng Zhao, widely known as “CZ,” the former CEO and co-founder of Binance, has recently suggested he may leave the United States after completing his four-month prison sentence stemming from a settlement with US authorities. Zhao’s release from a US correctional facility occurred on September 27, just two days earlier than initially expected.
 
CZ Announces Dubai Trip
 
In November 2023, Zhao pleaded guilty to failing to implement US anti-money laundering (AML) programs while leading Binance. As part of a corporate settlement, Binance had to pay $4.3 billion and Zhao personally faced a $50 million fine.
 
 
Following the settlement, a court order imposed strict travel restrictions on Zhao, revoking his passport and restricting his ability to travel outside the US, despite the executiv…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano Sets Legal Precedent With Enforceable Smart Contract In Argentina]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7443cee120</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/cardano-enforceable-smart-contract-argentina/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T17:55:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano has marked a significant legal milestone in Argentina with the signing of what is described as the first legally and judicially enforceable contract on the ADA blockchain network, fully compliant with Argentine law. On October 8, Cardano ambassador and Interim Constitutional Committee (ICC) member Mauro Andreoli announced via X (formerly Twitter) that he and fellow ADA ambassador and Token Allies co-founder Lucas Macchiavelli have formalized a loan agreement using the Cardano network.
 
“We did it, we have just signed the first legally and judicially enforceable contract on the Cardano network, in full compliance with the laws of the Argentine Republic. What does this mean? It means that, thanks to the legal framework provided and the process carried out, any breach can be enforced…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Korean Crypto Exchange Upbit Faces Monopoly Investigation]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19991277/South-Korean-Crypto-Exchange-Upbit-Faces-Monopoly-Investigation</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19991277/South-Korean-Crypto-Exchange-Upbit-Faces-Monopoly-Investigation"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T17:50:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Concerned about Upbit's market domination, the Financial Services Commission (FSC) of South Korea announced plans to look into the country's biggest cryptocurrency exchange on October 10.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitget tightens listing conditions following BGB fiasco and market manipulation accusations]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19991234/Bitget-tightens-listing-conditions-following-BGB-fiasco-and-market-manipulation-accusations</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19991234/Bitget-tightens-listing-conditions-following-BGB-fiasco-and-market-manipulation-accusations"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T17:47:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitget is raising the stakes. The exchange is introducing new, stricter conditions for listing tokens after the recent disaster with its native token BGB and allegations of market manipulation. Every blockchain project that wants to get listed now has to go through a comprehensive legal review....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zero Fee Crypto Exchanges to Buy Cryptos 2024: Top Platforms for Low Cost Trading]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19991213/Zero-Fee-Crypto-Exchanges-to-Buy-Cryptos-2024-Top-Platforms-for-Low-Cost-Trading</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19991213/Zero-Fee-Crypto-Exchanges-to-Buy-Cryptos-2024-Top-Platforms-for-Low-Cost-Trading"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T17:43:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore the best zero-fee crypto exchanges in 2024, highlighting platforms that allow users to buy cryptocurrencies without transaction fees.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Is Winning And We’re Closer Than Ever to Freeing Ross: NIKOLAUS]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19991200/Trump-Is-Winning-And-Were-Closer-Than-Ever-to-Freeing-Ross-NIKOLAUS</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19991200/Trump-Is-Winning-And-Were-Closer-Than-Ever-to-Freeing-Ross-NIKOLAUS"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T17:38:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We still have to fight like we’re 13% down.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the FBI Used a Crypto Token to Bust a Major Fraud Scheme]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19991193/How-the-FBI-Used-a-Crypto-Token-to-Bust-a-Major-Fraud-Scheme</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19991193/How-the-FBI-Used-a-Crypto-Token-to-Bust-a-Major-Fraud-Scheme"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T17:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The agency staged an undercover operation in collaboration with other authorities to expose market manipulation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Justin Sun is now prime minister of Liberland, an entirely made-up country]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19991195/Justin-Sun-is-now-prime-minister-of-Liberland-an-entirely-made-up-country</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19991195/Justin-Sun-is-now-prime-minister-of-Liberland-an-entirely-made-up-country"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T17:33:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Liberland announced Sun’s new status on Tuesday after an ‘entirely algorithmic blockchain-based election system’ was used to elect him.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC sues Cumberland, calls Solana and Polygon securities]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19991194/SEC-sues-Cumberland-calls-Solana-and-Polygon-securities</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19991194/SEC-sues-Cumberland-calls-Solana-and-Polygon-securities"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T17:33:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SEC announced on Thursday, October 10th that it is charging Cumberland DRW with different security charges. One of the charges states that the crypto trading firm is an unregistered dealer while handling more than $2 billion in crypto assets. Furthermore the complaint claims that Cumberland has...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scroll Integrates Chainlink CCIP to Boost Cross-Chain Interoperability]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19991186/Scroll-Integrates-Chainlink-CCIP-to-Boost-Cross-Chain-Interoperability</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19991186/Scroll-Integrates-Chainlink-CCIP-to-Boost-Cross-Chain-Interoperability"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T17:32:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR Scroll has integrated the Chainlink Cross-Chain Interoperability Protocol (CCIP) to enhance the creation of decentralized applications (dApps) in a multi-chain environment. The integration will enable token transfers and messaging between different blockchains, facilitating the development...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 Altcoins Poised for Explosive Growth – 10x Possible?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19991202/3-Altcoins-Poised-for-Explosive-Growth-10x-Possible</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19991202/3-Altcoins-Poised-for-Explosive-Growth-10x-Possible"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T17:31:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the fast moving world of crypto, meme coins pass in and out of the limelight on a regular rotation. This is largely due to the fact that meme coins are topical by nature. This means they’re naturally sustained by the cultural capital of their underlying meme. In this $50 billion market, only...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Extended Repayment Timeline from Mt. Gox Eases Investor Concerns]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19991178/Extended-Repayment-Timeline-from-Mt-Gox-Eases-Investor-Concerns</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19991178/Extended-Repayment-Timeline-from-Mt-Gox-Eases-Investor-Concerns"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T17:30:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mt. Gox has recently announced that it received court approval to extend its repayment plans, leading to a surge in market confidence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Bitcoin Revolution]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19991210/The-Bitcoin-Revolution</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19991210/The-Bitcoin-Revolution"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T17:30:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this riveting discussion from Bitcoin Amsterdam 2024, Jack Mallers and Dylan LeClair share groundbreaking insights on Bitcoin adoption, from El Salvador's bold move to potential US involvement. Discover how Bitcoin is reshaping corporate finance, challenging traditional payment systems, and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Launches ‘Bank-Grade’ Crypto Custody Solution]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7443ca5fbe</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ripple-launches-bank-grade-crypto-custody-solution/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T17:29:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple has announced updates to Ripple Custody, enhancing its “bank-grade” custody technology. The latest features include a transaction screening service integration, additional hardware security module (HSM) options, and an XRPL integration for tokenizing Real World Assets (RWA). Ripple Custody now supports the tokenization of various assets, enabling businesses to manage cryptocurrencies, fiat currencies, and real-world […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tron’s Justin Sun Wins Liberland Congress Election, Named Acting Prime Minister]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7443ca5fbd</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/trons-justin-sun-wins-liberland-congress-election-named-acting-prime-minister/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T17:29:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The blockchain-based Liberland Congress election results were announced, marking a new era for the micronation. Tron founder Justin Sun emerged as the winner and has been appointed as acting Prime Minister by Liberland President Vít Jedlička. Justin Sun Elected as Liberland Congress Speaker, Appointed Acting Prime Minister The Liberland congressional election, conducted entirely through blockchain […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Sues Crypto Market Maker Cumberland DRW]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7443ca8267</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/10/10/sec-sues-crypto-market-maker-cumberland-drw/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T17:28:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The regulator alleged the company "bought and sold" crypto assets that were sold as securities, but did not register as a securities dealer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Millionaire That Turned A $3200 Shiba Inu (SHIB) Trade Into $22 Million Says This Ethereum Presale Will Explode 14,000X This Winter]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7443cad3e5</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-millionaire-that-turned-a-3200-shiba-inu-shib-trade-into-22-million-says-this-ethereum-presale-will-explode-14000x-this-winter/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T17:25:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An Ethereum millionaire who made a $22 million fortune by longing Shiba Inu (SHIB) with $3200 in the 2021 crypto bull markets is driving an influx of smart crypto investors buying the ETFSwap (ETFS)  viral presale as he touts ETFS as the next hidden crypto gem to experience an explosive 14,000x rally this winter of the crypto bull run.
 
ETFSwap (ETFS) Viral ICO Token  Programmed To Create Millionaires With A 14,000x Explosive Rally Q4 2024 
ETFSwap (ETFS) viral presale token selling for an undervalued  $0.03846 is trending on X and is becoming scarce by the minute after a famous Ethereum millionaire who made $22 million with Shiba Inu (SHIB) in 2021 revealed it as the next presale token to surge 14,000% this bull run. ETFSwap (ETFS) groundbreaking DeFi utilities are placing the ETFS presa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Sues Crypto Trading Firm Cumberland, Again Alleges Solana and Polygon Are Securities]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285688</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285688/sec-sues-cumberland-solana-polygon"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T17:09:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC continued its crypto crackdown Thursday with charges against Cumberland, again calling Solana and other assets securities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward,Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gary Gensler, We’re Gonna Miss You (Not)]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7443b5506c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/opinion/2024/10/10/gary-gensler-were-gonna-miss-you-not/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T17:08:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC Chair’s comments on crypto Wednesday did nothing to encourage anyone in the industry to believe he should continue in his position past this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Schiller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pro-XRP Lawyer Breaks Down Ripple’s Next Steps In SEC Appeal]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7443b3e3c4</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/pro-xrp-lawyer-ripple-next-steps-sec-appeal/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T16:28:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an interview on Crypto Law TV, attorney James Murphy, also known as “MetaLawMan,” sat down with host Kristi Warner to discuss the latest developments in the XRP lawsuit between Ripple Labs and the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). Murphy discussed the SEC’s recent appeal and the potential avenues Ripple might explore in response.
 
Murphy began by affirming his anticipation of the SEC’s decision to appeal Judge Analisa Torres’ summary judgment, which had ruled that Ripple’s institutional sales of XRP were unregistered securities, while clarifying that XRP itself is not a security. “I thought that the SEC would appeal,” Murphy stated. “Anytime you lose some or all of a case, you can appeal after final judgment is entered.”
 
He emphasized that the SEC’s attempt at an interlocu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wisdomtree Introduces ‘Earn-Until-You-Spend’ Feature in Onchain Personal Finance App]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7443b3f60e</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/wisdomtree-introduces-earn-until-you-spend-feature-in-onchain-personal-finance-app/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T16:28:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wisdomtree, Inc. (NYSE: WT) has announced the launch of a new yield-bearing feature in its onchain personal finance app, Wisdomtree Prime, allowing users to take advantage of the “Earn-Until-You-Spend” capability. This feature enables users to utilize their investments in the Wisdomtree Government Money Market Digital Fund as a funding source for their spending, effectively linking […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video Game Giant Ubisoft Announces Release of First Web3 Game, ‘Champions Tactics’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7443b3f60c</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/video-game-giant-ubisoft-announces-release-of-first-web3-game-champions-tactics/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T16:28:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The prominent French video game publisher and developer Ubisoft is set to launch its first Web3 game, “Champions Tactics: Grimoria Chronicles,” on October 23. The game will utilize blockchain technology through the Oasys ecosystem, a layer two (L2) solution designed to enhance gameplay. Ubisoft Enters Web3 With Launch of ‘Champions Tactics’ RPG According to the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TON Holders Top 100 Million Following 'Hamster Kombat' Telegram Game Airdrop]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285674</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285674/ton-holders-100-million-hamster-kombat-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T16:27:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More than 100 million wallets now hold TON as the Telegram-linked network has surged via tap-to-earn games like Hamster Kombat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Walrus Protocol is Reinventing Decentralized Storage]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285471</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285471/how-walrus-protocol-is-reinventing-decentralized-storage"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T16:23:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The decentralized storage protocol’s novel data encoding algorithm will unlock applications across AI, websites and social media.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Plans 'Cross-Appeal' in SEC Case]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7443bf1d12</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/10/10/ripple-plans-cross-appeal-in-sec-case/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T16:08:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC announced it was filing an appeal last week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Expert Says Turbo, Memebet Token are the Best Meme Coins to Buy Now]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7443a60c51</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/crypto-expert-says-turbo-memebet-token-are-the-best-meme-coins-to-buy-now/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T15:28:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The meme coin hype isn’t letting up anytime soon. And new projects are constantly popping up, looking to grab the spotlight. One well-known crypto expert recently highlighted two contenders, Turbo and Memebet Token, which he believes are the best meme coins to buy now. Meme Coin Market Faces Volatility as Bitcoin Drags Sector Down It’s […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s World Liberty Financial Proposes Aave Deployment to Enhance Defi Accessibility]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7443a60c46</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/trumps-world-liberty-financial-proposes-aave-deployment-to-enhance-defi-accessibility/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T15:28:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[World Liberty Financial (WLF), the decentralized finance (defi) project backed by former President Donald Trump and his family, has submitted a proposal to Aave’s governance forum, seeking approval for the launch of an Aave v3 instance on the Ethereum mainnet. The proposal, subject to community and governance approval, aims to boost defi adoption through increased […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Todd Distressed Over HBO Linking Him To $60B Bitcoin Fortune: ‘He’s Putting My Life At Risk’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7443a646bf</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/todd-distressed-over-link-to-60b-bitcoin-fortune/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T15:26:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software developer Peter Todd has emphatically stated that he is not Satoshi Nakamoto, the enigmatic figure behind Bitcoin, in a recent interview with Bloomberg. This assertion comes in response to the HBO documentary Money Electric: The Bitcoin Mystery, which suggests Todd may be linked to Nakamoto through circumstantial evidence.
 
Peter Todd Responds To HBO Documentary Claims
 
In an email to Bloomberg on Wednesday, Todd clarified, “I am not Satoshi,” directly addressing the film’s implications. The documentary, directed by Cullen Hoback, suggests that Nakamoto may have inadvertently used Todd’s Internet message board account to continue discussions started under the Nakamoto pseudonym. 
 
However, Todd refuted this claim, pointing out that at the time of the posts, his account was name…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bybit Seeks Crypto License in Austria Following Kazakhstan Approval]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7443a69df2</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com/cryptocurrency/bybit-seeks-crypto-license-in-austria-following-kazakhstan-approval/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T15:24:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bybit has confirmed its pursuit  
of regulatory licensing in Austria. This move aligns with its efforts to expand  
into key markets while adhering to local compliance requirements.
Meanwhile, Kazakhstan  
has granted Bybit a full license from the Astana Financial Service  
Authority, enabling the cryptocurrency exchange to offer trading, custody, and  
investment management services. 
Bybit Awaits Austrian Approval
The company plans to begin operations once it secures  
approval from Austrian authorities. This step will ensure that the exchange  
operates within the country’s regulatory framework.
At present, Bybit is not licensed in Austria. As a result,  
it does not offer services in the Austrian market. Its team is evaluating the  
best time for a potential launch, with updates expect…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tareq Sikder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OKX Goes Live in UAE, Targeting TradFi Institutions, Retail Market]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7443a6f8ed</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2024/10/10/okx-goes-live-in-uae-targeting-tradfi-institutions-retail-market/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T15:23:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OKX, one of the four biggest cryptocurrency exchanges, has gone live in the UAE, Middle East General Manager Rifad Mahasneh said in an interview.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amitoj Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Heather 'Razzlekhan' Morgan Should Spend 18 Months in Prison, Prosecutors Tell Court]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7443a6f8ea</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/10/10/heather-razzlekhan-morgan-should-spend-18-months-in-prison-prosecutors-tell-court/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T15:23:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prosecutors have requested that Heather Morgan – better known by her rap moniker “Razzlekhan” – be sentenced to just 18 months behind bars for her role in laundering 120,000 bitcoins stolen from Bitfinex in a 2016 hack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cheyenne Ligon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto for Advisors: Bitcoin and the American Dream]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7443a0c303</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2024/10/10/crypto-for-advisors-bitcoin-and-the-american-dream/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T15:12:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As bitcoin continues to gain traction as a financial asset, its role in reshaping traditional mortgages could mark a significant advancement for homeownership and the American Dream.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Meredith Yarbrough, Sarah Morton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Is Today’s 'Captain Tsubasa: Rivals' Telegram Game Daily Combo]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=250928</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/captain-tsubasa-rivals-telegram-game-daily-combo"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T15:03:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anime soccer game Captain Tsubasa: Rivals gives out 5 million free daily balls ahead of the TON token airdrop. Here’s the combo for Thursday, October 10.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethena Picks BlackRock's BUIDL, Mountain, Superstate and Sky's USDS for $46M Tokenized RWA Investment]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7443a26326</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2024/10/10/ethena-picks-blackrocks-buidl-mountain-superstate-and-skys-usds-for-46m-tokenized-rwa-investment/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T15:02:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethena's $46 million allocation fits into the growing trend of DeFi platforms and protocol foundations investing in real-world asset-backed products to earn a yield without leaving blockchain rails.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Are Today’s ‘X Empire’ Elon Musk Game Daily Combo, Riddle, and Rebus Solutions]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241078</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/todays-musk-empire-stock-exchange-daily-combo"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T15:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking for the X Empire daily combo and rebus solution for Thursday, October 10? Here are the latest boosts for the Telegram game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Expands Custody Business to Offer 'Bank-Grade' Service to Crypto Firms]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7443add761</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2024/10/10/ripple-expands-custody-business-to-offer-bank-grade-service-to-crypto-firms/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T14:41:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new features could allow companies to tokenize and manage real-world assets (RWAs) as well as other cryptocurrencies on XRP Ledger.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tap-to-Earn Gaming Expands From Telegram to TikTok via Solana's Sonic SVM]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285619</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285619/tap-to-earn-gaming-expands-from-telegram-to-tiktok-via-solanas-sonic-svm"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T14:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana gaming ecosystem has launched Sonic X, a tap-to-earn game based natively inside TikTok as it aims to be the next ‘Notcoin.’]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uniswap Reveals Plans to Launch Ethereum Layer-2 Network Unichain]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285616</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285616/uniswap-ethereum-layer-2-unichain"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T13:13:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Uniswap will launch an Ethereum layer-2 network called Unichain in an effort to cut fees, boost liquidity, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward,Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ubisoft Reveals Release Date for ‘Champions Tactics’ NFT Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285608</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285608/ubisoft-champions-tactics-release-date"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T13:01:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Champions Tactics: Grimoria Chronicles will debut on the Oasys network on October 23, gaming giant Ubisoft announced Thursday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ronin Gaming Network Adopts Chainlink Protocol to Increase Security on Ethereum Bridge]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285606</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285606/ronin-network-adopts-chainlink-cross-chain-protocol-to-increase-security-on-its-ethereum-bridge"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Security was the number one most important factor," said Phuc Thai, Head Researcher at Ronin developer Sky Mavis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miner Iris Energy Accused of Overstating Data Center Capacity in Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285600</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285600/bitcoin-miner-iris-energy-lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T11:52:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The lawsuit claims that Iris Energy "knew or should have known" that its Childress County site in Texas was a poor fit for high-performance computing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vismaya V</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Jitters Intensify as Investors Brace for Inflation Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285598</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285598/bitcoin-price-jitters-inflation-report"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T11:10:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["While these outflows are still relatively modest, they signal waning institutional support as bullish momentum fades,” an analyst said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stripe Follows Through on Crypto Payment Support in USDC Following Six-Year Hiatus]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285581</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285581/stripe-crypto-payment-support-usdc-following-six-year-hiatus"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T06:03:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stripe’s reintroduction to crypto comes after a decision to end support for Bitcoin in 2018, where it cited market volatility concerns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vismaya V</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thai SEC Proposes New Rules for Crypto Investment in Mutual and Private Funds]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285578</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285578/thai-sec-proposes-new-rules-digital-asset-investment-mutual-private-funds"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T03:19:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thailand's SEC is trying to update domestic regulations to reflect the changes and opportunities in crypto investing globally.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Sinclair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Kamala Harris' VP Pick Just Twitch Streamed a Rally Alongside World of Warcraft]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285567</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285567/kamala-harris-vp-pick-twitch-streamed-rally-alongside-world-of-warcraft"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T00:54:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It marks the first time the Harris campaign has integrated live gaming with political content on its Twitch account.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Sinclair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Crypto Project Submits Proposal to Ethereum DeFi Giant Aave]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285548</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285548/trump-crypto-world-liberty-proposal-ethereum-defi-aave"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T22:32:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trump's World Liberty Financial plans to operate as an Aave instance, and AaveDAO stands to gain substantial fees from the deal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NASA Can Now Beam Cat Videos to Mars]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285512</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285512/nasa-can-now-beam-cat-videos-mars"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T22:28:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Good news for outer space colonizers: The next step for space telecommunications may be using light beams to stream data.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI Asks Judge to Dismiss Elon Musk Lawsuit as 'Blusterous' Harassment Campaign]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285528</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285528/openai-dismiss-elon-musk-lawsuit-blusterous-harassment"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T21:58:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The motion filed in federal court argues that Musk's claims lack a legal basis and merely aim to give him a competitive edge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[To Doxx or Not to Doxx: Crypto Sleuth Reignites Fiery Debate]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285530</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285530/to-doxx-or-not-zachxbt-murad"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T21:39:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain investigator ZachXBT sparked a robust debate about doxxing wallets after divulging a meme coin booster's associated addresses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feds Charge Meme Coin ‘Market Maker’ Gotbit, Three Others With Crypto Market Manipulation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285503</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285503/feds-charge-gotbit-others-market-manipulation"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T19:52:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feds on Wednesday unsealed indictments against Gotbit, ZM Quant, CLS Global and MyTrade for alleged crypto market manipulation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoin Use Booms in Argentina as Inflation Skyrockets: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285491</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285491/argentina-stablecoin-use-booms-inflation"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T19:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Argentina still suffers from hyperinflation and citizens in the country are using stablecoins as a result, according to a new report.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Latest Way to Catch a Virus: AI-Driven Porn Sites]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285455</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285455/the-latest-way-to-catch-a-virus-ai-driven-porn-sites"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T18:43:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Russian hacker group is using AI “deepnude” websites to spread malware, continuing a classic trend with a modern twist.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoins No ‘Safe Haven’ From US Monetary Policy, Says European Central Bank]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285473</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285473/stablecoins-no-safe-haven-us-policy-ecb"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T18:29:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ECB says that stablecoins are vulnerable to both shocks coming from within the crypto world and the decisions of U.S. central bankers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will McCurdy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Island Nation Palau Puts Digital Savings Bonds on Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285467</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285467/palau-digital-savings-bonds-blockchain"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T18:17:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The island nation is planning to fully launch the digital bond system next year to raise funds for critical infrastructure projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Napolitano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ready Player One-Inspired 'The Readyverse' Launches Generative AI Building Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285211</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285211/ready-player-one-readyverse-generative-ai"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T18:01:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Readyverse Studios has introduced Promptopia, enabling real-time, in-game creativity for all players via simple text prompts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why This Colombian Neobank is Switching From Ethereum to Avalanche]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285233</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285233/why-colombian-neobank-switching-ethereum-avalanche"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T16:01:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To scale with growing demand, Littio said it would transition its holdings from OpenTrade's vaults on Ethereum to those on Avalanche.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentraland Desktop Client Preview]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qqzvDcTC/decentraland-desktop-client-preview</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qqzvDcTC/decentraland-desktop-client-preview"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T15:53:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum metaverse game Decentraland has shared an exclusive look at the visual and performance upgrades coming via its new desktop client.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Is Still Undervalued and That Presents a Buying Opportunity, Say Analysts]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285423</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285423/bitcoin-undervalued-buying-opportunity-analysts"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T15:15:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Historically, when [Bitcoin] active addresses surge like this, it often precedes or accompanies price increases," an analyst told Decrypt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Settlement Requires Caroline Ellison to Give Up 'All of Her Assets']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285363</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285363/ftx-settlement-caroline-ellison-assets"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T14:38:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company noted that pursuing a lawsuit would deplete Ellison's remaining resources and incur additional costs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Economists Vouch for Ethereum Founder Vitalik Buterin as Nobel Prize Contender]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285379</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285379/ethereum-founder-vitalik-buterin-nobel-prize"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T14:13:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Vitalik has built a platform, created a currency ... obviously following in the footsteps of Satoshi [Nakamoto]," economist Tyler Cowen said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nintendo's Next Device Isn't the Switch 2—It's an Alarm Clock]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285388</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285388/nintendo-alarm-clock-not-switch-2"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T13:47:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Keep waiting for the Switch 2—Nintendo has revealed a smart alarm clock instead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Decentraland’ Reveals Huge Visual Upgrade via Upcoming Desktop Client]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285318</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285318/decentraland-reveals-huge-visual-upgrade-via-upcoming-desktop-client"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T13:01:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum metaverse game Decentraland is getting a big performance boost, with potential plans to bring it into VR too]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sui DeFi Platform DeepBook Reveals DEEP Token Launch Plans]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285223</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285223/sui-defi-platform-deepbook-reveals-token-launch-plans"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T13:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DeepBook, a central limit order book for DeFi built on Sui, is launching its long-awaited DEEP token next week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Irish Criminal Assets Bureau Unable to Access Drug Dealer's $378 Million in Seized Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285346</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285346/irish-police-378-million-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T11:50:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bitcoin, held in 12 wallets, was seized from a drug dealer who claims the seed phrases were lost in a break-in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Will Be 'Range Bound' While US Election Is Too Close to Call: Bernstein]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285319</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285319/bitcoin-range-bound-us-election-bernstein"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T11:19:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The $1.5 billion bet on the election is "real money in play and bettors would bet on probability than actually reflecting their bias," analysts said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[86-Year-Old Former Lawyer to Pay $14 Million for Running Bitcoin Ponzi Scheme]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285304</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285304/86-year-old-lawyer-14-million-settlement"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T09:27:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[He will serve probation at a Las Vegas senior care facility. If he leaves, he will be required to wear a monitoring device.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Trader Murad Mahmudov talks about the Supercycle and how he chooses Meme Coins.]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Hj3nDp7G/crypto-trader-murad-mahmudov-talks-about-the-supercycle-and-how-he-chooses-meme-coins</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Hj3nDp7G/crypto-trader-murad-mahmudov-talks-about-the-supercycle-and-how-he-chooses-meme-coins"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T21:47:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Trader Murad Mahmudov talks about the Supercycle and how he chooses Meme Coins. Crypto stable, had sold off after China stocks fall. Crypto adopted faster than other tech: BlackRock. Crypto adoption to hit 8% of world population. CryptoCom recieves Wells notice from SEC. HBO documentary on Satoshi airs tonight. FTX bankruptcy plan approved by judge. Scroll airdrop may be imminent. Jupiter goes live on mobile iOS. Phantom rolls out support for Base. AAVE launches GHO on Base. Gensler may be replaced by Robinhood CLO. 87% of new token launches on SOL. National Bank of Bahrain creates BTC fund. BedRock DeFi allows BTC staking on ARB.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Memecoins take off, funding stays low, China stocks keep on rising!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/703mAYhV/memecoins-take-off-funding-stays-low-china-stocks-keep-on-rising</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/703mAYhV/memecoins-take-off-funding-stays-low-china-stocks-keep-on-rising"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T08:27:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR EP213. Memecoins take off, funding stays low, China stocks keep on rising!
Many altcoins & memecoins soar despite stable BTC. Funding rates continue to be low or negative. Crypto funds saw $147m of outflows last week. BTC remains best performing major assets this year. SUI breaks into the top 20 coins again. TAO leads top 100 away from memes, sifu shorts. $100m bridge to SOL over the last 7 days. Metaplanet buys $6.7m more BTC. ETH proposal aims to improve throughput 50%. EIGEN, OP, APT lead token unlocks this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Walrus Protocol Unlocks New Applications for Decentralized Data Storage]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kwEYLYWj/how-walrus-protocol-unlocks-new-applications-for-decentralized-data-storage</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kwEYLYWj/how-walrus-protocol-unlocks-new-applications-for-decentralized-data-storage"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T11:19:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mysten Labs Chief Scientist George Danezis joined Decrypt to talk about its new decentralized storage protocol Walrus, which promises to unlock new applications such as AI and social media, thanks to its novel Red Stuff data encoding algorithm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Coinbase Sees Crypto as a Bipartisan, 'Purple' Political Issue]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/YR2YmmwR/why-coinbase-sees-crypto-as-a-bipartisan-purple-political-issue</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/YR2YmmwR/why-coinbase-sees-crypto-as-a-bipartisan-purple-political-issue"/>
        <updated>2024-10-05T22:18:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase VP of Corporate and Business Development, Shan Aggarwal, joined Decrypt's Sander Lutz and Liz Napolitano at Messari Mainnet 2024 to discuss the exchange's efforts to grow mainstream crypto adoption—and how the changing political conversation around digital assets is rapidly playing a major role in that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Is Playing Offense—Not Just Defense—Against Crypto Crime, Says Head of Financial Investigations]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DiJ8D2Qc/binance-is-playing-offensenot-just-defenseagainst-crypto-crime-says-head-of-financial-investigations</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DiJ8D2Qc/binance-is-playing-offensenot-just-defenseagainst-crypto-crime-says-head-of-financial-investigations"/>
        <updated>2024-10-05T01:58:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nils Anderson Röed, the exchange’s global head of financial investigations, sat down with Decrypt’s Sander Lutz at Messari Mainnet 2024 to discuss how Binance is proactively dismantling criminal networks around the world, the strategy with which the crypto exchange is approaching sensitive conflicts in the Middle East, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 212 - SEEDPHRASE TALKS ART!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PJfaJNkZ/fomo-hour-212-seedphrase-talks-art</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PJfaJNkZ/fomo-hour-212-seedphrase-talks-art"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T19:29:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Payrolls Higher than expected, Bitcoin reacts hard. Crypto sank early in the week as Middle East tensions spooked markets. Powell signals two more rate cuts this year. SUI leads L1s again, nears YTD high despite large unlock. Majority of FTX repayments still months away. EIGEN becomes non-transferable, hits $6bn FDV. SEC to appeal Ripple securities law ruling. Visa launches tokenization platform for banks. SWIFT plans digital asset trial in 2025. ByBit launched trading of global stock indices. SPX, GIGA & FWOG hit ATHs, most memes fall. XCOPY to release 250 piece collection on Shape. HBO documentary claims to have identified Satoshi.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Altcoins bleed, ByBit launches stock index trading, POCHITA soars]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kYjAt3nt/altcoins-bleed-bybit-launches-stock-index-trading-pochita-soars</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kYjAt3nt/altcoins-bleed-bybit-launches-stock-index-trading-pochita-soars"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T21:11:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Altcoins sink, BTC dominance nears cycle high. BTC in ‘three blind mice’ downtrend. Tron revenue hits record $577m in Q3. ByBit to launch trading of major stock indices. Franklin Templeton launch fund on APT. SWIFT banks to trial digital assets in 2025. Aerodrome hits $1bn TVL on Base. Cronje calls out Aerodrome for copyright. ETH ICO wallet sells $47m. SEC files appeal against Ripple ruling. EIGEN falls 20% on staking rewards FUD. FTX to auction off WLD position. Half of US voters think crypto ‘important’. North Korea ‘infiltrating’ crypto industry. Snowden challenged over SOL centralisation view. Top SEC official on crypto set to depart.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DACOM Summit: Fastex CLO Vardan Khachatryan on Crypto Compliance]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LGGnxkb6/dacom-summit-fastex-clo-vardan-khachatryan-on-crypto-compliance</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LGGnxkb6/dacom-summit-fastex-clo-vardan-khachatryan-on-crypto-compliance"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T14:32:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fastex Chief Legal Officer Vardan Khachatryan joined Rug Radio creator Mlow at DACOM Summit to discuss how the crypto exchange is advancing compliance, and the regulatory challenges that lie ahead for the sector.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 210 - MIDDLE EAST TENSIONS RISE]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Bcj37IF2/fomo-hour-210-middle-east-tensions-rise</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Bcj37IF2/fomo-hour-210-middle-east-tensions-rise"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T17:14:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto drops as Middle East tensions flare. $500m liquidations in drop. BTC ETFs see largest outflows in a month. Fidelity ETH ETF sees 2nd highest outflow ever. SUI hits 6-month highs, bridge goes live on mainnet. Hashdex set to launch XRP ETF. Wormhole leads altcoin gains after Upbit lists. BTC miners hit record low profits in September Crypto hackers stole $750m in Q3. Telegram has been disclosing IPs since 2018.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Arbitrum is Simplifying Web3 for Web2 Adopters]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Mm9OGAoG/how-arbitrum-is-simplifying-web3-for-web2-adopters</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Mm9OGAoG/how-arbitrum-is-simplifying-web3-for-web2-adopters"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T14:19:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arbitrum's Head of Korea, John Park, joined Rug Radio creator Pukerainbow at ArbiVerse to talk about the Ethereum layer-2's strategy in Asia, hackathons, and bringing enterprise clients to its ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rep. Tom Emmer Is Confident Crypto Laws Are Coming Soon—No Matter Who Wins the Election]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qWDybFgM/rep-tom-emmer-is-confident-crypto-laws-are-coming-soonno-matter-who-wins-the-election</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qWDybFgM/rep-tom-emmer-is-confident-crypto-laws-are-coming-soonno-matter-who-wins-the-election"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T20:37:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Republican Majority Whip Tom Emmer sat down with Decrypt’s Sander Lutz and Liz Napolitano to discuss the state of crypto legislation, Kamala Harris, Fairshake, and more at Messari Mainnet 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 209 - LET UPTOBER BEGIN!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DdOpex2X/fomo-hour-209-let-uptober-begin</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DdOpex2X/fomo-hour-209-let-uptober-begin"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T19:23:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETFs see inflows for 8 straight days. SUI enters top 20, $110m of unlocks today. SOL weekly DEX volume flips ETH. Firedancer sees very fast TPS on Testnet. ETH gas up 500% in 2 weeks. EIGEN opens at $7bn FDV. FTX creditors vote in favour of restructuring plan. Dell to sell another $1.2bn Dell stock. Metaplanet buys another 107 BTC.Grayscale opens decentralised AI fund to investors. Robinhood allows crypto transfer in EU. Pollak to head Coinbase Wallet & join exec team. Gemini to close in Canada. Japan considers lower cap gains tax on crypto. Ohio bill would make it legal to pay taxes in crypto. Trump project opens whitelist to non-US users. CZ pledges to invest in blockchain companies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance CEO Richard Teng Talks Progress on Exchange's Global Regulatory Goals]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DNhZEWGn/binance-ceo-richard-teng-talks-progress-on-exchanges-global-regulatory-goals</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DNhZEWGn/binance-ceo-richard-teng-talks-progress-on-exchanges-global-regulatory-goals"/>
        <updated>2024-09-28T22:11:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt Reporters Sander Lutz and Liz Napolitano spoke with Binance CEO Richard Teng about the crypto exchange's progress on establishing a global headquarters, improving its relationships with regulators, and expanding its global presence in the wake of founder Changpeng "CZ" Zhao's jailing in the U.S.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 207 - WELCOME BACK TO THE BULL!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/2OVTsv7N/fomo-hour-207-welcome-back-to-the-bull</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/2OVTsv7N/fomo-hour-207-welcome-back-to-the-bull"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T18:14:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kamala signals support for crypto. Top memecoins all soar, add $10bn in value in a week. MOODENG hits $180m, does 11x in a week. SUI & SEI continue to lead L1s for price & TVL growth. Revolut & Robinhood are considering stablecoin. Visa launches new tokenisation platform for banks. PayPal to allow business accounts to hold crypto Hamster kombat's HMSTER disappoints on launch. Biden admin may have forced Silvergate’s closure. Court rules crypto mining boxes ‘are securities’.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 206 - MEMES ARE PUMPING!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Uc5GOy50/fomo-hour-206-memes-are-pumping</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Uc5GOy50/fomo-hour-206-memes-are-pumping"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T15:50:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC nears $65k key resistance level. Kamala makes positive comments about crypto. PayPal allows businesses to hold crypto. Visa allows banks to test RWAs & smart contracts. Cuban wants to be head of SEC. Silvergate claims about ‘Chokepoint 2.0’ grow. Truflation hacked for $5m. Telegram Wallet blocked in UK & US. Court rules crypto mining boxes are securities. Infinex DeFi platform raises $65m. Ethena announces new stablecoin linked to BUIDL.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 205 - ALTCOINS CONTINUE TO RALLY!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mtR8OATG/fomo-hour-205-altcoins-continue-to-rally</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mtR8OATG/fomo-hour-205-altcoins-continue-to-rally"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T15:16:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SUI leads L1 gains as TVL crosses $1bn. Altcoin market cap close to breaking downtrend. SEI becomes top chain for 1 month TVL growth. ETH ETFs sees 3rd largest inflow ever. SEC delays ETH ETF options decision. SOL took most of ETH outflows over last 3 months. SOLETH continues to be trading at resistance. $8.1bn BTC options to expire this week. BTC heading to $500k-$1m in a year: PlanB. Stablecoin supply hits new ATH. Caroline Ellison sentenced to 2 years in jail. SBF & Diddy in the same jail. SEC settles against TUSD for not being collateralised. Gensler gets derided for crypto approach. Hester Pierce admits flaws in SEC crypto policy. Harris against regulation by litigation: Cuban. Golem claims ETH move to CEXs due to staking. Binance refutes data leak claims. Next Y combinator batch has ‘no crypto companies’. Celo overtakes Tron for stablecoin addresses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 204 - MOODENG MOO-NING!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/g2yV7DjU/fomo-hour-204-moodeng-moo-ning</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/g2yV7DjU/fomo-hour-204-moodeng-moo-ning"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T15:53:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC needs to top $65.2k to put in a higher high. ETH ETFs see biggest outflow since July. ETH outperformance could be start of ‘alt season’. BlackRock gets 12hr BTC withdrawal from Coinbase. cbBTC only wrapped BTC to not show reserves. Telegram to share user data upon legal requests. EIGEN non-transferability to be removed Sep 30th. TIA announces $100m funding round. TIA deal was OTC token sale ‘done months ago’. Polymarket considers token, trying $50m raise. Maybe we will pay off debt with crypto: Trump. Harris unlikely to give full crypto policy pre-election. 13m Binance users’ data may have been leaked. Caroline Ellison likely won’t serve time in jail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 203 - KAMALA GOES PRO-CRYPTO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZIgJfh06/fomo-hour-203-kamala-goes-pro-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZIgJfh06/fomo-hour-203-kamala-goes-pro-crypto"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T16:14:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto funds saw $321m inflows last week. Kamala commits to crypto & AI expansion. TAO leads gains in AI hype, does 2x in 2 weeks. SUI TVL breaks $900m. Average Q4 returns for BTC is 88%. BTC Google searches down 75% since 2021. BTC 161 days from halving, when it rallied in 2020. Crypto VCs raised $2.2bn this year, well below 2021.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 202 - SOL STARTS TO SEND IT]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kMr0ptrw/fomo-hour-202-sol-starts-to-send-it</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kMr0ptrw/fomo-hour-202-sol-starts-to-send-it"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T18:42:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SOL leads majors as Breakpoint begins. SOL launches Frankendancer on mainnet. Helio Pay allows Shopify items to sell on X. Franklin Templeton to launch fund on SOL. BTC short term holders fall at fastest rate in 12 years. MicroStrategy upsizes convertible note raise to $1bn. BingX loses $52m in hack. $243m crypto heist exposed by ZachXBT. Supreme Court of India hacked on X, shills scam. SocGen launches Euro stablecoin on SOL. Sky agrees to stop using WBTC. Germany shuts down 47 crypto exchanges. Stablecoin’s now 18th biggest holder of treasuries. Consensys lawsuit against SEC dismissed. Partisanship will stop Trump crypto plans: Hoskinson. Scaramucci working with Kamala on crypto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>