<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-02-02T20:14:37.750Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-02-02T20:14:37.750Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shibarium Ecosystem Grows: Shiba Inu Announces New Partner]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74e9639025</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-shibarium-new-partner/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T20:09:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Shiba Inu ecosystem has marked a significant milestone in its ongoing expansion with the addition of K9 Finance as an official partner in the Shibarium ecosystem. This development was announced by Shiba Inu’s marketing lead, Lucie, in a recent post. Lucie highlighted the importance of this partnership by stating, “Step by step, K9 Finance has been officially added as a Shibarium ecosystem partner.”
 
What K9 Brings To The Shiba Inu Ecosystem
 
K9 Finance, now a critical part of the Shibarium ecosystem, is a platform specifically designed for the Shibarium blockchain. It introduces a liquid staking derivative (LSD) model for the BONE token, akin to the role Lido plays for Ethereum.
 
Lucie explained in a detailed post, “K9 Finance is a platform for Shibarium that lets you stake your BON…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polkadot Sees Record Growth in Users and Developers in Q4]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19224771/Polkadot-Sees-Record-Growth-in-Users-and-Developers-in-Q4</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19224771/Polkadot-Sees-Record-Growth-in-Users-and-Developers-in-Q4"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T20:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Q4 2023 sees Polkadot’s dramatic rise, as developer base triples, active addresses skyrocket, and market capitalization grows by 111%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Valkyrie Enhances Security with Dual Custody Strategy for Bitcoin ETF]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19224772/Valkyrie-Enhances-Security-with-Dual-Custody-Strategy-for-Bitcoin-ETF</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19224772/Valkyrie-Enhances-Security-with-Dual-Custody-Strategy-for-Bitcoin-ETF"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T20:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JPMorgan Chase Customers’ Deposits Go Missing, Bank Says It Has No Idea Where Money Went: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19224767/JPMorgan-Chase-Customers-Deposits-Go-Missing-Bank-Says-It-Has-No-Idea-Where-Money-Went-Report</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19224767/JPMorgan-Chase-Customers-Deposits-Go-Missing-Bank-Says-It-Has-No-Idea-Where-Money-Went-Report"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T20:04:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Customers at a JPMorgan Chase branch say deposits aren’t showing up in their accounts, and the bank has been reluctant to address the issue. Carla Garling, a small business owner, says that despite having a deposit slip, her local Chase branch hasn’t confirmed a $13,478 deposit to her account,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shibarium Ecosystem Grows: Shiba Inu Announces New Partner]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19224763/Shibarium-Ecosystem-Grows-Shiba-Inu-Announces-New-Partner</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19224763/Shibarium-Ecosystem-Grows-Shiba-Inu-Announces-New-Partner"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T20:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Shiba Inu ecosystem has marked a significant milestone in its ongoing expansion with the addition of K9 Finance as an official partner in the Shibarium ecosystem. This development was announced by Shiba Inu’s marketing lead, Lucie, in a recent post. Lucie highlighted the importance of this...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Dips Are For Buying: Analyst Predicts Price Rally To $22]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19224752/XRP-Dips-Are-For-Buying-Analyst-Predicts-Price-Rally-To-22</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19224752/XRP-Dips-Are-For-Buying-Analyst-Predicts-Price-Rally-To-22"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T20:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling Solution Developer Polygon Labs Lays Off 19% of Workforce, CEO Says It’s Not for Financial Reasons]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19224726/Scaling-Solution-Developer-Polygon-Labs-Lays-Off-19-of-Workforce-CEO-Says-Its-Not-for-Financial-Reasons</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19224726/Scaling-Solution-Developer-Polygon-Labs-Lays-Off-19-of-Workforce-CEO-Says-Its-Not-for-Financial-Reasons"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T19:45:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The developer behind the Polygon (MATIC) ecosystem is laying off 19% of its workforce, though the company’s chief executive says the staff shakeup isn’t due to financial reasons. Marc Boiron, CEO of Polygon Labs, says in a new announcement that the company is letting go of 60 people to create...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Exchange Slapped With a Lawsuit in New York by Victims of October 7 Hamas Attack on Israel: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19224712/Binance-Exchange-Slapped-With-a-Lawsuit-in-New-York-by-Victims-of-October-7-Hamas-Attack-on-Israel-Report</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19224712/Binance-Exchange-Slapped-With-a-Lawsuit-in-New-York-by-Victims-of-October-7-Hamas-Attack-on-Israel-Report"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T19:41:35.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Data Including Code, Internal Passwords Leaked on GitHub: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215438</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/215438/binance-data-leak-code-security-passwords-on-github"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T19:41:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The leaked information reportedly included details on Binance's security measures, llike passwords and multi-factor authentication.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Data Including Code, Internal Passwords Leaked on GitHub: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19224710/Binance-Data-Including-Code-Internal-Passwords-Leaked-on-GitHub-Report</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19224710/Binance-Data-Including-Code-Internal-Passwords-Leaked-on-GitHub-Report"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T19:41:21.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No crypto ad spots are expected for Super Bowl LVIII]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19224696/No-crypto-ad-spots-are-expected-for-Super-Bowl-LVIII</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19224696/No-crypto-ad-spots-are-expected-for-Super-Bowl-LVIII"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T19:36:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BMW, Budweiser, State Farm, Oreo, DoorDash and Hellman’s Mayonnaise are reportedly planning to advertise for the big game — food and cars, not AI and crypto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Stamps Seek To Improve On Ordinals]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19224735/Bitcoin-Stamps-Seek-To-Improve-On-Ordinals</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19224735/Bitcoin-Stamps-Seek-To-Improve-On-Ordinals"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T19:35:45.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[End of the Line for OPNX, Built by Three Arrows Co-Founders Zhu and Davies]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74e96ff0d5</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/end-of-the-line-for-opnx-built-by-three-arrows-co-founders-zhu-and-davies/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T19:35:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OPNX has declared it will cease all activities next month. This decision comes as co-founders Su Zhu and Kyle Davies grapple with legal repercussions stemming from their previous venture’s failure, Three Arrows Capital.
 
OPNX to Shut Down Amid Three Arrows Co-Founders’ Legal Troubles
 
Open Exchange (OPNX), a platform unique for trading bankruptcy claims alongside its crypto exchange operations, has announced it will cease all operations by Feb. 14. The closure comes after a tumultuous period for the co-founders, Kyle Davies and Su Zhu, who are also known for their involvement in the collapse of the Singapore-based crypto hedge fund, Three Arrows Capital (3AC).
 
According to an email sent to OPNX users, the exchange has urged its clientele to close all positions by Feb. 7 and to ensure t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Sencil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump Won't Reappoint Fed Chair Jerome Powell If Elected President]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74e968ac34</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/markets/donald-trump-wont-reappoint-fed-chair-jerome-powell-if-elected-president"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T19:29:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent statement, former President Donald Trump made it clear that, if elected for a second term, he would not reappoint Jerome Powell as the Federal Reserve Chair. Trump has expressed his dissatisfaction with the current Fed Chair's performance, and suggests that Powell will rate cuts in attempt to give Democrats an advantage in the 2024 elections.



Trump's criticism comes amidst concerns over inflation and the Federal Reserve's handling of monetary policy. The former President believes that Powell's approach has not been in the best interest of the U.S. economy. The Federal Reserve plays a crucial role in shaping economic policies and managing interest rates, impacting everything from employment to inflation.
"No, I wouldn't do that," Trump stated when asked if he would reappoint Jerome Powell. “I think he’s going to do something to help the Democrats, if he lowers interest rates,” Trump continued. The former president then went on to mention that he has a "couple choices" of who he would replace Powell with, but declined to reveal exactly who.
The announcement adds an interesting dimension to the political and economic landscape, setting the stage for potential changes in leadership at the Federal Reserve if Trump were to secure a second term. Powell has faced challenges since being appointed for his second term as Fed Chair by current U.S. President Joe Biden, including navigating the economic fallout from the COVID-19 pandemic.
As political dynamics continue to evolve, Trump's stance on Powell and the Federal Reserve will continue to be focal point of discussion, considering the critical role the institution plays in shaping the nation's economic trajectory. Investors, policymakers, and the public will keenly watch how this declaration influences economic narratives and potential shifts in leadership within the Federal Reserve.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nik Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Presidential Election Puts El Salvador’s Bitcoin Future At A Crossroads]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74e968ac2b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/el-salvador-bitcoin-news/presidential-election-puts-el-salvadors-bitcoin-future-at-a-crossroads"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T19:29:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The below is an excerpt from a recent edition of Bitcoin Magazine Pro, Bitcoin Magazine's premium markets newsletter. To be among the first to receive these insights and other on-chain bitcoin market analysis straight to your inbox, subscribe now.
 
         
         
         
         
    
On Sunday, February 4, El Salvador’s presidential election will determine whether Nayib Bukele and his revolutionary experiment with Bitcoin will have a continued presence in the nation’s future.
Since Nayib Bukele became President of El Salvador in 2019, he has enjoyed a fairly broad base of support; he was the first man since 1984 to win independently of the nation’s two major political parties. The topic that has taken his administration to a subject of worldwide discussion, however, has been his …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Landon Manning</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Instant Settlement Series: Real Time Streaming Payments]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74e968ac1c</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/technical/instant-settlement-series-real-time-streaming-payments"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T19:29:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the previous articles, we found the disconnect between paid-for work and paid-for time. We also understood that if you want to get paid you have to provide work that is valuable for others. So when the person consumes the benefit of your work, the exchange happens value for value - work for sats. But what happens if the benefit that the consumer experiences is not a momentary but a continuous process? There are a few examples of this. I will start with the one that is not that captivating but still valuable.
Streaming services, like other industries, grapple with the limitations of the fiat payment system. The burden of fees and the absence of suitable technology for streaming payments have compelled them to adopt similar mitigations as other industries. This translates to charging us…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ivan Makedonski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC charges founder of online crypto course who targeted students to invest in nonexistent hedge fund]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19224667/SEC-charges-founder-of-online-crypto-course-who-targeted-students-to-invest-in-nonexistent-hedge-fund</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19224667/SEC-charges-founder-of-online-crypto-course-who-targeted-students-to-invest-in-nonexistent-hedge-fund"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T19:28:29.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A New Bitcoin-Linked Fraud Allegation from the SEC: Enforcement Director Makes Statement]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19224662/A-New-Bitcoin-Linked-Fraud-Allegation-from-the-SEC-Enforcement-Director-Makes-Statement</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19224662/A-New-Bitcoin-Linked-Fraud-Allegation-from-the-SEC-Enforcement-Director-Makes-Statement"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T19:24:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC has charged a Bitcoin-related entity with alleged fraud, according to an official notice. Continue Reading: A New Bitcoin-Linked Fraud Allegation from the SEC: Enforcement Director Makes Statement]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin 'Power Law' Predicts $1 Million BTC Price by 2033—Here's How It Works]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215484</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/215484/bitcoin-power-law-predicts-1-million-btc-price-2033-heres-how-it-works"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T19:21:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin's price is a "force of nature" that scales over time much like a city, according to this astrophysicist. Will this "power law" hold up?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin 'Power Law' Predicts $1 Million BTC Price by 2033—Here's How It Works]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19224656/Bitcoin-Power-Law-Predicts-1-Million-BTC-Price-by-2033Heres-How-It-Works</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19224656/Bitcoin-Power-Law-Predicts-1-Million-BTC-Price-by-2033Heres-How-It-Works"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T19:21:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin's price is a "force of nature" that scales over time much like a city, according to this astrophysicist. Will this "power law" hold up?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin mining difficulty hits new ATH after record 7.3% spike]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19224636/Bitcoin-mining-difficulty-hits-new-ATH-after-record-73-spike</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19224636/Bitcoin-mining-difficulty-hits-new-ATH-after-record-73-spike"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T19:14:59.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF launches Are Positive For Robinhood, But Limited Direct Driver of Transaction Revenue: Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19224675/Bitcoin-ETF-launches-Are-Positive-For-Robinhood-But-Limited-Direct-Driver-of-Transaction-Revenue-Analyst</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19224675/Bitcoin-ETF-launches-Are-Positive-For-Robinhood-But-Limited-Direct-Driver-of-Transaction-Revenue-Analyst"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T19:09:54.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BREAKING: BlackRock Now Owns 70,000 Bitcoin | EP 918]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19223913/BREAKING-BlackRock-Now-Owns-70000-Bitcoin-EP-918</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19223913/BREAKING-BlackRock-Now-Owns-70000-Bitcoin-EP-918"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T19:08:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Interest in the BlackRock spot Bitcoin ETF continues to rise, the largest asset manager in the world now holds 70,000 Bitcoin✓ SUBSCRIBE - https://bit.ly/3QbgqTQ✓ LEAVE A LIKE & COMMENT LIMITED MERCH DROP► https://simplybitcoin.com/collections/allSPONSORS► Bitcoin Well: https://bitcoinwell.com►...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Awakening: Here’s How Much SHIB Was Burned In January]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74e9540508</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-shib-burned-january/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T19:06:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Shiba Inu ecosystem has achieved a noteworthy milestone, effectively burning almost 10 billion tokens in just one month. This impressive feat highlights the community’s dedicated efforts to enhance the growth and value of the Shiba Inu native token, SHIB. 
 
Shiba Inu Massive Token Burn Tops Over 9 Billion
 
In an X (formerly Twitter) post, Shibburn, a Shiba Inu token burn tracker, announced the total amount of SHIB burns that occurred in January 2024. According to the burn tracker, approximately 9,937,949,070 SHIB tokens worth about $90,087 were burned in just January. 
 
 
Presently, the Shiba Inu community performs thousands of SHIB burns hourly and millions daily. This high volume of Shib burns reflects the community’s growing desire and commitment to counteract inflationary pressu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Catalyst Could Trigger Chainlink To Jump Further, According to Blockchain Analytics Firm Santiment]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19224617/This-Catalyst-Could-Trigger-Chainlink-To-Jump-Further-According-to-Blockchain-Analytics-Firm-Santiment</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19224617/This-Catalyst-Could-Trigger-Chainlink-To-Jump-Further-According-to-Blockchain-Analytics-Firm-Santiment"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T19:05:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto analytics firm Santiment says one metric is suggesting that decentralized oracle network Chainlink (LINK) could have more upside potential. In a new thread on the social media platform X, the market intelligence platform says that Chainlink’s rally may continue even as LINK wallets see a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC vs. Ripple Case Hits Deadlock with No Settlement in Sight]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19224615/SEC-vs-Ripple-Case-Hits-Deadlock-with-No-Settlement-in-Sight</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19224615/SEC-vs-Ripple-Case-Hits-Deadlock-with-No-Settlement-in-Sight"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T19:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Is Everyone Talking About Jupiter on Solana?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/EiN2WqlF/why-is-everyone-talking-about-jupiter-on-solana</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/EiN2WqlF/why-is-everyone-talking-about-jupiter-on-solana"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T19:04:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rug Radio Creator and crypto influencer AshleyDCan explains why the crypto world can't stop talking about Solana's Jupiter. What is JUP? Who qualified for the airdrop? And will there be another round?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FCC Chair Proposes Making AI-Generated Voice Calls Illegal Under TCPA]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19224613/FCC-Chair-Proposes-Making-AI-Generated-Voice-Calls-Illegal-Under-TCPA</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19224613/FCC-Chair-Proposes-Making-AI-Generated-Voice-Calls-Illegal-Under-TCPA"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T19:03:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On January 31, United States Federal Communications Commission (FCC) Chairwoman Jessica Rosenworcel made a significant...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s Big Breakout: This Bullish Pattern Signals An Imminent Price Surge]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19224594/Bitcoins-Big-Breakout-This-Bullish-Pattern-Signals-An-Imminent-Price-Surge</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19224594/Bitcoins-Big-Breakout-This-Bullish-Pattern-Signals-An-Imminent-Price-Surge"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T19:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bluechip Gives Synthetix and Beanstalk Stablecoins F Grades; Tokens Added to the ‘Red Flag List’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74e95053ee</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bluechip-gives-synthetix-and-beanstalk-stablecoins-f-grades-tokens-added-to-the-red-flag-list/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T18:35:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Feb. 1, 2024, the independent, nonprofit stablecoin assessment entity Bluechip made a noteworthy declaration. They officially bestowed an F grade upon Synthetix’s fiat tokens SUSD and SEUR, alongside Beanstalk’s dollar-pegged asset BEAN. Bluechip went on to reveal that both of these stablecoins have been included in the organization’s “Red Flag List,” signaling a strong recommendation against utilizing these particular stablecoin tokens.
 
SUSD, SEUR, and BEAN Graded F by Stablecoin Rating Organization Bluechip
 
As per a statement shared on the social media platform X, Bluechip has issued an F rating for Synthetix’s and Beanstalk’s fiat-backed cryptocurrency assets, namely, SUSD, SEUR, and BEAN. These stablecoins join Tron’s USDD stablecoin, which also received an F grade in Bluechip’s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GME Crash: GameStop Tribute Meme Coin on Solana Plunges 52%]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215477</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/215477/gme-crash-gamestop-tribute-meme-coin-solana-plunges-52"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T18:31:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just like the meme stock of the same name, the GME tribute coin based on GameStop is falling hard after this week’s spikes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Valkyrie Selects BitGo as Second Custodian for Bitcoin ETF]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74e95c1ed0</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/valkyrie-selects-bitgo-as-second-custodian-for-bitcoin-etf/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T18:03:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Valkyrie, one of the providers of spot bitcoin  
exchange-traded funds (ETFs) in the US, has appointed BitGo as its second  
custodian for its Bitcoin Fund (BRRR). Valkyrie is diversifying the custody of  
its coins by leveraging BitGo's expertise alongside Coinbase.
This collaboration marks a pivotal moment in the  
evolution of cryptocurrency investments, emphasizing the industry's commitment  
to robust risk mitigation strategies. The collaboration with BitGo aligns with regulators'  
requirements in the US and globally, setting a benchmark for Bitcoin ETF  
security.
Bitcoin ETF Adoption 
Mike Belshe, the CEO of BitGo, mentioned:  
"Valkyrie Investments has already made a name for itself, providing  
investors with funds to tap into the digital asset space. Earlier this year,  
they to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LN Markets Upgrades Bitcoin Trading With DLCs]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74e95ca515</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/technical/ln-markets-upgrades-bitcoin-trading-with-dlcs"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T17:59:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin is fixing money. 
Thanks to Bitcoin, anyone in the world is free to transfer money over a peer-to-peer network without having to go through a financial institution. Money that cannot be censored by authorities, devalued by governments, monopolized by corporations, or stopped by borders.
However, when it comes to trading, going through a trusted third party still remains necessary. Why is that a problem? Because trusted third parties always have been, and continue to be, security holes. 
Bitcoin Trading Is Broken
Individuals and financial institutions alike rely on trusted third parties such as clearinghouses and exchanges to clear their Bitcoin spot and derivatives transactions.

“Banks must be trusted to hold our money and transfer it electronically, but they lend it out in waves …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LN Markets</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bitcoin ETF Will Never Be Your Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74e95ca3ba</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2024/02/02/a-bitcoin-etf-will-never-be-your-bitcoin/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T17:59:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETFs give investors exposure to price movements but not to the financial ownership and sovereignty that makes crypto different from other financial assets, says Pascal Gauthier, Chairman and CEO at Ledger.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pascal  Gauthier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Probably Will Go Meme': OPNX Investors Refuse to Sell Tokens Despite Shutdown]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215453</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/215453/opnx-investors-refuse-to-sell-be-comfortable-with-fear"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T17:41:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["What are the chances they can fail again," one OPNX investors asked. "It’s almost statistically impossible."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple's 'Vision Pro' Set to Get First Crypto-Focused Metaverse App From Victoria VR]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74e95f3c43</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2024/02/02/apples-vision-pro-set-to-get-first-metaverse-app-from-victoria-vr/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T17:40:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The app is set to be released in the second qaurter and the token VR has already surged 60% in last 24 hours.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aoyon Ashraf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[By The Numbers: How Much Bitcoin Supply Do ETFs Hold?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74e95fbb75</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/by-the-numbers-how-much-bitcoin-supply-do-etfs-hold/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T17:36:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few weeks have passed since the Bitcoin ETFs have gone live on trading. Here’s how much of the asset’s circulating supply these funds hold now.
 
Bitcoin Spot ETFs Now Carry This Much Of The Cryptocurrency’s Supply
 
On January 10, the much-anticipated spot ETFs gained approval for Bitcoin from the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). The next day, January 11th, these ETFs went live on trading, marking a historic day for the cryptocurrency.
 
Exchange-traded funds (ETFs) refer to financial instruments that allow investors to gain exposure to a commodity without actually owning said asset. In the case of BTC, ETFs can be a more appealing way to invest in the coin for traders who aren’t well-versed in how cryptocurrencies work.
 
 
The spot ETFs trade on traditional exchanges, so s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OFAC Blocks Venezuelan Gold Business, Warns About Upcoming Oil Sanctions]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74e9581143</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ofac-blocks-venezuelan-gold-business-warns-about-upcoming-oil-sanctions/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T17:33:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Office of Foreign Assets Control (OFAC) has revoked the license of Minerven, the Venezuela-owned gold company, for commercializing gold in international markets. The sanctions on Minerven, which were eased in October, will be applied again on February 13, with oil and gas sanctions reported to return in April.
OFAC Winds Down Venezuelan Gold Operations in International Markets
The U.S. Treasury Office of Foreign Assets Control (OFAC) has revoked a license that allowed CVG Compania General de Mineria de Venezuela CA (Minerven), the Venezuela state-owned gold company, to be part of gold transactions in international markets. The U.S. convened to revoke the sanctions on Minerven back in October when an agreement was reached with Maduro’s government to review the participation of key oppos…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Arrows Capital-Backed OPNX Exchange Faces Imminent Shutdown]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74e9470a41</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/opnx-exchange-faces-imminent-shutdown/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T16:44:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OPNX (Open Exchange), a Singapore-based cryptocurrency exchange established by the co-founders of the failed crypto hedge fund Three Arrows Capital (3AC), is set to cease operations less than a year after its inception. 
 
OPNX To Shut Down Amidst Legal Issues
 
OPNX was launched by Zhu Su and Kyle Davies, along with co-founders Mark Lamb and Leslie Lamb, to make a comeback following the collapse of Three Arrows Capital and the infamous fall of Sam Bankman-Fried’s crypto exchange FTX. 
 
Mark and Leslie Lamb are also known for their involvement in CoinFlex, a digital asset exchange filed for restructuring in the Seychelles in August 2022. OPNX aimed to enable creditors of insolvent exchanges, such as FTX, to tokenize their claims and use them as collateral.
 
 
Zhu Su and Kyle Davies, scho…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s Mining Difficulty Skyrockets by 7.33%, Setting New Record for 2024]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74e9404e6f</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoins-mining-difficulty-skyrockets-by-7-33-setting-new-record-for-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T16:35:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Friday, Feb. 2, 2024, the Bitcoin network witnessed a significant milestone as its mining complexity metric surged by 7.33% at block height 828,576. This marked the most substantial increase in difficulty for the year thus far. The current level of difficulty stands at 75.50 trillion, reaffirming its status as the most challenging period for bitcoin mining to date.
 
Bitcoin’s 7.33% Mining Difficulty Spike Marks 2024 Record
 

 
Bitcoin (BTC) mining has recently become a far more challenging endeavor, with the difficulty metric rising by an impressive 7.33%, marking the most significant increase in 2024. This notable rise comes on the heels of a 3.90% decrease observed on Jan. 20. 2024 has witnessed a total of two increases and one reduction in mining difficulty thus far. Additionally, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Ends Week Up 2%, PYTH Gains 15% on Binance Listing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215416</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/215416/bitcoin-ends-week-up-2-pyth-gains-15-binance-listing"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T16:34:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ended the week up slightly after a strong U.S. jobs report dashed remaining hopes the Fed will drop interest rates in March.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Enters the Field: Juventus Welcomes Zondacrypto as Sponsor]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74e940c97a</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/crypto-enters-the-field-juventus-welcomes-zondacrypto-as-sponsor/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T16:31:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zondacrypto has announced its sponsorship of  
Juventus F.C., one of Italy's most successful football clubs. The partnership,  
unveiled with anticipation by both parties, marks a stride in Zondacrypto's  
expansion into the Italian market while reinforcing Juventus' stature as a  
global footballing powerhouse.
Zondacrypto's Sponsorship  
and Juventus' Pursuit of Excellence
The announcement comes amidst a backdrop of  
shared values and aspirations between the cryptocurrency platform and the  
football club. Drawing parallels between the relentless pursuit of goals on and  
off the pitch, Zondacrypto's sponsorship aligns with Juventus' legacy of  
unyielding determination and pursuit of excellence, embodied by iconic figures  
such as Zinedine Zidane, Alessandro Del Piero, and Andrea Pirl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tareq Sikder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF Provider Valkyrie Adds BitGo as Second Custodian in Risk Mitigation Move]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74e94c26df</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/02/02/bitcoin-etf-provider-valkyrie-adds-bitgo-as-second-custodian-in-risk-mitigation-move/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T16:09:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The digital asset investment firm has become the first of the ETF providers to diversify custody of its coins by tapping BitGo's expertise in addition to Coinbase.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3-Year High: Bitcoin (BTC) Investor Sentiment Surges – Details]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74e94d49e2</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/3-year-high-bitcoin-investor-sentiment-surges/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T16:03:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a significant development for the cryptocurrency space, Bitcoin (BTC) is experiencing a surge in accumulation, reaching a three-year high in the Accumulation Trend Score. This indicates growing confidence from major players in the market.
 
 
Crypto analyst Ali Martinez first brought attention to this trend, highlighting that the Accumulation Trend Score has remained near 1 for the past four months. This score is used to gauge the buying activity of large entities, and a value closer to 1 suggests active accumulation.
 
 
#Bitcoin is witnessing one of its most significant accumulation streaks in almost 3 years!
 
Notably, the Accumulation Trend Score has hovered near 1 for the past 4 months, signaling that larger entities are accumulating $BTC. This trend indicates strong confidence in …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[1,210 ‘Sleeping Bitcoins’ From 2016 Stir After Years of Inactivity, Following Previous Day’s Mysterious Movements]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74e949f4b6</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/1210-sleeping-bitcoins-from-2016-stir-after-years-of-inactivity-following-previous-days-mysterious-movements/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T15:35:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On the final day of January 2024, a series of nine enigmatic transactions emerged from wallets established in 2016. Subsequently, another tranche of 15 transactions from wallets created on that same day in 2016 moved a total of 1,210.41 bitcoin, valued at $52 million. This marked the first movement of these funds in almost eight years.
 
After the 9 Enigmatic Transactions 2 Days Ago, the Same 2016 Whale Moves a Tranche of Bitcoins Worth $52 Million
 

 
In the last three days, an entity that accumulated a significant amount of bitcoins in 2016 has chosen to transfer these assets for the first time in several years. On Feb. 1, 2023, Bitcoin.com News covered the activity of a 2016 whale, highlighting the transfer of 726 BTC across nine separate bitcoin wallets, with each transaction involvin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Farm the Aevo Airdrop on Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215296</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/215296/how-to-farm-aevo-airdrop-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T15:22:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aevo, an Ethereum decentralized perpetual futures and options exchange, announced an airdrop program this week. Here's how to make the most of it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Play Games Like 'Doom' on Bitcoin and Dogecoin—Here’s What That Means]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=214570</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/how-play-classic-games-doom-bitcoin-dogecoin"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T15:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Legendary games like Pac-Man and Tetris are running on Bitcoin and beyond, but what does that even mean? Here’s what you need to know.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Behind $400 Million FTX Breach Have Been Exposed]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74e932ee61</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/hackers-400-million-ftx-breach/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T14:39:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recent report has provided insights into the hackers who may have been responsible for the infamous hack on the defunct FTX. This breach, which occurred after FTX filed for bankruptcy had led to the hackers draining over $400 million worth of crypto from the crypto exchange. 
 
DOJ Charges Three People Like Responsible For FTX Hack
 
According to Bloomberg, the Department of Justice (DOJ) has charged Robert Powell, Emily Hernandez, and Carter Rohn for their involvement in a SIM-swapping ring that targeted a crypto exchange and other individuals. 
 
 
The report noted that the court documents didn’t mention FTX as the crypto exchange that was hacked, but there was confirmation from sources familiar with the case that it was indeed FTX. Specifically, these hackers are reported to have gain…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Hidden New AI Model From Google Beats OpenAI's Dall-E and MidJourney—For Free]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215362</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/215362/google-imagefx-bard-better-than-midjourney-dall-e-free"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T12:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tucked behind a drop-down menu in Google’s suite of AI tools, ImageFX makes photorealistic, high quality images —and even gives you suggestions to improve them. See how it compares against its rivals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bipartisan Lawmakers Seek to Repeal SEC Crypto Accounting Policy]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215406</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/215406/bipartisan-lawmakers-seek-to-repeal-sec-crypto-accounting-policy"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T11:49:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Senator Cynthia Lummis and Representatives Wiley Nickel and Mike Flood introduced a joint resolution to repeal SEC Staff Accounting Bill 121.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$4.2 Million Worth of Stolen XRP Tokens Frozen on Binance]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215405</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/215405/4-2-million-worth-of-stolen-xrp-tokens-frozen-on-binance"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T10:30:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's good news, but there's still a lot of funds missing. The exploiter made off with $113 million worth of XRP.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grand Jury Indicts Hackers Linked to $400 Million Stolen from FTX]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215367</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/215367/grand-jury-indicts-hackers-linked-to-400-million-stolen-from-ftx"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T02:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Three Americans have been charged with orchestrating the massive attack on the failed cryptocurrency exchange.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From NFT Punchline to $8 Million Raise, ‘Pixelmon’ Preps for MON Token Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215348</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/215348/from-nft-punchline-8-million-raise-pixelmon-preps-mon-token-launch"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T01:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kevin lives! Under new ownership and with fresh funding, Pixelmon is ready to roll out games and debut its MON-powered IP protocol.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OPNX, the Crypto Exchange From the Founders of Bankrupt Three Arrows Capital, Is Shutting Down]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215346</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/215346/opnx-the-crypto-exchange-from-bankrupt-three-arrows-capital-is-shutting-down"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T00:48:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pitched as a "home for those harmed by crypto crises," the Open Exchange prepares to meet its own demise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Kawailani Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Andrew Tate Disavowed Crypto—Now He's Pitching His Own Coin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215326</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/215326/andrew-tate-shitcoin-token-coin"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T23:44:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The "most famous man alive" had his Bitcoin seized, but is mulling minting his own token.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Larry David Lost Money on FTX Too—An 'Idiot' for Doing the Ad, He Says]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215293</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/215293/larry-david-lost-money-ftx-too-idiot-doing-ad-he-says"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T23:24:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comedian Larry David admits regret for doing that Super Bowl ad for FTX—and wouldn't mind getting in on the class action lawsuit against him and other celebs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jupiter Founder Brushes Off Airdrop Backlash: 'People Don’t Understand Anything']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215295</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/215295/jupiter-founder-solana-airdrop-backlash-response"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T20:53:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The pseudonymous Meow isn’t bothered by the ‘FUD,” and says crypto influencers crying foul “only understand buy/sell.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Collapsed Genesis Agrees to Settle SEC’s Earn Lawsuit for $21M]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215289</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/215289/genesis-failed-crypto-lender-settles-sec-lawsuit-21-million"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T20:16:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC hit the failed crypto lender with a lawsuit last January, calling its Gemini Earn product a security.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Ordinals Mint for Quantum Cats Delayed Again—What's Going On?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215283</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/215283/bitcoin-ordinals-mint-for-quantum-cats-is-delayed-again"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T20:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Technical issues push back the highly awaited Taproots Wizard NFT mint for a second time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Billionaire Arthur Hayes: It's Time to ‘Get Back on the Solana Train’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215282</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/215282/get-back-on-the-solana-train-arthur-hayes-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T19:35:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The respected crypto authority predicts a significant rally for Solana (SOL) amid brewing banking sector challenges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jupiter Founder Meow Unloads on the Solana Airdrop 'FUD']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/YSpISivs/jupiter-founder-meow-unloads-on-the-solana-airdrop-fud</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/YSpISivs/jupiter-founder-meow-unloads-on-the-solana-airdrop-fud"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T18:35:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meow, the pseudonymous founder of Solana DEX aggregator Jupiter, made a surprise appearance today on Rug Radio's "FOMO Hour" to address the JUP airdrop "FUD,"  and explain why he believes the backlash to the team's launch liquidity pool is unfounded.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Overwatch’ Esports League Bans Crypto, NFT, and AI Sponsors]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215273</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/215273/overwatch-esports-league-crypto-nft-ai-sponsor-ban"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T18:15:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blizzard’s new Overwatch Champions Series says “no thanks” to esports teams that have crypto and AI sponsors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[El Salvador Will Race Ahead With Bitcoin Plans If Bukele Wins Reelection]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215265</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/215265/el-salvador-race-ahead-bitcoin-plans-bukele-wins-reelection"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T17:37:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[El Salvador president Nayib Bukele is set to win Sunday's election, polls say. And if he does, he'll continue with his Bitcoin push.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon Labs Cuts 60 Staff in Ethereum Scaler's Latest Shakeup]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215252</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/215252/polygon-labs-cuts-60-staff-ethereum-scaler-latest-shakeup"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T16:49:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company behind Ethereum scaling network Polygon has laid off 19% of its team, less than a year after an even larger layoff.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mutant Ape Game 'Serum City' Launches—How to Claim an Ethereum NFT Pass]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215245</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/215245/mutant-ape-game-serum-city-launches-how-claim-ethereum-nft-pass"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T16:43:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[City-builder game Serum City is now live, and holders of Bored Ape NFTs and more can claim a free Ethereum access pass.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Future is Multichain w/ Jason Trikakis from Holograph]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QGJdd57G/the-future-is-multichain-w-jason-trikakis-from-holograph</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QGJdd57G/the-future-is-multichain-w-jason-trikakis-from-holograph"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T16:21:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reza is joined by Jason from Holograph.xyz

They dive into the multichain future and what that means for NFTs, DeFi, RWAs, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Parallel' Teases Open Beta Plans as New Ethereum NFT Cards Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215233</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/215233/parallel-teases-open-beta-plans-new-ethereum-nft-cards-launch"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T16:21:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GG’s 2023 Game of the Year debuts new NFT cards with the Season 1 battle pass—and the Parallel open beta launch is coming soon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum’s Dencun Upgrade: Technical Overview and Potential Market Impact]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215212</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/ethereums-dencun-upgrade-technical-overview-and-potential-market-impact"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T15:52:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dencun introduces "proto-danksharding" to Ethereum, aiming to decrease transaction costs for layer-2 blockchains and address scalability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ilan Hazan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Launches In-App Bitcoin Inscriptions Marketplace for BRC-20 Tokens]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215204</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/215204/binance-launches-in-app-bitcoin-inscriptions-marketplace-brc-20-tokens"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T14:59:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Binance Inscriptions Marketplace provides a "one-stop solution" within the Binance Web3 Wallet for Bitcoin BRC-20 tokens such as ORDI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Most New Ethereum Tokens Appear to Be Pump and Dumps—But There's Good News]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215205</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/215205/ethereum-tokens-pump-and-dumps-chainalysis"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T13:59:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The potentially scammy tokens only represented 1.3% of DEX volume in 2023, suggesting only a small number of traders fall for them, according to a Chainalysis report.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Ramps Up Monitoring of Crypto Miners' Energy Use]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215198</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/215198/us-ramps-up-monitoring-of-crypto-miners-energy-use"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T11:35:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Energy Information Administration will track U.S. crypto miners' energy consumption following an “emergency collection of data request.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Fortnite' Fail: Epic Games Scrambles to Remove Racist AI-Generated Images]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215146</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/215146/fortnite-fail-epic-games-scrambles-remove-racist-ai-generated-images"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T02:17:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer Epic Games is working to purge user-created islands with imagery depicting racist stereotypes, apparently generated by AI tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Is Key to Microsoft’s Blockbuster Growth, Quarterly Earnings Show]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215184</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/215184/ai-is-key-to-microsofts-blockbuster-growth-quarterly-earnings-show"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T01:57:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Logging a staggering 30% growth in Azure and a 49% increase in gaming revenue, Microsoft's AI strategy is paying off.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inject Botox Where? Twitter Weighs In On Billionaire Biohacker's New Penis Plan]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215181</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/215181/penis-botox-injections-increase-length-bryan-johnson-biohacking-longevity"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T01:11:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bryan Johnson's latest venture in his longevity mission is Botox injections for erectile enhancement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[People Are Going Nuts for This New 'Crypto-AR' Game on Solana]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215156</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/215156/gg-zip-crypto-ar-solana-hunger-games"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T00:39:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Early access for a mobile augmented reality game based on "Hunger Games" is causing a frenzy among the crypto kids.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Bitcoin DeFi Exchange Wants to Save You From Hacks]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215174</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/215174/bitcoin-defi-dex-decentralized-exchange-portal"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T00:32:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Swapping BTC for other crypto is risky. Flush with new cash, San Francisco-based Portal wants to put your mind at ease.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana's Jupiter Hits $1.2 Billion in Daily Volume, Outpacing Uniswap on Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215162</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/215162/solanas-jupiter-hits-1-2-billion-in-daily-volume-outpacing-uniswap-on-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2024-01-31T23:48:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jupiter is seeing surging trading action amid the JUP airdrop on Solana—and it’s way ahead of Ethereum’s Uniswap V3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nintendo Switch 2 Preview: Everything You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197793</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197793/nintendo-switch-2-rumors-leaks-latest-news"/>
        <updated>2024-01-31T22:31:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATED: Will Electronic Arts embrace the Switch 2? Read how EA's CEO responded when asked about Nintendo's next console.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GME 2.0? 'GameStop' Meme Coin on Solana Keeps Pumping]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215138</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/215138/gme-2-0-gamestop-meme-coin-solana-keeps-pumping"/>
        <updated>2024-01-31T21:57:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The GameStop meme stock craze has given way to a GME tribute coin on Solana—and it’s still rising and rising.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Argentina President Javier Milei Drops Crypto Tax Plan]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215122</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/215122/argentina-president-javier-milei-drops-crypto-tax-plan"/>
        <updated>2024-01-31T21:13:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Argentine President Javier Milei has rewritten the country’s sweeping reform bill and jettisoned crypto amidst debate over more fundamental issues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Generative AI Makes for a More Inclusive Metaverse in 'Avalon']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/J5j39bBG/how-generative-ai-makes-for-a-more-inclusive-metaverse-in-avalon</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/J5j39bBG/how-generative-ai-makes-for-a-more-inclusive-metaverse-in-avalon"/>
        <updated>2024-01-31T04:31:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avalon Chief Product Officer Jeffrey Butler speaks with Decrypt reporter Jason Nelson about the use of generative AI within the upcoming game and how it will help players from anywhere and everywhere truly see themselves represented in the online world.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a Perfume DAO Crafted a 'Scent of the Metaverse']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LIUXdAv0/how-a-perfume-dao-crafted-a-scent-of-the-metaverse</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LIUXdAv0/how-a-perfume-dao-crafted-a-scent-of-the-metaverse"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T18:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rook Perfumes founder Nadeem Crowe and Melissa Gilmour of Web3 creative agency Lily & Piper join Stephen Graves to talk about how they created a fragrance with a DAO and brought it to the shelves of London department store Harvey Nichols.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trash-Fueled BTC Mining w/ Chris Bennet]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/uLy5Y1E7/trash-fueled-btc-mining-w-chris-bennet</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/uLy5Y1E7/trash-fueled-btc-mining-w-chris-bennet"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T19:09:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reza is joined by Chris Bennet from Spacestation Investments.

They discuss:
- Mining BTC with energy generated from landfills
- How to increase deal-flow
- Running an agency vs running a fund]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Preview of Agoria's 'Le Code d’Orsay']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PK7ynKMB/preview-of-agorias-le-code-dorsay</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PK7ynKMB/preview-of-agorias-le-code-dorsay"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A first look at "Sigma Lumina," a sculpture by artist and musician Agoria in collaboration with Johan Lescure. It features in "Le Code d’Orsay," the first NFT exhibition at the Musée d’Orsay.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are you the one being farmed? w/ Frisson]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/i3sesrao/are-you-the-one-being-farmed-w-frisson</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/i3sesrao/are-you-the-one-being-farmed-w-frisson"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T18:38:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reza is joined by Frisson from Tallyx.xyz

They reflect on:
- building in the bear market
- the points system meta
- will zoomers care about decentralization]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Look Touch Own': OONA Discusses Her Performance Art Exhibition]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/79jpGlCe/look-touch-own-oona-discusses-her-performance-art-exhibition</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/79jpGlCe/look-touch-own-oona-discusses-her-performance-art-exhibition"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T16:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Conceptual artist OONA joins moderator Raina Marie to discuss "Look Touch Own," her performance art exhibition featuring her own former breast implants, which have been tokenized. This conversation was recorded at Rug Radio's R Haus event at Art Basel Miami in December 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Genius Marketing by Genius Marketers: How Crypto Builders Can Reach the Masses]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/YiQgzWJW/genius-marketing-by-genius-marketers-how-crypto-builders-can-reach-the-masses</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/YiQgzWJW/genius-marketing-by-genius-marketers-how-crypto-builders-can-reach-the-masses"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rug Radio founder Farokh Sarmad moderates a conversation between 9dcc founder and CEO Gmoney and Serotonin founder and CEO Amanda Cassatt about the challenges and opportunities in Web3 marketing and how they're navigating the ever-evolving space. Recorded at Rug Radio's R Haus event at Art Basel Miami in December 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generative Art Across Mediums: Artists Discuss the Evolving Space]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/GK3aN0zo/generative-art-across-mediums-artists-discuss-the-evolving-space</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/GK3aN0zo/generative-art-across-mediums-artists-discuss-the-evolving-space"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T02:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this panel discussion from Rug Radio's R Haus at Art Basel Miami 2023, Sofia Garcia, Ismail Tazi, Emily Edelman, and Aleksandra Art discuss the expanding generative art space—and why "generative" doesn't necessarily have to mean digital.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The AI Coin to Rule Them All with Mike Grantis]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rkYpU8TJ/the-ai-coin-to-rule-them-all-with-mike-grantis</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rkYpU8TJ/the-ai-coin-to-rule-them-all-with-mike-grantis"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T18:46:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reza is joined by Mike Grantis from Contango Digital to discuss
- The AI coin to rule them all
- The Solana Ecosystem 
- What's next for Solana airdrops]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conversation With Snowfro: Bringing 'Chromie Squiggle' #8107 to the Physical Space]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/DcrU04gG/conversation-with-snowfro-bringing-chromie-squiggle-8107-to-the-physical-space</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/DcrU04gG/conversation-with-snowfro-bringing-chromie-squiggle-8107-to-the-physical-space"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Art Blocks founder and CEO and "Chromie Squiggle" project creator Erick "snowfro" Calderon spoke with Benny Redbeard Gross at Rug Radio's R Haus event at Art Basel 2023, to discuss how and why "Chromie Squiggle" NFT #8107 was given a special edition print run in collaboration with Avant Arte.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don't Underestimate Mobile Gaming: Qualcomm's Matthew Grossman]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/34Oil4Qu/dont-underestimate-mobile-gaming-qualcomms-matthew-grossman</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/34Oil4Qu/dont-underestimate-mobile-gaming-qualcomms-matthew-grossman"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Qualcomm product marketing manager Matthew Grossman tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin why mobile esports is exploding in popularity around the world—and dispels some of the misconceptions around mobile gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF: This Is the 'Calm Before the Storm', Says ETF Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/VOX04ytt/bitcoin-etf-this-is-the-calm-before-the-storm-says-etf-analyst</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/VOX04ytt/bitcoin-etf-this-is-the-calm-before-the-storm-says-etf-analyst"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T20:20:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bloomberg Senior ETF Analyst Eric Balchunas joins Farokh Sarmad, Michael Anderson, and Ovie Faruq on the FOMO Hour to share the latest intel on the looming approval for a spot Bitcoin ETF, what might happen when the very different worlds of TradFi and crypto collide, and his insights on “Genslish,” the unique and strategic language of SEC chair Gary Gensler.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>