<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-06-17T01:18:50.194Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-06-17T01:18:50.194Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celsius to DUMP $215 Million in Altcoins? #shorts]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18593847/Celsius-to-DUMP-215-Million-in-Altcoins-shorts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18593847/Celsius-to-DUMP-215-Million-in-Altcoins-shorts"/>
        <updated>2023-06-17T01:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celsius to DUMP $215 Million in Altcoins? Bankrupt Crypto lender Celsius has proposed a plan to sell off $215 Million dollars worth of altcoins it holds for its users and convert them to BTC and ETH on July 1st. There larges holdings are $70 Million of CEL tokens and $52 Million of Matic!...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Korean Security Tokens Market ‘May Be Worth $287B by 2030’]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18593848/South-Korean-Security-Tokens-Market-May-Be-Worth-287B-by-2030</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18593848/South-Korean-Security-Tokens-Market-May-Be-Worth-287B-by-2030"/>
        <updated>2023-06-17T01:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[South Korea’s financial industry thinks the nation’s security token offerings (STO) market could be worth $287 billion by 2030, with the biggest commercial banks in the country “lining up” to get involved. Per EDaily, the Hana Financial Group’s Management Research Institute predicted that the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto whistleblower ZachXBT sued in defamation case, invites donations]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18593842/Crypto-whistleblower-ZachXBT-sued-in-defamation-case-invites-donations</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18593842/Crypto-whistleblower-ZachXBT-sued-in-defamation-case-invites-donations"/>
        <updated>2023-06-17T00:58:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ZachXBT, a prominent whistleblower in the crypto community, is named in a June 15 lawsuit that alleges he published a defamatory article. Crypto entrepreneur Machi Big Brother wrote on June 16: A year ago, [ZachXBT] published a Medium article about me that damaged my reputation … I have...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nike teases upcoming ‘Airphoria’ NFT sneaker hunt on Fortnite]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18593840/Nike-teases-upcoming-Airphoria-NFT-sneaker-hunt-on-Fortnite</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18593840/Nike-teases-upcoming-Airphoria-NFT-sneaker-hunt-on-Fortnite"/>
        <updated>2023-06-17T00:45:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a short promotional video, Nike’s logo for its web3 platform .SWOOSH features alongside the logos for Epic Games’ Unreal Engine and Fortnite game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Government Sued for Allegedly Seizing $100,000,000 in Cash, Gold and Jewelry From Citizens Without Explanation]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18593818/US-Government-Sued-for-Allegedly-Seizing-100000000-in-Cash-Gold-and-Jewelry-From-Citizens-Without-Explanation</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18593818/US-Government-Sued-for-Allegedly-Seizing-100000000-in-Cash-Gold-and-Jewelry-From-Citizens-Without-Explanation"/>
        <updated>2023-06-17T00:04:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US government won’t specify why it abruptly seized more than $100 million from people’s safety deposit boxes in California, according to a new lawsuit. The nonprofit Institute for Justice says it’s seeking to halt forfeiture proceedings for a group of citizens who’ve had their assets...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Rival Polkadot (DOT) Launches New Governance System, but Token Price Slumps Amid Bearish Market Trend]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18593819/Ethereum-Rival-Polkadot-DOT-Launches-New-Governance-System-but-Token-Price-Slumps-Amid-Bearish-Market-Trend</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18593819/Ethereum-Rival-Polkadot-DOT-Launches-New-Governance-System-but-Token-Price-Slumps-Amid-Bearish-Market-Trend"/>
        <updated>2023-06-17T00:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) challenger Polkadot (DOT) is revamping its decision-making system with the introduction of a new decentralized and open governance platform, OpenGov. The launch of OpenGov places full control of the network in the hands of the Polkadot community by allowing holders of native token...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bittrex US Allows Fiat and Crypto Withdrawals Amid Bankruptcy Proceedings]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757d804e66</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bittrex-us-allows-fiat-and-crypto-withdrawals-amid-bankruptcy-proceedings/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T23:37:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bittrex US, the now-defunct cryptocurrency exchange in the United States, has recently introduced a plan that permits American customers to withdraw crypto and fiat from the platform, provided they satisfy the required regulatory criteria. This withdrawal arrangement was approved on Tuesday by the U.S. bankruptcy court located in Delaware.
 
Cryptocurrency Exchange Bittrex US Enables Customer Withdrawals
 
On May 8, 2023, Bittrex US filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy protection, citing liabilities ranging from $500 million to $1 billion and having over 100,000 creditors. Before the bankruptcy filing, the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) had sued Bittrex for running an unregistered exchange, broker, and clearing agency, and for listing unregistered crypto securities.
 
Bittrex sent emails to its U.S. customers this week, following approval from the U.S. bankruptcy court to enable withdrawals. However, there is a caveat: users must update their know-your-customer (KYC) information and agree to the latest terms of service. Bittrex asserts that this step is “necessary to comply with state and federal regulations.”
 
 
Withdrawals opened on June 15, 2023, and the company has provided resources for identity verification, withdrawal instructions, and wire instructions. “Customers have until August 31, 2023, to withdraw any remaining funds,” Bittrex states. While cryptocurrency withdrawals are relatively simple, fiat withdrawals require the submission of an application to link a bank account. Additionally, there is a $25 wire fee for customers who choose to wire funds through Bittrex.
 
What are your thoughts on Bittrex US allowing fund withdrawals for customers amidst its bankruptcy proceedings? Share your thoughts and opinions about this subject in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uniswap Taps Wormhole and Axelar For Cross-Chain Bridging After Lengthy Analysis]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18593828/Uniswap-Taps-Wormhole-and-Axelar-For-Cross-Chain-Bridging-After-Lengthy-Analysis</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18593828/Uniswap-Taps-Wormhole-and-Axelar-For-Cross-Chain-Bridging-After-Lengthy-Analysis"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T23:35:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bridges Will Be Used to Govern Uniswap's Non-Ethereum Deployments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Asked an Insider if the Bitcoin ETF Will Pass]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18593795/I-Asked-an-Insider-if-the-Bitcoin-ETF-Will-Pass</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18593795/I-Asked-an-Insider-if-the-Bitcoin-ETF-Will-Pass"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T23:24:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blackrock, the world's largest asset manager, has filed for a Bitcoin spot ETF. Eric Balchunas (ETF Expert) joins the podcast to discuss the chances the BTC ETF gets approved, when it would pass, how a Bitcoin ETF would work, the price impact, Grayscale Bitcoin trust, Gold ETFs, what it means...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Newly Released Documents Detail Tether’s Exposure to Chinese Securities]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18593829/Newly-Released-Documents-Detail-Tethers-Exposure-to-Chinese-Securities</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18593829/Newly-Released-Documents-Detail-Tethers-Exposure-to-Chinese-Securities"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T23:09:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Media Obtain Tether’s 2021 Financials Via Freedom of Information Request.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CFTC to Review Prediction Market Kalshi’s Contracts to Bet on Control of Congress]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757d8365e1</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/06/16/cftc-to-review-prediction-market-kalshis-contracts-to-bet-on-control-of-congress/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T22:59:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Commodity Futures Trading Commission will decide on June 26 whether to start a formal 90-day review of prediction market provider KalshiEX’s contract that allows users to bet on which party takes control of the U.S. Congress.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Detective ZachXBT Faces Defamation Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757d8365cf</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/06/16/crypto-detective-zachxbt-faces-defamation-lawsuit/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T22:59:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MachiBigBrother has sued ZachXBT for an investigation the latter published in June 2022 alleging the trader stole tens of millions of dollars worth of crypto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Napolitano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CFTC to Review Prediction Market Kalshi’s Contracts to Bet on Control of Congress]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18593763/CFTC-to-Review-Prediction-Market-Kalshis-Contracts-to-Bet-on-Control-of-Congress</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18593763/CFTC-to-Review-Prediction-Market-Kalshis-Contracts-to-Bet-on-Control-of-Congress"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T22:57:25.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Sleuth ZachXBT Sued, Doxxed by Former Target]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145025</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145025/crypto-sleuth-zachxbt-sued-doxxed-by-former-target"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T22:50:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jeffrey Huang filed suit over allegations that he stole $38M in crypto. Now ZachXBT has enlisted Johnny Depp's lawyers to fight the claims.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DAI Emerges as Third-Largest Stablecoin, Overtaking BUSD in Market Capitalization]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757d8d49cd</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/dai-emerges-as-third-largest-stablecoin-overtaking-busd-in-market-capitalization/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T22:36:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Makerdao’s DAI stablecoin is now the third-largest stablecoin by market capitalization, surpassing Binance USD (BUSD), which has officially declined to $4.304 billion. DAI’s market valuation on Friday, June 16, 2023, is approximately $4.394 billion, but the number of circulating DAI has decreased by 5.7% since last month.
 
Stablecoin Rankings Shuffle: DAI Ascends to Third-Largest Stablecoin Position
 
In May 2022, terra usd (UST), now known as terra usd classic (USTC), decoupled from its $1 parity, causing its value to plummet by over 98%. As a result, BUSD emerged as the third-largest stablecoin asset. Additionally, the stablecoin token issued by Paxos held a position among the top ten largest crypto assets by market valuation for several months, until February 13, 2023, when the New Yor…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big Eyes Price Prediction - 99% Crash, Token Claim Fail, Coffeezilla Video Soon?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18593754/Big-Eyes-Price-Prediction-99-Crash-Token-Claim-Fail-Coffeezilla-Video-Soon</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18593754/Big-Eyes-Price-Prediction-99-Crash-Token-Claim-Fail-Coffeezilla-Video-Soon"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T22:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Crypto to Buy Now 16 June – Immutable X, Curve DAO, NEO]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18593742/Best-Crypto-to-Buy-Now-16-June-Immutable-X-Curve-DAO-NEO</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18593742/Best-Crypto-to-Buy-Now-16-June-Immutable-X-Curve-DAO-NEO"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T22:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin is currently up about 3% in the past 24 hours, thanks in part to investment management corporation BlackRock's commitment to creating a Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF). This has also led to a price increase in Ether and other leading non-stablecoin cryptocurrencies. With the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock Bitcoin ETF Is the ‘Real Deal’—Is This Finally the One?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145000</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145000/blackrock-bitcoin-etf-real-deal"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T22:02:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For 10 years, crypto startup after crypto startup has tried its luck with the SEC. Now Wall Street’s heaviest hitter is lending its weight.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Billionaire Mike Novogratz Says BlackRock Filing for a Bitcoin ETF Is the Best Thing That Could Happen to BTC]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18593737/Billionaire-Mike-Novogratz-Says-BlackRock-Filing-for-a-Bitcoin-ETF-Is-the-Best-Thing-That-Could-Happen-to-BTC</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18593737/Billionaire-Mike-Novogratz-Says-BlackRock-Filing-for-a-Bitcoin-ETF-Is-the-Best-Thing-That-Could-Happen-to-BTC"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T22:01:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Billionaire Mike Novogratz says that BlackRock filing for a Bitcoin (BTC) exchange-traded fund (ETF) is the best thing that could happen to the king crypto. In a new interview on The Claman Countdown, the Galaxy Digital chief executive says that he’s hoping for BlackRock, an investment firm with...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Allegedly Attacked By SEC’s Hinman For Ethereum’s Benefit]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18593736/XRP-Allegedly-Attacked-By-SECs-Hinman-For-Ethereums-Benefit</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18593736/XRP-Allegedly-Attacked-By-SECs-Hinman-For-Ethereums-Benefit"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T22:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Detective ZachXBT Faces Defamation Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18593724/Crypto-Detective-ZachXBT-Faces-Defamation-Lawsuit</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18593724/Crypto-Detective-ZachXBT-Faces-Defamation-Lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T21:59:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MachiBigBrother has sued ZachXBT for an investigation the latter published in June 2022 alleging the trader stole tens of millions of dollars worth of crypto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain sleuth ZachXBT sued for libel after claiming plaintiff drained funds from project]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18593725/On-chain-sleuth-ZachXBT-sued-for-libel-after-claiming-plaintiff-drained-funds-from-project</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18593725/On-chain-sleuth-ZachXBT-sued-for-libel-after-claiming-plaintiff-drained-funds-from-project"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T21:58:16.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Judge Considers if Crashed Coins of Terraform Labs Were Securities]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757d8ab5b5</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/us-judge-considers-if-crashed-coins-of-terraform-labs-were-securities/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T21:36:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A judge in the United States considered on Thursday whether the cryptocurrencies created by Terraform Labs were securities. The failed blockchain firm and its founder, Do Kwon, have asked the court to dismiss a case filed by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) alleging that they defrauded investors whom they sold unregistered securities. 
 
Judge Reviews Status of the Digital Assets Sold by Terraform in SEC’s Fraud Case
 
A judge in New York has considered whether the digital coins issued by Terraform Labs were securities during a hearing in the SEC’s case against the crypto company and its South Korean co-founder and CEO Kwon Do-Hyung, better known as Do Kwon.
 
Earlier this year, the U.S. securities regulator charged the crypto entrepreneur and his company with defrauding i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lubomir Tassev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is BlackRock's Bitcoin ETF Application A Political Message?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18593692/Is-BlackRocks-Bitcoin-ETF-Application-A-Political-Message</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18593692/Is-BlackRocks-Bitcoin-ETF-Application-A-Political-Message"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T21:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[World's largest asset manager BlackRock has filed for a Bitcoin spot ETF. They've been approved for 575 out of their last 576 ETF applications. Given that there are no indications that the SEC has changed its tune on spot ETFs, the industry is left asking: what does Larry Fink know that we...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blackrock Bitcoin ETF | Larry Fink's Plot to Control Bitcoin!!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18593683/Blackrock-Bitcoin-ETF-Larry-Finks-Plot-to-Control-Bitcoin</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18593683/Blackrock-Bitcoin-ETF-Larry-Finks-Plot-to-Control-Bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T21:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beeple Says It's Time to Delete Your JPEGs—Here's Why]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144980</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144980/beeple-says-time-delete-your-jpegs-heres-why"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T21:17:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Was the $11 million Sotheby's auction on Thursday the "final hurrah" for NFTs? Leading artists and collectors in the space push back.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beeple Says It's Time to Delete Your JPEGs—Here's Why]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18593675/Beeple-Says-Its-Time-to-Delete-Your-JPEGsHeres-Why</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18593675/Beeple-Says-Its-Time-to-Delete-Your-JPEGsHeres-Why"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T21:17:58.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Look at the Reserve Statements That Tether Tried to Conceal]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144994</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144994/a-look-at-the-reserve-statements-that-tether-tried-to-conceal"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T21:17:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Documents released from the New York Attorney General's investigation into Tether confirmed rumors that it held securities issued by Chinese companies to support its USDT reserves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Look at the Reserve Statements That Tether Tried to Conceal]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18593676/A-Look-at-the-Reserve-Statements-That-Tether-Tried-to-Conceal</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18593676/A-Look-at-the-Reserve-Statements-That-Tether-Tried-to-Conceal"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T21:17:56.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock’s Spot Bitcoin ETF Not The Same As Grayscale’s Product, Experts Say]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757d768393</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/06/16/blackrocks-spot-bitcoin-etf-not-the-same-as-grayscales-product-experts-say/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T20:57:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Exchange Traded Fund (ETF) terminology can sometimes be tricky, and fund management giant BlackRock’s application for a spot Bitcoin ETF has raised some questions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock’s Bitcoin ETF Would Be a Big Deal]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757d77b81c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/06/16/blackrocks-bitcoin-etf-would-be-a-big-deal/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T20:46:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[And it doesn’t really matter if it’s technically a trust.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Kaloudis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock’s New Strategy: This Could Be The Key To Securing Bitcoin ETF Approval]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757d728d57</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/blackrocks-strategy-the-key-to-bitcoin-etf-approval/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T20:18:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock, the world’s largest asset manager, applied with the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) for its iShares Bitcoin (BTC) Trust to be listed and traded on the Nasdaq stock exchange.
 
However, the SEC has previously expressed concerns about the potential for market manipulation related to Bitcoin prices and has cited this as a reason for rejecting previous applications for BTC ETFs. 
 
To address this concern, BlackRock has partnered with Nasdaq to enter into a surveillance-sharing agreement with an operator of a spot trading platform for Bitcoin.
 
 
Potential Approval For Blackrock’s Spot Bitcoin ETF
 
The iShares Bitcoin Trust, filed by BlackRock, differs from other proposed BTC ETFs in key ways.
 
According to Blackrock’s application, the Trust will be issued by a Delawa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Abra Cease-and-Desist Reveals Ties to Binance and Prime Trust]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144947</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144947/abra-cease-and-desist-reveals-ties-to-binance-and-prime-trust"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T19:42:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Texas regulator claims Abra has ties to Binance and Prime Trust, and roughly $70M stuck on Babel, Genesis, and 3AC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Introduces 4% USDC Rewards Amidst SEC Dispute]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757d7f6159</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/coinbase-introduces-4-usdc-rewards-amidst-sec-dispute/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T19:32:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On June 15, the San Francisco-based cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase announced that customers can now earn 4% rewards on the stablecoin USDC. The news follows Coinbase’s current dispute with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) over the firm’s staking-as-a-service product.
 
Coinbase Rolls Out 4% Stablecoin Rewards for Global Customers, Except Hawaii Residents
 
Coinbase is now allowing users to earn 4% rewards by holding USDC on the centralized cryptocurrency trading platform, according to a Thursday announcement. “Grow your savings with a rewarding, secure digital dollar,” Coinbase announced. “Global Coinbase customers can now earn 4% rewards on USDC.” Coinbase explains that as little as $1 in USDC can be held on the exchange to earn rewards.
 
Coinbase’s most recent USDC rewards service comes in the wake of the exchange being sued by the SEC. The complaint alleges that the firm “failed to register its staking-as-a-service program as required by securities laws.” Additionally, the Alabama securities regulator contends that Coinbase violated state securities regulations by “offering its staking rewards program accounts to Alabama residents without a registration to offer or sell these securities.”
 
 
Regarding the recent USDC rewards service, Coinbase specifies that the annual percentage rate (APR) of 4% is subject to change. “The rewards rate is subject to change and can vary,” the exchange explained on Thursday. “Customers will be able to see the latest applicable rates directly within their accounts.”
 
The Coinbase rewards program is accessible in 71 countries, including the United States, but excludes residents of Hawaii. To participate, Coinbase customers must be verified at tier two, the exchange’s latest announcement concludes.
 
What are your thoughts on Coinbase’s decision to offer 4% rewards on USDC amidst its ongoing dispute with the SEC? We’d love to hear your perspective in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Europe Moves on AI Regulation to 'Counter Dangers to Democracy']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144973</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144973/europe-moves-ai-regulation-counter-dangers-democracy"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T19:29:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the United States stalls on AI regulation, the European Parliament is moving along after passing a draft law on Wednesday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donovan Choy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance France under Probe over ‘Illegal’ Crypto Service, Money Laundering: Report]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757d790e07</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/binance-france-under-probe-over-illegal-crypto-service-money-laundering-report/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T19:17:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance’s  
local unit in France is being investigated by public prosecutors in Paris over ‘illegal’ provision of crypto services before it was licensed  
in May last year, CoinDesk reports. The exchange is also being probed for ‘acts of  
aggravated money laundering”, the outlet said, citing the French city’s public  
prosecutor’s office. 
Local  
French daily, Le Monde, also reported receiving the same information from the  
prosecutor’s office. The outlet said Binance is suspected to have been offering digital  
asset services in the country since 2020. The exchange is also being scrutinized over the likelihood it engaged in crypto promotion  
before it became registered. 
French  
anti-financial crime agency, the Financial Judicial Investigation Service,  
started investigating Binance…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Solomon Oladipupo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Predicts 'Catastrophic Outcome' Without AI Regulation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144959</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144959/elon-musk-predicts-catastrophic-outcome-without-ai-regulation"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T18:52:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk is warning again that unchecked development of artificial intelligence can lead to a "catastrophic outcome" for humanity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Recrosses $26.3K to Hit Highest Level in a Week Amid BlackRock Optimism]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757d64c63c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/06/16/bitcoin-recrosses-263k-to-hit-highest-level-in-a-week-amid-blackrock-optimism/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T18:44:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Markets surged for a second time in the less than 24 hours following the fund management giant’s announcement that it had filed paperwork for the formation of a spot bitcoin ETF.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Rubin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Policy Chief Shirzad Squares Off With SEC Enforcement Director Grewal]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757d655f2f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/06/16/coinbase-policy-chief-shirzad-squares-off-with-sec-enforcement-director-grewal/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T18:39:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A sneak peek of the looming crypo regulatory prize fight highlights that everyone is talking past each other.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Z. Morris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GBTC Discount Narrows After BlackRock’s Filing for Spot Bitcoin ETF]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757d604113</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/06/16/gbtc-discount-narrows-after-blackrocks-filing-for-spot-bitcoin-etf/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T18:15:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fund manager Grayscale is currently in a legal standoff with the SEC after the agency denied an application to convert the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) into an exchange-traded fund.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto On Trial: U.S. Judge Examines Whether Terraform Labs’ Coins Are Securities]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757d6043de</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/judge-examines-terraform-coins-are-securities/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T18:15:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to a Reuters report, a U.S. judge is considering whether the digital assets created by Terraform Labs were securities in a case brought by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) against the company and its founder, Do Kwon.
 
Whether the tokens created by Terraform Labs constitute securities is central to the SEC’s fraud case, alleging that the company defrauded investors and sold billions of dollars in unregistered securities.
 
 
Terraform Labs’ Coins In The Hot Seat
 
The SEC’s complaint alleges that Terraform Labs and Kwon misled investors about the stability of TerraUSD and falsely claimed that their crypto tokens would increase in value. 
 
At a hearing on Thursday, U.S. District Judge Jed Rakoff questioned whether Terraform Labs’ offering of an Anchor protocol, which…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bakkt Takes Proactive Measures, Delists Polygon, Solana, and Cardano Amid Regulatory Crackdowns]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757d609062</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bakkt-takes-proactive-measures-delists-polygon-solana-and-cardano-amid-regulatory-crackdowns/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T18:13:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to a Fortune report published on June 16, the cryptocurrency asset platform Bakkt is delisting three cryptocurrencies due to the current regulatory climate. Bakkt’s general counsel stated that the platform will expand its coin offering once there is “further clarity.”
 
Bakkt Reacts to Regulatory Pressure, Delists Solana, Polygon, and Cardano
 
Bakkt, the New York-based digital asset platform, revealed Friday that it is delisting solana (SOL), polygon (MATIC), and cardano (ADA). The move comes as the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) intensifies its scrutiny of cryptocurrency platforms and designates certain assets as unregistered securities.
 
The announcement of Bakkt’s delisting of SOL, MATIC, and ADA was made by the company’s general counsel and secretary, Marc D’Annunzio, in an interview with Fortune. D’Annunzio stated that the proactive removal would continue “until there is further clarity on how to compliantly offer a more extensive list of coins.”
 
Prior to Bakkt’s decision, the digital trading platform Robinhood has chosen to delist cardano (ADA), solana (SOL), and polygon (MATIC). Similarly, Tel Aviv-based Etoro has announced the delisting of ALGO, MANA, DASH, and MATIC for U.S. customers, citing the same reasons. Both Robinhood and Etoro said the firms are implementing proactive measures until regulatory clarity is established in the United States.
 
 
All the tokens that were previously listed on Bakkt, Robinhood, and Etoro and subsequently delisted have been classified as unregistered securities by the U.S. SEC. The SEC’s enforcement lawsuits also identify XRP, TON, OMG, POWR, BTT, KIN, TRX, MIR, EMAX, ALGO, and IHT, among others, as securities.
 
Are the recent delistings by Bakkt, Robinhood, and Etoro a necessary step towards regulatory compliance, or do they hinder innovation in the cryptocurrency space? Share your thoughts and opinions about this subject in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Weeknd and Binance Enter the Metaverse]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144944</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144944/weeknd-launches-metaverse-game-amid-binance-backed-tour"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T18:10:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The digital experience arrives amid The Weeknd's Binance-sponsored, "crypto-powered" world tour, which is currently in Europe.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lucy Harley-McKeown</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bakkt to Delist Solana, Cardano and Polygon Following SEC Lawsuits]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144945</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144945/bakkt-to-delist-solana-cardano-and-polygon-following-sec-lawsuits"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T17:34:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The publicly-listed company is waiting for further regulatory clarity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Outlook for June]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757d6dcf28</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-price-outlook-for-june/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T17:33:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Halfway through June, crypto markets have been rocked by several macro factors, which have brought bears to return to action. Bitcoin has moved below $25,000 for the first time since March, as the Security and Exchange Commission (SEC) sued both Binance and Coinbase. The Federal Reserve has also paused its rate hike policy, with traders still unsure of what this could mean for markets.
 
Current Market Status
 
The action taken by the SEC earlier this month has been the main source of bearishness, with the regulator moving to crack down on operators in the space.
 
Following this, inflation in the United States fell to lower than expected, coming in at a low of 4%, briefly boosting the U.S. dollar.
 
However, with the Fed opting to keep rates unchanged for now, market uncertainty has heightened, with traders processing the potential long-term impacts of tighter monetary policy.
 
June Outlook
 
Bitcoin (BTC) rose back above $25,000 on Friday, as traders moved to buy the recent dip in price.
 
The world’s largest cryptocurrency plunged to its weakest point since March 16 earlier this week, triggered by the latest Federal Reserve interest rate decision.
 
Bulls that have returned to BTC in recent days would have done so due to prices being oversold, with the relative strength index (RSI) hovering below the 30.00 mark.
 
 
Looking at the chart, the index has now broken out of a ceiling at 43.00, and is tracking at 43.26, which has prompted a rise in momentum.
 
The next visible point of resistance is at the 50.00 mark, and 57.00 thereafter. Should bulls move beyond both of these, BTC will likely be trading above $27,500 in the next few weeks.
 
Where will bitcoin end the month? Let us know your thoughts in the comments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Arrows Capital’s NFT Collection Fetches $10.9 Million at Sotheby’s Auction]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757d6878a9</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/three-arrows-capital-nft-collection/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T17:14:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A set of non-fungible tokens (NFTs) previously acquired by bankrupt cryptocurrency hedge fund Three Arrows Capital was sold for an impressive $10.9 million at Sotheby’s in New York. The auction showcased the enduring fascination and potential of NFTs in the art and investment worlds.
 
Three Arrows Capital, which filed for bankruptcy in the United States in 2022, had originally purchased the 37 NFTs for $15.5 million worth of cryptocurrency in July and August 2021. These digital assets represent ownership of various digital items, such as images, videos, or pieces of text, and are based on blockchain technology.
 
Among the collection, the most expensive item was “Ringers #879 (The Goose),” a computer-generated abstract image by Canadian artist Dmitri Cherniak. It sold for $6.2 million, se…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Blockchain Technology Mark a Turning Point in Fraud Prevention?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757d6af53c</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/education-centre/will-blockchain-technology-mark-a-turning-point-in-fraud-prevention/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T16:57:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fraud has been  
a persistent problem in many industries, causing enormous financial losses for  
both corporations and individuals. The intricacy of fraudulent acts grows in  
lockstep with technological advancement. Blockchain technology, on the other  
hand, has emerged as a possible game changer in the fight against fraud. 
In this  
article, we will look at blockchain technology and its implications for fraud  
prevention. We will examine whether blockchain technology can signal a turning  
point in fraud prevention, from the benefits of blockchain in improving  
security and transparency to the hurdles and considerations in its  
implementation.
Understanding  
Blockchain Technology
Blockchain is a  
decentralized, immutable database that records transactions across several  
compute…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Ferreira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi Credit Protocol Concordia Raises $4M in Round Led by Tribe, Kraken]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757d57b736</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/06/16/defi-credit-protocol-concordia-raises-4m-in-round-led-by-tribe-kraken/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T16:27:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Concordia, now live in public testnet on Aptos, offers a multi-chain risk and collateral management platform for digital assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandy Betz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The $11M NFT Auction and Snoop Dogg’s Evolving Collection]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757d5086c9</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/web3/2023/06/16/11m-for-sothebys-nft-auction-snoop-doggs-collection-evolves/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T16:22:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rapper Snoop Dogg has released new NFTs that evolve in utility throughout his tour this summer, while Sotheby’s concluded a successful second 3AC NFT auction, including $6.2M for Dmitri Cherniak’s “The Goose.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rosie Perper</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jack Dorsey Pledges $5M to Help Bitcoin Core Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144932</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144932/jack-dorsey-pledges-5m-to-help-bitcoin-core-developers"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T13:57:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The funding will come from his charity, Start Small, and will be disbursed $1 million at a time over the next five years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alyssa Hertig</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[French Authorities Investigating Binance for ‘Aggravated Money Laundering’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144927</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144927/french-authorities-investigating-binance-for-aggravated-money-laundering"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T12:52:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[France’s financial judicial investigation service is reportedly investigating Binance for offenses including “aggravated money laundering.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance to Leave Netherlands After Failing to Acquire VASP License]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144920</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144920/binance-to-leave-netherlands-after-failing-to-acquire-vasp-license"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T11:57:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The world’s largest cryptocurrency exchange today announced the termination of its operations in the Netherlands.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FDIC Targets Crypto Exchange OKCoin Over ‘False’ Insurance Assertions]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144918</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144918/fdic-targets-crypto-exchange-okcoin-over-false-insurance-assertions"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T11:16:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation has warned OKCoin over “misleading” claims on its website implying FDIC account protection.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[French Crypto Entrepreneur Hasheur: U.S. Crackdown Chance for EU, Asia to 'Capture' Volume]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144908</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144908/french-crypto-entrepreneur-hasheur-u-s-crackdown-chance-for-eu-asia-to-capture-volume"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T10:33:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Owen Simonin, aka Hasheur, spoke to Decrypt at the Proof-of-Talk conference about the U.S. crypto crackdown—and the opportunity it presents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Brief History of Artificial Intelligence (AI): From Turing to IoT]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137088</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/a-brief-history-of-artificial-intelligence-ai-from-turing-to-iot"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T09:06:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence (AI) as a concept dates back to ancient times, but modern AI began in the mid-20th century with pioneers like Alan Turing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Reiff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mercedes-Benz Is Adding ChatGPT to Cars for AI Voice Commands]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144872</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144872/mercedes-benz-adding-chatgpt-cars-ai-voice-commands"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T01:55:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The luxury automaker is set to integrate OpenAI's ChatGPT chatbot into its Mercedes-Benz User Experience (MBUX) feature in the U.S.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlockFi Sues State Commission for Not Accepting Its Surrendered License]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144879</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144879/blockfi-sues-connecticut-banking-commission"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T01:23:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bankrupt crypto exchange wants to surrender its license, but regulators are insisting on what BlockFi says would be an expensive court proceeding.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alchemy's ChatGPT Plugin Enables Easier Blockchain Analysis Via AI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144856</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144856/alchemy-chatgpt-ai-plugin-enables-easier-blockchain-analysis"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T23:02:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alchemy’s new GPT-4 plugin harnesses the power of AI to deliver user-friendly, real-time blockchain analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["AI Is Game-Changing But Needs Fact-Checking": AlchemyAI Project Lead]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/HXlThlXv/ai-is-game-changing-but-needs-fact-checking-alchemyai-project-lead</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/HXlThlXv/ai-is-game-changing-but-needs-fact-checking-alchemyai-project-lead"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this interview, Decrypt's Jason Nelson chats with Alchemy product manager and AlchemyAI project lead Elan Halpern on blockchain analysis using ChatGPT, what AI means for better user experience, and the need to fact-check AI. Halpern also gives a demo of the new AlchemyAI ChatGPT plugin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Banned In New York, CoinEx Returns $1.7 Million to Settle Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144820</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144820/banned-in-new-york-coinex-returns-1-7-million-to-settle-lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T22:50:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New York Attorney General Letitia James announced a $1.7 million settlement with Hong Kong-based CoinEx over securities violations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prometheum: What You Need to Know About the SEC’s Poster Child for Crypto Compliance]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144833</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144833/prometheum-sec-poster-child-crypto-compliance"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T22:21:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prometheum's co-CEO gave remarks on Capitol Hill that mirrored the SEC's stance. Now industry observers are poring over the startup’s paper trail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitch's New Favorite Game 'Only Up' Is Loaded With Goblintown NFT Art]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144815</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144815/twitch-new-game-only-up-goblintown-nft"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T21:31:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More than 100,000 simultaneous viewers watched streamers play clumsy climbing game Only Up, which is packed with Goblintown references.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock Files Bitcoin ETF Application With the SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144782</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144782/blackrock-filing-bitcoin-etf-application-soon-reports"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T21:28:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock, with Coinbase as its partner, has submitted an application for a spot Bitcoin ETF following a Thursday morning report.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jack Dorsey's Block Bitcoin Wallet Opens Beta, Announces Coinbase Support]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144825</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144825/jack-dorseys-block-bitcoin-wallet-opens-beta-announces-coinbase-support"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T21:05:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitkey will allow beta users to withdraw Bitcoin from Coinbase and Cashapp using "copy and paste."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFT Artwork Owned by Three Arrows Capital Sells for $6.2 Million at Sotheby's]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144816</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144816/nft-artwork-owned-three-arrows-capital-sells-6-2-million-sothebys"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T20:37:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ringers #879, a.k.a. "The Goose," sold for over $6.2 million with fees at today's Sotheby's Grails: Part II live auction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[As Crypto Burned Stateside, NFT Believers Partied Through the Night in Lisbon]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144748</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144748/crypto-burned-stateside-nft-believers-partied-through-night-lisbon"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T19:22:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC's actions against the largest crypto exchanges were barely a footnote during the NFT extravaganza at NFC Lisbon in Portugal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former FTX Ventures Head Amy Wu Turns to AI After Being 'Duped' by SBF]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144795</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144795/former-ftx-ventures-head-amy-wu-turns-to-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T18:26:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite a dark episode at FTX Ventures, Wu has now joined Menlo Ventures to help spearhead its investments in AI and consumer tech.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Colombia’s Central Bank Taps Ripple to Pilot CBDC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144799</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144799/colombia-central-bank-ripple-cbdc"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T18:15:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Colombia already makes use of Ripple's technology for land distribution efforts in the country.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Devs Cry Foul on Uniswap v4 'Open Source' Promises]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144802</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144802/ethereum-devs-cry-foul-on-uniswap-v4-open-source-promises"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T17:54:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's a few licenses that Ethereum devs consider the mark of a truly open source project. The one Uniswap chose for its v4 isn't one of them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD Debuts AI Chip to Challenge Nvidia]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144788</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144788/amd-debuts-ai-chip-to-challenge-nvidia"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T17:29:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company's new MI300X AI Chip will be a direct competitor to the dominance of Nvidia's H100.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Heads East as Huobi HK Launches Trading Service in Hong Kong]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142955</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142955/crypto-heads-east-as-huobi-hk-launches-trading-service-in-hong-kong"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T17:25:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Huobi has joined the Hong Kong Virtual Assets Consortium (HKVAC), while its Hong Kong arm now offers crypto spot trading and virtual asset custody.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Whale Moves $1.2 Million After 13 Years of Inactivity]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144786</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144786/bitcoin-whale-moves-million-after-13-years"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T16:53:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some long-term investors are moving their stashes after years of remaining dormant.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arbitrum's New 'Layer-3' Xai Network Is Built to Power Web3 Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144775</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144775/arbitrums-new-layer-3-xai-network-built-power-web3-games"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T16:01:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dedicated gaming network Xai is launching with support from Offchain Labs, with games like Final Form and LAMOverse up first.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fedi's Bitcoin Federations Could Onboard Next 1 Billion Users, Says CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144599</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144599/fedis-bitcoin-federations-could-onboard-next-1-billion-users-says-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T14:21:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fedi CEO Obi Nwosu has big plans for kickstarting Bitcoin adoption via a unique, Lightning-powered community app called "Federations."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cyber Criminals Are Turning to Crypto Mining Pools to Wash Ill-Gotten Funds: Chainalysis]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144762</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144762/cyber-criminals-are-turning-crypto-mining-pools-wash-ill-gotten-funds-chainalysis"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T13:01:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ransomware actors are increasingly trying to pass off their own funds as proceeds received from cryptocurrency mining, claims Chainalysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Artificial Intelligence (AI) Take Over Your Job?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137047</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/will-artificial-intelligence-take-over-your-job-decryptu"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T10:39:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jobs requiring human ingenuity or creativity, or which rely heavily on social and emotional skills, might be the safest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Reiff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum, Cardano, and Dogecoin Lead Weekly Crypto Losses]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144741</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144741/ethereum-cardano-dogecoin-lead-weekly-crypto-losses"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T09:59:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After the largest altcoins, Bitcoin is also shedding value as the crypto market continues to digest yesterday’s fed notes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried Trial Can Proceed on Original Charges Only, Says DoJ]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144740</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144740/sam-bankman-fried-trial-can-only-proceed-original-charges-says-doj"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T09:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Government is willing to wait a bit longer to try the FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried on several additional counts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alys Key</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether CTO Says 'Let Them Come' as Stablecoin's Dollar Peg Wobbles]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144735</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144735/tether-cto-says-let-them-come-stablecoin-peg-wobbles"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T08:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the market's largest stablecoin waffling, the Tether CTO took to Twitter to assure investors that redemptions won't be a problem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fractal Is Like an Arcade, Says Twitch Co-Founder Justin Kan]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/6r6Mdwt6/fractal-is-like-an-arcade-says-twitch-co-founder-justin-kan</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/6r6Mdwt6/fractal-is-like-an-arcade-says-twitch-co-founder-justin-kan"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Justin Kan was a co-founder of Twitch and now works on Fractal, a Web3 gaming startup. Kan tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about his new company and what he's up to.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are NFTs the Next SEC Target?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/YaGgY87J/are-nfts-the-next-sec-target</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/YaGgY87J/are-nfts-the-next-sec-target"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T20:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin discusses the current regulatory climate in the U.S. with Gala Games' President of Blockchain Jason Brink.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Collab.Land Co-Founder Said There Was No ‘Aha Moment’ When Launching DAO Toolkit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/kcBRKFGk/collabland-co-founder-said-there-was-no-aha-moment-when-launching-dao-toolkit</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/kcBRKFGk/collabland-co-founder-said-there-was-no-aha-moment-when-launching-dao-toolkit"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T09:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CCO and co-founder of Collab.Land Anjali Young explained at this year’s NFC Lisbon the origins of the crypto community tool kit, which industry niches are turning to its suite of products, and what’s next for the project since its token distribution event last February.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Buying a Slice of H.R. Giger's 'Alien' Is Fine Art, Not Memorabilia: Particle CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/VACG0WVg/buying-a-slice-of-hr-gigers-alien-is-fine-art-not-memorabilia-particle-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/VACG0WVg/buying-a-slice-of-hr-gigers-alien-is-fine-art-not-memorabilia-particle-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T08:49:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With H.R. Giger's original "Alien" statue on full display at this year's NFC Lisbon, Particle CEO Harold Eytan told Decrypt that owning an NFT-ified slice of the piece isn't just for fans of the iconic creature and movie series but also for fine art collectors. Interested in owning a piece? Be prepared to cough up half an ETH for one of the 500 tranches of the digitized sculpture.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Community Co-Creation 'Is a Big Step for Fashion Brands' Entering the Metaverse: BNV Founder and CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/z6NSMnNm/community-co-creation-is-a-big-step-for-fashion-brands-entering-the-metaverse-bnv-founder-and-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/z6NSMnNm/community-co-creation-is-a-big-step-for-fashion-brands-entering-the-metaverse-bnv-founder-and-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T08:49:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The founder and CEO of metaverse fashion platform BNV Richard Hobbs said big brands are still nervous to let fans and community members customize their favorite garments. Still, he believes that as long as you can meet a firm's commercial bottom lines while stirring engagement, there's nothing to lose.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Standard Crypto VC Co-Founder on NFTs and Their Stigma in Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/bmtrrLio/standard-crypto-vc-co-founder-on-nfts-and-their-stigma-in-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/bmtrrLio/standard-crypto-vc-co-founder-on-nfts-and-their-stigma-in-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T18:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alok Vasudev is a co-founder of venture capital firm Standard Crypto. In an interview with Decrypt's Kate Irwin, he shares his thoughts on NFT marketing, NFT utility in gaming, and the stigma that pervades the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ava Labs Announces Avalanche Arcad3 for Game Developers at 3XP]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XPHp9r4j/ava-labs-announces-avalanche-arcad3-for-game-developers-at-3xp</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XPHp9r4j/ava-labs-announces-avalanche-arcad3-for-game-developers-at-3xp"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T15:21:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ava Labs Head of Gaming Ed Chang shares news with Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the crypto firm's latest push to help traditional game developers break into blockchain gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Like a Middle Finger to Western Culture’: YuYu Unpacks Inspiration Behind NFT Expo GAG]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Vuoplr6a/like-a-middle-finger-to-western-culture-yuyu-unpacks-inspiration-behind-nft-expo-gag</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Vuoplr6a/like-a-middle-finger-to-western-culture-yuyu-unpacks-inspiration-behind-nft-expo-gag"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T13:33:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At this year’s NFC Lisbon, multimedia artist and photographer YuLiang "YuYu" Liu broke down how themes from traditional painting and BDSM informed his latest NFT exhibition called “GAG.” He also shared exclusively with Decrypt a yet-to-be-launched drop for fans of his work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Competition Was Rather Low' in Mobile Wallet Space, Says Zerion Head of Growth]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/vCg8O2oy/competition-was-rather-low-in-mobile-wallet-space-says-zerion-head-of-growth</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/vCg8O2oy/competition-was-rather-low-in-mobile-wallet-space-says-zerion-head-of-growth"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T13:33:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zerion's move to launch a mobile-first crypto wallet not only helped NFT users swap jpegs on the go but was also a play to get away from crypto's desktop-centric user experience. And with such little competition, Zerion's head of growth Alexander Guy told Decrypt at NFC Lisbon it's managed to rake in 150,000 funded wallets. Next step? Taking on MetaMask and contending as a browser-extension wallet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘We’ve Never Seen Anything Like This in VR’, Says The Sandbox COO on Apple’s Vision Pro Headset]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/GQ29RaHw/weve-never-seen-anything-like-this-in-vr-says-the-sandbox-coo-on-apples-vision-pro-headset</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/GQ29RaHw/weve-never-seen-anything-like-this-in-vr-says-the-sandbox-coo-on-apples-vision-pro-headset"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T13:33:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Sandbox COO Sebastien Borget told Decrypt at this year’s NFC Lisbon that despite the high price point, Apple’s new VR headset is nonetheless “groundbreaking.” And though the tech giant never used the term “metaverse” in its reveal, Borget is sure that the technology will be key in growing participation in various digital worlds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Gala Safe? Gala Games Head of Blockchain on GALA, Crypto, and SEC Regulatory Turmoil]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5bcrE8nL/is-gala-safe-gala-games-head-of-blockchain-on-gala-crypto-and-sec-regulatory-turmoil</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5bcrE8nL/is-gala-safe-gala-games-head-of-blockchain-on-gala-crypto-and-sec-regulatory-turmoil"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T15:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gala Games President of Blockchain shares his thoughts on the GALA token upgrade and the latest SEC turmoil with Decrypt's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Artists Adopting NFTs Has Been ‘Really Market Dependent’, Says NFT Club Berlin’s Rebekka Revel]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/QKlIVlj3/artists-adopting-nfts-has-been-really-market-dependent-says-nft-club-berlins-rebekka-revel</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/QKlIVlj3/artists-adopting-nfts-has-been-really-market-dependent-says-nft-club-berlins-rebekka-revel"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T15:07:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Getting non-crypto artists to make the leap into Web3 comes in ebbs and flows according to the market’s bear and bull waves, says co-founder of NFT Club Berlin and Superteam Germany Rebekka Revel. But she’s hoping to change that by changing the narrative around digital collectibles, regardless of the market, one word at a time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big Brands Exploring Web3 to ‘Scale Up Their Super-fan Base’: Superduper Co-founder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/he6UzJwz/big-brands-exploring-web3-to-scale-up-their-super-fan-base-superduper-co-founder</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/he6UzJwz/big-brands-exploring-web3-to-scale-up-their-super-fan-base-superduper-co-founder"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T14:49:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Co-founder and co-CEO of Web3 media brand Superduper Dom Smith says big brands are eager to enter the space—they just don’t know how. Still, they all maintain a thesis of turning their communities into “super fans” that generate value for users as well as a firm’s bottom line.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How 1 Simple Question Kickstarted Performance Artist Foodmasku's Plunge Into NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/w86DMn3p/how-1-simple-question-kickstarted-performance-artist-foodmaskus-plunge-into-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/w86DMn3p/how-1-simple-question-kickstarted-performance-artist-foodmaskus-plunge-into-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T10:10:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As his food mask creations went viral on the Internet during the COVID lockdowns, reposted on TikTok and Instagram without his consent, he soon asked: "How do I protect my digital files?" Performance artist Foodmasku describes at this year's NFC Lisbon how that simple question spiraled into a minting collection after collection of his edible works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arianee CEO Pegs Wine and Spirits as Next 'Exciting' Industry to Make Web3 Leap]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Bo2NeG9Z/arianee-ceo-pegs-wine-and-spirits-as-next-exciting-industry-to-make-web3-leap</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Bo2NeG9Z/arianee-ceo-pegs-wine-and-spirits-as-next-exciting-industry-to-make-web3-leap"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T09:28:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CEO and co-founder of Arianee Pierre Nicolas Hurstel unpacks the wide spectrum of digital collectibles from 10,000 PFP collections to access passes for exclusive events. And with an unannounced big brand soon joining, Hurstel revealed at NFC Lisbon which kind of NFTs big brands are moving towards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why 'Words With Friends' Creator Paul Bettner is 'Allergic' to Pay-to-Win NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JkfOleb4/why-words-with-friends-creator-paul-bettner-is-allergic-to-pay-to-win-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JkfOleb4/why-words-with-friends-creator-paul-bettner-is-allergic-to-pay-to-win-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T20:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Words With Friends and Wildcard creator Paul Bettner tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about his perspective on what to do when NFTs become in-game characters and assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitch Co-Founder Justin Kan: 18 Months is 'Several Decades' in Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rKVvsPFb/twitch-co-founder-justin-kan-18-months-is-several-decades-in-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rKVvsPFb/twitch-co-founder-justin-kan-18-months-is-several-decades-in-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fractal and Twitch co-founder Justin Kan gives Decrypt's Kate Irwin an update on all things Fractal and his perspective on blockchain technology in gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Playing for Money in Web3 Games Not 'Durable,' Says Fractal's Justin Kan]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MQG3SaBM/playing-for-money-in-web3-games-not-durable-says-fractals-justin-kan</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MQG3SaBM/playing-for-money-in-web3-games-not-durable-says-fractals-justin-kan"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twitch and Fractal co-founder Justin Kan and Fractal co-founder Dan Borstelmann share their perspectives on Web3 gaming's changing landscape with Decrypt's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Cyber Cafe to Web3: How Everquest Dev Jeffrey Butler Got Into Game Development]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/hRlI4WXe/from-cyber-cafe-to-web3-how-everquest-dev-jeffrey-butler-got-into-game-development</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/hRlI4WXe/from-cyber-cafe-to-web3-how-everquest-dev-jeffrey-butler-got-into-game-development"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T14:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everquest developer turned Avalon Chief Product Officer Jeffrey Butler tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how he got into game development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>