<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-10-04T01:05:14.470Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-10-04T01:05:14.470Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BREAKING: Ripple Scores Yet Another Win As Judge Torres Rejects SEC’s Appeal Attempt]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74beb5a680</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/breaking-ripple-win-as-judge-rejects-secs-appeal/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T00:49:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a significant development in the legal battle between Ripple and the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), Judge Analisa Torres has rejected the SEC’s motion to appeal the Ripple ruling. 
 
This decision comes as another win for Ripple, the blockchain payment company, as it fights allegations of conducting an unregistered securities offering.
 
Judge Rejects SEC’s Motion To Appeal in Ripple Case
 
According to court documents, the SEC’s motion for leave to file an interlocutory appeal has been denied. The court ruled that the SEC failed to provide sufficient evidence to demonstrate that the “speculative motive derived from the entrepreneurial or managerial efforts of others” for the Programmatic Buyers who purchased XRP, Ripple’s native cryptocurrency.
 
 
Judge Torres emphasized th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BREAKING: Ripple Scores Yet Another Win As Judge Torres Rejects SEC’s Appeal Attempt]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18945938/BREAKING-Ripple-Scores-Yet-Another-Win-As-Judge-Torres-Rejects-SECs-Appeal-Attempt</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18945938/BREAKING-Ripple-Scores-Yet-Another-Win-As-Judge-Torres-Rejects-SECs-Appeal-Attempt"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T00:20:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a significant development in the legal battle between Ripple and the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), Judge Analisa Torres has rejected the SEC’s motion to appeal the Ripple ruling. This decision comes as another win for Ripple, the blockchain payment company, as it fights...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Analyst Sees Bullish Continuation for Arbitrum and Injective, Calls for Bitcoin To Move Higher]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18945912/Crypto-Analyst-Sees-Bullish-Continuation-for-Arbitrum-and-Injective-Calls-for-Bitcoin-To-Move-Higher</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18945912/Crypto-Analyst-Sees-Bullish-Continuation-for-Arbitrum-and-Injective-Calls-for-Bitcoin-To-Move-Higher"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T00:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A closely followed crypto strategist is predicting sustained rallies for layer-2 protocol Arbitrum (ARB) and decentralized derivatives exchange Injective (INJ). Pseudonymous analyst Altcoin Sherpa tells his 196,600 followers on the social media platform X that Arbitrum could rise by over 23%...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Great Crypto Shuffle: How 2017’s Top 100 Coins Fared In The Rollercoaster Market]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18945898/The-Great-Crypto-Shuffle-How-2017s-Top-100-Coins-Fared-In-The-Rollercoaster-Market</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18945898/The-Great-Crypto-Shuffle-How-2017s-Top-100-Coins-Fared-In-The-Rollercoaster-Market"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T00:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recent analysis by an analyst has painted a clearer picture of just how volatile the crypto market has been, especially for those who took their chances on lesser-known altcoins a few years back. The analyst studied the top 100 cryptocurrencies as they stood in December 2017 and found that the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Under $100Mn Crypto Bullrun Gem | Radiant Rdnt]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18945909/UNDER-100MN-CRYPTO-BULLRUN-GEM-RADIANT-RDNT</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18945909/UNDER-100MN-CRYPTO-BULLRUN-GEM-RADIANT-RDNT"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aave enjoys the bulk of the market share in the lending market. But, Radiant Capital’s mainnet launch on Ethereum could introduce a new rival. This video takes a deep dive into Radiant Capital and what the launch could mean. Manage Your Crypto Portfolio with Regular Updates and Top Insights for...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Humata AI Raises $3.5 Million Led by Google’s Gradient Ventures]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199865</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199865/humata-ai-pdf-questions-3-million-dollar-fundraise"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T23:53:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building upon a PDF tool, the company aspires to redefine the future of work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Humata AI Raises $3.5 Million Led by Google’s Gradient Ventures]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18945895/Humata-AI-Raises-35-Million-Led-by-Googles-Gradient-Ventures</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18945895/Humata-AI-Raises-35-Million-Led-by-Googles-Gradient-Ventures"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T23:53:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building upon a PDF tool, the company aspires to redefine the future of work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Judge rejects SEC’s request to appeal Ripple decision]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18945892/Judge-rejects-SECs-request-to-appeal-Ripple-decision</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18945892/Judge-rejects-SECs-request-to-appeal-Ripple-decision"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T23:50:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ongoing legal skirmish between the SEC and Ripple Labs added another chapter as Judge Analisa Torres denied the SEC’s request for an interlocutory appeal on Oct. 3. With the appeal motion off the table, both parties gear up for a trial set for April 23, 2024. The verdict could reshape...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BREAKING: CRYPTO WINS MAJOR LEGAL VICTOY AGAINST SEC!! XRP NOT A SECURITY (can’t be appealed)]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18945910/BREAKING-CRYPTO-WINS-MAJOR-LEGAL-VICTOY-AGAINST-SEC-XRP-NOT-A-SECURITY-cant-be-appealed</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18945910/BREAKING-CRYPTO-WINS-MAJOR-LEGAL-VICTOY-AGAINST-SEC-XRP-NOT-A-SECURITY-cant-be-appealed"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T23:49:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grab a VPN so Gary can’t see your browser history!! https://nordvpn.com/ellio#nft #ethereum #defi #blockchain #crypto #cryptocurrency #bitcoin #btc #eth #news #protocols #sidechain #altcoin #nftmarketplace #opensea #cryptoart #protocol #altcoins #nonfungibletoken #dao #sidechain #layer2 #erc20...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Judge Torres rejects the SEC’s motion for an interlocutory appeal in Ripple case]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18945890/Judge-Torres-rejects-the-SECs-motion-for-an-interlocutory-appeal-in-Ripple-case</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18945890/Judge-Torres-rejects-the-SECs-motion-for-an-interlocutory-appeal-in-Ripple-case"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T23:49:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[District Judge Analisa Torres rejected the SEC’s move to certify for interlocutory appeal and set trial dates for next year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chainalysis Trims Workforce By 15% Amid Broader Crypto Job Market Fluctuations]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74beb2eebd</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/chainalysis-trims-workforce-amid-broader-crypto-job/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T23:49:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Facing challenges in the crypto job market, blockchain data company Chainalysis has confirmed another wave of layoffs in a series of employment reductions across the crypto sector, a report from Bloomberg noted.
 
Founded in 2014, Chainalysis swiftly gained a reputation for tracking digital asset transactions and its collaborations with government agencies, including the US.
 
 
Realigning Amid Changing Market Conditions
 
In a report late Monday in the US, a spokesperson for Chainalysis Inc. disclosed the company’s decision to part with 15% of its workforce.
 
The spokesperson elaborated on the rationale and mentioned the company’s focus on efficient growth. The representative expressed that current “market conditions” have necessitated this adjustment to company “expenses.”
 
The recent …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 Simple Ways To Improve Your Chances Of Success With Crypto]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74beb2eeb2</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/improve-chances-of-success-crypto/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T23:49:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto has become one of the most prominent investments, especially among young people but it is not all profits/gains as is usually believed. Due to its highly volatile nature, crypto carries as much risk of losing money as it does the promise of making life-changing gains. To make sure the latter is the case, here are 4 simple ways to improve your chances of making money with crypto.
 
Don’t FOMO
 
One of the most important lessons to learn as a crypto investor is to avoid FOMO (Fear Of Missing Out). This feeling usually comes when an asset has grown so much that it’s all anyone can talk about, and investors start feeling like they will keep missing the boat if they don’t buy in. By giving into this fear, many investors will rush to buy the token, usually buying at a price referred to as…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Best Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ether Futures ETFs Debut Fails to Attract Volume]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18945886/Ether-Futures-ETFs-Debut-Fails-to-Attract-Volume</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18945886/Ether-Futures-ETFs-Debut-Fails-to-Attract-Volume"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T23:45:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first exchange-traded funds (ETFs) linked to Ether futures made their debut on Monday, providing investors with new ways to gain exposure to the second-largest crypto by market capitalization. However, the launch failed to generate much trading activity.The six new Ether futures ETFs from...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hyperbitcoinisation Can’t Happen with Mike Brock]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18945913/Hyperbitcoinisation-Cant-Happen-with-Mike-Brock</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18945913/Hyperbitcoinisation-Cant-Happen-with-Mike-Brock"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T23:44:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SHOW NOTES:https://www.whatbitcoindid.com/podcast/hyperbitcoinisation-cant-happenMike Brock is the lead at TBD, the Bitcoin-focused subsidiary of Block. In this interview, we discuss Bitcoin’s limitations in solving complex societal problems, counter-arguments to the narrative that monetary...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Argentinian presidential candidate wants CBDCs to 'solve' hyperinflation]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18945885/Argentinian-presidential-candidate-wants-CBDCs-to-solve-hyperinflation</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18945885/Argentinian-presidential-candidate-wants-CBDCs-to-solve-hyperinflation"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T23:43:45.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking: SEC’s Motion To Appeal XRP Security Ruling Denied]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18945931/Breaking-SECs-Motion-To-Appeal-XRP-Security-Ruling-Denied</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18945931/Breaking-SECs-Motion-To-Appeal-XRP-Security-Ruling-Denied"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T23:36:18.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla CEO Elon Musk Calls Fiat Currency a Scam]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74bebc173b</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/tesla-ceo-elon-musk-calls-fiat-currency-a-scam/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T23:35:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla and Spacex CEO Elon Musk believes that fiat currency is a scam that is so normalized that we don’t even realize that it’s a scam. Many people share a similar view, including Rich Dad Poor Dad author Robert Kiyosaki, who has frequently cautioned against investing in the U.S. dollar and other fiat currencies, which he labels “fake” money.
 
Elon Musk Thinks Fiat Currency Is a Scam
 
The CEO of Tesla and Spacex, Elon Musk, believes that fiat currency is a scam. In a post on social media platform X, user Wall Street Silver shared an image with a question on Sunday: “What’s a scam that’s so normalized that we don’t even realize it’s a scam anymore?” Musk replied: “Fiat currency.”
 

 
 
Musk has long been critical of fiat currency. In February 2021, he tweeted, “When fiat currency has negative real interest, only a fool wouldn’t look elsewhere.” He also compared fiat currency to BTC, stating: “Bitcoin is almost as bs as fiat money.” Nonetheless, he added: “The true battle is between fiat & crypto. On balance, I support the latter.”
 
The Tesla boss is not the only one who holds the view that fiat currency is a scam, fraud, or Ponzi scheme. Vailshire Capital founder Jeff Ross described on X Tuesday: “The fiat currency system exists to methodically extract purchasing power from its participants.” Rich Dad Poor Dad author Robert Kiyosaki has also called the U.S. dollar a scam, and predicted the demise of the USD. The famous author refers to fiat money as “fake money,” while gold and silver are “God’s money” and bitcoin is “people’s money.” He wrote in July: “Giant crash [is] coming … Get into real gold, silver, bitcoin asap … End of fiat (fake) money [is] near.”
 
Do you agree with Elon Musk that fiat currency is a scam? Let us know in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC’s Motion to Appeal Loss in Ripple Case Is Denied]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74bebc3db4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/10/03/secs-motion-to-appeal-loss-in-ripple-case-is-denied/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T23:34:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XRP rallied about 5% following the decision.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Judge rejects SEC’s motion to file an appeal against Ripple ruling]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18945875/Judge-rejects-SECs-motion-to-file-an-appeal-against-Ripple-ruling</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18945875/Judge-rejects-SECs-motion-to-file-an-appeal-against-Ripple-ruling"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T23:28:26.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto-Friendly Congressman McHenry Temporarily Takes Over U.S. House]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74bebe0ab2</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/10/03/crypto-friendly-congressman-mchenry-temporarily-takes-over-us-house/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T23:15:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto-friendly Rep. Patrick McHenry (R-N.C.) has landed in the driver’s seat of the U.S. House of Representatives just as legislation to establish digital-asset regulations nears a finish line there.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC’s Motion to Appeal Loss in Ripple Case Is Denied]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18945859/SECs-Motion-to-Appeal-Loss-in-Ripple-Case-Is-Denied</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18945859/SECs-Motion-to-Appeal-Loss-in-Ripple-Case-Is-Denied"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T23:13:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Chair Gary Gensler, left, and Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse are at the center of the U.S. dispute over the future of crypto oversight. (Kevin Dietsch/Getty and Scott Moore/Shutterstock/CoinDesk)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto-Friendly Congressman McHenry Temporarily Takes Over U.S. House]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18945846/Crypto-Friendly-Congressman-McHenry-Temporarily-Takes-Over-US-House</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18945846/Crypto-Friendly-Congressman-McHenry-Temporarily-Takes-Over-US-House"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T23:03:16.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BREAKING: Judge Denies SEC’s Motion to Appeal Ripple (XRP) Decision]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18945842/BREAKING-Judge-Denies-SECs-Motion-to-Appeal-Ripple-XRP-Decision</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18945842/BREAKING-Judge-Denies-SECs-Motion-to-Appeal-Ripple-XRP-Decision"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T23:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to breaking information, the judge in the Ripple case rejected the SEC's decision to appeal the recent Ripple victory. The decision was made by Judge Analisa Torres on October 3, 2023. The SEC's request for a postponement was also denied as moot. The hearing will begin at 9:00 on April...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 Simple Ways To Improve Your Chances Of Success With Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18945833/4-Simple-Ways-To-Improve-Your-Chances-Of-Success-With-Crypto</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18945833/4-Simple-Ways-To-Improve-Your-Chances-Of-Success-With-Crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[At Least 3 SBF Jurors Recused Themselves Because They Lost Money in Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200014</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200014/sam-bankman-fried-jury-voir-dire-lost-money-in-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T22:57:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The court weighed potential bias among candidates who worked for banks, or watched Sunday's 60 Minutes broadcast.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[At Least 3 SBF Jurors Recused Themselves Because They Lost Money in Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18945848/At-Least-3-SBF-Jurors-Recused-Themselves-Because-They-Lost-Money-in-Crypto</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18945848/At-Least-3-SBF-Jurors-Recused-Themselves-Because-They-Lost-Money-in-Crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T22:57:08.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Could House Speaker Kevin McCarthy's Ouster Be Good for Crypto?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200015</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200015/could-house-speaker-kevin-mccarthys-ouster-good-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T22:53:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top candidates to replace the former Speaker of the House, who was removed from office in a historic vote Tuesday, include ardent pro-crypto advocates Patrick McHenry and Tom Emmer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Could House Speaker Kevin McCarthy's Ouster Be Good for Crypto?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18945836/Could-House-Speaker-Kevin-McCarthys-Ouster-Be-Good-for-Crypto</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18945836/Could-House-Speaker-Kevin-McCarthys-Ouster-Be-Good-for-Crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T22:53:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top candidates to replace the former Speaker of the House, who was removed from office in a historic vote Tuesday, include ardent pro-crypto advocates Patrick McHenry and Tom Emmer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celsius Unveils Revival Strategy Backed By $450M Seed Funding]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74beb8c231</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/celsius-strategy-backed-by-450m-seed-funding/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T22:47:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celsius Network has commenced its bankruptcy trial as it seeks to relaunch itself as a user-owned Bitcoin miner. During a New York bankruptcy hearing, the company informed a judge that it intends to repay customers whose funds have been frozen on the platform since June 2022 with a portion of what they are owed by the end of the year.
 
According to a Bloomberg report, Celsius’s lawyer, Christopher S. Koenig, revealed that the restructured company, expected to emerge from Chapter 11, will receive $450 million in capital and financial backing. 
 
A consortium called Fahrenheit LLC, led by Arrington Capital has been selected to manage the mining business and provide the required financial support. Koenig emphasized Fahrenheit’s belief in Celsius’s business: “They are putting their money wher…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Even More Celebrities Battle Deepfakes of Themselves]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200012</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200012/celebrity-deepfakes-mr-beast-tom-hanks-robin-williams"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T22:39:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mr. Beast, Tom Cruise, Robin Williams, Gayle King, Tucker Carlson, Bill Maher, Taylor Swift, Natalie Portman, Emma Watson...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Even More Celebrities Battle Deepfakes of Themselves]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18945830/Even-More-Celebrities-Battle-Deepfakes-of-Themselves</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18945830/Even-More-Celebrities-Battle-Deepfakes-of-Themselves"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T22:39:16.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase’s Desire to End SEC Lawsuit Should Be Rejected, U.S. Regulator Argues]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74bea4a11a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/10/03/coinbases-desire-to-end-sec-lawsuit-should-be-rejected-us-regulator-argues/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T22:09:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“To distract from the fatal flaws in its legal arguments, Coinbase cries foul and seeks to blame the SEC for its current legal predicament,” the SEC said in a Tuesday court filing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Baker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Martin Shkreli on E/ACC and SBF in Prison]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QONaWXKZ/martin-shkreli-on-e-acc-and-sbf-in-prison</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QONaWXKZ/martin-shkreli-on-e-acc-and-sbf-in-prison"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T22:03:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reza Jafery and Martin Shkreli sit down for a casual conversation about the growing movement that is E/ACC, what songs they could recite at gunpoint, and whether or not SBF will thrive or just survive during his time in prison.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Binance Joined Thai Law Enforcement To Take Down Crypto Scam Scheme]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74bea6e85e</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/binance-thai-law-enforcement-take-down-crypto-scam/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T21:48:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto exchange Binance was the prime assistant in an official investigation by Thailand’s law enforcement agency. The crypto trading venue often boasts about its cooperation with international regulators and law enforcement bodies and this time, it claimed to have taken a critical role in shutting down a crypto scam network.
 
 
Binance Joins Forces With Royal Thai Police, Here Are The Details
 
According to an official post, Binance worked with the Royal Thai Police in an investigation that led to the arrest of several suspects behind fraudulent activities. The Thai agency approached the crypto trading venue to aid the investigation and seize the assets linked to the scheme.
 
The investigation was assisted by Binance, the Cyber Crime Investigation Bureau (CCIB), and the US Homeland Secu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reynaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Raves in the Metaverse Are a Thing—Here's What It's Like Inside]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199958</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199958/ai-raves-in-the-metaverse-are-a-thing-heres-what-its-like-inside"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T21:43:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Influential DJ Carl Cox is set to launch his own metaverse rave in a lava-filled venue, complete with AI dancers. Here's what to expect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Is on Trial Alongside Sam Bankman-Fried]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74bea0c8cb</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/10/03/crypto-is-on-trial-alongside-sam-bankman-fried/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T21:30:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is crypto "uniquely" responsible for the rise and fall of FTX?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Kuhn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bankman-Fried’s Legal Team Cries Foul Over Ukrainian Customer Testimony]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74bea0d3bb</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bankman-frieds-legal-team-cries-foul-over-ukrainian-customer-testimony/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T21:30:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Attorneys for Sam Bankman-Fried have written a letter to the judge, requesting the court block a government witness, a Ukrainian customer who “lost a substantial portion” of his life savings due to the FTX collapse. Bankman-Fried’s lawyers believe the witness’s testimony about hardships faced due to the Russian invasion of Ukraine would be irrelevant to the charges and highly prejudicial, as it would appeal unfairly to the jury’s sympathies.
 
Bankman-Fried’s Attorneys Oppose Ukrainian Witness Testimony in FTX Legal Battle
 
On Oct. 2, 2023, the law firm Cohen & Gresser submitted a letter to the judge presiding over the criminal case against the former FTX boss Sam Bankman-Fried. The government wants to allow a customer witness from Ukraine to testify remotely and detail how he “lost a sub…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Energy FUD Is The New Bitcoin Mining FUD: HIVE Digital]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=200007</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/200007/artificial-intelligence-energy-consumption-versus-bitcoin-mining"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T21:20:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite improvements, criticisms of AI energy use are quite familiar.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Alameda CEO Sam Trabucco, Anthony Scaramucci May Be Called to Testify in SBF Trial]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199989</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199989/former-alameda-ceo-sam-trabucco-anthony-scaramucci-may-be-called-to-testify-in-sbf-trial"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T20:57:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The two weren't expected to be involved in the trial, but may be called to testify.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Firms Used Crypto Payments to Run Fentanyl Network, U.S. Claims in Charges]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74beaced5c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/10/03/chinese-firms-used-crypto-payments-to-run-fentanyl-network-us-claims-in-charges/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T20:53:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Department of Justice (DOJ) targeted several Chinese businesses and their employees Tuesday in the latest round of charges tied to production and trafficking of fentanyl – a network that depended on cryptocurrency payments, according to authorities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple IPO Goes To Harvard: Business School Study Dives Into Valuation]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74bead9469</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ripple-ipo-harvard-valuation/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T20:47:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Harvard Business School case study titled “Ripple: The Business of Crypto Case – An Analysis and Solution” that could be used in Ripple’s IPO valuation is presently sending waves across the cryptocurrency world and has caught the attention of the XRP community.
 
Harvard’s Business School Case Study And Ripple IPO Valuation
 
The case study dives deep into Ripple’s CEO Brad Garlinghouse’s ambitions to revolutionize the global payments industry through the use of XRP, and how the firm plans to achieve this particular goal.
 
 
The case study also covers Ripple’s vision for the future. It study provides a wider survey of Ripple’s unique business model, introduces students and crypto enthusiasts to Bitcoin and blockchain technology, and it creates a solid foundation for an expansive blockch…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Candidate for Argentina President Promises to Push a CBDC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199960</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199960/candidate-for-argentina-president-promises-to-push-a-cbdc"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T20:43:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During a live, televised presidential debate, Sergio Massa evangelized a “digital currency of Argentina.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uptober Begins: Bitcoin’s Rally Sparks $40K Hopes; Yet $20K Threat Lingers]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74beae4d7f</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/uptober-begins-bitcoins-rally-sparks-40k-hopes-yet-20k-threat-lingers/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T20:40:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price of bitcoin (BTC) has risen 6% over the previous 30 days, pushed higher by factors such as its finite availability and growing investor confidence, according to this week’s Bitfinex Alpha report. Moreover, on October 1, a popular cryptocurrency trader suggested that $40,000 could be a “reasonable” BTC price in the upcoming fourth quarter; however, another analysis warned of a possible decline to the $20K mark.
 
Up or Down? Bitcoin’s October Saga Unfolds With Poles Apart Price Predictions
 
Bitcoin (BTC) began October on a strong note, with many dubbing the month ‘Uptober’ as BTC surged 6% within 30 days and 4.5% in just seven days. A Bitfinex report released on October 2 stated that bitcoin exchange reserves have reached their lowest point in five years, indicating limited supply…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Sneaker Is Actually a $3,800 Gaming PC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199959</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199959/this-sneaker-actually-3800-gaming-pc"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T20:21:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hardware company Cooler Master is bringing a footwear-shaped gaming PC to the masses in the U.S. and Europe. Is this shoe worth the spend?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Slips To $27,500 As Kraken Receives Largest Inflow Since 2018]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74be948e7a</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-slips-27500-kraken-largest-inflow-2018/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T19:47:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin has dropped to $27,500 today as on-chain data shows Kraken’s cryptocurrency exchange has received its largest deposit since 2018.
 
A Large Amount Of Bitcoin Has Entered Kraken In The Past Day
 
An analyst in a CryptoQuant Quicktake post explained that the Kraken platform has observed a historic inflow of 14,924 BTC during the past day or so. The indicator of interest here is the “exchange inflow,” which keeps track of the total amount of Bitcoin entering into the wallets of any given centralized exchange.
 
When the value of this metric spikes, it means that the exchange in question is receiving deposits of a large amount right now. Generally, one of the main reasons why holders may move their coins from their self-custodial wallets to these platforms is for selling-related purpos…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hououin Kyouma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miners Brace for Increased Challenge as Network Difficulty Hits New High of 57.32 Trillion]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74be954453</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-miners-brace-for-increased-challenge-as-network-difficulty-hits-new-high-of-57-32-trillion/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T19:40:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On October 3, 2023, at block height 810,432, the Bitcoin network experienced its second consecutive difficulty increase since September 19. The challenge of uncovering block rewards escalated as the difficulty reached a new pinnacle, rising by 0.35% to 57.32 trillion on Tuesday.
 
Bitcoin Network Difficulty Peaks at 57.32 Trillion
 
For the subsequent fortnight, Bitcoin miners confront a heightened level of difficulty following Tuesday’s 0.35% rise at block height 810,432. The metric climbed from 57.11 trillion to its present value of 57.32 trillion.
 
 
A difficulty rating of 57.32 trillion implies an elevated degree of effort needed to generate new blocks on the network. The difficulty undergoes adjustments every 2,016 blocks or approximately every two weeks.
 
If a greater number of min…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jump Trading Lost Almost $300M in FTX’s Collapse, Michael Lewis Says in ‘Going Infinite’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74be961faf</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/10/03/jump-trading-lost-almost-300m-in-ftxs-collapse-michael-lewis-says-in-going-infinite/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T19:33:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This makes the trading giant one of FTX’s top creditors, Lewis wrote, citing documents from the crypto exchange’s former chief operating officer, Constance Wang.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Venmo's Stablecoin Integration Can Grow the Bitcoin Economy]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74be909f54</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/markets/how-venmos-stablecoin-integration-can-grow-the-bitcoin-economy"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T19:13:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week, PayPal, alongside their infrastructure partner Paxos, announced an integration of their PYUSD stablecoin product with Venmo, one of the largest mobile financial applications on the market. With over 78 million users, Venmo is currently one of the largest platforms for purchasing, selling, and transacting bitcoin. As the extended digital asset realm continues to evolve alongside the Bitcoin network, a significant market share of this expansion has continued to pour into dollar trading pairs. A large percentage of volume in the Bitcoin market has trended specifically towards these dollar instruments known as stablecoins, currently dominated by USDT and USDC. 
As large, long-running financial institutions such as PayPal make waves into the stablecoin market with products like PYUSD…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Goodwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unchained Is Now Helping Customers Custody Over $2 Billion in Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74be909f3d</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/unchained-is-now-helping-customers-custody-over-2-billion-in-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T19:13:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unchained, a leading bitcoin financial services provider, has expanded its collaborative custody network with the addition of Coincover, a company known for protecting and insuring over 5 million crypto wallets, according to a press release sent to Bitcoin Magazine. This move aims to bolster the security of Unchained's collaborative custody product, which now secures over $2 billion in Bitcoin, representing a 37% year-over-year increase since October 2022.
Unchained, known for its multisignature collaborative custody, caters to institutional investors, corporate treasuries, governments, and retail customers. This approach leverages the decentralized capabilities of the Bitcoin network, requiring a minimum of two private keys to access an account's Bitcoin holdings. This security measure is…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nik Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nintendo Switch 2: Everything You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197793</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197793/nintendo-switch-2-rumors-leaks-latest-news"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T19:02:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATE: Nintendo's president has revealed how long the company will support the Switch, which could point to the Switch 2 release window.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Star Atlas Unlocks Tools to Help Game Devs Build on Solana]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199924</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199924/star-atlas-open-sources-game-development-tools-on-solana"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T19:01:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ATMTA gives Solana developers and creators free access to build using its Star Atlas tools, starting with the SAGE Labs web game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized Exchange Bluefin’s New Version Goes Live on Sui Network]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74be922ebf</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/10/03/decentralized-exchange-bluefins-new-version-goes-live-on-sui-network/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T19:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The platform’s v2 allows sub-second optimistic trades and trading without a crypto wallet, the company said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Representation Matters: How Film3 Can Help Cinema Reflect Our Diverse World]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199908</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199908/representation-matters-how-film3-can-help-cinema-reflect-our-diverse-world"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T18:12:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Filmmaker Jordan Bayne writes about the potential for decentralized technologies to help ensure that a wide range of voices are reflected onscreen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jordan Bayne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 12 People Who Will Decide Sam Bankman-Fried's Fate]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199907</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199907/jurors-who-will-decide-sam-bankman-frieds-fate"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T17:25:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The process is underway to choose the 12 jurors who will decide disgraced crypto mogul Sam Bankman-Fried's fate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo,André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Can AI Do in Gaming?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JKuqCMao/what-can-ai-do-in-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JKuqCMao/what-can-ai-do-in-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T17:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI Arena CEO Brandon Da Silva and COO Wei Xie discuss how artificial intelligence can shape the video game experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your Kids Are Going to Work Three Days a Week Thanks to AI, Says Jamie Dimon]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199913</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199913/your-kids-are-going-work-three-days-week-thanks-ai-says-jamie-dimon"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T16:27:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It might just be a virtual assistant, or artificial intelligence could also “replace humans,” said JP Morgan’s Jamie Dimon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK Financial Watchdog Hints at New Crypto Sandbox for Next Year]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199900</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199900/uk-financial-watchdog-hints-new-crypto-sandbox-next-year"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T15:23:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once it is given its powers by the Treasury, the FCA will use the UK’s upcoming crypto sandbox to draft comprehensive legislation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Trial of Sam Bankman-Fried: Live Blog, Latest News and Insights]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199892</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199892/trial-sam-bankman-fried-live-blog-latest-news-insights"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T14:28:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried faces seven criminal charges related to the dramatic collapse of his crypto empire. Here's the latest on his trial.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ledger and Sotheby's Team Up for Digital Art Exclusives]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199870</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199870/ledger-sothebys-team-digital-art-exclusives"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T13:01:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sotheby’s collectors will be provided with exclusive hardware wallets from Ledger as part of this collaboration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Is Coming to Cosmos With New Nomic Bridge]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199875</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199875/bitcoin-is-coming-cosmos-new-nomics-bridge"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T12:30:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An upgrade to the Nomic blockchain will enable the issuance of Bitcoin-based tokens within the Cosmos ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong Adds ‘Potential Tailwind’ for East Asia Crypto Trading Volumes: Chainalysis]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199874</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199874/hong-kong-adds-potential-tailwind-east-asia-crypto-trading-volumes-chainalysis"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T10:49:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong may be providing a haven for crypto investors from war-torn nations and Chinese citizens dodging restrictions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On-Chain Sleuthing Firm Chainalysis Slashes Headcount by 135]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199873</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199873/on-chain-sleuthing-firm-chainalysis-slashes-headcount-135"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T10:12:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Chainalysis cuts follow an earlier 5% workforce reduction in February, reflecting a broader trend of layoffs in the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bankrupt Crypto Lender Celsius Eyes Creditor Payback by Year End]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199871</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199871/bankrupt-crypto-lender-celsius-eyes-creditor-payback-year-end"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T09:11:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bankrupt crypto lender’s restructuring plan includes the establishment of a new entity with $450 million in seed funding.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Extends Investment Streak to 27 Weeks of Inflows: CoinShares]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199860</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199860/solana-institutional-investors-27-weeks-of-inflows"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T01:10:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The one-time "Ethereum killer" remains the darling of institutional investors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Says Its AI Training Used Public Social Media Posts—Mostly]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199855</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199855/meta-ai-training-public-social-media-posts"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T00:38:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The social media giant tapped the massive cache of posts by Facebook and Instagram users, the “majority” of the content deemed publicly available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Reasons SBF Will Be Convicted: Former SEC Lawyer]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199852</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199852/three-reasons-sbf-will-be-convicted-former-sec-lawyer"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T00:15:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["SBF has simply refused to shut-up," John Reed Stark opined on Twitter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tom Hanks and Zelda Williams Warn Fans of AI-Generated Deepfakes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199842</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199842/tom-hanks-and-zelda-williams-warn-fans-of-ai-generated-deepfakes"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T23:39:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A deepfake video shows actor Tom Hanks endorsing a dental plan; Hanks responds it's not him.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crowdfunding Site BackerKit Bans AI-Generated Imagery from Campaigns]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199835</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199835/crowdfunding-site-backerkit-bans-ai-generated-imagery-from-campaigns"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T22:56:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following Kickstarter's move, BackerKit is the latest crowdfunding site requiring users to disclose the use of AI-generated images in campaigns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Livestreams Diablo IV on Twitter to Show Off Twitch-Like Feature]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199798</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199798/elon-musk-livestream-diablo-iv-twitter-twitch"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T20:48:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[X has rolled out a livestreaming studio. How will it fare against Kick and Amazon’s Twitch?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Lewis Claims FTX Was a ‘Great Real Business’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199832</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199832/ftx-great-business-not-ponzi-micheal-lewis-pilloried"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T20:37:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author Michael Lewis claimed that FTX wasn’t a Ponzi scheme. Crypto Twitter strenuously disagreed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adidas and Moncler Collab Features AI 'Adventurers' and NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199800</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199800/adidas-moncler-fashion-collab-features-ai-adventurers-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T19:34:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The collaboration between iconic apparel brands Adidas and Moncler includes a campaign created with generative AI, plus NFT collectibles.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephanie Hirschmiller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Final Fantasy VII Rebirth: Everything You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199763</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199763/final-fantasy-vii-rebirth-everything-need-know-news-rumors-trailers"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T17:05:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The second game in the remake trilogy, Final Fantasy VII Rebirth, is just around the corner. Here’s the latest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Future ETFs Start Trading in US for First Time]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199751</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199751/ethereum-future-etfs-start-trading-us-first-time"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T16:22:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nine Ethereum futures ETFs started trading today, but demand has been lower so far than at the ProShares Bitcoin Strategy ETF launch in 2021.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale Files to Convert Ethereum Trust Into Spot ETF]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199754</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199754/grayscale-files-convert-ethereum-trust-spot-etf"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T16:09:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If approved, the conversion would likely help drop the hefty discount on Grayscale's Ethereum trust.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UBS Launches Tokenization Trial on Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199733</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199733/ubs-launches-tokenization-trial-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T14:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The initiative is part of the Monetary Authority of Singapore's Project Guardian to tokenize real-world assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Investors Lost $686 Million to Hacks, Fraud in Just 3 Months: Immunefi]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199728</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199728/investors-lost-686-million-last-quarter-to-hacks-fraud-immunefi"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T13:01:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two major hacks, Mixin Network and Multichain, accounted for nearly half of the total stolen amount, per a new report from Immunefi.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Lands Full Operating License in Singapore]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199727</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199727/coinbase-lands-full-operating-license-singapore"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T11:20:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The popular crypto exchange Coinbase continues its global expansion strategy as the crackdown stateside shows no side of abatement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried Mulled Paying Trump $5 Billion Not to Run for President, Says Michael Lewis]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199720</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199720/former-ftx-ceo-explored-paying-donald-trump-5b-not-run-office-report"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T10:23:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Promoting his newest book, author Michael Lewis revealed a startling detail about Bankman-Fried's political engagements.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Hits 2-Month High as $100M in Short Positions Liquidated Around the Market]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199718</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199718/bitcoin-hits-2-month-high-100m-in-short-positions-liquidated-around-the-market"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T09:36:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin and the crypto market kicked off October with a bullish start, driven by a wave of liquidations and a short squeeze.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana's Total Value Locked Hits New High for 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199717</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199717/solanas-total-value-locked-hits-new-high-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T09:15:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Solana on the rise, the network’s DeFi ecosystem has enjoyed a hefty surge. That could change soon, though.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SBF Can't Blame FTX Attorneys At the Start Of His Trial, Says Judge]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199696</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199696/sam-bankman-fried-advice-of-counsel-defense-blocked-in-opening-statements"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T00:33:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The defense can't say "his lawyers made him do it" in its opening statement, but the “advice of counsel” argument can be made later.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['There Are No Real Standards': Ready Player Me CEO Timmu Tõke on Building for an Open Gaming Ecosystem]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TH3KEAI0/there-are-no-real-standards-ready-player-me-ceo-timmu-tke-on-building-for-an-open-gaming-ecosystem</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TH3KEAI0/there-are-no-real-standards-ready-player-me-ceo-timmu-tke-on-building-for-an-open-gaming-ecosystem"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T17:29:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Timmu Tõke, co-founder and CEO of Ready Player Me, joins Decrypt contributor Ryan Gladwin to discuss the startup's approach to powering avatars that are interoperable across games and metaverse platforms—and what's needed to convince the industry to adopt standards and open up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain Is 'Only Way' Forward for Gaming, Says Shrapnel Studio Head]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/fhoy7Z8f/blockchain-is-only-way-forward-for-gaming-says-shrapnel-studio-head</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/fhoy7Z8f/blockchain-is-only-way-forward-for-gaming-says-shrapnel-studio-head"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T21:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shrapnel Studio Head Don Norbury tells Kate Irwin the reasons why the upcoming first-person shooter game will offer a wide range of NFTs. He also reveals team-based gameplay plans and shares how game maps have already changed this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Social Media Sentiment Is Key to Crypto Price Discovery]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/981TBppa/social-media-sentiment-is-key-to-crypto-price-discovery</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/981TBppa/social-media-sentiment-is-key-to-crypto-price-discovery"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T23:47:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sacha Ghebali, Director of Strategy and Business Development at The TIE, says social media sentiment remains a key factor in price movements for major cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin and Ethereum. However, he notes that sentiment has turned more negative lately amid regulatory uncertainty. Ghebali believes events like the Ripple lawsuit ruling significantly impacted sentiment and prices. André Beganski interviewed him at Messari Mainnet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[500Altcoins discusses DeFi Summer and the Dubai Crypto Scene - This Time Will Be Different - Episode 2]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cI7p8AK3/500altcoins-discusses-defi-summer-and-the-dubai-crypto-scene-this-time-will-be-different-episode-2</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cI7p8AK3/500altcoins-discusses-defi-summer-and-the-dubai-crypto-scene-this-time-will-be-different-episode-2"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our host Reza Jafery is joined by Gareth Fenney aka 500Altcoins. They discuss the glory days of DeFi Summer and whether or not its a smart move for builders in the crypto space to relocate to Dubai.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralize Derivatives Trading with Custom Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/lfmwAjB9/decentralize-derivatives-trading-with-custom-blockchain</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/lfmwAjB9/decentralize-derivatives-trading-with-custom-blockchain"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T10:37:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Gogel of dYdX discusses how the decentralized exchange is building a custom blockchain to fully decentralize derivatives trading. He explained how the new dYdX chain will allow validators to run order books in memory, enabling decentralized order matching at scale. This shift aims to increase security and transparency for traders while maintaining the performance of centralized exchanges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Accounting Challenges and Opportunities]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/0Sezz6pZ/crypto-accounting-challenges-and-opportunities</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/0Sezz6pZ/crypto-accounting-challenges-and-opportunities"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As crypto matures, accounting and tax regulations are evolving. Amy Kalnoki of Bitwave explains how her company helps crypto companies properly account for digital assets. She notes the importance of flexibility as new crypto assets emerge and regulations change. Stacy Elliott interviewed her at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Most Crypto Users Don't Trust Themselves to Keep Their Seed Phrase Safe: Ledger CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/0kYf2Qed/most-crypto-users-dont-trust-themselves-to-keep-their-seed-phrase-safe-ledger-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/0kYf2Qed/most-crypto-users-dont-trust-themselves-to-keep-their-seed-phrase-safe-ledger-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Stacy Elliott sat down with Ledger CEO Pascal Gauthier to discuss crypto custody post-FTX, and the hardware wallet manufacturer's controversial Ledger Recover service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[India's 1% Crypto Tax Has Been a Nightmare for High-Frequency Traders, Says Shardeum CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/fxygwLvH/indias-1-crypto-tax-has-been-a-nightmare-for-high-frequency-traders-says-shardeum-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/fxygwLvH/indias-1-crypto-tax-has-been-a-nightmare-for-high-frequency-traders-says-shardeum-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As India figures out its regulatory approach to the crypto industry, one thing is clear to Shardeum co-founder Nischal Shetty: “If you're a high-frequency trader, you can't afford to lose a percentage every time you sell,” he told Decrypt's Andre Beganski at Messari Mainnet in New York. “That's something that's caused a lot of issues.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Newly Partnered with Visa, Solana Focuses on Reliability]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/MZoxvulr/newly-partnered-with-visa-solana-focuses-on-reliability</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/MZoxvulr/newly-partnered-with-visa-solana-focuses-on-reliability"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana has improved network reliability through upgrades like Quick and local fee markets. It recently partnered with Visa to allow settling transactions in USDC on Solana. This could enable merchants to receive instant payments and save on credit card processing fees. Stacy Elliott spoke with Austin Federa, Head of Strategy for the Solana Foundation, at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Need to Start Thinking About How we Make Crypto Easy to Use: Robinhood Crypto General Manager]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PLZ0FpdC/we-need-to-start-thinking-about-how-we-make-crypto-easy-to-use-robinhood-crypto-general-manager</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PLZ0FpdC/we-need-to-start-thinking-about-how-we-make-crypto-easy-to-use-robinhood-crypto-general-manager"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Stacy Elliott sat down with Robinhood Crypto general manager Johann Kerbrat at Messari Mainnet 2023, to talk about the trading platform's crypto wallet, onboarding new users through simplicity, and keeping platform fees sustainable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin's Narrative Is Shifting Towards Layer-2 Solutions]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/axArPRp3/bitcoins-narrative-is-shifting-towards-layer-2-solutions</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/axArPRp3/bitcoins-narrative-is-shifting-towards-layer-2-solutions"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rich Rines, original Core DAO contributor and former Coinbase engineer, discusses how the narrative around Bitcoin is shifting in 2023. While Bitcoin remains digital gold, new layer 2 solutions are emerging to unlock more utility and value from the huge amounts of capital stored in Bitcoin. He says these innovations can benefit Bitcoin holders while keeping Bitcoin maximalists happy by building outside the base layer. André Beganski interviewed him at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Regulation Threatens U.S. Dominance of Financial Markets, Says CoinRoutes CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/CrpvzFjL/regulation-threatens-us-dominance-of-financial-markets-says-coinroutes-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/CrpvzFjL/regulation-threatens-us-dominance-of-financial-markets-says-coinroutes-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dave Weisberger, Co-Founder and CEO of CoinRoutes, argued that excessive regulation in the U.S. threatens to undermine the country's long-standing dominance in global financial markets. He warned that other countries are embracing blockchain and crypto to build more efficient digital markets, which could cause the US to lose its competitive edge and trillions in GDP. Weisberger said CoinRoutes is now focusing more on expanding internationally due to restrictive policies in the U.S. He was interviewed by André Beganski of Decrypt at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Developer-Friendly zkRollup to Scale Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/OvAFgxTd/building-a-developer-friendly-zkrollup-to-scale-ethereum</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/OvAFgxTd/building-a-developer-friendly-zkrollup-to-scale-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daniel Helm, head of Developer Relations at Scroll, discussess how they are building a zkRollup to scale Ethereum transactions and lower fees. He explained their focus on creating a seamless developer experience by maintaining Ethereum's ethos and tooling. Scroll aims to launch their mainnet soon, providing more scalable blockspace for Ethereum developers. Stacy Elliott of Decrypt interviewed him at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Explosive Growth Ahead for Enterprise Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/xXOrNbX9/explosive-growth-ahead-for-enterprise-blockchain</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/xXOrNbX9/explosive-growth-ahead-for-enterprise-blockchain"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paul Brody drives Ernst & Young (EY) initiatives and investments in blockchain technology across consulting, audit, and tax business lines. He says enterprise blockchain adoption is nearing an inflection point. Brody believes blockchains will one day handle 40 billion transactions daily across industries like automotive and pharma. Stacy Elliott interviewed him at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Base as a 'Bridge, Not an Island']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/oZPr7bzY/base-as-a-bridge-not-an-island</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/oZPr7bzY/base-as-a-bridge-not-an-island"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:41:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase's Jesse Pollak, creator of layer-2 blockchain Base, says the launch of the network has exceeded expectations, even if plans changed along the way. He believes Arbitrum One will help bring billions onto blockchain by enabling seamless user experiences. Stacy Elliott interviewed him at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On-Chain Gaming Poised for Mass Adoption]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/6ZryETKh/on-chain-gaming-poised-for-mass-adoption</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/6ZryETKh/on-chain-gaming-poised-for-mass-adoption"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T02:23:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jack O'Holleran is CEO and co-founder of SKALE Labs. He explains how on-chain gaming is ready for the mainstream after overcoming early challenges like high fees and poor user experience. Companies can now build blockchain games that look and feel like traditional games, and scalability improvements allow games to support hundreds of millions of players without performance issues. He was interviewed by André Beganski at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Blockchains Boom Creates Opportunity and Challenges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/7Ys4Rxay/new-blockchains-boom-creates-opportunity-and-challenges</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/7Ys4Rxay/new-blockchains-boom-creates-opportunity-and-challenges"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T02:07:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Billy Sebell of the XDC Foundation discussed the proliferation of new layer-1 and layer-2 blockchain solutions. While this expands possibilities, he noted projects must still attract users amidst growing competition. Sebell highlighted the benefits of targeting niche use cases and bringing real-world assets on-chain via tokenization. He was interviewed by André Beganski of Decrypt at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accessible Self-Custody for Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/kA1Bqu4H/accessible-self-custody-for-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/kA1Bqu4H/accessible-self-custody-for-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T00:52:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dave Lemke is the CFO & CCO at Giddy, creators of a crypto wallet with decentralized private key security. He explains how their solution allows self-custody while still being recoverable. He highlighted increasing demand for self-custody after the FTX collapse. Lemke also touched on upcoming US crypto regulations and Getty's roadmap to simplify staking and other complex processes. Stacy Elliott interviewed him at Messari Mainnet 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>