<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-12-21T03:15:39.380Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-12-21T03:15:39.380Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Scandal: Russian Oligarch Accused Of Sanctions Evasion In £15 Million Firm Share Sale]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748c9d7a23</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/russian-sanctions-evasion-in-15-million-crypto/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T03:09:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A sanctioned “Russian oligarch”, Mikhail Klyukin, has come under scrutiny for allegedly evading sanctions by selling over £15 million worth of shares in a crypto firm chaired by former UK Chancellor Philip Hammond. 
 
The transaction, which involved transferring the funds into cryptocurrency, is believed to have been an attempt to circumvent US sanctions.
 
Crypto Company Copper Technologies Under Fire
 
According to a report by The Guardian, Mikhail Klyukin faced sanctions due to his role on the supervisory board of Russian lender Sovcombank, following the invasion of Ukraine and the US’s targeting of “elites close to Vladimir Putin.” 
 
 
Copper Technologies, a company specializing in digital systems for cryptocurrency investment and trading, became concerned when Klyukin, who owned more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Claude AI Creator Anthropic to Raise $750 Million in New Funding: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19123714/Claude-AI-Creator-Anthropic-to-Raise-750-Million-in-New-Funding-Report</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19123714/Claude-AI-Creator-Anthropic-to-Raise-750-Million-in-New-Funding-Report"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T03:01:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic clarifies its $18.4 billion pre-funding round valuation as a new fundraising push targets a $750 million raise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Scandal: Russian Oligarch Accused Of Sanctions Evasion In £15 Million Firm Share Sale]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19123711/Crypto-Scandal-Russian-Oligarch-Accused-Of-Sanctions-Evasion-In-15-Million-Firm-Share-Sale</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19123711/Crypto-Scandal-Russian-Oligarch-Accused-Of-Sanctions-Evasion-In-15-Million-Firm-Share-Sale"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T03:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A sanctioned “Russian oligarch”, Mikhail Klyukin, has come under scrutiny for allegedly evading sanctions by selling over £15 million worth of shares in a crypto firm chaired by former UK Chancellor Philip Hammond. The transaction, which involved transferring the funds into cryptocurrency, is...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The AI-Driven Future of CRM in Law Firms]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19123705/The-AI-Driven-Future-of-CRM-in-Law-Firms</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19123705/The-AI-Driven-Future-of-CRM-in-Law-Firms"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T02:52:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the rapidly evolving legal industry, effective client relationship management, now AI-driven, has become the linchpin for law firms aiming not just to survive but to thrive. The infusion of Artificial Intelligence (AI) into Client Relationship Management (CRM) has emerged as a game-changer,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized Exchange PancakeSwap Announces Massive CAKE Token Burn Amid Rising Trading Fees]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19123689/Decentralized-Exchange-PancakeSwap-Announces-Massive-CAKE-Token-Burn-Amid-Rising-Trading-Fees</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19123689/Decentralized-Exchange-PancakeSwap-Announces-Massive-CAKE-Token-Burn-Amid-Rising-Trading-Fees"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T02:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Popular decentralized exchange PancakeSwap has recently announced the burn of over 9 million of its native $CAKE tokens in a move that destroyed over $19 million worth of tokens, in a move that helps to reduce their circulating supply. In a post on the microblogging platform X (formerly known as...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Major Crypto Exchange Drops Shiba Inu, Dogecoin, and Cardano in Canada Amid Delisting Wave, Stands by XRP]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19123672/Major-Crypto-Exchange-Drops-Shiba-Inu-Dogecoin-and-Cardano-in-Canada-Amid-Delisting-Wave-Stands-by-XRP</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19123672/Major-Crypto-Exchange-Drops-Shiba-Inu-Dogecoin-and-Cardano-in-Canada-Amid-Delisting-Wave-Stands-by-XRP"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T01:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prominent cryptocurrency exchange Uphold has recently announced a significant wave of delisting impacting several major cryptocurrencies for its users in Canada, in a move that comes after the platform classified several of these tokens as Tier 3. According to an email sent to Canadian users,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Executive Predicts ‘Breakout Moment’ for Crypto Institutional Adoption]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748c859747</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ripple-executive-predicts-breakout-moment-for-crypto-institutional-adoption/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T01:38:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple’s president has shared her crypto predictions, stating that 2024 could mark “the breakout moment where institutional adoption for real-world utility takes off.” She emphasized: “The industry needs to build compliance tooling in a decentralized environment. It’s the next frontier of innovation in blockchain.”
 
‘We Reached the Tipping Point for Crypto to Be Recognized as Mainstream’
 
Ripple’s president, Monica Long, shared several predictions regarding the future of crypto and blockchain over the next 12 months on social media platform X Tuesday.
 
“Within the past couple of years, we’ve seen many more traditional financial players such as Fidelity, Blackrock, Paypal, and Visa integrating or partnering with crypto-native companies to offer crypto and blockchain services and products…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are Ethereum Layer-2s The Next Fraud Paradise? This Co-Founder Asks Hard Questions]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748c859f7a</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-layer-2s-fraud-paradise/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T01:37:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bartek Kiepuszewski, the co-founder of L2Beat, a portal for tracking Ethereum layer-2 activities, is concerned about the security and consistency of existing off-chain scaling solutions, suggesting that without fraud-proofs, there is room for fraud and irregularities.
 
Focus On Optimism And Manta: What’s Going On?
 
Taking to X on December 20, Kiepuszewski observed that some layer-2 solutions, such as Manta and Optimism, rely on sequencers to post data to Ethereum. However, without fraud-proofs, there is no way to verify that the data published by the Sequencer on the Ethereum mainnet is accurate or complete. 
 
In the co-founder’s view, whenever a sequencer posts the batch of transactions on the main net, there is no layer-1 state or event change. Per Kiepuszewski ‘s assessment, this is …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dalmas Ngetich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are Ethereum Layer-2s The Next Fraud Paradise? This Co-Founder Asks Hard Questions]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19123638/Are-Ethereum-Layer-2s-The-Next-Fraud-Paradise-This-Co-Founder-Asks-Hard-Questions</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19123638/Are-Ethereum-Layer-2s-The-Next-Fraud-Paradise-This-Co-Founder-Asks-Hard-Questions"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T01:30:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bartek Kiepuszewski, the co-founder of L2Beat, a portal for tracking Ethereum layer-2 activities, is concerned about the security and consistency of existing off-chain scaling solutions, suggesting that without fraud-proofs, there is room for fraud and irregularities. Focus On Optimism And...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2 risks around Bitcoin ETF launch that no one’s talking about]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19123626/2-risks-around-Bitcoin-ETF-launch-that-no-ones-talking-about</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19123626/2-risks-around-Bitcoin-ETF-launch-that-no-ones-talking-about"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T01:25:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a Dec. 19 podcast, Coinbase researchers warned there are at least two potential problems that could arise with the launch of spot Bitcoin ETFs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Trader Prints 4,827x Gains in Two Weeks Trading New Avalanche-Based Memecoin: On-Chain Data]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19123610/Crypto-Trader-Prints-4827x-Gains-in-Two-Weeks-Trading-New-Avalanche-Based-Memecoin-On-Chain-Data</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19123610/Crypto-Trader-Prints-4827x-Gains-in-Two-Weeks-Trading-New-Avalanche-Based-Memecoin-On-Chain-Data"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T01:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An unknown crypto trader is seeing astronomical gains after holding a new meme token for just a couple of weeks. On-chain data tracker Lookonchain says that the trader spent less than $500 to acquire a stack of Coq Inu (COQ), a memecoin running on the Avalanche (AVAX) network. According to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin disrupts Banks #bitcoin #crypto #shorts]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19123614/Bitcoin-disrupts-Banks-bitcoin-crypto-shorts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19123614/Bitcoin-disrupts-Banks-bitcoin-crypto-shorts"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T01:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protocol Village: Bitfinex Securities Announces First Tokenized Bond on Liquid Network]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748c83bea0</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/12/20/protocol-latest-tech-news-crypto-blockchain/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T00:32:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest in blockchain tech upgrades, funding announcements and deals. For the period of Dec 21-Jan. 3. (EDITOR'S NOTE: We will be taking much-needed time off around the end of the year, so updates will be less frequent. Happy holidays!)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bradley Keoun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Korea’s Financial Chief Reportedly Plans Crypto Discussion with Gary Gensler]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19123596/South-Koreas-Financial-Chief-Reportedly-Plans-Crypto-Discussion-with-Gary-Gensler</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19123596/South-Koreas-Financial-Chief-Reportedly-Plans-Crypto-Discussion-with-Gary-Gensler"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T00:21:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yoo Bok-hyun, the head of South Korea’s Financial Supervisory Services (FSS) is set to visit the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to engage in discussions about cryptocurrency with SEC Chair Gary Gensler. The primary agenda of this visit revolves around sharing insights into the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trust Machines – Building the Bitcoin Economy]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19123573/Trust-Machines-Building-the-Bitcoin-Economy</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19123573/Trust-Machines-Building-the-Bitcoin-Economy"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T00:16:53.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Powerball Hits $572 Million: 10 Things To Buy With The Winnings, Including Cybertrucks, Cryptocurrency, Stocks, Gold And More]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19123578/Powerball-Hits-572-Million-10-Things-To-Buy-With-The-Winnings-Including-Cybertrucks-Cryptocurrency-Stocks-Gold-And-More</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19123578/Powerball-Hits-572-Million-10-Things-To-Buy-With-The-Winnings-Including-Cybertrucks-Cryptocurrency-Stocks-Gold-And-More"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T00:10:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Winning a large lottery prize continues to be a dream of many Americans with large payouts for the Powerball and Mega Millions in 2022 leading to both lottery drawings among the most searched items on Google for the year. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is The XRP Price Action Something You Should Worry About? Legal Expert Chimes In]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748c8e098c</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/xrp-price-action-legal-expert/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T00:08:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The XRP price action continues to be a concern for many in the XRP community. Some have gone as far as stating that the crypto token’s price is suppressed. This pro-XRP legal expert, however, thinks otherwise as he provides a different perspective on XRP’s relatively tepid movement. 
 
XRP Holders Need Deeper Conviction
 
In a post on his X (formerly Twitter) platform, Bill Morgan said that convictions (likely in reference to XRP holders) need to be “deeper than a day, week, or month of price action.” He mentioned how he doesn’t read much into a month’s price action in the crypto market. 
 
 
Before then, the legal expert had highlighted how XRP’s price action hasn’t been great, as it is down over 2% over the last month. Although the 2% drop seems to be significant to Morgan, he was choosi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK top court rejects patents for two inventions birthed by AI]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19123565/UK-top-court-rejects-patents-for-two-inventions-birthed-by-AI</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19123565/UK-top-court-rejects-patents-for-two-inventions-birthed-by-AI"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T00:04:22.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is The XRP Price Action Something You Should Worry About? Legal Expert Chimes In]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19123563/Is-The-XRP-Price-Action-Something-You-Should-Worry-About-Legal-Expert-Chimes-In</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19123563/Is-The-XRP-Price-Action-Something-You-Should-Worry-About-Legal-Expert-Chimes-In"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T00:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The XRP price action continues to be a concern for many in the XRP community. Some have gone as far as stating that the crypto token’s price is suppressed. This pro-XRP legal expert, however, thinks otherwise as he provides a different perspective on XRP’s relatively tepid movement. XRP Holders...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ledger to halt blind signing on dApps, encourages clear signing for security]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19123534/Ledger-to-halt-blind-signing-on-dApps-encourages-clear-signing-for-security</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19123534/Ledger-to-halt-blind-signing-on-dApps-encourages-clear-signing-for-security"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T23:39:31.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Judge Kaplan Rejects Bankman-Fried’s Request for Sentencing Delay, Affirms March 2024 Date]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748c892975</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/judge-kaplan-rejects-bankman-frieds-request-for-sentencing-delay-affirms-march-2024-date/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T23:37:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent development in the high-profile case of Sam Bankman-Fried, the founder of the now-defunct crypto exchange FTX, a request for postponement of the sentencing hearing was firmly denied by U.S. District Judge Lewis Kaplan. Bankman-Fried’s legal team had sought a four to six-week adjournment, citing the need for additional preparation time. However, the court’s refusal to grant this extension marks a significant moment in this ongoing legal saga.
 
Sam Bankman-Fried Sentencing Date Proceeds as Kaplan Denies Delay
 
The defense, representing Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF), submitted a formal request for the adjournment of the sentencing hearing, originally scheduled for March 28, 2024. This plea was grounded in the defense’s requirement for more time to gather necessary materials and prepar…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Trader Turns $454 into $2.19 Million Trading Avalanche-Based Memecoin]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19123533/Crypto-Trader-Turns-454-into-219-Million-Trading-Avalanche-Based-Memecoin</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19123533/Crypto-Trader-Turns-454-into-219-Million-Trading-Avalanche-Based-Memecoin"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T23:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improbable’s Sale of The Multiplayer Group to Keywords Studios Marks Metaverse Industry Milestone]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19123528/Improbables-Sale-of-The-Multiplayer-Group-to-Keywords-Studios-Marks-Metaverse-Industry-Milestone</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19123528/Improbables-Sale-of-The-Multiplayer-Group-to-Keywords-Studios-Marks-Metaverse-Industry-Milestone"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T23:22:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On December 18, metaverse technology company Improbable made an important announcement, revealing the sale of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Black Market Bazaar To Digital Dungeon: Silk Road Bitcoin Hoard Forfeited, Ulbricht's Shadow Remains]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19123532/From-Black-Market-Bazaar-To-Digital-Dungeon-Silk-Road-Bitcoin-Hoard-Forfeited-Ulbrichts-Shadow-Remains</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19123532/From-Black-Market-Bazaar-To-Digital-Dungeon-Silk-Road-Bitcoin-Hoard-Forfeited-Ulbrichts-Shadow-Remains"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T23:15:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a definitive chapter for the infamous Silk Road online black market, a U.S. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are Dogecoin Payments Coming To X? DOGE Wallet CTO Says Yes]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748c8bee6c</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-payments-x-doge/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T23:09:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The expectation of Dogecoin payments on the X (formerly Twitter) platform has ramped up over the last few years, most especially when billionaire Elon Musk took control of the social media platform. But even a year after the was completed, there is yet to be an official acceptance of DOGE payments on the platform. However, this has not discouraged users who believe that Dogecoin payments are coming to X, one of whom is MyDoge Wallet CTO Alex Lewis.
 
Dogecoin Payments Are Coming To X
 
In an interview with Fabrice Calmels, Alex Lewis shared some interesting thoughts about Dogecoin payments and when they are coming to the X platform. Sharing his expectations for the X platform, Lewis explains that the company already carried out applications to become a custodial service such as PayPal. Thi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Best Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. appeals court finalizes mandate for forfeiture of Silk Road bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19123495/US-appeals-court-finalizes-mandate-for-forfeiture-of-Silk-Road-bitcoin</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19123495/US-appeals-court-finalizes-mandate-for-forfeiture-of-Silk-Road-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T23:08:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A U.S. appeals court finalized a mandate on Wednesday that formalizes the forfeiture of 69,370 bitcoin connected to the Silk Road.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[If You Invested $1,000 In Robinhood Stock When The Justice Department Seized Sam Bankman-Fried's Stake In The Company, Here's How Much You'd Have Today]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19123500/If-You-Invested-1000-In-Robinhood-Stock-When-The-Justice-Department-Seized-Sam-Bankman-Frieds-Stake-In-The-Company-Heres-How-Much-Youd-Have-Today</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19123500/If-You-Invested-1000-In-Robinhood-Stock-When-The-Justice-Department-Seized-Sam-Bankman-Frieds-Stake-In-The-Company-Heres-How-Much-Youd-Have-Today"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T23:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smart Contract Tokens Solana and Avalanche Surge, Closing in on BNB and Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748c7dba84</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/smart-contract-tokens-solana-and-avalanche-surge-closing-in-on-bnb-and-ethereum/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T21:38:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, the smart contract platform tokens solana (SOL) and avalanche (AVAX), both considered layer one (L1) crypto assets, have been narrowing the gap with ethereum (ETH), the most prominent smart contract platform in terms of market valuation. Over the past month, solana has experienced a 42% surge, while avalanche has soared by 104%.
 
Solana and Avalanche Make Strong Comeback in Crypto Market
 
Following the collapse of the Terra blockchain and the FTX failure, SOL and AVAX suffered substantial declines against the U.S. dollar. These cryptocurrencies, once ranked among the top ten, were briefly ousted from their elite top ten status.
 
However, they have since reclaimed their positions among the top ten leading tokens, with SOL currently in fifth place, having overtaken XRP, and AVAX…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Espionage Unveiled: Poland Sentences 14 ‘Spies’ For Sabotage]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748c7debe1</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-espionage-unveiled-poland-sentences-14-spies/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T21:37:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a high-profile case, a Polish court has pronounced its verdict, finding 14 individuals from Russia, Belarus, and Ukraine guilty of espionage. The alleged spy ring operated within Poland and accepted crypto payments of up to $10,000 to carry out acts of espionage in support of Russia’s interests.
 
Crypto-Paid Spy Network Exposed
 
According to a report by Barron’s, the defendants faced charges last month for various offenses, including plotting to derail trains carrying aid to Ukraine and monitoring critical infrastructure and military facilities in the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) member state. The court delivered jail sentences ranging from 13 months to six years.
 
 
While delivering the verdict, Judge Jaroslaw Kowalski stated that all the defendants were found guilty of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Leapfrogs XRP as Fifth-Largest Crypto, Spurred by Meme Coin Mania]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748c7a5b68</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/12/20/solana-leapfrogs-xrp-as-fifth-largest-crypto-spurred-by-meme-coin-mania/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T20:58:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana has overtaken XRP as the fifth-largest cryptocurrency, with its market cap hitting a 20-month high of $33.7 billion, according to CoinMarketCap.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[If You're in Crypto, You're a Criminal]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748c673c67</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/12/20/if-youre-in-crypto-youre-a-criminal/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T20:15:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Senator Warren thinks all crypto people are crooks. We obviously agree. 100%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Kuhn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX's Former CEO Sam Bankman-Fried Denied Request for Prolonged Sentencing Process]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748c678f71</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/ftxs-former-ceo-sam-bankman-fried-denied-request-for-prolonged-sentencing-process/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T20:12:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The legal tussle surrounding Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF), the Former CEO of FTX, intensified after a federal judge denied his defense team's  
plea for an extended sentencing process. This decision occurred amid the prospect  
of a looming second trial following SBF's recent conviction on  
charges of fraud and conspiracy.
As initially reported by Coindesk, SBF's  
defense team had sought an extension of four to six weeks for his sentencing. The team emphasized a potential second trial  
slated for March 11, which could impact the pending sentencing scheduled for  
March 28. 
SBF's Defense Team Wants All Charges  
Resolved
SBF's defense team sought to delay the sentencing and  
presentencing interview with the US Probation and Pretrial Services System,  
citing the need to resolve all charges …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Charles Hoskinson Praises Cardano For New Achievement]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748c604ffd</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/charles-hoskinson-praises-cardano/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T20:06:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano has been one of the fastest-growing decentralized finance (DeFi) networks in recent weeks and this has shone through in the number of transactions being carried out on a daily basis. As this growth ramps up, founder Charles Hoskison has celebrated the achievements of the network.
 
Cardano Founder Celebrates Full Blocks
 
For the longest time, the Cardano network has been referred to as a zombie chain due to it not seeing as many transactions as other networks in the same category. However, as the price of its native token, ADA, has been on the rise, so has the network usage.
 
 
Recently, the community has gone from being worried about not enough activity to the blocks being produced on the blockchain being too full. This has been a welcome development for Hoskinson who took to X …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ledger Responds to Connect Kit Exploit With Reimbursement Plan, Security Overhaul]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748c6366f1</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ledger-responds-to-connect-kit-exploit-with-reimbursement-plan-security-overhaul/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T19:40:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a decisive move following a significant security incident, Ledger, a well known crypto hardware wallet manufacturer and security firm, announced a response plan. Approximately $600,000 in assets were stolen from users due to an exploit involving blind signing on EVM decentralized applications (dapps). Ledger detailed on Dec. 20, 2023, that it has vowed to fully reimburse all affected users, including non-customers, a commitment underscored by the company’s CEO, Pascal Gauthier.
 
Crypto Security Firm Ledger Vows Full Payback Post $600K Hack
 
The incident, detected on December 14, 2023, involved an exploit of the Ledger Connect Kit, which led to the injection of malicious code into various dapps. This code deceived users into signing transactions that drained their wallets. Ledger’s det…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin As A CBDC]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748c688e43</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/bitcoin-as-a-cbdc"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T18:59:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article is featured in Bitcoin Magazine’s “The Primary Issue”. Click here to get your Annual Bitcoin Magazine Subscription.
Click here to download a PDF of this article.
"What luck for rulers that men do not think.” 
– Adolf Hitler
Bitcoin will not kill the U.S. dollar. It will become the U.S. dollar, with all controls and restrictions that any CBDC issuer could dream of. “Impossible!” I hear you crying out, giggling to myself in the face of the utmost ignorance that seems to have accumulated quadratically with bitcoin’s price increase. “Bitcoin is freedom money!” 
And this is where you’re wrong. Bitcoin is anything we make it out to be. It’s a technology just like the internet, which we’ve managed to successfully turn into the most efficient surveillance technology the world has ever…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>L0la L33tz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cogwise AI News Aggregator: Revolutionizing Decision-Making in Real Time]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748c69bf17</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/cogwise-ai-news-aggregator-revolutionizing-decision-making-in-real-time/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T18:50:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a groundbreaking leap for financial technology, Cogwise AI unveils its state-of-the-art “AI News Aggregator,” reshaping how traders approach decision-making. This cutting-edge feature integrates advanced artificial intelligence and machine learning algorithms, providing real-time analysis of news and global trends. By monitoring diverse news sources and social media in real-time, the trading bot predicts market movements tied to events, offering traders a unique advantage in navigating the ever-changing landscape.
 
What does Cogwise offer?
 
Cogwise (COGW) is designed for blockchain technology, global industries, and the crypto world, using cutting-edge algorithms and high-speed computing capabilities. The AI Inference Engine empowers users to harness the power of cutting-edge innovati…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Rise of Chain Abstraction and End of Blockchain Factionalism]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748c56a142</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/12/20/the-rise-of-chain-abstraction-and-end-of-blockchain-factionalism/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T18:14:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Will 2024 be the beginning of the end of maximalism in crypto? NEAR Foundation CEO Illia Polosukhin thinks so.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Illia  Polosukhin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Achieves Regulatory Triumph: Officially Enlisted In Central Bank Of Ireland’s VASPs Register]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748c57e910</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ripple-secures-regulatory-approval-irelands-vasps/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T18:05:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a series of regulatory achievements, blockchain company Ripple has marked another significant milestone by announcing the inclusion of its Irish subsidiary, Ripple Markets Ireland Limited, in the Central Bank of Ireland’s list of registered Virtual Asset Service Providers (VASPs).
 
Ireland’s Favorable Stance On Blockchain Innovation
 
According to the company’s announcement on December 20, Ripple’s registration as a VASP further solidifies its commitment to working closely with regulators worldwide to promote the adoption and benefits of blockchain and cryptocurrency technology in the enterprise sector. 
 
 
Eric van Miltenburg, Senior Vice President of Strategic Initiatives at Ripple, emphasized the importance of the Central Bank of Ireland’s decision, stating that it marks a “signifi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s Hashrate Hits Historic 527 EH/s Lifetime Peak, Shattering Previous Records]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748c535d97</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoins-hashrate-hits-historic-527-eh-s-lifetime-peak-shattering-previous-records/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T17:40:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recent data, analyzing the seven-day average of Bitcoin’s hashrate, reveals yet another lifetime peak in the network’s performance. On Dec. 20, 2023, Bitcoin’s hashrate climbed to an unprecedented high. The seven-day simple moving average (SMA) indicates that the hashrate hit 527 exahash per second (EH/s), surpassing the former high of 507 EH/s recorded on Dec. 16.
 
Bitcoin Miners Reap Record Rewards as Hashrate Skyrockets to 527 EH/s
 
On Wednesday, Dec. 20, 2023, Bitcoin’s total hashrate soared to a new record, as reported by Luxor’s hashrateindex.com seven-day SMA. The hashrate currently stands at 527 EH/s, surpassing half a zettahash per second (ZH/s), which translates to 527 quintillion hashes every second. Over the last 90 days, the average hashrate hovered around 462 EH/s, with the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitfinex Raises $5.2M via Tokenized Bond in Collaboration with Mikro Kapital]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748c5c6f90</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/bitfinex-raises-52m-via-tokenized-bond-in-collaboration-with-mikro-kapital/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T17:32:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitfinex Securities Ltd. has raised over $5.2  
million USDt through its tokenised bond ALT2612. This was facilitated by ALTERNATIVE,  
a Luxembourg-based securitization fund managed by microfinancing leader Mikro  
Kapital, the company noted in a statement today(Wednesday). 
ALT2612 is a bond issued on Liquid Network, a  
Bitcoin blockchain side-chain tailored for regulated security token offerings.  
Bitfinex Securities, in collaboration with Mikro Kapital, has praised this  
achievement as a joint commitment to innovation within the microfinancing  
sector.
Bitfinex Targets Expansion in Microfinancing Sector
Paolo Adoino, the CEO of Tether and CTO of Bitfinex  
Securities, mentioned: "This proof of concept is more than just  
fundraising; it's a significant stride towards integrating US…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>