<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-12-23T03:15:32.774Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-12-23T03:15:32.774Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There Is a Crypto Museum Being Built and You Need To Pay Attention]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7483eaf6f4</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/there-is-a-crypto-museum-being-built-and-you-need-to-pay-attention/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-23T03:09:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the cryptocurrency industry, a monumental project is underway: the Crypto Museum.
 
This unique initiative aims to create an interactive, vibrant space that explores the rich history and dynamic future of cryptocurrencies.
 
The Crypto Museum promises to be a cornerstone of the new narrative of digital finance as a hub for education, preservation, and innovation.
 
Crypto.Museum’s Scope and Goals
 
Crypto Museum celebrates the past, but it’s also a roadmap for the future.
 
Its main objectives are as follows:
 
Cryptography history should be preserved 
The documentation of the evolution of cryptocurrencies and blockchain, ensuring that significant events and breakthroughs are preserved.
 
Identify key milestones in the industry 
Exhibits and timelines highlight key developments and chan…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Orguno</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple’s Bold Move – Exploring AI Integration, XRP Price Holds Steady]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19128556/Ripples-Bold-Move-Exploring-AI-Integration-XRP-Price-Holds-Steady</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19128556/Ripples-Bold-Move-Exploring-AI-Integration-XRP-Price-Holds-Steady"/>
        <updated>2023-12-23T03:02:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a noteworthy development, Ripple Labs’ Chief Technology Officer (CTO), Joel Katz, has hinted at the AI integration into the blockchain landscape by 2024. Katz envisions a transformative impact on cybersecurity and financial services, particularly in bolstering the security of ledger systems....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There Is a Crypto Museum Being Built and You Need To Pay Attention]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19128554/There-Is-a-Crypto-Museum-Being-Built-and-You-Need-To-Pay-Attention</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19128554/There-Is-a-Crypto-Museum-Being-Built-and-You-Need-To-Pay-Attention"/>
        <updated>2023-12-23T03:01:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the cryptocurrency industry, a monumental project is underway: the Crypto Museum. This unique initiative aims to create an interactive, vibrant space that explores the rich history and dynamic future of cryptocurrencies. The Crypto Museum promises to be a cornerstone of the new narrative of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Strikes Settlement Over Embed Acquisition Amid Bankruptcy With Founder Sam Bankman-Fried And Others]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19128534/FTX-Strikes-Settlement-Over-Embed-Acquisition-Amid-Bankruptcy-With-Founder-Sam-Bankman-Fried-And-Others</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19128534/FTX-Strikes-Settlement-Over-Embed-Acquisition-Amid-Bankruptcy-With-Founder-Sam-Bankman-Fried-And-Others"/>
        <updated>2023-12-23T02:35:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FTX, amidst bankruptcy, reaches a settlement related to their acquisition of Embed, ensuring recovery for debtors but still pursuing claims against founder Sam Bankman-Fried and others, following a series of lawsuits. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Chair Gary Gensler Issues Crypto Warnings as Anticipation of Spot Bitcoin ETF Approval Soars]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7483d5815c</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/sec-chair-gary-gensler-issues-crypto-warnings-as-anticipation-of-spot-bitcoin-etf-approval-soars/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-23T02:33:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Chairman Gary Gensler has issued warnings regarding cryptocurrency investments. “There is a lot of noncompliance in the crypto space,” he stressed, emphasizing that it “undermines confidence when so many people have been hurt and all they can do is stand in line in the bankruptcy court.” Gensler’s warnings came as the market expects imminent approvals of spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs).
 
Gary Gensler’s Crypto Warnings
 
The chairman of the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), Gary Gensler, issued crypto warnings on social media platform X Thursday. The SEC chief wrote:
 

There is a lot of noncompliance in the crypto space. It undermines confidence when so many people have been hurt and all they can do is stand in line in t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum’s Dencun upgrade set for launch in 2024, details here]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19128528/Ethereums-Dencun-upgrade-set-for-launch-in-2024-details-here</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19128528/Ethereums-Dencun-upgrade-set-for-launch-in-2024-details-here"/>
        <updated>2023-12-23T02:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum developers aim for a January deployment of the Dencun upgrade on the testnet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Case’s Epic Flaws Exposed: SEC’s Bold Plea For Sanction Waiver Uncovers Critical Insights]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7483d74af9</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-case-errors-sec-appeals-for-sanction-waiver/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-23T02:08:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) lawyers have issued an apology to a judge for misrepresenting facts in a case involving a crypto firm. 
 
The SEC lawyers expressed deep regret and acknowledged their errors in securing a restraining order and asset freeze against Digital Licensing Inc., also known as DEBT Box.
 
Regret And Corrective Actions In Crypto Lawsuit
 
According to a Fortune Magazine report, following the judge’s order to explain the reasons behind their missteps, the SEC lawyers submitted a filing to the US District Court of Utah. 
 
In the filing, they stated that the Commission deeply regrets the issued orders and has taken measures to address the situation, including mandatory training for the staff members involved in the crypto investigation.
 
 
SEC Enforcement C…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Case’s Epic Flaws Exposed: SEC’s Bold Plea For Sanction Waiver Uncovers Critical Insights]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19128514/Crypto-Cases-Epic-Flaws-Exposed-SECs-Bold-Plea-For-Sanction-Waiver-Uncovers-Critical-Insights</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19128514/Crypto-Cases-Epic-Flaws-Exposed-SECs-Bold-Plea-For-Sanction-Waiver-Uncovers-Critical-Insights"/>
        <updated>2023-12-23T02:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) lawyers have issued an apology to a judge for misrepresenting facts in a case involving a crypto firm. The SEC lawyers expressed deep regret and acknowledged their errors in securing a restraining order and asset freeze against Digital Licensing Inc.,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Alarm: XRP’s Trade Volume Hits Six-Year Low, A Cause For Concern?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19128506/Crypto-Alarm-XRPs-Trade-Volume-Hits-Six-Year-Low-A-Cause-For-Concern</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19128506/Crypto-Alarm-XRPs-Trade-Volume-Hits-Six-Year-Low-A-Cause-For-Concern"/>
        <updated>2023-12-23T02:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A significant dip in XRP daily trading volume has caught the attention of investors and analysts alike. On Thursday, XRP’s trading volume plummeted to levels not seen in the past six years, a development that has raised eyebrows among crypto enthusiasts. On this day, December 21st, #XRP :...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI eyes potential funding round exceeding $100B: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19128504/OpenAI-eyes-potential-funding-round-exceeding-100B-Report</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19128504/OpenAI-eyes-potential-funding-round-exceeding-100B-Report"/>
        <updated>2023-12-23T01:53:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The news follows OpenAI's Sam Altman declaring to his 2.5 million followers that 2023 is the "crazy year" when AI started being taken seriously.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paxos Recieves Nod to Launch New Stablecoin on Solana]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19128489/Paxos-Recieves-Nod-to-Launch-New-Stablecoin-on-Solana</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19128489/Paxos-Recieves-Nod-to-Launch-New-Stablecoin-on-Solana"/>
        <updated>2023-12-23T01:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After shutting down BUSD, Paxos is back with another stablecoin, USDP.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Survey Reveals Shift in Crypto Industry as Equity Gains Favor Over Tokens Among Hires]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19128483/New-Survey-Reveals-Shift-in-Crypto-Industry-as-Equity-Gains-Favor-Over-Tokens-Among-Hires</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19128483/New-Survey-Reveals-Shift-in-Crypto-Industry-as-Equity-Gains-Favor-Over-Tokens-Among-Hires"/>
        <updated>2023-12-23T01:09:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recent survey conducted by Variant and Union Square Ventures has shed light on a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$10,000 Exits Wells Fargo Account and Allegedly Vanishes, Triggering Lawsuit Against Two US Banks: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19128481/10000-Exits-Wells-Fargo-Account-and-Allegedly-Vanishes-Triggering-Lawsuit-Against-Two-US-Banks-Report</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19128481/10000-Exits-Wells-Fargo-Account-and-Allegedly-Vanishes-Triggering-Lawsuit-Against-Two-US-Banks-Report"/>
        <updated>2023-12-23T01:04:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A North Carolina couple is suing banking giants Wells Fargo and Truist after thousands of dollars allegedly disappeared without a trace. Court documents show Kevin Kohl and Taylor Goodnough accuse the banks of violating the Electronic Funds Transfer Act and engaging in unfair and deceptive trade...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Makes ‘Rare’ Calls to Spot Bitcoin ETF Applicants — Analyst Says ‘Good Sign’ for January 10 Approval]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7483dc3fe5</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/sec-makes-rare-calls-to-spot-bitcoin-etf-applicants-analyst-says-good-sign-for-january-10-approval/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-23T01:02:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has reportedly made “rare” calls to spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) issuers and exchanges regarding their applications. A Bloomberg ETF analyst views this development as a “good sign” for the expected approvals by Jan. 10. The securities regulator has insisted on the cash creation model, rather than the in-kind model, for spot bitcoin ETFs.
 
SEC’s ‘Rare’ Calls Regarding Spot Bitcoin ETFs
 
The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) actively held meetings with spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) applicants this week. Blackrock, the world’s largest asset manager, and several other spot bitcoin ETF applicants met with the securities watchdog on Thursday, according to filings with the SEC.
 
Moreover, Fox Business Network’s …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) Layer-2 Scaling Solution Witnesses 391% Growth in Addresses This Year: IntoTheBlock]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19128478/Ethereum-ETH-Layer-2-Scaling-Solution-Witnesses-391-Growth-in-Addresses-This-Year-IntoTheBlock</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19128478/Ethereum-ETH-Layer-2-Scaling-Solution-Witnesses-391-Growth-in-Addresses-This-Year-IntoTheBlock"/>
        <updated>2023-12-23T01:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One Ethereum (ETH) layer-2 scaling solution has witnessed staggering address growth since January, according to the crypto analytics firm IntoTheBlock. The firm notes that Optimism’s (OP) network currently clocks more than 5.9 million addresses with a balance, a massive 391% increase from the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Whales Do $2.2 Billion Selloff, But BTC Stays Strong]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19128476/Bitcoin-Whales-Do-22-Billion-Selloff-But-BTC-Stays-Strong</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19128476/Bitcoin-Whales-Do-22-Billion-Selloff-But-BTC-Stays-Strong"/>
        <updated>2023-12-23T01:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Brutally Denied: Doomed to Miss Bull Run?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19128482/XRP-Brutally-Denied-Doomed-to-Miss-Bull-Run</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19128482/XRP-Brutally-Denied-Doomed-to-Miss-Bull-Run"/>
        <updated>2023-12-23T01:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XRP failed yet again, and it is not clear what can save it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Ramps Up For Paxos’ Stablecoin Expansion With NYDFS’s Positive Nod For January 2024]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7483de16a2</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/solana-paxos-stablecoin-expansion-january-2024/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-23T00:38:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a significant development for the stablecoin industry, Paxos, one of the largest stablecoin issuers, has received regulatory approval to extend its product offering to the Solana (SOL) blockchain.
 
The expansion, scheduled to launch on January 17, 2024, follows a directive from the financial regulator ordering Paxos to halt the minting of Binance’s BUSD tokens earlier this year due to “several issues.”
 
New York’s DFS Grants Paxos First Trust Charter
 
Paxos has established itself as the world’s most regulated stablecoin issuer, with a track record of issuing regulated stablecoins at scale. 
 
According to a Fortune Magazine report, the company obtained the first trust charter granted to a crypto firm under the digital asset regulatory framework implemented by the New York Department …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BNB loses its spot to Solana – Here’s why it’s not all bad news]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19128468/BNB-loses-its-spot-to-Solana-Heres-why-its-not-all-bad-news</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19128468/BNB-loses-its-spot-to-Solana-Heres-why-its-not-all-bad-news"/>
        <updated>2023-12-23T00:30:17.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Ramps Up For Paxos’ Stablecoin Expansion With NYDFS’s Positive Nod For January 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19128469/Solana-Ramps-Up-For-Paxos-Stablecoin-Expansion-With-NYDFSs-Positive-Nod-For-January-2024</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19128469/Solana-Ramps-Up-For-Paxos-Stablecoin-Expansion-With-NYDFSs-Positive-Nod-For-January-2024"/>
        <updated>2023-12-23T00:30:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a significant development for the stablecoin industry, Paxos, one of the largest stablecoin issuers, has received regulatory approval to extend its product offering to the Solana (SOL) blockchain. The expansion, scheduled to launch on January 17, 2024, follows a directive from the financial...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Soars, Sparking Speculation: Can the ‘Ethereum Killer’ Live Up to the Hype?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19128453/Solana-Soars-Sparking-Speculation-Can-the-Ethereum-Killer-Live-Up-to-the-Hype</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19128453/Solana-Soars-Sparking-Speculation-Can-the-Ethereum-Killer-Live-Up-to-the-Hype"/>
        <updated>2023-12-23T00:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SOL’s YTD performance is an 809.50% increase after starting the year below $10. Solana’s TVL has been recovering, but Ethereum stays on top of other chains. SOL may hit $100 before the year ends if the accumulation of the token increases. Solana (SOL), one of the top 10 cryptocurrencies in the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk says X payments likely by mid-2024]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19128448/Elon-Musk-says-X-payments-likely-by-mid-2024</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19128448/Elon-Musk-says-X-payments-likely-by-mid-2024"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T23:50:53.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hashdex Names BitGo as Bitcoin ETF Custodian as Applicants Continue SEC Meetings]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7483da982e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/12/22/hashdex-names-bitgo-as-bitcoin-etf-custodian-as-applicants-continue-sec-meetings/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T23:43:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Would-be bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) issuer Hashdex changed its paperwork Friday, naming BitGo as its bitcoin custodian and changing the name of its Bitcoin Futures ETF to the Hashdex Bitcoin ETF as it – and other companies – continue to hope for an approval for the U.S.'s first spot bitcoin ETF early in the new year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2024 Crypto Economy Forecast — Bitfinex Researchers Predict $3.2 Trillion Market Cap Amid Rising Adoption]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7483dac6d1</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/2024-crypto-economy-forecast-bitfinex-researchers-predict-3-2-trillion-market-cap-amid-rising-adoption/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T23:41:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As 2024 approaches, Bitfinex market strategists have expressed optimism for bitcoin and crypto assets in general, acknowledging their resilience amid regulatory and reputational challenges. The crypto market, according to Bitfinex analysts, is oscillating between bouts of greed and regulation and is set to witness an upward trajectory with market capitalization possibly doubling.
 
Bitfinex Analysts Forsee a Bullish Trajectory for Bitcoin and Crypto Assets Amidst Macro Stability
 
The year 2024 is eyed with optimism, with Bitfinex analysts suggesting a potential market cap for the crypto economy increasing up to $3.2 trillion amidst historical pullbacks and market oscillations. The latest Bitfinex Alpha report says a shift towards “extreme greed” in the crypto fear and greed index suggests…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former BitMEX CEO Predicts Ethereum Price Will Surge to $5,000 After Professing Love for ‘Archangel Vitlaik’]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19128414/Former-BitMEX-CEO-Predicts-Ethereum-Price-Will-Surge-to-5000-After-Professing-Love-for-Archangel-Vitlaik</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19128414/Former-BitMEX-CEO-Predicts-Ethereum-Price-Will-Surge-to-5000-After-Professing-Love-for-Archangel-Vitlaik"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T23:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BREAKING: Central Bank of Nigeria (CBN) lifts ban on crypto transactions]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19128408/BREAKING-Central-Bank-of-Nigeria-CBN-lifts-ban-on-crypto-transactions</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19128408/BREAKING-Central-Bank-of-Nigeria-CBN-lifts-ban-on-crypto-transactions"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T23:20:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Central Bank of Nigeria (CBN) has officially rescinded its ban on cryptocurrency transactions, as revealed in a December 22, 2023 circular. Haruna Mustafa, Director of the Financial Policy and Regulation Department, made the announcement, further underscoring Nigeria’s commitment to adapting...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin-Themed DOGE-1 Satellite Launch Draws Closer, Here Are The Coins To Watch]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7483c58c52</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-satellite-coins-to-watch/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T23:07:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Dogecoin-themed satellite, DOGE-1, which was funded using DOGE is getting closer to its launch. According to Geometric Energy Corporation, the company behind the launch, it is scheduled for takeoff on January 12, 2024, from the Kennedy Space Center in conjunction with Elon Musk’s SpaceX. With less than a month left to go for this launch, here are the three tokens to keep an eye on for a potential rally.
 
Dogecoin (DOGE)
 
Naturally, Dogecoin comes first on this list given its direct connection to the launch of the satellite. It first made the headlines in 2021 when the mission was announced, and unlike other rocket launches, this mission was apparently funded entirely using the DOGE token. For this reason, it has become a highly anticipated event, especially among Dogecoin holders who…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Best Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Co-Founder Calls Out ‘Useless in Every Single Way’ SEC Chair Gary Gensler]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19128402/Dogecoin-Co-Founder-Calls-Out-Useless-in-Every-Single-Way-SEC-Chair-Gary-Gensler</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19128402/Dogecoin-Co-Founder-Calls-Out-Useless-in-Every-Single-Way-SEC-Chair-Gary-Gensler"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T23:01:39.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Might Be the Last Hurdle for Bitcoin ETF Approval]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210777</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210777/last-hurdle-for-bitcoin-etf-approval"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T22:41:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the days tick down to the SEC's next Bitcoin ETF deadline, there's one last hurdle to clear: Getting clear on authorized participants.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Founder Vitalik Buterin Sells Trillions Of Tokens]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7483c3329b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-vitalik-buterin-tokens/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T22:04:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum founder, Vitalik Buterin has undertaken a large-scale transaction involving trillions of meme tokens, leaving the broader cryptocurrency space curious about the motives behind the founder’s decision. 
 
Ethereum Founder Executes Massive Memecoin Sales
 
Ethereum inventor and founder, Vitalik Buterin has made new headlines as reports surface of his substantial memecoin sales. According to blockchain security company, PeckShield Alerts, a Vitalik labeled wallet address was seen swapping 100,000,000,000,111.111 DOBE tokens worth approximately $22,900 for 10.44 Ethereum tokens (ETH). Additionally, the wallet also initiated another sale of 1,858,140,000,000 DOJO tokens worth $6800 for 3.12 ETH.
 
 
The motivation behind the sell-offs remains unknown however the large-scale memecoin tra…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bloxroute to Reject Blocks With OFAC Flagged Transactions]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7483c34fa3</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bloxroute-to-reject-blocks-with-ofac-flagged-transactions/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T22:03:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bloxroute, a company that provides relaying services, has declared that it will start rejecting block bids with transactions from wallets part of the Office of Foreign Assets Control (OFAC) Specially Designated Nationals And Blocked Persons List (SDN List). Based in the U.S., the company clarified it is still committed to supporting Ethereum’s decentralized nature.
Bloxroute to Comply With OFAC SDN List Designation
Bloxroute, a company that provides relaying services for Ethereum and other networks, has reported that it will start rejecting block bids with transactions coming from wallets part of the Office of Foreign Assets Control (OFAC) Specially Designated Nationals And Blocked Persons List (SDN List).
Based in the U.S., Bloxroute stated it will still support Ethereum’s decentralized a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wildcard's Plans for 2024 with Founders Paul and Katy Bettner]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/TI3aFBhO/wildcards-plans-for-2024-with-founders-paul-and-katy-bettner</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/TI3aFBhO/wildcards-plans-for-2024-with-founders-paul-and-katy-bettner"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T21:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wildcard developers Paul and Katy Bettner tell Decrypt's Kate Irwin about why they see their game as a "Web3 game," not a crypto game, and share why they've stuck with their initial vision despite the challenging broader market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Korean Game Publisher Wemade Launches $100 Million Blockchain Investment Fund]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210764</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210764/south-korean-game-publisher-wemade-launches-100-million-blockchain-investment-fund"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T21:17:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[South Korea's strict anti-blockchain gaming rules have led game studios like Wemade to develop for markets abroad.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Real World Asset Trends in 2024 That Will Unlock the Future of Finance]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7483c8a94d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/12/22/7-real-world-asset-trends-in-2024-that-will-unlock-the-future-of-finance/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T21:08:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoins, tokenized treasuries, decentralized private credit, physical-backed NFTs, DeFi in climate and regenerative finance – these are just some of the trends set to remake capital markets in the coming year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sanjay Raghavan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Unified Future of AI, Blockchain and Virtual Worlds in 2024]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7483ca08aa</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/12/22/the-unified-future-of-ai-blockchain-and-virtual-worlds-in-2024/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T20:54:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Convergence is more than just a blending of technologies: It is a harmonization that enhances, expands, and redefines our experience of the digital world, says the co-founder of Decentraland Foundation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yemel  Jardi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nexo's Money Laundering Investigation in Bulgaria Closed Due to Lack of Evidence: Report]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7483cada9f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/12/22/nexos-money-laundering-investigation-in-bulgaria-closed-due-to-lack-of-evidence-report/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T20:46:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bulgarian Prosecutor's Office reported to have said that it found “no evidence of criminal activity,” adding that “no evidence of tax offenses or computer fraud was found against the defendants, either.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paxos Expands to Solana Following NYDFS Nod, Widening Stablecoin’s Horizon]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7483b41434</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/paxos-expands-to-solana-following-nydfs-nod-widening-stablecoins-horizon/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T20:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The tokenization and stablecoin platform Paxos has revealed plans to broaden its stablecoin issuance to the Solana blockchain. The company, which oversees the pax dollar (USDP), anticipates that Solana-issued USDP will be publicly available starting Jan. 17, 2024.
 
Paxos Set to Launch Stablecoin on Solana, Expanding USDP Reach in Crypto Market
 

 
On Friday, Paxos revealed that its Solana venture represents the first expansion to a new blockchain, as USDP was initially launched on Ethereum. The New York Department of Financial Services (NYDFS) reportedly endorsed Paxos’ initiative, enabling public access to USDP via Solana by mid-January 2024.
 

 
“The expansion of our stablecoin platform to support Solana marks an important step towards making stablecoins ubiquitous for everyday consum…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong Opens Doors For Spot Crypto ETFs Applications Amid US SEC Anticipated Approval]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7483b41e3c</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/hong-kong-opens-doors-spot-crypto-etfs-applications/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T20:33:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong has announced its readiness to accept applications for spot crypto exchange-traded funds (ETFs). The Securities and Futures Commission (SFC), Hong Kong’s financial watchdog, alongside the Hong Kong Monetary Authority, the city’s central banking institution, jointly published circulars today, laying the groundwork for this significant shift in the crypto landscape.
 
The move marks a decisive step in Hong Kong’s efforts to position itself as a leading hub for digital asset innovation and regulation. The SFC’s readiness to consider applications for spot crypto ETFs signals a progressive approach to embracing the growing interest in digital assets.
 
The regulator has specified that these ETFs should primarily focus on investments directly in spot virtual asset tokens available to t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is it Really ‘Up Only’ for Bitcoin?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7483b6664c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/12/22/is-it-really-up-only-for-bitcoin/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T20:11:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With spot Bitcoin ETFs set to be approved, and a halving on the way in April, everyone expects bitcoin to rise in 2024. But history suggests that might not be the case, says Frank Corva.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Frank  Corva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How NFTs Will Make a Comeback in 2024]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7483b758f7</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/12/22/how-nfts-will-make-a-comeback-in-2024/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T20:01:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NFTs are poised to be a major driver of Web3 adoption in 2024 – but the successful projects will look very different from what’s come before.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott  Kominers, Steve Kaczynski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Argentina’s President Javier Milei Issues Major Deregulation Measures via Executive Order]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7483bd425f</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/argentinas-president-javier-milei-issues-major-deregulation-measures-via-executive-order/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T19:06:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Javier Milei, president of Argentina, has issued an emergency executive order repealing a series of laws to prepare the state for upcoming privatization and modernization moves. The executive order, which has 366 articles, touches on major aspects of Argentine life, including rents, job regulation and land regulation. It also converts all state companies into limited companies.
Argentine President Javier Milei Launches Massive Deregulation Measures
President Javier Milei has launched the first batch of measures focusing on reducing the footprint and reach of the state in Argentina, as he promised during his campaign. On December 21, Milei issued a national emergency executive order that modifies — and eliminates — some of the most relevant laws that regulate work, rent, product pricing, an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Founder Slams SEC Boss Over Crypto Regulation Comments]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7483bddc15</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-founder-sec-boss/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T19:01:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Chairman Gary Gensler has been getting a lot of backlash from the crypto industry and the latest comes from Dogecoin founder Billy Markus. The backlash has persisted over the years in relation to regulations to help govern the crypto industry, something that the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has failed to provide to stakeholders in the industry.
 
The Gensler Interview On Regulation
 
Gary Gensler appeared on CNBC in an interview where he talked about compliance when it comes to investing. More specifically, the interview focused on laws that govern the crypto space and how the agency is working to regulate it.
 
 
In a clip of the interview shared by the SEC chairman on X (formerly Twitter), Gensler talks about how non-compliance is rampant in the crypto space…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Cancels Saga Orders After Selling Phones It Didn't Have]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210739</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210739/solana-cancels-saga-orders-after-selling-phones-didnt-have"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T18:46:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Labs apologized for overselling the Saga, which saw surging demand after customers realized the incentives outvalued the phone itself.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Insomniac Games Breaks Silence on 'Extremely Distressing' Bitcoin Ransom Hack]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210735</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210735/insomniac-games-breaks-silence-extremely-distressing-bitcoin-ransom-hack"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T18:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sony PlayStation studio Insomniac Games has finally responded to the devastating Bitcoin ransom attack that leaked game and employee data.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2024: The Revenge of Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7483b9d066</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/12/22/2024-the-revenge-of-bitcoin/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T18:27:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETFs can drive adoption, but the world's first cryptocurrency must continue to evolve as a technology, Thesis CEO Matt Luongo writes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Luongo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Pops 4% as Solana Nips at Its Heels]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210699</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210699/ethereum-pops-4-as-solana-nips-at-its-heels"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T18:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The second-largest cryptocurrency by market cap is up today as developers prepare for the DenCun testnet rollout in January.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Is Giving Away Free Gaming NFTs—Here's How to Claim]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151872</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151872/amazon-giving-away-free-gaming-nfts-how-claim"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T16:59:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATE: Blockchain games like Gods Unchained, Brawlers, Champions Ascension, and Mojo Melee are giving out free stuff via Amazon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Satoshi, Not Satoshi: Craig Wright UK Case Inches Further Forward]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210675</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210675/satoshi-not-satoshi-craig-wright-uk-case-inches-further-forward"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T12:23:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The trial was scheduled to begin on January 15, 2024, but the ruling has pushed the start date back at least a year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Ordinals Critic Caves as Jack Dorsey-Backed Ocean Mining Pool Flips on Inscriptions]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210662</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210662/bitcoin-ordinals-critic-caves-jack-dorsey-backed-ocean-mining-pool-flips-inscriptions"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T23:18:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin developer Luke Dashjr fought the rise of Ordinals, which he called "spam," but now his mining pool is allowing them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Got a Solana Saga Before They Sold Out? Here Are All the Airdrops You Can Claim]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210634</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210634/solana-saga-airdrops-tokens-nfts-you-can-claim"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T19:48:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond BONK: Solana Saga owners can now claim multiple token airdrops and other perks, with more in the works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New MidJourney V6 Release Upgrades Visuals and Tackles Text Generation (Mostly)]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210637</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210637/midjourney-v6-base-model-upgrade-text-generation"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T18:51:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new model promises better enhancers, upscalers, prompt following, and text generation capabilities. Stricter censorship, too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3AC Liquidators Freeze $1.4 Billion From Founders]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210622</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210622/3ac-liquidators-freeze-1-4-billion-from-founders"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T17:57:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The freeze stops 3AC co-founders Su Zhu and Kyle Davies, along with Davies’ wife, Kelly Chen, from accessing the funds in question.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt and Rug Radio Merge to Create Global Web3 Publishing Company]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/VTEBYFD8/decrypt-and-rug-radio-merge-to-create-global-web3-publishing-company</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/VTEBYFD8/decrypt-and-rug-radio-merge-to-create-global-web3-publishing-company"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T17:04:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt and Rug Radio have announced their intent to merge, creating the world’s biggest decentralized publishing company. Codenamed [REDACTED], the alliance is aimed at revolutionizing tech-media, bringing together the forces of content creation and consumption.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meme Coin Mania Helps Push Solana DeFi Volume Over Ethereum for First Time]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210597</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210597/meme-coin-mania-helps-push-solana-dex-volume-over-ethereum-first-time"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T16:55:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Frenzied trading on meme coins like BONK and Dogwifhat have helped push activity on Solana’s decentralized exchanges to the top]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Up 12% and Dogwifhat Surges as Bitcoin Dips Under $44K]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210589</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210589/solana-up-11-dogwifhat-surges-bitcoin-dips-under-44k"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T16:32:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin and Ethereum are mostly flat today but, Solana (SOL) and tokens that run on its network continue to rise in price.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Animoca Brands CEO: Open Metaverse will Enable DeFi-Style 'Vampiric Attacks' By Web3 Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210566</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210566/animoca-brands-ceo-open-metaverse-defi-vampiric-attacks-games"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T15:57:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Interoperablility between in-game NFTs would enable new titles to create a user acquisition funnel from established games, said Robby Yung.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MoonPay Launches Streamlined Checkout Tool for Buying NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210515</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210515/moonpay-launches-enhanced-checkout-tool-buying-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The MoonPay Checkout widget enables quick and easy NFT buying with credit and debit cards, along with multi-mint support and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Claude AI Creator Anthropic to Raise $750 Million in New Funding: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210507</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210507/claude-ai-creator-anthropic-to-raise-750-million-in-new-funding-report"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T03:01:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The $18.4 billion pre-funding round valuation comes as a fundraising push targets a $750 million raise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Every Game on Ethereum Scaler Immutable in the Epic Games Store]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208341</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208341/all-games-ethereum-scaler-immutable-epic-games-store"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T23:17:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATE: Gods Unchained is back in action after being relisted. Here are the Immutable games that you'll find on the Epic Games Store.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emerge 2023 Company of the Year: Nvidia]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210448</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210448/emerge-company-of-the-year-nvidia"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T22:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From gaming to crypto to the bleeding edge of AI, the chipmaker’s Grace Hopper hardware line will power the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saga Blockchain Launches ‘Play-to-Airdrop’ Game Tournaments—Here's How to Earn]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210472</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210472/saga-blockchain-launches-play-airdrop-game-tournaments-heres-how-earn"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T22:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Saga Protocol airdrop is coming. Players can earn a share of SAGA tokens by performing well in crypto game competitions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cathie Wood’s ARK Dumps $245M in Coinbase, Grayscale Bitcoin Trust Shares in Last 30 Days]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210462</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210462/cathie-woods-ark-245m-coinbase-grayscale-bitcoin-30-days"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T21:31:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The profit-taking will continue until prices stop improving—probably.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Training Data Included Child Sexual Abuse Material, Say Stanford Researchers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210461</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210461/stability-ai-stable-diffusion-laion-csam"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T21:25:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Illegal and inappropriate images are so pervasive, one researcher says, some tools depict nude women and children by default.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Phantom Wallet Adoption Shows Bitcoin Is No Longer 'Stagnant Uncle of Crypto']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210432</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210432/bitcoin-support-added-phantom-wallet-alongside-solana-and-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T20:21:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Taproot Wizards founder and Crypto Twitter staple Udi Wertheimer says Phantom adding Bitcoin validates the ecosystem's vast expansion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Art of Confusion: Humans Prefer ‘Real’ Art to AI Art, But Struggle to Tell the Difference]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210437</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210437/human-reference-people-art-over-ai-creations-study"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T20:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“While people may perceive human- and machine-generated art in the same way, the way they feel about the art is different,” a recent study concluded.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Immutable Hits 20-Month High as Gaming Tokens Outpace Bitcoin Gains]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210425</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210425/immutable-hits-20-month-high-gaming-tokens-outpace-bitcoin-gains"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T19:11:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gaming tokens are rising again, with Immutable's IMX token as well as The Sandbox (SAND), Gala Games (GALA), and Ronin (RON) all gaining.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3War is Shaking up Crypto Gaming With ‘Skill-to-Earn’ Rewards]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209957</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209957/web3war-is-shaking-up-crypto-gaming-with-skill-to-earn-rewards"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T18:11:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first-person shooter is taking aim at play-to-earn titles that “burn time” with a model that rewards the best players.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Flips XRP as SOL Hits Another Yearly High]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210409</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210409/solana-flips-xrp-sol-hits-another-yearly-high"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T17:07:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana (SOL) is outpacing gains by Bitcoin and Ethereum, surging above $80 on Wednesday as its recent hot streak continues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Breaks Above $44K as Market Braces for Potential ETF]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210400</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210400/bitcoin-breaks-above-44k-market-braces-potential-etf"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T16:04:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin continues to rise in price and on Wednesday morning popped above $44,000—bringing the rest of the crypto market with it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ledger to Disable Blind Signing on Dapps by June 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210393</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210393/ledger-to-disable-blind-signing-on-dapps-by-june-2024"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T13:59:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The hardware wallet manufacturer stated it would reimburse victims of last week's exploit involving a malicious version of its Connect Kit library.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Art Banned from Magic: The Gathering After Controversial Ads]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210358</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210358/magic-the-gathering-ai-art-wizards-of-the-coast"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T12:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wizards of the Coast said artists are now barred from using generative AI to create artwork and content for its massively popular role-playing game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock, Nasdaq Meet SEC Again to Discuss Spot Bitcoin ETF]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210385</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210385/blackrock-nasdaq-meet-sec-again-to-discuss-spot-bitcoin-etf"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T11:57:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock's Head of Digital Assets met with the SEC's Division of Trading and Markets Tuesday to discuss its propsed spot Bitcoin ETF.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Gods Unchained' Returns to Epic Games Store After Play-to-Earn Policy Change]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210340</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210340/gods-unchained-returns-epic-games-store-after-play-earn-policy-change"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T22:48:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Epic Games Store will now allow some Adults Only-rated crypto games like Gods Unchained, after the ESRB gave it a restrictive rating over play-to-earn elements.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Halving Has Miners Prepping as Marathon Aims to Beef Up Rigs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210321</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210321/bitcoin-halving-miners-prepping-marathon"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T22:35:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marathon plans to spend $179 million to buy two more Bitcoin mining sites in Texas and Nebraska.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Portal Airdrop Set for January as Gaming Token Nears Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210341</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210341/portal-airdrop-set-january-gaming-token-nears-launch"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T22:24:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Multi-chain gaming token Portal is nearly set to launch its airdrop following last week’s presale and news of WME representing the project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Immutable Debuts Passport Gaming Wallet in 'Gods Unchained' and More]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210334</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210334/immutable-debuts-passport-gaming-wallet-gods-unchained-more"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T22:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a beta launch, the simplified Immutable Passport wallet and universal profile is now live across multiple games and marketplaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Did You Trade Ethereum NFTs in the Last Two Years? You Can Claim This Airdrop]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210322</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210322/did-you-trade-ethereum-nfts-last-two-years-claim-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T20:30:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Frame, a new layer-2 Ethereum scaling network for NFTs, launched a token airdrop on Tuesday. Here's how to claim it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Leak Insomniac's 'X-Men' Game After Bitcoin Ransom Demand]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210303</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210303/hackers-leak-insomniac-xmen-game-after-bitcoin-ransom-demand"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T18:34:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Insomniac Games attackers have released over 1.3 million documents that reveal Sony and Marvel contracts, game details, and personal data.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Team Seeks to Launch SHIB Domains for Websites and Email]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210301</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210301/shiba-inu-team-seeks-launch-shib-domains-websites-ema"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T18:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SHIB team is partnering with domain company D3 to lobby for approval of the first-ever crypto top-level-domain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terra Founder Do Kwon Avoids Extradition to US—For Now]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210277</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210277/terra-do-kwon-extradition-montenegro"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T16:54:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Terra founder was set to be extradited to the U.S. but an appeal means he will for the time being stay in Montenegro.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BONK Goes Bust? Solana Meme Coin Plunges 44% After Setting All-Time High]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210270</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210270/bonk-goes-bust-solana-meme-coin-plunges-44-after-setting-all-time-high"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T16:36:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What went up last week has come crashing down—but Solana’s BONK is still up 500% this month despite the losses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock Makes Key Changes to Bitcoin ETF Ahead of Expected Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210278</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210278/blackrock-makes-key-changes-to-bitcoin-etf-ahead-of-expected-launch"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T16:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a new SEC filing, BlackRock said its iShares Bitcoin Trust would only allow cash—not in-kind—creation and changed its ticker to IBIT.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['If You Play Well, You're Gonna be Rewarded': How FPS Web3War is Bringing 'Skill-to-Earn' to Crypto Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Jl5AEFuD/if-you-play-well-youre-gonna-be-rewarded-how-fps-web3war-is-bringing-skill-to-earn-to-crypto-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Jl5AEFuD/if-you-play-well-youre-gonna-be-rewarded-how-fps-web3war-is-bringing-skill-to-earn-to-crypto-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T10:20:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roll1ng Thund3rz co-founder Valentin Cobelea and Zilliqa CEO Matt Dyer joined Decrypt to discuss how the new FPS game Web3War is shaking up the crypto gaming space with a novel "skill to earn" mechanic that rewards players for high-quality gameplay.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating peaceful money & taking over your local government w/ Joseph Schiarizzi]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zb0VG27G/creating-peaceful-money-taking-over-your-local-government-w-joseph-schiarizzi</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zb0VG27G/creating-peaceful-money-taking-over-your-local-government-w-joseph-schiarizzi"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T23:23:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week our host Reza Jafery is joined by Joseph Schiarizzi, founder of OpenDollar and prolific solidity developer. 


We discuss: 
- Onchain beer
- Taking over your local government
- His Emmy and 3 patents?!?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INTERVIEW: Ember Sword CEO Says NFT Games Are More 'Transparent']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/M9OHCVpA/interview-ember-sword-ceo-says-nft-games-are-more-transparent</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/M9OHCVpA/interview-ember-sword-ceo-says-nft-games-are-more-transparent"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T21:58:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ember Sword CEO Mark Laursen shares why some big game studios "irk" him—and why he got into game development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Director Jordan Bayne on the State of Film3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZLoEDkL9/director-jordan-bayne-on-the-state-of-film3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZLoEDkL9/director-jordan-bayne-on-the-state-of-film3"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T00:11:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the 2023 Film3 Summit, Jordan Bayne—director and founder of The Squad—spoke with Decrypt's Sander Lutz about how the Film3 world has progressed over the last year and what decentralized technologies can offer to creators that want to buck the Hollywood system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Questions With SCENE: Phil Mohun]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TwOjXfOR/5-questions-with-scene-phil-mohun</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TwOjXfOR/5-questions-with-scene-phil-mohun"/>
        <updated>2023-12-01T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bright Moments co-founder Phil Mohun joins 5 Questions With SCENE to recount some favorite moments from the road, including negotiating with Patagonian gauchos, falling in love with Tokyo, and gaining a newfound appreciation for shrooms chocolate bars.

Shot and edited by Vincent Roazzi Jr.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are NFTs Ever Coming Back?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qLmFpNKE/are-nfts-ever-coming-back</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qLmFpNKE/are-nfts-ever-coming-back"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T18:38:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this weeks episode we sit down with Cashtro from Arcade.xyz to discuss NFTs, shitcoins, what collections have held onto their floor prices, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Summit: Will Web3 Gaming Ever be Mainstream?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OvVWhGbW/web-summit-will-web3-gaming-ever-be-mainstream</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OvVWhGbW/web-summit-will-web3-gaming-ever-be-mainstream"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T19:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animoca Brands CEO Robby Yung, EndeavorXR CEO Amy Peck and Gamee co-founder CEO Bozena Rezab joined Decrypt's Stephen Graves on stage at Web Summit to talk about the future of Web3 gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>