<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-12-20T06:16:22.784Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-12-20T06:16:22.784Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Ban Bill Exposed: Bankers’ Involvement Confession Surfaces]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748df2cceb</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bankers-collaborated-on-warrens-bitcoin-ban-bill/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T06:06:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Through 2023, Bitcoin and the crypto industry have faced increasing scrutiny from US Senator Elizabeth Warren, who has expressed concerns about the potential misuse of cryptocurrencies for illicit activities.
 
Now, the senator has highlighted the involvement of former military personnel, civilian government officials, and lawmakers in crypto organizations as a particular area of concern. 
 
However, advocates for the crypto industry argue that these individuals play a vital role in strengthening national security and fostering innovation.
 
Furthermore, the recent admission by a co-sponsor of Elizabeth Warren’s proposed “Bitcoin Ban Bill” or the Digital Asset Anti-Money Laundering Act has sparked further controversy. 
 
Bankers’ Involvement In “Bitcoin Ban Bill” 
 
The co-sponsor, US Sena…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Ban Bill Exposed: Bankers’ Involvement Confession Surfaces]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19121158/Bitcoin-Ban-Bill-Exposed-Bankers-Involvement-Confession-Surfaces</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19121158/Bitcoin-Ban-Bill-Exposed-Bankers-Involvement-Confession-Surfaces"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T06:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Through 2023, Bitcoin and the crypto industry have faced increasing scrutiny from US Senator Elizabeth Warren, who has expressed concerns about the potential misuse of cryptocurrencies for illicit activities. Now, the senator has highlighted the involvement of former military personnel, civilian...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Much Can AI Really Change? Examining Operational Impact]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19121146/How-Much-Can-AI-Really-Change-Examining-Operational-Impact</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19121146/How-Much-Can-AI-Really-Change-Examining-Operational-Impact"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T05:55:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the ever-evolving landscape of technological advancements, Artificial Intelligence (AI) has emerged as a transformative force, promising operational enhancements and unparalleled capabilities. Yet, amidst the excitement and buzz surrounding the “New Age of AI,” it becomes imperative to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock, Nasdaq, SEC Met Regarding Bitcoin ETF]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19121143/BlackRock-Nasdaq-SEC-Met-Regarding-Bitcoin-ETF</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19121143/BlackRock-Nasdaq-SEC-Met-Regarding-Bitcoin-ETF"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T05:40:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the second meeting in a month between the parties about rule changes required to list the bitcoin ETF.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI’s Role in Shaping Safer and More Sustainable Transportation]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19121124/AIs-Role-in-Shaping-Safer-and-More-Sustainable-Transportation</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19121124/AIs-Role-in-Shaping-Safer-and-More-Sustainable-Transportation"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T05:16:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence (AI) is revolutionizing the transportation sector, potentially significantly enhancing safety, sustainability, and equity. A recent report, “The Impact of AI on Transportation and Mobility,” prepared by ITS America in collaboration with Cambridge Consultants, sheds light...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Revolut Launches Crypto Trading in New Zealand with over 100 Pairs]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748df81d68</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/revolut-launches-crypto-trading-in-new-zealand-with-over-100-pairs/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T05:15:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Only a couple of days after the reports of Revolut limiting its crypto services in the United Kingdom surfaced, the fintech launched cryptocurrency trading services in New Zealand. The services will be available to customers in the country starting today (Wednesday).
Additional Services for the Crypt Customers
According to the official press release, the London-headquartered fintech has supplemented its service in the country with the ‘Learn and Earn’ program, offering free courses for crypto traders. Further, it has partnered with and integrated Koinly to ease the crypto tax filing for New Zealanders.
“Revolut is excited to edge closer to our goal of simplifying the money experience for Kiwis by expanding into new verticals like education and trading,” said Georgia Grange, Revolut’s Head …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arnab Shome</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miner Marathon Acquires 2 High-Capacity Mining Facilities for $178.6M]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748df8de51</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-miner-marathon-acquires-2-high-capacity-mining-facilities-for-178-6m/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T05:08:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Tuesday, Marathon Digital Holdings, a leading bitcoin mining company listed on public markets, revealed its acquisition of two fully operational bitcoin mining facilities, representing a combined capacity of 390 megawatts (MW). For these facilities, Marathon invested a total of $178.6 million in cash, averaging $458,000 per MW.
 
Marathon Boosts Mining Capacity Ahead of Bitcoin Halving
 
Marathon‘s (Nasdaq: MARA) strategic expansion includes the acquisition of two bitcoin mining locations in Texas and Nebraska, previously owned by Generate Capital subsidiaries. This move marks Marathon’s transition from an “asset-light organization” to one possessing a substantial portfolio of mining operations. The acquired sites provide a substantial 390 MW of power, with the purchase amounting to $17…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Outperforms Ethereum In Key Metrics, But Running Nodes Proving To Be Expensive]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748df92643</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/solana-outperforms-ethereum-running-nodes-expensive/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T05:05:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recent analysis by Ryan Watkins, co-founder of Syncracy Capital, highlights Solana’s growing momentum in several key metrics that Ethereum once dominated. However, Watkins notes that running Solana nodes is more expensive amid this revelation.
 
Solana Is Rallying; Key Metrics Swell
 
 In a post on X, Watkins noted that Solana has surpassed Ethereum regarding decentralized exchange (DEX) and non-fungible token (NFT) volumes, active addresses, transaction count, and stablecoin transfers.
 
This rapid shift in Solana’s metrics is when the network has been the center of attention among developers and traders. Over the past few trading months, SOL prices have been on a tear, racing past immediate resistance levels and registering new 2023 highs.
 
 
The spike in SOL prices also seems to have…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dalmas Ngetich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Outperforms Ethereum In Key Metrics, But Running Nodes Proving To Be Expensive]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19121104/Solana-Outperforms-Ethereum-In-Key-Metrics-But-Running-Nodes-Proving-To-Be-Expensive</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19121104/Solana-Outperforms-Ethereum-In-Key-Metrics-But-Running-Nodes-Proving-To-Be-Expensive"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T05:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recent analysis by Ryan Watkins, co-founder of Syncracy Capital, highlights Solana’s growing momentum in several key metrics that Ethereum once dominated. However, Watkins notes that running Solana nodes is more expensive amid this revelation. Solana Is Rallying; Key Metrics Swell In a post on...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Silicon Valley’s Ideological Clash: Effective Altruists vs. Effective Accelerationists]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19121088/Silicon-Valleys-Ideological-Clash-Effective-Altruists-vs-Effective-Accelerationists</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19121088/Silicon-Valleys-Ideological-Clash-Effective-Altruists-vs-Effective-Accelerationists"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T04:59:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recent corporate drama at OpenAI has thrust the organization into the spotlight and exposed a deep ideological clash within Silicon Valley. In a swift and surprising turn of events, the company’s CEO, Sam Altman, was ousted from his position, only to be reinstated shortly after that. The...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Galaxy Digital CEO Calls Elizabeth Warren A 'Disingenuous Know-It-All' Amid Anti-Crypto Bill]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19121159/Galaxy-Digital-CEO-Calls-Elizabeth-Warren-A-Disingenuous-Know-It-All-Amid-Anti-Crypto-Bill</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19121159/Galaxy-Digital-CEO-Calls-Elizabeth-Warren-A-Disingenuous-Know-It-All-Amid-Anti-Crypto-Bill"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T04:58:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Goldman Sachs partner and CEO of Galaxy Digital, Mike Novogratz, called out Senator Elizabeth Warren (D.Mass.) as a ‘disingenuous know-it-all.' read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Experts at Oak Ridge National Laboratory Tackle Growing Threat of Cyber Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19121083/AI-Experts-at-Oak-Ridge-National-Laboratory-Tackle-Growing-Threat-of-Cyber-Attacks</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19121083/AI-Experts-at-Oak-Ridge-National-Laboratory-Tackle-Growing-Threat-of-Cyber-Attacks"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T04:41:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The threat of cyber attacks and ransomware is growing alarmingly in today’s digital age. The relentless onslaught of malicious actors targeting individuals, businesses, and organizations is a grave concern. To counter this ever-evolving menace, a team of artificial intelligence (AI) experts at...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[As Bitcoin Flirts With $43K, Dormant BTC Stash Worth $88M Comes To Life After Nearly A Decade]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19121087/As-Bitcoin-Flirts-With-43K-Dormant-BTC-Stash-Worth-88M-Comes-To-Life-After-Nearly-A-Decade</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19121087/As-Bitcoin-Flirts-With-43K-Dormant-BTC-Stash-Worth-88M-Comes-To-Life-After-Nearly-A-Decade"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T04:40:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An enormous stock of dormant Bitcoins (CRYPTO: BTC), untouched for nearly nine years, sprang to life on Tuesday when a whale transferred more than 2,101 Bitcoins valued at $88.55 million. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cathie Wood's Ark Invest Unloads Coinbase And Robinhood Shares Amid Crypto Volatility]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19121082/Cathie-Woods-Ark-Invest-Unloads-Coinbase-And-Robinhood-Shares-Amid-Crypto-Volatility</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19121082/Cathie-Woods-Ark-Invest-Unloads-Coinbase-And-Robinhood-Shares-Amid-Crypto-Volatility"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T04:33:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Tuesday, Cathie Wood-led Ark Invest made significant moves in the stock market, notably selling shares of Coinbase Global Inc (NASDAQ:COIN) amidst a turbulent cryptocurrency market. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoins yet to recover despite market rebound – Why?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19121064/Stablecoins-yet-to-recover-despite-market-rebound-Why</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19121064/Stablecoins-yet-to-recover-despite-market-rebound-Why"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T04:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Chainlink’s Big 2024 Real-World Assets Push Move LINK Prices?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19121137/Will-Chainlinks-Big-2024-Real-World-Assets-Push-Move-LINK-Prices</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19121137/Will-Chainlinks-Big-2024-Real-World-Assets-Push-Move-LINK-Prices"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T04:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Saylor Stays Bullish On MicroStrategy's Bitcoin Stance Amid Potential ETF Approvals]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19121066/Michael-Saylor-Stays-Bullish-On-MicroStrategys-Bitcoin-Stance-Amid-Potential-ETF-Approvals</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19121066/Michael-Saylor-Stays-Bullish-On-MicroStrategys-Bitcoin-Stance-Amid-Potential-ETF-Approvals"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T04:09:44.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Digital Markets Secure Global Settlement: Positive Outcome For Customers?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748de6934a</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ftx-digital-markets-secure-global-settlement/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T04:08:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a significant development, FTX Debtors and FTX Digital Markets have announced a global settlement agreement with the Joint Official Liquidators (JOLs) representing FTX Digital Markets. 
 
The settlement, subject to court approvals, addresses the complex legal challenges arising from the collapse of the FTX group and proposes a mutually beneficial solution.
 
Consensual Resolution Achieved
 
The Global Settlement Agreement contains several key provisions to ensure a consensual resolution, according to a recent joint press release:
 
Firstly, the debtors and FTX Digital Markets will pool their assets, enabling substantially identical relative distributions for FTX.com customers in both proceedings. This coordinated approach aims to prioritize the interests of the company’s customers and d…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Digital Markets Secure Global Settlement: Positive Outcome For Customers?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19121046/FTX-Digital-Markets-Secure-Global-Settlement-Positive-Outcome-For-Customers</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19121046/FTX-Digital-Markets-Secure-Global-Settlement-Positive-Outcome-For-Customers"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T04:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a significant development, FTX Debtors and FTX Digital Markets have announced a global settlement agreement with the Joint Official Liquidators (JOLs) representing FTX Digital Markets.  The settlement, subject to court approvals, addresses the complex legal challenges arising from the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meme Coin FRENZY - CRAZY money to be made? (or DUMP coming)]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19121008/Meme-Coin-FRENZY-CRAZY-money-to-be-made-or-DUMP-coming</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19121008/Meme-Coin-FRENZY-CRAZY-money-to-be-made-or-DUMP-coming"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T03:50:58.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Copilot – Transform Your Ideas into AI-Generated Songs]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19121037/Microsoft-Copilot-Transform-Your-Ideas-into-AI-Generated-Songs</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19121037/Microsoft-Copilot-Transform-Your-Ideas-into-AI-Generated-Songs"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T03:44:51.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zooko Wilcox Ends Eight-Year Association With Company Behind Privacy Coin Zcash]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748de1570a</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/zooko-wilcox-ends-eight-year-association-with-company-behind-privacy-coin-zcash/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T03:38:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zooko Wilcox, the CEO of Electric Coin Co., revealed on Dec. 18 that he is ending his eight-year association with the entity which is behind the privacy coin zcash. Despite leaving his role as the company’s top executive, Wilcox said he remains committed to anything focused on human freedom.
 
Wilcox’s Continued Reign Not Good for Himself or Zcash
 
On Dec. 18, Zooko Wilcox, the CEO of the Electric Coin Co. — the entity behind the privacy-focused crypto asset zcash — announced his resignation and revealed that Josh Swihart is set to become the new public face of the privacy coin. While he admitted to butting heads with Swihart in the past, Wilcox nonetheless expressed confidence in his successor’s ability to steer the Electric Coin Co forward.
 
In a statement explaining his decision to le…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Senator Warren Challenges Ex-Gov Officials in Crypto Advocacy Roles]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19121065/Senator-Warren-Challenges-Ex-Gov-Officials-in-Crypto-Advocacy-Roles</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19121065/Senator-Warren-Challenges-Ex-Gov-Officials-in-Crypto-Advocacy-Roles"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T03:29:19.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Social Media Flooded with AI-Generated Images and How to Detect Them]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19121014/Social-Media-Flooded-with-AI-Generated-Images-and-How-to-Detect-Them</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19121014/Social-Media-Flooded-with-AI-Generated-Images-and-How-to-Detect-Them"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T03:23:32.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Rejects $43.5K, Why BTC Could Tumble In Short-Term]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19121010/Bitcoin-Price-Rejects-435K-Why-BTC-Could-Tumble-In-Short-Term</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19121010/Bitcoin-Price-Rejects-435K-Why-BTC-Could-Tumble-In-Short-Term"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T03:13:19.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum, Dogecoin Drop Amid $116M Liquidations: Analyst Says King Crypto To Surge Over 30% In Two Days After This Catalyst Is Triggered]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19121013/Bitcoin-Ethereum-Dogecoin-Drop-Amid-116M-Liquidations-Analyst-Says-King-Crypto-To-Surge-Over-30-In-Two-Days-After-This-Catalyst-Is-Triggered</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19121013/Bitcoin-Ethereum-Dogecoin-Drop-Amid-116M-Liquidations-Analyst-Says-King-Crypto-To-Surge-Over-30-In-Two-Days-After-This-Catalyst-Is-Triggered"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T03:09:12.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock’s Bold Move: Transforming Spot Bitcoin ETF With Cash Redemption Twist – Approval Looms?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748dec5e24</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/blackrock-turn-spot-bitcoin-etf-cash-redemption/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T03:06:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock, a global leader in investment management, has revised its proposed spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) to allow cash redemptions. This update could be a strategic move in gaining approval from the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).
 
The updated filing for the iShares Bitcoin Trust ETF indicates that the Trust will issue and “redeem baskets” in exchange for cash. This flexibility, subject to regulatory approval, could also extend to Bitcoin exchanges in the future.
 
 
Cash Redemptions To Set New Course For Spot Bitcoin ETF
 
Eric Balchunas, a respected Bloomberg analyst, highlighted the importance of this update on the X platform, terming it a “wrap.” This move signifies BlackRock’s commitment to aligning its offering with regulatory expectations, potentially pavi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Industry Funnels $78 Million Into War Chest to Elect Pro-Crypto Candidates in 2024 Elections]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748de9b7d3</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/crypto-industry-funnels-78-million-into-war-chest-to-elect-pro-crypto-candidates-in-2024-elections/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T02:08:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prominent crypto companies and leaders have contributed to a war chest to support pro-crypto candidates in the 2024 elections, amassing $78 million to date. “The U.S. cannot afford to continue taking a back seat on the global stage. Regulatory overreach (esp from the SEC) is actively moving the U.S. in the wrong direction,” said Ripple’s CEO. “The crypto industry has a large war chest now to elect pro-crypto candidates in 2024,” stated the CEO of crypto exchange Coinbase.
 
The U.S. Cannot Afford to Continue Taking Back Seat on Global Stage
 
Fairshake, a federal independent expenditure-only political action committee (super PAC), announced Monday that crypto and blockchain leaders have amassed $78 Million “for Fairshake Super PAC and its affiliates to support pro-innovation and pro-crypto…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Extradition Battle Win For Do Kwon: Montenegro Court Decision Reversed, LUNC Jumps 13%]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748dd4c65d</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/extradition-do-kwon-decision-reversed-lunc-jumps-13/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T01:35:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a significant turn of events, a court in Montenegro has overturned the extradition order of Do Kwon, co-founder of Terraform Labs, to the United States or South Korea. The Podgorica-based Appeals Court made the decision, which cited procedural irregularities and lack of clarity in its ruling. 
 
The court’s decision came in response to an appeal filed by Do Kwon’s defense, which resulted in the case being sent back to the Supreme Court for reconsideration.
 
Do Kwon’s Extradition In Limbo
 
The appellate court’s ruling adds new uncertainty to extraditing Do Kwon. As reported by Bitcoinist, authorities last week extended Do Kwon’s extradition detention until mid-February, giving them time to decide whether he should be extradited to the United States or South Korea. 
 
The final decision…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spot Bitcoin ETFs Poised to Tap $30 Trillion Market, Says Grayscale CEO]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748dd24db2</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/spot-bitcoin-etfs-poised-to-tap-30-trillion-market-says-grayscale-ceo/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T00:37:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale Investments expects the approval of spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to allow the $30 trillion advised wealth market to gain exposure to bitcoin. “I do think there is a lot of optimism in the market,” said the crypto asset manager’s chief executive. “I think a lot of investors are adding bitcoin to their portfolios.”
 
Grayscale’s CEO Sees Much Optimism in the Market
 
The CEO of crypto asset manager Grayscale Investments, Michael Sonnenshein, discussed his perspective on bitcoin and the market’s expectations regarding the potential approval of spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) in an interview with CNBC and Bloomberg on Monday.
 
“If you look back at this yea…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Team Advises Community On How To Accelerate SHIB Burns]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748ddd618d</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-team-shib-burns/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T00:05:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu burns have become one of the most important initiatives in the SHIB ecosystem as the community comes together to try to drastically reduce the supply of the meme coin. Over time, the burns have come to involve the Shiba Inu team who have been directing fees garnered from the Shibarium ecosystem toward the burn initiative.
 
However, as the demands to carry out more burns grow, the project’s team members have come forward to inform the community of what they can do on their part to help accelerate the burns.
 
Shiba Inu Holders Hold The Keys To Burns
 
A Shiba Inu team member popularly known as Da Vinci has asked the SHIB community to play their role in ensuring further token burns. According to the post made on Discord and shared by marketing lead Lucie, all of the money used to …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ETHW Core Team Dissolved Just Weeks After Pleading for Funds to Maintain Servers]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748dd84d87</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ethw-core-team-dissolved-just-weeks-after-pleading-for-funds-to-maintain-servers/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T23:37:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ethereum Proof of Work (ETHW) core development organization has been dissolved to help the protocol achieve full autonomy. In late November, the ETHW team pleaded for $200,000 in funding to maintain servers and recruit part-time engineers. ETHW Core team’s development approach has been criticized. 
 
Upholding PoW as the Chain’s Consensus
 
On Dec. 18, the Ethereum Proof of Work (ETHW) core development organization was dissolved to help the protocol achieve full autonomy. A statement released by an ETHW core team member said the decision, which allows ETHW to operate independently without the Core’s support, followed “in-depth discussions and [was] based on a majority consensus.”
 
Explaining the rationale behind the decision, the ETHW core team claimed that this has been its commitmen…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Network Strengthens: Hashrate Sets New All-Time High]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748ddb7347</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-network-strengthens-hashrate-all-time-high/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T23:06:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data shows the Bitcoin mining hashrate has continued its recent uptrend and has reached a new all-time high.
 
Bitcoin 7-Day Average Mining Hashrate Has Just Set A New All-Time High
 
The “mining hashrate” refers to a metric that keeps track of the total computing power the miners have connected to the Bitcoin blockchain.
 
This indicator can correlate with the network’s security, as this combined computing power controls and manages the chain. If a malicious attacker intends to take over the network, they would have to gain control over most of the online mining rigs.
 
 
Thus, the more computing power connected to the network, the harder it is to perform such a 51% hack, so the tighter the security of Bitcoin. This is only, of course, given that the hashrate is sufficiently dece…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Gods Unchained' Returns to Epic Games Store After Play-to-Earn Policy Change]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210340</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210340/gods-unchained-returns-epic-games-store-after-play-earn-policy-change"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T22:48:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Epic Games Store will now allow some Adults Only-rated crypto games like Gods Unchained, after the ESRB gave it a restrictive rating over play-to-earn elements.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase 2024 Outlook Marks End of Crypto Winter, Ordinals Leading NFT Shift, Heralds Era of Prosperity]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748dc5c14e</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/coinbase-2024-outlook-marks-end-of-crypto-winter-ordinals-leading-nft-shift-heralds-era-of-prosperity/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T22:44:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the crypto market navigates through a transformative era, Coinbase’s 2024 Crypto Market Outlook provides insights and predictions. The report, encompassing data up to November 30, 2023, delves into pivotal crypto market shifts and institutional practices.
 
Coinbase’s 80-Page 2024 Crypto Market Outlook Suggests Brighter Days for Digital Assets
 
Coinbase’s comprehensive 80-page report indicates that the total crypto market capitalization doubled in 2023, signaling an end to the crypto winter and the onset of a transition phase. Despite past challenges, the market’s remarkable recovery and sustained development underline the resilience and staying power of cryptocurrencies.
 
“What’s clear, however, is that in spite of the hurdles directed towards the asset class, the developments we wit…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Halving Has Miners Prepping as Marathon Aims to Beef Up Rigs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210321</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210321/bitcoin-halving-miners-prepping-marathon"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T22:35:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marathon plans to spend $179 million to buy two more Bitcoin mining sites in Texas and Nebraska.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Portal Airdrop Set for January as Gaming Token Nears Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210341</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210341/portal-airdrop-set-january-gaming-token-nears-launch"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T22:24:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Multi-chain gaming token Portal is nearly set to launch its airdrop following last week’s presale and news of WME representing the project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Immutable Debuts Passport Gaming Wallet in 'Gods Unchained' and More]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210334</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210334/immutable-debuts-passport-gaming-wallet-gods-unchained-more"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T22:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a beta launch, the simplified Immutable Passport wallet and universal profile is now live across multiple games and marketplaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain Association’s Employment of ‘Small Army’ of Former Security Officials Angers US Senator Elizabeth Warren]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748dcc6170</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/blockchain-associations-employment-of-small-army-of-former-security-officials-angers-us-senator-elizabeth-warren/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T21:43:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Senator Elizabeth Warren has criticized the Blockchain Association’s use of former security officials to push back against her attempts to link crypto to terrorism funding. Warren claimed that the ease with which U.S. officials can leave their positions in government to work as lobbyists shows the gaps in the country’s ethics laws. Kristin Smith, CEO of the Blockchain Association, has urged Warren and her supporters to direct their attacks on perpetrators of crime and not those who are assisting U.S. law enforcement.
 
Crypto Industry’s Alleged ‘Abuse of the Revolving Door’
 
The United States Senator for Massachusetts, Elizabeth Warren, has written a letter criticizing the Blockchain Association for enlisting the help of “a small army” of past security officials in its bid to undermi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance And CZ Grapple With Massive $2.7 Billion Fines In CFTC Court Verdict]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748dccfb9b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/binance-cz-grapple-with-massive-2-7-billion-fine/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T21:38:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amid the legal proceedings Binance and its former CEO faced, a US court has issued an order imposing significant fines on the cryptocurrency exchange and Changpeng Zhao (CZ) for charges related to alleged money laundering operations. 
 
The case was initiated by the US Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC), and the court recently reaffirmed the imposition of these fines.
 
Binance Hit With Multi-Billion Dollar Penalties
 
According to a report by Reuters, Changpeng Zhao will personally pay a fine of $150 million, while Binance, the world’s largest crypto exchange, will pay $2.7 billion to the CFTC.
 
The settlement reached in late November has now been approved by the US District Court for the Northern District of Illinois through a consent order of permanent injunction, civil moneta…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Predictions About the Crypto Lending Landscape in 2024]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748dcbb034</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/12/19/7-predictions-about-the-crypto-lending-landscape-in-2024/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T20:40:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From the emergence of TradFi arbitrage interest to the winnowing of decentralized exchanges, Ledn co-founder Mauricio Di Bartolomeo predicts the changes that may follow the resurgence of crypto lending.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mauricio  Di Bartolomeo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin’s $1 Million Ethereum Transfer to Coinbase Sparks Speculation]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748db47aa5</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/vitalik-buterins-1-million-ethereum-transfer-to-coinbase-sparks-speculation/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T20:33:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Monitoring of high-profile crypto addresses by onchain analysts has recently revealed that Ethereum co-founder, Vitalik Buterin, transferred 500 ETH, valued at slightly over $1 million, to Coinbase. This action is part of a pattern, following Buterin’s previous transfers to exchanges in September and his assertion in October that he hasn’t “sold ether for personal gain since 2018.”
 
Ethereum Co-Founder Buterin Moves 500 Ether to Coinbase
 
Whales and those prominent in the crypto world, like Vitalik Buterin, often find their transactions scrutinized by vigilant onchain detectives tracking significant movements across various blockchain networks. Recently, Buterin’s Ethereum wallet has been active, notably transferring $3.79 million in ether over a ten-day period in September.
 
In a discu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Did You Trade Ethereum NFTs in the Last Two Years? You Can Claim This Airdrop]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210322</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210322/did-you-trade-ethereum-nfts-last-two-years-claim-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T20:30:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Frame, a new layer-2 Ethereum scaling network for NFTs, launched a token airdrop on Tuesday. Here's how to claim it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Asia Drives the Next Crypto Bull Market]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748db61911</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/12/19/how-asia-drives-the-next-crypto-bull-market/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T20:19:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With substantial developer communities, flourishing Web3 scenes, and a headstart in SocialFi, Asia’s blockchain hotpots are primed to lead the next cycle of crypto adoption.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amanda Cassatt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Ethereum To $10,000 Is Programmed’: Analyst Gives 11 Reasons Why]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748db7be77</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-to-10000-programmed/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T20:05:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The second largest cryptocurrency by market cap, Ethereum, is the crypto token in focus as this crypto analyst has eleven reasons why it is “programmed” to hit $10,000. Interestingly, one of the reasons he outlined happens to be one of the recent major talking points in the Ethereum ecosystem. 
 
Why Ethereum Will “Easily” Hit $10,000
 
In a post on his X (formerly Twitter) platform, prominent crypto analyst Altcoin Daily mentioned Ethereum’s deflationary status as one of the reasons it will “easily” hit $10,000. This has been a major talking point even as the number of ETH burned continues to outpace the number of those issued. 
 
 
This is undoubtedly a positive sign for the ecosystem, as it is common knowledge the effect that token burns can have on the value of the tokens still in circ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Leak Insomniac's 'X-Men' Game After Bitcoin Ransom Demand]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210303</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210303/hackers-leak-insomniac-xmen-game-after-bitcoin-ransom-demand"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T18:34:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Insomniac Games attackers have released over 1.3 million documents that reveal Sony and Marvel contracts, game details, and personal data.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Team Seeks to Launch SHIB Domains for Websites and Email]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210301</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210301/shiba-inu-team-seeks-launch-shib-domains-websites-ema"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T18:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SHIB team is partnering with domain company D3 to lobby for approval of the first-ever crypto top-level-domain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terra Founder Do Kwon Avoids Extradition to US—For Now]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210277</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210277/terra-do-kwon-extradition-montenegro"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T16:54:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Terra founder was set to be extradited to the U.S. but an appeal means he will for the time being stay in Montenegro.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BONK Goes Bust? Solana Meme Coin Plunges 44% After Setting All-Time High]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210270</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210270/bonk-goes-bust-solana-meme-coin-plunges-44-after-setting-all-time-high"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T16:36:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What went up last week has come crashing down—but Solana’s BONK is still up 500% this month despite the losses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock Makes Key Changes to Bitcoin ETF Ahead of Expected Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210278</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210278/blackrock-makes-key-changes-to-bitcoin-etf-ahead-of-expected-launch"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T16:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a new SEC filing, BlackRock said its iShares Bitcoin Trust would only allow cash—not in-kind—creation and changed its ticker to IBIT.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elizabeth Warren: Crypto Industry Lobbyists 'Undermine' Anti-Terrorism Efforts]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210241</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210241/elizabeth-warren-crypto-industry-lobbyists-undermine-anti-terrorism-efforts"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T12:54:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a letter to the Blockchain Association, Warren reiterated earlier claims that cryptocurrency is used by terrorist groups to bypass sanctions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Court Approves $2.7 Billion Binance-CFTC Settlement, CZ to Pay $150 Million Fine]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210238</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210238/court-approves-2-7-billion-binance-cftc-settlement-cz-to-pay-150-million-fine"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T11:30:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The settlement requires Binance to pay a $1.35 billion fine to the CFTC, as well as handing over $1.35 billion in "ill-gotten transaction fees."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitter Faces EU Inquiry Over Failing to Moderate Illegal Content and Disinformation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210217</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210217/twitter-faces-eu-inquiry-over-failing-to-moderate-illegal-content-and-disinformation"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T00:07:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first-of-its-kind investigation will review whether Twitter did what it said it would do about Israel-Palestine content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ubisoft's 'Champions Tactics' Ethereum NFTs Generate Millions After Free Mint]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210213</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210213/ubisoft-champions-tactics-ethereum-nfts-generate-millions-after-free-mint"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T23:42:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following a drop that minted out in under 20 minutes, Ubisoft’s Warlords NFTs for Champions Tactics are reselling for $600 or more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK Builds Digital Securities Sandbox to Test New Technolgies]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210202</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210202/uk-builds-digital-securities-sandbox-to-test-new-technolgies"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T22:46:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The setup aims to house controlled testing of blockchain and other emerging infrastructure technologies before wider deployment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Game 'Aurory' Suffers $830K Exploit, Disables Arbitrum Bridge]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210153</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210153/solana-game-aurory-suffers-830k-exploit-disables-arbitrum-bridge"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T22:30:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An exploit on Aurory's marketplace led to one user siphoning about 600,000 AURY tokens. The game's bridge is down while devs work on a fix.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitwise Is First to Bitcoin ETF Ad Race With ‘Most Interesting Man in the World’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210186</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210186/bitwise-firstbitcoin-etf-ad-with-most-interesting-man-in-the-world"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T22:05:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The message: "Bitwise Is Interesting.” It stars Jonathan Goldsmith, well-known for portraying “The Most Interesting Man in the World” in beer ads.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Fees Continue to Surge Thanks to Ordinal Mania]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210168</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210168/bitcoin-fees-continue-to-surge-thanks-to-ordinal-mania"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T22:01:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s again very expensive to make a transaction on Bitcoin’s blockchain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Next BONK? Solana Meme Coin Dogwifhat Pumps 2,000X in a Month]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210151</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210151/next-bonk-solana-meme-coin-dogwifhat-pumps-2000x-month"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T20:04:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s a dog. With a hat. And the Solana token based on the dogwifhat meme is the latest to surge in value after BONK's boom.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Funds See 'Profit-Taking' Dip, But Investors Still Like Solana]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210155</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210155/bitcoin-funds-see-profit-taking-dip-but-investors-still-like-solana"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T19:16:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana and other altcoin funds saw $21 million deposited last week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Helium Tokens Surge Amid Network Expansion, Solana Saga BONK Mania]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210147</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210147/helium-tokens-surge-amid-network-expansion-solana-saga-bonk-mania"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T14:04:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following Helium's nationwide U.S. rollout, the Solana-based tokens powering the decentralized 5G network have surged.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Slips Below $41,000 as Crypto Price Rally Cools]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210131</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210131/bitcoin-slips-below-41000-as-crypto-price-rally-cools"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T10:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price slump comes as Bitcoin's average transaction fee has surged to a yearly high, driven by the growing popularity of Ordinals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week on Crypto Twitter: BONK Simply Won’t Quit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210073</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210073/this-week-on-crypto-twitter-bonk-simply-wont-quit"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T10:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ever-ascendant Solana meme coin dominated Twitter discourse for yet another week, as inscriptions hobbled traffic on multiple layer 2 networks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Biggest Games Coming Out in 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210052</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210052/biggest-games-coming-out-nintendo-playstation-xbox-pc"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From Final Fantasy VII Rebirth to Star Wars Outlaws and plenty in between, these are our most anticipated games of 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Bonk Continues Surge With Solana Hype, Bitcoin Dips]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210009</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210009/this-week-in-coins-bonk-continues-surge-with-solana-hype-bitcoin-dips"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T10:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin and other major coins and tokens are down. But new meme coin BONK is still rallying.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Voice Generating Startup Resemble AI Promises to Restore Old Audio]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210063</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210063/resemble-ai-voice-enhance-recordings"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T01:34:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An AI startup has built a tool that it says can make low-fidelity speech recordings sound like new.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not That Grok: Musician Grimes and OpenAI Launch Plush Toy with AI Inside]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210024</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210024/grok-ai-twitter-toy-elon-musk-grimes-trademark"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T22:36:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk’s ex partners with Curio to launch a line of AI-powered toys designed to cut back on screen time and enhance interaction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jupiter Airdrop Set for January With a Billion JUP for Solana DeFi Users]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210017</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210017/jupiter-airdrop-set-january-billion-jup-solana-defi-users"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T22:10:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Half of the 10 billion JUP supply will ultimately go to the Jupiter community, with 10% landing in Solana wallets during the first airdrop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Weighs Demand for Saga Phones After Sellout Amid BONK Boom]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210036</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210036/solana-weighs-demand-saga-phones-after-sellout-amid-bonk-boom"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T21:51:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Saga is sold out in the U.S. and EU supplies are nearly tapped out. Solana Labs told Decrypt how it’s assessing next moves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Tech Giant Alibaba Unveils New AI Video Tool]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210018</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210018/alibaba-ai-text-to-video-generative-cloud"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T21:07:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alibaba says its I2VGen-XL model can handle “visualization, sampling, training, inference, join training using images and videos, acceleration, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitch Walks Back Changes After Surge in Nudity: 'We Went Too Far']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209998</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209998/twitch-walks-back-changes-after-surge-nudity-went-too-far"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T19:37:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, Twitch announced it would allow artistic nudity. Now, it’s blocked again, in part because of concerns around AI realism.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Plans to Challenge SEC Denial of Crypto Rulemaking Petition]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209997</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209997/coinbase-plans-challenge-sec-denial-crypto-rulemaking"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T18:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC today denied crypto exchange Coinbase's petition to clarify new crypto rules for the digital assets industry. Coinbase isn't taking "no" for an answer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Scaler Arbitrum Suffers Outage—And Inscriptions Are to Blame]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209996</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209996/ethereum-scaler-arbitrum-suffers-outage-inscriptions-blame"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T18:12:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arbitrum and other chains have recently been bombarded by users making "inscriptions" as on Bitcoin, even though such networks support NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gary Gensler: SEC 'Taking a New Look' at Bitcoin ETF Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209964</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209964/gary-gensler-sec-taking-new-look-bitcoin-etf-applications"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T16:06:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC chair stated that the regulator is reviewing spot Bitcoin ETF applications in light of a recent court ruling.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BONK Spikes 101% Amid Solana Saga Sales Frenzy to Claim Airdrop]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209966</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209966/bonk-spikes-101-amid-solana-saga-sales-frenzy-to-claim-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T15:40:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana-based meme coin BONK has continued to soar in value and hit new all-time highs—and the Saga smartphone is an unexpected beneficiary.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SocialFi Startup Reach Aims to Improve Crypto Twitter With Anti-Bot Protocol]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209903</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209903/socialfi-reach-crypto-twitter-anti-bot-protocol-token"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T15:01:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest addition to the "point" meta seeks to address the challenges of Crypto Twitter with the support of Seedphrase, Pranksy, Gmoney, and Zeneca.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating peaceful money & taking over your local government w/ Joseph Schiarizzi]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zb0VG27G/creating-peaceful-money-taking-over-your-local-government-w-joseph-schiarizzi</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zb0VG27G/creating-peaceful-money-taking-over-your-local-government-w-joseph-schiarizzi"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T23:23:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week our host Reza Jafery is joined by Joseph Schiarizzi, founder of OpenDollar and prolific solidity developer. 


We discuss: 
- Onchain beer
- Taking over your local government
- His Emmy and 3 patents?!?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INTERVIEW: Ember Sword CEO Says NFT Games Are More 'Transparent']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/M9OHCVpA/interview-ember-sword-ceo-says-nft-games-are-more-transparent</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/M9OHCVpA/interview-ember-sword-ceo-says-nft-games-are-more-transparent"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T21:58:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ember Sword CEO Mark Laursen shares why some big game studios "irk" him—and why he got into game development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Director Jordan Bayne on the State of Film3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZLoEDkL9/director-jordan-bayne-on-the-state-of-film3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZLoEDkL9/director-jordan-bayne-on-the-state-of-film3"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T00:11:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the 2023 Film3 Summit, Jordan Bayne—director and founder of The Squad—spoke with Decrypt's Sander Lutz about how the Film3 world has progressed over the last year and what decentralized technologies can offer to creators that want to buck the Hollywood system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Questions With SCENE: Phil Mohun]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TwOjXfOR/5-questions-with-scene-phil-mohun</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TwOjXfOR/5-questions-with-scene-phil-mohun"/>
        <updated>2023-12-01T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bright Moments co-founder Phil Mohun joins 5 Questions With SCENE to recount some favorite moments from the road, including negotiating with Patagonian gauchos, falling in love with Tokyo, and gaining a newfound appreciation for shrooms chocolate bars.

Shot and edited by Vincent Roazzi Jr.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are NFTs Ever Coming Back?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qLmFpNKE/are-nfts-ever-coming-back</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qLmFpNKE/are-nfts-ever-coming-back"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T18:38:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this weeks episode we sit down with Cashtro from Arcade.xyz to discuss NFTs, shitcoins, what collections have held onto their floor prices, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Summit: Will Web3 Gaming Ever be Mainstream?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OvVWhGbW/web-summit-will-web3-gaming-ever-be-mainstream</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OvVWhGbW/web-summit-will-web3-gaming-ever-be-mainstream"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T19:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animoca Brands CEO Robby Yung, EndeavorXR CEO Amy Peck and Gamee co-founder CEO Bozena Rezab joined Decrypt's Stephen Graves on stage at Web Summit to talk about the future of Web3 gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Allie Eve Knox on Spankchain and the life of a Crypto Financial Dominatrix]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/16rVeg6o/allie-eve-knox-on-spankchain-and-the-life-of-a-crypto-financial-dominatrix</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/16rVeg6o/allie-eve-knox-on-spankchain-and-the-life-of-a-crypto-financial-dominatrix"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T21:20:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the first IRL episode of This Time Will Be Different!

In this week's episode, our host, Reza Jafery, is joined by Allie Eve Knox, the Spankchain Chief of Staff and FinDomme. 

They discuss
- How to sell feet pics
- If crypto is really as permissionless as it seems
- the intersections between crypto and sex work]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>