<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-05-14T14:14:50.407Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-05-14T14:14:50.407Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DMarket tops NFT charts but loses three-day streak above US$900,000]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19487015/DMarket-tops-NFT-charts-but-loses-three-day-streak-above-US900000</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19487015/DMarket-tops-NFT-charts-but-loses-three-day-streak-above-US900000"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T14:05:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DMarket tops daily NFT sales despite recording less sales than the previous day.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former chief of the U.S. CFTC joins Paxos board of directors]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19487013/Former-chief-of-the-US-CFTC-joins-Paxos-board-of-directors</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19487013/Former-chief-of-the-US-CFTC-joins-Paxos-board-of-directors"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T14:04:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Christopher Giancarlo, former CFTC chief has joined Paxos board. Giancarlo’s advocacy for blockchain innovation aligns with Paxos’ mission for regulated solutions. Paxos aims to drive financial sector innovation with Giancarlo’s guidance on board. J. Christopher Giancarlo, former chairman of the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin braces for Fed's Powell as trader says $65K key BTC price level]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19487010/Bitcoin-braces-for-Feds-Powell-as-trader-says-65K-key-BTC-price-level</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19487010/Bitcoin-braces-for-Feds-Powell-as-trader-says-65K-key-BTC-price-level"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T14:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC price volatility continues within a narrow range — but some BTC price data shows the path toward all-time highs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Merchants: This Time IS Different...]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19487002/Bitcoin-Merchants-This-Time-IS-Different</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19487002/Bitcoin-Merchants-This-Time-IS-Different"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T14:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Previous efforts to promote Bitcoin merchant adoption may have been premature due to insufficient interest, but now, a burgeoning circular economy is gaining momentum, heralding a shift towards widespread acceptance. This growing ecosystem fosters increased demand for Bitcoin as a medium of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brace For Impact: Mt. Gox Set To Inject 142,000 BTC And 143,000 Bitcoin Cash Into The Market- Here’s When]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19486970/Brace-For-Impact-Mt-Gox-Set-To-Inject-142000-BTC-And-143000-Bitcoin-Cash-Into-The-Market-Heres-When</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19486970/Brace-For-Impact-Mt-Gox-Set-To-Inject-142000-BTC-And-143000-Bitcoin-Cash-Into-The-Market-Heres-When"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T14:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tokyo-based Bitcoin exchange, Mt. Gox is preparing to release a substantial amount of Bitcoin (BTC) into the market, signaling the upcoming disbursement of payments to creditors who had been affected by its hack attack in 2011.   Mt. Gox Set To Release 142,000 Bitcoin Into Market Reports from...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stacks Foundation joins Uphold to drive Bitcoin adoption]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19486967/Stacks-Foundation-joins-Uphold-to-drive-Bitcoin-adoption</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19486967/Stacks-Foundation-joins-Uphold-to-drive-Bitcoin-adoption"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Stacks Foundation, a leading blockchain platform, has just announced a new partnership with Uphold, the multi-asset money platform, aimed … Continue reading]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Thiel's Founders Fund, Vitalik Buterin Back $45M Investment in Polymarket]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19487009/Peter-Thiels-Founders-Fund-Vitalik-Buterin-Back-45M-Investment-in-Polymarket</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19487009/Peter-Thiels-Founders-Fund-Vitalik-Buterin-Back-45M-Investment-in-Polymarket"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The series B funding round comes during a breakout year for the crypto-based prediction market platform, and brings its total funding close to $75 million.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Poloniex Hacker Transfers $53.5 Million Worth of ETH Through Tornado Cash]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19486964/Poloniex-Hacker-Transfers-535-Million-Worth-of-ETH-Through-Tornado-Cash</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19486964/Poloniex-Hacker-Transfers-535-Million-Worth-of-ETH-Through-Tornado-Cash"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T13:58:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Six months post-hack, the Poloniex attacker moved 17.8K ETH through multiple wallets to Tornado Cash.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Rune etchings plummet by 99%; What’s behind the dramatic fall?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19486966/Bitcoin-Rune-etchings-plummet-by-99-Whats-behind-the-dramatic-fall</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19486966/Bitcoin-Rune-etchings-plummet-by-99-Whats-behind-the-dramatic-fall"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T13:58:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In less than a month following its launch on the Bitcoin (BTC) blockchain, the Bitcoin Runes protocol has seen a … Continue reading]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Institutional ETPs Post First Inflow In Five Weeks Despite Bitcoin Price Pullback]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19486950/Institutional-ETPs-Post-First-Inflow-In-Five-Weeks-Despite-Bitcoin-Price-Pullback</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19486950/Institutional-ETPs-Post-First-Inflow-In-Five-Weeks-Despite-Bitcoin-Price-Pullback"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T13:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Weekly ETP trade volume is down 53% compared to April.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Meme Token Flow Stimulated the Markets! These Altcoins Are on the Rise Under the Leadership of PEPE! Will the Rise Continue?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19486947/New-Meme-Token-Flow-Stimulated-the-Markets-These-Altcoins-Are-on-the-Rise-Under-the-Leadership-of-PEPE-Will-the-Rise-Continue</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19486947/New-Meme-Token-Flow-Stimulated-the-Markets-These-Altcoins-Are-on-the-Rise-Under-the-Leadership-of-PEPE-Will-the-Rise-Continue"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T13:53:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stock trader and analyst Keith Gill, who fueled the GameStop craze, made meme tokens such as DOGE, FLOKI, PEPE, POCAT rise. Continue Reading: New Meme Token Flow Stimulated the Markets! These Altcoins Are on the Rise Under the Leadership of PEPE! Will the Rise Continue?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[32 Vintage ‘Sleeping Bitcoin’ Wallets Spring to Life in May, Surpassing April’s Activity]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7423eaf38f</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/32-vintage-sleeping-bitcoin-wallets-spring-to-life-in-may-surpassing-aprils-activity/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T13:50:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following the awakening of numerous dormant bitcoins in March, April was rather uneventful, with just 72 transfers from idle wallets dating between 2010 and 2017. To date, May has seen 32 transfers from vintage wallets, moving about 1,181 more bitcoin in the past two weeks than during the whole month of April. May Outpaces April […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paul Grewal criticizes SEC’s approach in Coinbase case following Debt Box mishandling]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19486934/Paul-Grewal-criticizes-SECs-approach-in-Coinbase-case-following-Debt-Box-mishandling</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19486934/Paul-Grewal-criticizes-SECs-approach-in-Coinbase-case-following-Debt-Box-mishandling"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T13:49:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chief Legal Officer of Coinbase, Paul Grewal, charged the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) with moving from a traditional Wells notice process to penalizing the company for their case against Coinbase. Grewal’s criticism is a reaction to a disclosure of the SEC’s failure to use its...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase ‘on top of it’ despite withdrawals not processing]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19486937/Coinbase-on-top-of-it-despite-withdrawals-not-processing</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19486937/Coinbase-on-top-of-it-despite-withdrawals-not-processing"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T13:47:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Users are still struggling to withdraw their funds from Coinbase despite the exchange claiming it had 'fully recovered.']]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Asia: China Emerges As New Frontier For Bitcoin Innovation]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7423ebfcdc</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/china-new-frontier-bitcoin-innovation"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T13:43:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ah, the wild west. John Wayne, the Man with No Name, Billy the Kid and Jesse James. 
The frontier has a way of capturing everyone’s imagination – young and old. The cowboys, the outlaws, the gold prospectors. A land of opportunity and harsh cruelty. Unforgiving yet irresistible. 
Bitcoin was once such a frontier. The early days were rife with scams, “criminals” and underground markets. The underbelly of the internet embraced it first. It was an agora filled with foreign and obscure figures. It thrived as a counterculture, void of any rules and regulations. No government to protect you from yourself. No KYC, no AML – only your name, your PGP key, gribble, and the Web-Of-Trust. Fortunes were made, and fortunes were lost. A beautiful chaos where only the authority of the Bitcoin blockchain re…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Bergeron</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tornado Cash Dev Alexey Pertsev Sentenced to 64 Months in Prison]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7423ebfcc7</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/tornado-cash-dev-alexey-pertsev-sentenced-to-64-months-in-prison"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T13:43:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alexey Pertsev, a developer for the Ethereum-based crypto mixer Tornado Cash, has been sentenced to 64 months in prison after a Dutch court found him guilty of money laundering charges on Tuesday.
The judge stated that the platform was "intended for criminals" and that Pertsev should have been suspicious of the criminal origins of transactions.
The closely-watched case marks a major blow to financial privacy advocates. Many critics argue that Pertsev is being unfairly targeted as the developer of an open-source platform. 
Further, they say he did not have control over how users chose to employ Tornado Cash to obscure transaction histories on the public blockchain.
Nonetheless, prosecutors successfully argued that Pertsev did too little to prevent the mixer from being utilized for money laundering. 
They rejected claims that his obligations were lessened due to the decentralized nature of the platform's operations.
 
                         
                         
                         
                     
                    
Experts predict it will have a chilling effect on development of open-source tools that enable anonymity on Bitcoin and other blockchains. They argue it sets a precedent for holding developers liable for the actions of anonymous users.
Tornado Cash was sanctioned by the US Treasury Department in 2022 over allegations it obscured funds stolen by North Korean state hackers. Pertsev was arrested days later, dealing a major blow to the embryonic crypto privacy sector.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vivek Sen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinShares’ AUM Tops $6B Following Valkyrie ETF Acquisition]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19486892/CoinShares-AUM-Tops-6B-Following-Valkyrie-ETF-Acquisition</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19486892/CoinShares-AUM-Tops-6B-Following-Valkyrie-ETF-Acquisition"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T13:41:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CoinShares sees “its most successful quarter in company history.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Empire Newsletter: It’s memecoins all the way down]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19486891/Empire-Newsletter-Its-memecoins-all-the-way-down</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19486891/Empire-Newsletter-Its-memecoins-all-the-way-down"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T13:38:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is it time to treat memecoin launches as the new standard moving forward?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zeta Markets secures $5 million for Solana DeFi expansion]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19486857/Zeta-Markets-secures-5-million-for-Solana-DeFi-expansion</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19486857/Zeta-Markets-secures-5-million-for-Solana-DeFi-expansion"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T13:33:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized exchange (DEX) for perpetual trading Zeta Markets has completed a strategic $5 million funding round, led by Electric Capital and with contributions from DACM, Selini Capital, Airtree Ventures, and several notable angel investors, including Anatoly Yakovenko of Solana. The fresh...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here is my Bank Account]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19486894/Here-is-my-Bank-Account</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19486894/Here-is-my-Bank-Account"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T13:30:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[🔥 GET MY FREE NEWSLETTER 👉 https://cryptolark.co/WEALTH_MASTERY💎 BITGET 👉 $30,000 IN BONUSES ►► https://cryptolark.co/BITGET30K 💸 BYBIT $30,030 BONUS & FEE DISCOUNT 👉 https://cryptolark.co/BYBIT💡💡💡 ESSENTIAL CRYPTO KNOWLEDGE 💡💡💡🔥 GET MY FREE NEWSLETTER 👉 https://cryptolark.co/WEALTHMASTERY💎...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Exchange Listing and Delisting Announcements: May 13, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19486834/Crypto-Exchange-Listing-and-Delisting-Announcements-May-13-2024</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19486834/Crypto-Exchange-Listing-and-Delisting-Announcements-May-13-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T13:28:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is our weekly collection of digital asset listing and delisting, trading pair-related announcements by crypto exchanges that we found last week and today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is the meme coin mania back to crypto?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19486821/Is-the-meme-coin-mania-back-to-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19486821/Is-the-meme-coin-mania-back-to-crypto"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T13:22:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meme coins are trending in the cryptocurrency market after a month of low activity. Renewed interest surged when the famous … Continue reading]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paxos Appoints Former CFTC Chairman J. Christopher Giancarlo to Board]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7423d7ea21</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//executives/moves/paxos-appoints-former-cftc-chairman-j-christopher-giancarlo-to-board/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T13:21:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paxos, a regulated  
blockchain and tokenization infrastructure platform, announced today the  
appointment of J. Christopher Giancarlo, former Chairman of the US Commodity  
Futures Trading Commission (CFTC), to its board of directors.
Paxos Scores Regulatory  
Heavyweight from CFTC
Giancarlo,  
a respected figure in the financial services industry and a passionate advocate  
for blockchain technology, brings decades of expertise to Paxos as the company  
continues to innovate in the digital asset space. 
During his  
tenure at the CFTC from 2014 to 2019, Giancarlo oversaw the introduction of the  
first Bitcoin futures products and applied a "Do No Harm" regulatory  
approach to blockchain technology.
"Chris  
brings unparalleled expertise and understanding of complex market dynamics to …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Damian Chmiel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Floki Inu (FLOKI) Recovers Close to Monthly High, Extends Meme Token Trend]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19486796/Floki-Inu-FLOKI-Recovers-Close-to-Monthly-High-Extends-Meme-Token-Trend</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19486796/Floki-Inu-FLOKI-Recovers-Close-to-Monthly-High-Extends-Meme-Token-Trend"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T13:16:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Floki Inu (FLOKI) is up alongside other meme tokens. FLOKI represents doge-themed assets and is one platform that aims to onboard Web3 activities and gaming. FLOKI went up close to its monthly high, reaching $0.0001894 with nearly 10% daily gains. FLOKI marks a second round of the meme token...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LUNC And USTC Revival: Terra Community Votes To Make Allnodes An Official Organization]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7423d1c8cd</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/lunc-ustc-terra-community-votes/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T13:09:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Terra community isn’t relenting in its efforts to revive the LUNC and USTC tokens and take them back to their old glory days. This time, the community has proposed a proposal to ensure that the Luna Classic’s (LUNC) circulating supply data is well documented. 
 
Terra Community Proposes All Allnodes As An Official Organization
 
The text proposal titled ‘Change official CS API endpoint to Allnodes FCD’ aims to make Allnodes an official organization of the Terra community. Allnodes will be responsible for “hosting the endpoint, providing the correct circulating supply data for Luna Classic.” The proposal also aims to get an agreement from community members about how this circulating supply should be calculated. 
 
Related Reading: Crypto Price Predictions For 2024: Dogecoin To $2 And XR…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pepe Price Prediction as it Hits New ATH – Does WienerAI Have Higher Potential?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7423d1e141</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/pepe-price-prediction-as-it-hits-new-ath-does-wienerai-have-higher-potential/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T13:09:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The wildly popular Pepe (PEPE) coin is again drawing attention after an explosive rally sent its price to a new all-time high. With “Pepe mania” now gripping the market, how high could this frog-themed token go in the coming weeks and months? PEPE Price Rallies to New ATH as Spot Volumes Rocket PEPE’s price is […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['CryptoDad' Giancarlo Joins Paxos Board]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7423d30638</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/05/14/cryptodad-giancarlo-joins-paxos-board/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T13:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paxos has added J. Christopher Giancarlo, a former chairman of the U.S. Commodity Futures Trading Commission who has been a public advocate for the cryptocurrency sector, to its board of directors, the company told CoinDesk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RWA Platform Re Debuts Tokenized Reinsurance Fund on Avalanche with $15M Commitment from Nexus Mutual]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7423d3061d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2024/05/14/rwa-platform-re-debuts-tokenized-reinsurance-fund-on-avalanche-with-15m-commitment-from-nexus-mutual/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T13:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The aims to broaden access to the $1 trillion reinsurance industry, making it more efficient and transparent with blockchain technology.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Mover Americas: Bitcoin Dips Below $62K Ahead of U.S. Inflation Figures]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7423d90f19</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/05/14/first-mover-americas-bitcoin-dips-below-62k-ahead-of-us-inflation-figures/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T12:28:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest price moves in bitcoin (BTC) and crypto markets in context for May 14, 2024. First Mover is CoinDesk’s daily newsletter that contextualizes the latest actions in the crypto markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley, Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Glassnode Report Highlights Diverging Performance Between Bitcoin and Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7423da52fc</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/glassnode-report-highlights-diverging-performance-between-bitcoin-and-ethereum/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T12:21:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The onchain analytics firm Glassnode has released a new report detailing the contrasting performance of bitcoin and ethereum during the 2023-24 cycle. The report highlights bitcoin’s resilience and ethereum’s comparative lag in speculative interest and price performance. Bitcoin’s Post-Halving Resilience Contrasts With Ethereum’s Struggles, Says Glassnode Glassnode researchers noted a significant divergence in performance between […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tornado Cash Dev Alexey Pertsev Found Guilty by Dutch Court]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230597</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230597/tornado-cash-dev-alexey-pertsev-found-guilty-by-dutch-court"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T12:07:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A developer behind Ethereum mixer Tornado Cash has been convicted of laundering $1.2 billion through the platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tornado Cash Developer Alexey Pertsev Sentenced to 64 Months in Prison by Dutch Court]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7423c5666c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/05/14/tornado-cash-developer-alexey-pertsev-found-guilty-of-money-laundering/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T12:03:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alexey Pertsev was found guilty of money laundering $1.2 billion worth of crypto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camomile Shumba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Exchange Spot Volumes Plunge 60% Post BTC Halving]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7423c734d8</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/crypto-exchange-spot-volumes-plunge-60-post-btc-halving/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T11:52:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a  
record-breaking March driven by equally impressive Bitcoin (BTC) performance,  
spot volumes on the top 10 cryptocurrency exchanges dropped by more than 60% in  
April. According to a benchmark by Finance Magnates Intelligence, their  
trading volume fell from $2.1 trillion in March to just under $1.3 trillion in  
April.
Cryptocurrency Exchange  
Volumes Plummet Post-Bitcoin Halving
In March,  
volumes on the largest cryptocurrency platforms reached their highest levels in  
nearly four years, increasing by an average of 120%. This surge coincided with  
a new all-time high (ATH) for Bitcoin, recorded on March 14, when the price  
tested nearly $74,000, sparking significant investor activity. 
In April,  
anticipation centered on Bitcoin's halving, which reduced the reward for m…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Damian Chmiel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pepe Jumps 19% to All-Time High Following Roaring Kitty Return]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230591</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230591/pepe-jumps-19-to-all-time-high-following-roaringkitty-return"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T11:45:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The last 24 hours has been a perfect storm for Pepe: Roaring Kitty has returned, causing a meme rally, and Coinbase listing rumors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pro-XRP Lawyer Deaton Secures Spot On Massachusetts GOP Ballot]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7423c1535b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/pro-xrp-lawyer-deaton-spot-massachusetts-ballot/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T11:39:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John E. Deaton, a fervent advocate for XRP and critic of current regulatory approaches to digital assets, has officially secured his place on the Massachusetts Republican ballot for the 2024 US Senate elections. Deaton’s campaign announcement has stirred notable attention, setting the stage for a direct challenge against incumbent Democrat Senator Elizabeth Warren.
 
Pro-XRP Lawyer Is Officially On The Ballot
 
Deaton’s entry into the political arena follows his vocal criticism of what he perceives as overreach by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and particularly targets Senator Warren’s stance on cryptocurrency regulations. “Bad news for one of Washington’s most entrenched career politicians. Elizabeth Warren: Look who’s on the ballot!” Deaton announced on X after confirming t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop Rally Sends Meme Coins Skywards; PEPE, FLOKI, MOG Surge]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7423c1b870</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/05/14/gamestop-rally-sends-meme-coins-skywards-pepe-floki-mog-surge/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T11:36:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Roaring Kitty is living proof that retail can mog (outperform) institutions at the highest level,” one meme coin developer said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ghana’s Vice President Says His Government Aims to Become the First to Be Powered by Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7423c2f805</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ghanas-vice-president-says-his-government-aims-to-become-the-first-to-be-powered-by-blockchain/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T11:29:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ghanaian government’s next phase in its digitalization drive is set to be the adoption of blockchain technology, according to the country’s vice president. He stated that his administration aims to become one of the few governments worldwide powered by blockchain, and the first in Africa. A Blockchain-Powered Government The Vice President of Ghana, Mahamadu […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Meme Coin Devs Fight on Livestream to Pump Price—Until One Loses a Tooth]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230526</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230526/solana-meme-coin-devs-fight-livestream-pump-price"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T11:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These Solana meme coin developers fought valiantly for fame and riches, but gained just four viewers while losing one tooth in the process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Comes Back Online after 3 Hours of Outage; Users Face Withdrawal Issues]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7423b7ff70</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/coinbase-comes-back-online-after-3-hours-of-outage-users-face-withdrawal-issues/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T10:11:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The services of cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase have been restored after a “system-wide outage” of over three hours. The exchange confirmed that its functionalities are “now fully recovered.”

Coinbase is now fully recovered. We appreciate your patience and apologize for the inconvenience. https://t.co/AAzEMPaJGL
— Coinbase Support (@CoinbaseSupport) May 14, 2024
Withdrawal Issues Persist
However, many Coinbase users on social media are complaining of difficulties in fund withdrawals and transfers. Some even pointed out that crypto transfers and cash withdrawals remain offline.

We are sorry for the inconvenience, rocket. Our team is actively working towards a resolution. While we can't provide a specific timeline for the fix, we suggest that you keep checking your account for updates. 1/…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arnab Shome</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Reports Full Recovery, But 'Degraded Performance' After System Outage]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230582</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230582/coinbase-reports-full-recovery-but-degraded-performance-after-system-outage"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T10:08:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Coinbase is now fully recovered," it wrote, although its status website says its mobile app and website are experience "degraded performance."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance To Bookshelves? Former CEO’s Next Chapter Might Surprise You]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7423b3856b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/binance-to-bookshelves-former-ceos-next-chapter-might-surprise-you/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T09:48:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Changpeng Zhao, the enigmatic founder of cryptocurrency giant Binance, has sparked a firestorm of speculation with a recent social media post hinting at a potential career shift.
 
Following a legal battle with the US Department of Justice that concluded with a surprisingly lenient sentence, CZ, as he’s known in the crypto world, may be trading spreadsheets for scribbles.
 
 
Binance In The Hot Seat
 
The past few months have been turbulent for Binance. The exchange, once dominating the cryptocurrency landscape with its vast trading volume, found itself embroiled in a legal tussle with American authorities.
 
While the specifics remain shrouded in secrecy, the resolution came as a surprise to many. A mere four-month jail sentence for CZ, far shorter than anticipated, left many wondering wh…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Runes Protocol Sees Traction Waning After Much-Hyped Introduction]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7423bc4611</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2024/05/14/bitcoin-runes-protocol-sees-traction-waning-after-much-hyped-introduction/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T09:44:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[User activity has plunged after a hyped run-up to the start of the Runes protocol , which was expected by some to mirror Solana’s meme coin ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Neighbor Alice Season 1 Beta Goes Live]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/sGfYcHuB/my-neighbor-alice-season-1-beta-goes-live</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/sGfYcHuB/my-neighbor-alice-season-1-beta-goes-live"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T09:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rug Radio Creator Orangie plays the new season of multiplayer builder-game My Neighbor Alice and tries out all its features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How DLCs Can Enable Defi Deposits and Fulfill Bitcoin’s Promise]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7423a695fb</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/how-dlcs-can-enable-defi-deposits-and-fulfill-bitcoins-promise/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T08:37:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin embodies decentralization, security, and self-sovereignty. But today, financial transactions with Bitcoin require the use of custodians or bridges – a reliance on intermediaries that has led to disastrous losses numbering in the billions of dollars. Discreet Log Contracts (DLCs) are poised to change that by allowing users in the space, for the first time, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Guest Author</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cross-Border Banking: Wirex Teams Up with OpenPayd for Virtual IBAN]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7423a7acf3</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//fintech/cross-border-banking-wirex-teams-up-with-openpayd-for-virtual-iban/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T08:31:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To enhance financial services for customers across the UK  
and European Economic Area (EEA), OpenPayd, an embedded finance and  
Banking-as-a-Service (BaaS) platform, has announced a strategic partnership  
with Wirex, a Web3 money app. This collaboration aims to fortify easy, fast,  
and secure payment solutions.
Forging Alliance for Virtual IBAN Payments
Under the newly forged partnership, OpenPayd will facilitate  
the issuance of named virtual IBANs to Wirex customers in over 30 countries  
spanning the UK and EEA regions. These virtual IBANs will grant customers  
access to the Faster Payments network in the UK and enable Single Euro Payments  
Area (SEPA) Instant transactions for Euro-denominated deposits and withdrawals.
The integration of OpenPayd's services into Wirex's  
infrast…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tareq Sikder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who Is Roaring Kitty, and What Does His Return Mean for Crypto?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230566</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230566/who-is-roaring-kitty-keith-gill-deepfuckingvalue-back-on-twitter"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T01:38:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Keith Gill's Twitter account came back to life after more than two years, leading GameStop stock to more than double in value and a Solana-based tribute coin to spike 1,900%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop Meme Coins Are Taking Over Solana as Pump.fun Sets Record]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230546</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230546/gamestop-meme-coins-are-taking-over-solana-as-pump-fun-sets-record"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T21:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Among the 14,500 tokens deployed on Solana through pump.fun were more than a few GameStop-themed tokens.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Andrew Tate Says He’s Cashed $500K in Bitcoin to Go ‘All In’ on GameStop]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230538</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230538/andrew-tate-bitcoin-gamestop-gme-taking-down-wall-street"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T19:20:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The controversial influencer says he’s “taking down Wall Street” through meme coin stocks, with GME short sellers out $1.4 billion in its revival.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF Weekly Investments Grow For First Time In Over a Month]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230520</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230520/bitcoin-etf-130-million-inflows-ethereum-etf-hope-dims"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T19:08:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Investor sentiment may be shifting, CoinShares says, as Grayscale’s GBTC outflows were the lowest since January.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI Shows Off Voice Chatbot, Touts New GPT-4o AI Model]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230460</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230460/openai-chatgpt-4-o-voice-chatbot"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T18:24:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The live demonstration of new conversational capabilities fueled comparisons to the virtual companion depicted in the movie “Her.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF Bonanza: Largest Holder of BlackRock, Ark Funds Revealed]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230512</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230512/bitcoin-etf-bonanza-largest-holder-blackrock-ark-revealed"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T17:37:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A little-known hedge fund in Boston has a massive stake in spot Bitcoin ETFs from BlackRock and ARK Invest/21Shares.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Pumps as GameStop Rally Kickstarts Memes Frenzy]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230509</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230509/dogecoin-pumps-gamestop-rally-memes-frenzy"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T16:54:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin and political meme coins are booking significant gains amid the GameStop stock resurgence, with some Donald Trump coins up 30% or more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop Tribute Meme Coin on Solana Surges 1,900% as GME Fever Returns]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230508</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230508/gamestop-meme-coin-solana-surges-gme-fever-returns"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T16:16:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The GME tribute meme coin on Solana is blasting off Monday, delivering sizable returns outpacing those of GameStop shares.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop Trading Paused Nine Times as Roaring Kitty Return Drives Meme Rally]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230459</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230459/gamestop-trading-paused-nine-times-roaring-kitty-meme-rally"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T15:22:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meme stocks and cryptocurrencies boomed Monday after Roaring Kitty, the internet figure behind the 2021 GameStop saga, posted online.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fantasy Top Volume Jumps as Crypto Twitter NFT Game Adds 40 New Heroes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230444</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230444/fantasy-top-volume-jumps-as-crypto-twitter-nft-game-adds-40-new-heroes"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T13:40:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The game's latest update adds tweaked mechanics and new heroes to Fantasy Top, while two big competitions have been announced.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Filing Hits Back at Coinbase 'Power Grab' Accusations]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230437</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230437/sec-filing-hits-back-at-coinbase-power-grab-accusations"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T11:42:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a court filing, the SEC argued that Coinbase can't demand that the regulator write new rules for crypto "from the ground up."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Leads The Bounce]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QoXLhFzb/solana-leads-the-bounce</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QoXLhFzb/solana-leads-the-bounce"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T11:06:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto up despite ETF outflow, SOL outperforms. HK ETFs also see another net daily outflow. SOL flips ETH again in 24hr DEX volume. SOL revenue now 50% of ETH. Bitcoin above $1m by 2030: Dorsey. Bitcoin & Kucoin get license in India. Kraken tries to get SEC case dismissed. Stand with Crypto sets up election war chest. VIP customers make up two thirds of Binance volume. NOT to launch on Binance & OKX. TON up 20%, speculation it will be listed after NOT. Securitize & BlackRock look to launch on ARB. Franklin Templeton calls for ‘Base season’. EIGEN claims go live today, will be un-transferable. Eclipse founder leaves after harassment claims.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To AI: Fine Tune Your Chatbot Privacy Settings]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230311</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230311/how-to-ai-chatbot-privacy-history-settings-training"/>
        <updated>2024-05-12T18:08:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Privacy is a huge concern amid the widespread deployment of artificial intelligence. Here's how you can take (some) control of your information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Crypto Games: 'Notcoin' Token Launch Date, 'Fantasy Top' Takes Over, and Rugging for Fun]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230404</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230404/this-week-crypto-games-notcoin-token-launch-date-fantasy-top-rugging-fun"/>
        <updated>2024-05-12T17:27:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Catch up on this week’s biggest crypto and NFT gaming news and find some weekend reads in our latest roundup.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week on Crypto Twitter: Fantasy Top Tops the Charts, Trump Courts Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230285</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230285/this-week-on-crypto-twitter-fantasy-top-donald-trump-crypto-election"/>
        <updated>2024-05-12T17:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tom Brady also reentered the crypto conversation, albeit likely against his will.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Bitcoin Is Boring But Bizarre Meme Coin Antics Continue]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230265</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230265/this-week-in-coins-bitcoin-boring-meme-coins-down"/>
        <updated>2024-05-11T16:49:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top cryptocurrencies Bitcoin and Ethereum are down and meme coins followed—but they at least kept things interesting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Crypto Startup Founder’s Diary]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230365</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230365/crypto-startup-founder-diary"/>
        <updated>2024-05-11T15:58:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this occasional series, Brother Bing takes us inside “MegaETH,” a company she co-founded that aims to make Ethereum more user friendly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shuyao Kong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum ETFs: Here Are All the Applications Awaiting SEC Approval]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230228</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230228/ethereum-etfs-all-applications-awaiting-sec-approval"/>
        <updated>2024-05-11T12:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many major investment firms hope to get the green light from the SEC to list spot Ethereum ETFs in the U.S. Here's the running list.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why ShapeShift Founder Erik Voorhees Is Pivoting to a Privacy-Centric AI Startup]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230281</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230281/venice-ai-shapeshift-founder-erik-voorhees-morpheus-open-source"/>
        <updated>2024-05-11T00:25:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new decentralized, open-source Venice AI tool has a less-censored premium tier that is free for Morpheus token holders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will OpenAI Let ChatGPT Make Porn? AI Maker Says It Depends]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230145</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230145/openai-chatgpt-porn-erotica-gore-depends-on-definition-of-porn"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T22:15:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[”We are not in it for creating AI deepfakes or AI porn,” a company product lead says, noting the announcement could have been “more precise.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Vitalik Buterin’s Gas Fee Proposal Make Ethereum More Like Solana?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230223</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230223/vitalik-fee-proposal-ethereum-solana"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T21:25:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ethereum co-founder is proposing some significant changes to the network’s gas fee structure. Would it make it more like its chief competitor?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Banking Giant Wells Fargo Reveals Investments in Bitcoin ETFs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230234</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230234/banking-giant-wells-fargo-reveals-investments-bitcoin-etfs"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T20:03:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wells Fargo has disclosed exposure to Bitcoin via several crypto product investments, a filing with the SEC shows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Is Approaching a Golden Cross: What Does It Mean for Traders?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230242</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230242/dogecoin-price-golden-cross-what-mean"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T19:18:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The meme-inspired cryptocurrency is showing signs of a potential bullish trend. What should traders expect?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Commencement Speaker Defends Ayahuasca-Fueled Speech, Praises Satoshi]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230222</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230222/bitcoin-commencement-speaker-defends-ayahuasca-fueled-speech-praises-satoshi"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T18:57:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From an "embarrassing" paper-hands trade in 2020 to spreading the word in a controversial speech, Christopher Pan recalls his Bitcoin journey.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lightning Labs Is Bringing Stablecoins to the Bitcoin Blockchain: CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230216</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230216/lightning-labs-stablecoins-on-bitcoin-blockchain-ceo"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T18:17:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CEO Elizabeth Stark said that Lightning Labs just ran a test transaction with an asset created using its Taproot Assets protocol.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Is Again Dictated By Fed Policy: Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230233</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230233/bitcoin-price-federal-reserve-interest-rates-alignment-coinshares"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T18:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Fed will likely cut rates later this year, which will bolster Bitcoin’s price, predicts CoinShares.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin and Ethereum Tank as Crypto Liquidations Top $150 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230199</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230199/bitcoin-and-ethereum-tank-as-crypto-liquidations-top-150-million"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T15:13:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Both Bitcoin and Ethereum plunged early Friday, prompting a wave of crypto long positions to be liquidated.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Week in Polkadot: Monthly Active Accounts Hit All-Time High]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230182</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230182/the-week-in-polkadot-monthly-active-accounts-hit-all-time-high"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T14:50:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Polkadot network reached a landmark in terms of active accounts, while the Relay Chain gets an important technical update.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will McCurdy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friend.tech Price Bounces Back 23% After Chaotic V2 Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230170</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230170/friend-tech-price-bounces-back-23-after-chaotic-v2-launch"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T13:10:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Social media platform Friend.tech endured a challenging launch last week, but its FRIEND token has shown signs of recovering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Manhattan’s Newest On-Chain Fashion Store: 9dcc]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Oyjyb2JX/inside-manhattans-newest-on-chain-fashion-store-9dcc</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Oyjyb2JX/inside-manhattans-newest-on-chain-fashion-store-9dcc"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T20:25:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At NFT NYC, Decrypt’s Sander Lutz explored the on-chain fashion brand’s latest pop-up, and spoke to its founder Gmoney about 9dcc’s future expansion plans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BTC Sinks Lower]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rUBpJmbc/btc-sinks-lower</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rUBpJmbc/btc-sinks-lower"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T19:54:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HK ETF volumes disappoint at $11M, crypto sinks. US ETFs see another $52M outflow, 4th straight day. EigenLayer FUD after 5% non-transferable airdrop. EigenLayer also geoblocks USA for claims. 5K+ withdrawals after EigenLayer announcement. Microstrategy bought another $8M BTC in April. Miner revenue drops to 2023 lows. Consensys vs SEC litigation will take years: Cowen. SEC had been investigating ETH for a year. Gensler may have misled Congress with ETH stance.KMNO hits $363M on launch. Decentralised Rune airdrop opens at $102M. Friend Tech airdrop delayed until Thursday. NFTfi airdrop claim today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Very Red Week For Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XVGCQVOH/a-very-red-week-for-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XVGCQVOH/a-very-red-week-for-crypto"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T19:54:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Majors hit locals lows, break key support levels. Liquidations hit $420M, funding remains neutral. ETFs saw $344M withdrawals in April. CZ gets 4-month jail sentence. FTX sells $232M locked SOL at ‘around $100’. Final integration of SOL Firedancer ‘well underway’. SOL, DOGE, XRP open interest down 51% in a month. BlackRock BUIDL largest tokenised treasury fund. Uniswap integrates with Robinhood connect. Stablecoin bill may be coming very soon. Gensler lied to Congress: McHenry. KSI steps back from crypto trading. Coinbase supports Lightning network. BCH creator arrested in Spain. EigenLayer sees 12K queued withdrawals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Full Send]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zCrCMabk/solana-full-send</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zCrCMabk/solana-full-send"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T19:51:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SOL leads majors higher, DEX volume flips ETH. ETH burn rate hits yearly low. BTC needs to reach $67k for a ‘higher high’. Robinhood receives Wells Notice from SEC. Only 10% of stablecoin transactions are real: Visa. May 15th will see corporate filings of BTC purchases. Hayes continues to OTC buy PENDLE. Cartier arrested for USDT money laundering. ENA up 20% on rumours of integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Memecoin Bounce]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yw5MtFvY/memecoin-bounce</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yw5MtFvY/memecoin-bounce"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T19:38:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto volatile but bounces after dovish Fed speech. ETFs see record $563m outflow. BlackRock ETF sees first outflow in 77 days. BlackRock expects more institutions to buy BTC. BNP bank buys BlackRock ETF. BTC continues to sit below STH average cost. Coinbase earnings today. Tether made $4.5bn profit in Q1. MicroStrategy building identity protocol on Ordinals. Dorsey’s Block Inc investigated in US. BlackRock leads investment in RWA firm. STX Nakamoto upgrade delayed by 8 weeks. LayerZero 1st snapshot taken ahead of airdrop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Do A Little With Mike Demarais]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ajrh0oiK/we-do-a-little-with-mike-demarais</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ajrh0oiK/we-do-a-little-with-mike-demarais"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T15:11:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mike dropped knowledge bombs from years of building in the trenches alongside some deep cuts on the early Williamsburg crypto mafia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eth Rally Fails]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Gj7TMrbP/eth-rally-fails</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Gj7TMrbP/eth-rally-fails"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T12:45:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto falls, ETH/BTC rally again marks mini sell-off. Yen carry-trade implosion linked to worries. ETH gas fees hit 6-month lows. 3rd straight week of institutional outflows. Slowing BTC ETF flows are just a pause: Bernstein. BTC now on track for 5 red weeks in a row. BTC may have topped, could hit $35k: Brandt. ETFs may become big sellers: Bianco. Consensys list 4 reasons ETH isn’t a security. Rumours continue to grow of EigenLayer airdrop. Perp DEX volumes continue fall, GMX underperforms. Wallets begin to block US users after Samourai case. WLD in reported partnership talks with OpenAI. Large unlocks this week for SUI, PYTH & MEME.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Sasha Stiles’ Experiential, AI-Infused NFT Drop with Bang & Olufsen]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/6Vi2IgYj/inside-sasha-stiles-experiential-ai-infused-nft-drop-with-bang-olufsen</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/6Vi2IgYj/inside-sasha-stiles-experiential-ai-infused-nft-drop-with-bang-olufsen"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T22:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At a launch party for the collection in New York’s SoHo neighborhood, the artist broke down her latest art experiment, “Four Core Texts,” with Decrypt’s Sander Lutz.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interview: How 'Notcoin' Will Evolve After the NOT Token Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PprnGP14/interview-how-notcoin-will-evolve-after-the-not-token-launch</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PprnGP14/interview-how-notcoin-will-evolve-after-the-not-token-launch"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Open Builders founder Sasha Plotvinov speaks with Decrypt's Sander Lutz at Token 2049 Dubai about how he envisions Notcoin's expansion and evolution after the token drop—into something akin to the "Netflix of social, viral games."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Magic Runes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IGWg0R64/magic-runes</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IGWg0R64/magic-runes"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T13:59:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC stables at $66k, liquidations in narrow range. BTC funding again turns negative in bullish sign. ETFs net inflow after Grayscale moves to lower fees. BTC demand 5x vs supply post-halving: Bitfinex. SOL congestion issue now largely solved. Two SEC lawyers resign after ‘gross abuse of power’. Ripple fights to lower $2bn SEC fine. SAFE trades at $2.8bn FDV after OKX lists. MANEKI hits $150m on first day, China memes pump. Memecoins are ‘black hole you can’t ignore’. DeGods up 20%, may switch back to SOL. Magic Eden launches Runes platform ahead of time.  Louis Vuitton gifts Pharrell jacket to NFT holders. Melania Trump launches necklace with SOL NFTs. Hoodie Punk trades for $620K.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Luxury Watches, Designer Shoes Will Soon Trade Like NFTs: Arianee CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/CSNQG2md/luxury-watches-designer-shoes-will-soon-trade-like-nfts-arianee-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/CSNQG2md/luxury-watches-designer-shoes-will-soon-trade-like-nfts-arianee-ceo"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arianee CEO Pierre-Nicolas Hurstel sat down with Rug Radio founder Farokh and Decrypt’s Sander Lutz at NFT Paris to discuss everything from the future of on-chain luxury to the secret hack to finding the best restaurants in France.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notcoin's Co-Creator Explains the Game's Token Delay—And When to Expect NOT Now]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/7Zx33xo5/notcoins-co-creator-explains-the-games-token-delayand-when-to-expect-not-now</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/7Zx33xo5/notcoins-co-creator-explains-the-games-token-delayand-when-to-expect-not-now"/>
        <updated>2024-04-22T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Notcoin co-creator Sasha Plotvinov spoke with Decrypt's Sander Lutz at Token 2049 Dubai to discuss why the NOT token launch was pushed back from the original 4/20 target, when to expect the listing, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TON’s Justin Hyun Breaks Down The Importance of USDT Coming to Telegram]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ODQI6ACA/tons-justin-hyun-breaks-down-the-importance-of-usdt-coming-to-telegram</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ODQI6ACA/tons-justin-hyun-breaks-down-the-importance-of-usdt-coming-to-telegram"/>
        <updated>2024-04-19T10:14:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Token 2049 in Dubai, The Open Network’s director of investments sat down with Decrypt’s Sander Lutz to discuss what he sees as the game-changing integration of USDT onto TON, and his plans for getting Telegram’s 900 million users to start using crypto in the immediate future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Influencer Ansem Explains His Meme Coin Thesis and Why He’s Bullish on Bitcoin Runes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/u9DHFoK0/crypto-influencer-ansem-explains-his-meme-coin-thesis-and-why-hes-bullish-on-bitcoin-runes</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/u9DHFoK0/crypto-influencer-ansem-explains-his-meme-coin-thesis-and-why-hes-bullish-on-bitcoin-runes"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T21:56:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ansem, the crypto trader who's amassed a sizable following on the back of meme coin Dogwifhat (WIF) and other calls, chats with Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz at Token 2049 Dubai about his meme coin thesis, why he's bullish on Bitcoin Runes, and what he sees ahead for the crypto markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Sander Lutz Braves the Dubai Floods for a Crypto Conference]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/mtjVHGa3/decrypts-sander-lutz-braves-the-dubai-floods-for-a-crypto-conference</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/mtjVHGa3/decrypts-sander-lutz-braves-the-dubai-floods-for-a-crypto-conference"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T21:33:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz reports from Dubai amid a historic storm that flooded the famed city, trudging through the streets to complete his essential task: Attending the Token 2049 crypto conference.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gold Beats Its All Time High]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/6ULgUKVk/gold-beats-its-all-time-high</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/6ULgUKVk/gold-beats-its-all-time-high"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T09:53:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) maintains its trend of reaching higher lows amidst choppy market conditions. Exchange-traded funds (ETFs) witness another influx of $125 million. There's anticipation of Hong Kong approving ETFs for both Bitcoin and Ethereum (ETH) come Monday. Notable institutional investor BlackRock shows interest in Bitcoin. Recent filings reveal increased Bitcoin purchases by banks. A Bitcoin-friendly political party secures victory in the South Korean election. Analyst Kang predicts Bitcoin could surge to $80-100k by May. Meanwhile, Ethereum sees accumulation by stablecoin whales on the rise. A new Ethereum Improvement Proposal (EIP) aims to streamline signing requests. Solana (SOL) experiences a resurgence in activity, reaching yearly highs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>