<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-10-28T01:01:17.255Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-10-28T01:01:17.255Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SBF Takes the Stand]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19000145/SBF-Takes-the-Stand</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19000145/SBF-Takes-the-Stand"/>
        <updated>2023-10-28T00:38:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SBF start testifying in his own defense. It .... did not go well. Today's Sponsor: KrakenKraken: See what crypto can be - https://kraken.com/TheBreakdownEnjoying this content?SUBSCRIBE to the Podcast: https://pod.link/1438693620Watch on YouTube:...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SBF Trial – Week 4 concludes with SBF telling jury he was blindsided by $8B shortfall]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19000144/SBF-Trial-Week-4-concludes-with-SBF-telling-jury-he-was-blindsided-by-8B-shortfall</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19000144/SBF-Trial-Week-4-concludes-with-SBF-telling-jury-he-was-blindsided-by-8B-shortfall"/>
        <updated>2023-10-28T00:36:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF) took the stand again on Oct. 27 — this time in front of a jury — and told the courtroom that he had been blindsided by the $8 billion shortfall that led to FTX and Alameda Research’s collapse. The former billionaire testified and went through a thorough cross-examination...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nobody Cares About Bitcoin (BTC) In The US: Google Trends]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74ae30fd08</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/nobody-cares-about-bitcoin-us-google-trends/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-28T00:35:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If Google Trends data is anything to go by, it could mean that Americans don’t care about Bitcoin (BTC) or the interest is ultra-low and falling despite the series of bullish events in the last few days. 
 
Americans Are Not Interested In Bitcoin?
 
A spot check of Google Trends over the past years shows that not only are searches related to “buy Bitcoin” discouragingly falling but are at 2023 lows, with related average daily searches scoring less than 20. The only time “buy Bitcoin” searches spiked was in early September when it rose to a score of 70, an indicator that more people were curious, willing to explore, and even buy the world’s most valuable coin.
 
 
 
 
Sentiment is a crucial factor in crypto because it can influence prices. To illustrate, when sentiment improves, crypto inve…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dalmas Ngetich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Litecoin flashes signs of a rally as traders become greedy]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19000128/Litecoin-flashes-signs-of-a-rally-as-traders-become-greedy</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19000128/Litecoin-flashes-signs-of-a-rally-as-traders-become-greedy"/>
        <updated>2023-10-28T00:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Litecoin's market value rip caused frantic activity on the network, evidenced by the jump in whale transactions and liquid supply.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHY ARE WE BULLISH? Rafael Cordon, Peter Dunworth, Portland Hodl - BITCOIN Chat]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18996849/WHY-ARE-WE-BULLISH-Rafael-Cordon-Peter-Dunworth-Portland-Hodl-BITCOIN-Chat</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18996849/WHY-ARE-WE-BULLISH-Rafael-Cordon-Peter-Dunworth-Portland-Hodl-BITCOIN-Chat"/>
        <updated>2023-10-28T00:28:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join Rafael Cordon, Peter Dunworth, and Portland Hodl for an enlightening discussion about Bitcoin! Our show explores the latest innovations, groundbreaking developments, price trends, institutional interest, cutting-edge technology, and more, all within the realm of Bitcoin. Whether you're a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Considering 8-10 Spot Bitcoin ETF Applications, Says Chair Gary Gensler]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74ae3310f8</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/sec-considering-8-10-spot-bitcoin-etf-applications-says-chair-gary-gensler/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-28T00:09:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) is currently considering between eight and 10 bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) applications, according to SEC Chairman Gary Gensler. He insisted that “the vast majority of crypto assets likely meet the investment contract test, making them subject to the securities laws.”
 
SEC Chair Gary Gensler on Spot Bitcoin ETFs
 
U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Chairman Gary Gensler said Thursday that the regulator has eight to 10 spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) applications under review. The SEC has not yet approved a spot bitcoin ETF, even though the agency has greenlighted several ETFs linked to bitcoin futures contracts.
 
Regarding bitcoin ETF decisions, the SEC chairman stated:
 

They’ll come potentially to the five-memb…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Major US Bank Refuses to Reimburse Customer After Criminal Caught on Camera Stealing Cash From Account: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19000121/Major-US-Bank-Refuses-to-Reimburse-Customer-After-Criminal-Caught-on-Camera-Stealing-Cash-From-Account-Report</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19000121/Major-US-Bank-Refuses-to-Reimburse-Customer-After-Criminal-Caught-on-Camera-Stealing-Cash-From-Account-Report"/>
        <updated>2023-10-28T00:04:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the biggest banks in the US reportedly refused to reimburse a customer despite security footage showing a criminal stealing cash from an ATM. Then, the media got involved. Berkeley resident and Bank of America customer Kyle Fischer says he recently noticed money had mysteriously vanished...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nobody Cares About Bitcoin (BTC) In The US: Google Trends]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19000119/Nobody-Cares-About-Bitcoin-BTC-In-The-US-Google-Trends</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19000119/Nobody-Cares-About-Bitcoin-BTC-In-The-US-Google-Trends"/>
        <updated>2023-10-28T00:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If Google Trends data is anything to go by, it could mean that Americans don’t care about Bitcoin (BTC) or the interest is ultra-low and falling despite the series of bullish events in the last few days. Americans Are Not Interested In Bitcoin? A spot check of Google Trends over the past years...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hidden Signals: Bitcoin’s On-Chain Data Points To Bullish Outlook, But There’s A Catch]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19000110/The-Hidden-Signals-Bitcoins-On-Chain-Data-Points-To-Bullish-Outlook-But-Theres-A-Catch</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19000110/The-Hidden-Signals-Bitcoins-On-Chain-Data-Points-To-Bullish-Outlook-But-Theres-A-Catch"/>
        <updated>2023-10-28T00:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RFK Jr: Bitcoin is Freedom Currency #bitcoin #crypto #shorts]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19000127/RFK-Jr-Bitcoin-is-Freedom-Currency-bitcoin-crypto-shorts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19000127/RFK-Jr-Bitcoin-is-Freedom-Currency-bitcoin-crypto-shorts"/>
        <updated>2023-10-28T00:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RFK Jr is on point. He knows that it's either Bitcoin or death!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pepe, Polygon, Fantom and Six Other Altcoin Rallies Could Continue, Says Analytics Firm Santiment – Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19000112/Pepe-Polygon-Fantom-and-Six-Other-Altcoin-Rallies-Could-Continue-Says-Analytics-Firm-Santiment-Heres-Why</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19000112/Pepe-Polygon-Fantom-and-Six-Other-Altcoin-Rallies-Could-Continue-Says-Analytics-Firm-Santiment-Heres-Why"/>
        <updated>2023-10-28T00:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A prominent market intelligence platform says that a handful of altcoins should continue to rally as traders continue to focus on Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH). In a new thread on the social media platform X, crypto analytics firm Santiment says that nine altcoins – including Polygon (MATIC),...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kieran Warwick Co-Founder of Illuvium, Do You Even Crypto?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19000117/Kieran-Warwick-Co-Founder-of-Illuvium-Do-You-Even-Crypto</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19000117/Kieran-Warwick-Co-Founder-of-Illuvium-Do-You-Even-Crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-10-28T00:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s Fifth Bull Market Started and Could Take BTC’s Price to $125,000 by 2024, Matrixport Report Says]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19000120/Bitcoins-Fifth-Bull-Market-Started-and-Could-Take-BTCs-Price-to-125000-by-2024-Matrixport-Report-Says</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19000120/Bitcoins-Fifth-Bull-Market-Started-and-Could-Take-BTCs-Price-to-125000-by-2024-Matrixport-Report-Says"/>
        <updated>2023-10-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken To Suspend All USDT, WBTC Deposits In Canada]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19000098/Kraken-To-Suspend-All-USDT-WBTC-Deposits-In-Canada</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19000098/Kraken-To-Suspend-All-USDT-WBTC-Deposits-In-Canada"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T23:40:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken is the next major Canadian exchange to wind down support for stablecoins amid regulatory pressure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meme Coins Are Dominating Once Again, Here Are The Winners]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74ae3e0489</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/meme-coins-winners/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T23:34:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meme coins have been showing their prowess once again with incredible gains. These meme coins were initially slow to the party but have picked up the pace quite nicely since then. In the last two days, meme coin gains have dominated the market, making them some of the top gainers at the time. Here is a list of the top meme coins that have done incredibly well so far.
 
Floki Inu (FLOKI) Takes The Lead With Meme Coins
 
When the crypto market rally first began, the price of Floki Inu (FLOKI) had stalled just like the rest of the meme coins. In what seemed to be an out-of-character rally for the crypto market, FLOKI was nowhere to be found; that is, until Thursday.
 
 
On Thursday, FlOKI had broken out of a range that it had been trading in and went on a green spree. The result of this rally…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Best Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI and ICE: U.S. Immigration Scans Social Media Before Approving Visas]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203545</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203545/ai-immigration-ice-social-media-scan-threat-level"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T23:06:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence speeds the process of reviewing online posts by people seeking to enter the country, sparking debate over privacy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI and ICE: U.S. Immigration Scans Social Media Before Approving Visas]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19000082/AI-and-ICE-US-Immigration-Scans-Social-Media-Before-Approving-Visas</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19000082/AI-and-ICE-US-Immigration-Scans-Social-Media-Before-Approving-Visas"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T23:06:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence speeds the process of reviewing online posts by people seeking to enter the country, sparking debate over privacy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meme Coins Are Dominating Once Again, Here Are The Winners]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19000071/Meme-Coins-Are-Dominating-Once-Again-Here-Are-The-Winners</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19000071/Meme-Coins-Are-Dominating-Once-Again-Here-Are-The-Winners"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T23:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meme coins have been showing their prowess once again with incredible gains. These meme coins were initially slow to the party but have picked up the pace quite nicely since then. In the last two days, meme coin gains have dominated the market, making them some of the top gainers at the time. Here is […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Doubles Down with $2 Billion Investment in Claude AI Developer Anthropic]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203563</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203563/google-follows-400-million-dollar-investment-in-anthropic-with-2-billion"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T22:59:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amid a high-stakes rivalry with Microsoft, Google is beating big on the OpenAI rival.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Doubles Down with $2 Billion Investment in Claude AI Developer Anthropic]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19000072/Google-Doubles-Down-with-2-Billion-Investment-in-Claude-AI-Developer-Anthropic</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19000072/Google-Doubles-Down-with-2-Billion-Investment-in-Claude-AI-Developer-Anthropic"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T22:59:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amid a high-stakes rivalry with Microsoft, Google is beating big on the OpenAI rival.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$XRP Price Could Surpass $100 and Has ‘No Ceiling’, Says Early Ethereum Advisor]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19000061/XRP-Price-Could-Surpass-100-and-Has-No-Ceiling-Says-Early-Ethereum-Advisor</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19000061/XRP-Price-Could-Surpass-100-and-Has-No-Ceiling-Says-Early-Ethereum-Advisor"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T22:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JPMorgan Settles Transactions for $1 Billion Daily Using JPM Coin]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74ae3b0bfc</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/jpmorgan-settles-transactions-for-1-billion-daily-using-jpm-coin/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T22:38:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JPMorgan announced that it is registering transactions for $1 billion daily using its own currency, jpm coin. JPMorgan Global Head of Payments Takis Georgakopoulos added that while these movements are denominated in U.S. dollars mostly, the institution is seeking to expand on that in the future.
JPMorgan’s JPM Coin Sees $1 Billion in Movements Daily
JPMorgan has reported that jpm coin, the cryptocurrency created by the financial giant, is being used to settle $1 billion daily. According to statements from JPMorgan’s Global Head of Payments Takis Georgakopoulos, the bank plans to expand on jpm coin’s usage in the future, widening adoption.
In an recent interview with Bloomberg, Georgakopoulos stated:
JPM Coin gets transacted on a daily basis mostly in US dollars, but we again intend to cont…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF Breakthrough: First-Ever BTC Spot ETF Set To Launch In Just 75 Days, Analyst Says]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74ae3b6c20</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-etf-first-ever-set-to-launch-just-75-days/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T22:34:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cryptocurrency industry is abuzz with excitement and speculation as the long-awaited approval of the first-ever Bitcoin spot exchange-traded fund (ETF) in the United States draws closer. 
 
With the potential to significantly impact BTC’s price and market capitalization, industry experts and enthusiasts eagerly await the decision of the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).
 
Bitcoin ETF Approval Nears?
 
Amidst the anticipation, predictions have emerged regarding the timing of this development, which could reshape the landscape for institutional investors seeking exposure to the world’s leading cryptocurrency. 
 
 
Notably, prominent crypto YouTuber “Crypto Rover” recently stated that the first Bitcoin ETF will be launched within 75 days, and provided insights on the factors be…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hester Peirce objects to SEC’s handling of LBRY case]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19000048/Hester-Peirce-objects-to-SECs-handling-of-LBRY-case</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19000048/Hester-Peirce-objects-to-SECs-handling-of-LBRY-case"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T22:30:41.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried Says He Wanted to Sell FTX to Binance Since It Was Founded]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203544</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203544/sam-bankman-fried-always-planned-to-sell-ftx-to-binance"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T22:26:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The disgraced crypto founder testified that he built FTX to serve a niche that would make it an acquisition target of Binance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried Says He Wanted to Sell FTX to Binance Since It Was Founded]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19000049/Sam-Bankman-Fried-Says-He-Wanted-to-Sell-FTX-to-Binance-Since-It-Was-Founded</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19000049/Sam-Bankman-Fried-Says-He-Wanted-to-Sell-FTX-to-Binance-Since-It-Was-Founded"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T22:26:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The disgraced crypto founder testified that he built FTX to serve a niche that would make it an acquisition target of Binance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried Rebuffed Barry Silbert's and Celsius' Requests for Help, Ex-FTX CEO Testifies at His Trial]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74ae244be5</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/10/27/sam-bankman-fried-rebuffed-barry-silberts-and-celsius-requests-for-help-ex-ftx-ceo-testifies-at-his-trial/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T22:25:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto mogul served as a white knight for other struggling companies, though, before his empire fell, too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Napolitano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bridging protocols express ‘concern’ over LayerZero’s wstETH token integration]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19000032/Bridging-protocols-express-concern-over-LayerZeros-wstETH-token-integration</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19000032/Bridging-protocols-express-concern-over-LayerZeros-wstETH-token-integration"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T22:13:27.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried Speaks Out: Admits Mistakes as FTX's CEO]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74ae2699d6</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/sam-bankman-fried-speaks-out-admits-mistakes-as-ftxs-ceo/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T22:01:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF) faced the jury yesterday (Friday) and acknowledged the widespread fallout when the cryptocurrency  
exchange FTX, which he co-founded, crumbled. 
BBC reported that the 31-year-old entrepreneur,  
accused of deceiving investors and embezzling customer funds, opened up about  
his actions and decisions that led to this point. "A lot of people got  
hurt, customers, employees, and the company ended up in bankruptcy," he  
added.
Throughout his testimony at the Manhattan federal  
court, SBF admitted to making a series of errors, both minor and significant,  
while managing the now-defunct exchange. He identified the absence of a  
dedicated risk management team as one of his most critical oversights.
Sam Bankman-Fried Maintains His Innocence
Despite the allegations aga…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Has a Huge Week As Elon Musk Aims for X Financial Services To Launch by End of 2024: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19000018/Dogecoin-Has-a-Huge-Week-As-Elon-Musk-Aims-for-X-Financial-Services-To-Launch-by-End-of-2024-Report</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19000018/Dogecoin-Has-a-Huge-Week-As-Elon-Musk-Aims-for-X-Financial-Services-To-Launch-by-End-of-2024-Report"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T22:01:24.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gemini Files Lawsuit Against Genesis Over Disputed $1.6 Billion Bitcoin Trust Shares]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74ae2163df</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/gemini-lawsuit-genesis-1-billion-bitcoin-shares/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T21:34:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent development, crypto exchange Gemini has filed a lawsuit against the crypto platform Genesis Global about the ownership of shares in the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC). 
 
Per the lawsuit, the exchange is seeking a determination from a federal judge to establish that Genesis has no right to over 60 million GBTC shares pledged as collateral for loans made by its users. Gemini argues that these shares should not be used to repay other creditors of Genesis.
 
Gemini Seeks Court Determination To Secure Over 60 Million GBTC Shares
 
According to the lawsuit filed on Friday, October 27, 2023, the exchange entered into a security agreement with Genesis. Genesis allegedly promised to deliver 62,086,586 GBTC shares in two tranches as collateral to secure loans made by Gemini users. 
 
 
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum’s Dencun Upgrade Faces Setback — Delay Amid Testing Requirements]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74ae2c3fa3</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ethereums-dencun-upgrade-faces-setback-delay-amid-testing-requirements/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T21:07:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The highly anticipated Dencun upgrade for the Ethereum blockchain won’t be making its debut in 2023 as initially expected. Ethereum’s core developers have decided to push back the upgrade’s release until at least 2024, a revelation made during the latest All Core Developers meeting. After the meeting, software developer Tim Beiko took to social media to provide an update on the expected timeline for the upgrade.
 
Ethereum’s Dencun Upgrade: Mainnet Release Now Anticipated in 2024
 
The primary objective of the Dencun upgrade is to elevate Ethereum’s performance on multiple fronts, including scalability, security, and user-friendliness. One of its key features is the introduction of “data blobs,” a novel transaction type designed to optimize data storage and accessibility for layer two (L2)…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FCA: Bitfinex May Be Promoting Financial Services "Without Our Permission"]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74ae2caf68</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/fca-bitfinex-may-be-promoting-financial-services-without-our-permission/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T21:03:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitfinex has recently come under scrutiny. The  
Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) raised concerns about the cryptocurrency  
exchange today (Friday), warning investors of potential risks associated with it.  
The regulator stated that Bitfinex may be promoting financial services or  
products without its permission. 
Finance Magnates contacted Bitfinex for comments. However, at the time of this publication, a representative from the company had not responded to the inquiry. 
"If you deal with this firm, you won't have  
access to the Financial Ombudsman Service if you have a complaint," the  
financial watchdog cautioned. "You also won't be protected by the  
Financial Services Compensation Scheme if things go wrong."
FCA Identifies Critical Crypto Marketing Issues
In the official stateme…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Korea’s Crypto Shift: 6 Million Investors Rally Behind Altcoins Over Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74ae281b63</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/south-koreas-crypto-shift-million-investors-rally/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T20:32:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to a recent report from Web3 market strategy consulting firm DeSpread report, the Korean crypto space will be populated by roughly 6 million investors, comprising more than 10% of the entire population.
 
Centralized Exchanges (CEX) appear to be the choice for most of these enthusiasts, according to the report. This massive influx of investors indicates a growing trust and interest in crypto, making South Korea a crucial player in global digital finance.
 
 
Dominance Of Korean Crypto-Centralized Exchanges
 
Against the backdrop of a worldwide slump in crypto trading volumes, Korean Centralized Exchanges (CEXs) tell a different story. Four pivotal players, Upbit, Bithumb, Coinone, and Korbit, seem to be driving this momentum, together accounting for 10% of the global trading volu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Financial Freedom And The Fight Against Censorship]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74ae2b476f</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/financial-freedom-and-the-fight-against-censorship"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T20:04:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The atmosphere at Bitcoin Amsterdam, organised by Bitcoin Magazine, starkly contrasted with the real guts and heart of the movement headlined by Edward Snowden and Stella Assange, both lives have been profoundly impacted by the struggle against censorship. This isn't to diminish the buzzing hope and optimism of the conference with over 2,000 attendees, rather, it amplified the urgency and gravitas that these key figures bring to the broader conversation on financial and informational freedom.
Hosted in the culturally vibrant Westerpark, a historic gas factory turned into an artistic hub, the conference was a masterstroke of planning and technology. 
The tone for the event was set by an initial panel discussion questioning the readiness of Bitcoin to meet global financial challenges. This l…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Susie Ward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Girlfriend Amouranth Wants to Use Her 'Vaginal Yeast' to Brew Beer]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203517</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203517/ai-girlfriend-amouranth-vaginal-yeast-brew-beer"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T19:39:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From digital darling to brew enthusiast, Amouranth introduces a beer that's bound to raise eyebrows and glasses alike.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dydx Chain Unveils Network Fee Distribution and USDC Trading Fee Allocation]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74ae16532b</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/dydx-chain-unveils-network-fee-distribution-and-usdc-trading-fee-allocation/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T19:36:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Dydx chain, a proof-of-stake blockchain network, has successfully launched its mainnet and introduced dydx as its layer one (L1) token. On October 26, at 1 p.m. EDT, the network’s validators created the first block, signifying the start of a new era for the Dydx chain. The introduction of dydx as the L1 token brings with it enhanced utility, including the distribution of network fees to validators and stakers, and the allocation of trading fees to stakers in the USDC stablecoin.
 
Dydx Chain’s Mainnet Goes Live, Introducing Dydx as Integral L1 Token
 
Located in Zug, Switzerland, the Dydx Foundation oversees the Dydx chain, ensuring a secure and efficient operation of the network. Utilizing the Cosmos SDK and leveraging CometBFT for consensus, the Dydx network requires validators to st…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nigerian Crypto Twitter Up In Arms As Prominent Influencer Rug Pulls STIMMY Coin]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74ae16fb36</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/nigerian-crypto-rug-pull-stimmy/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T19:31:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unfortunately, rug pulls have become synonymous with the crypto market as scammers see it as an opportunity to make quick cash. One such rug pulls has hit the Nigerian crypto X (formerly Twitter) community, where what is assumed to be one of the most trusted influencers rug-pulled a project that raised $300,000 in its presale.
 
The Genesis Of Stimmy Coin (STIMMY)
 
Surfing through the X (formerly Twitter) posts related to the Stimmy Coin, it looks to be that the coin was created as a parody of the stimulus checks received by United States residents during the COVID-19 lockdowns.
 
 
The coin seemed to gain popularity quickly due to the founder being widely known in the Nigerian crypto community. The founder Feyi, whose X (formerly Twitter) account @feyi_x has over 84,000 followers, was ab…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shutterstock Integrates AI Into Its Library of 700 Million Images]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203436</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203436/ai-generated-stock-photos-shutterstock-700-million-images"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T19:20:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shutterstock joins Getty Images and Canva in introducing creator-friendly AI art generators.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chainlink Jumps 6% While Bitcoin and Ethereum Hold Steady]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203502</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203502/chainlink-jumps-6-while-bitcoin-and-ethereum-hold-steady"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T19:17:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The main cause of Bitcoin’s soaring price: Mounting hype and certainty among investors that the SEC will soon approve a spot Bitcoin ETF.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried Started Buying Solana's SOL at 20 Cents Using 'Alameda Profits,' He Says at His Trial]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74ae12570b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/10/27/sam-bankman-fried-started-buying-solanas-sol-at-20-cents-using-alameda-profits-he-says-at-his-trial/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T19:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["I believed the funds came from Alameda’s operating profits" as well as third-party lenders, he testified Friday at his fraud and conspiracy trial.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Chainlink Moons 44%, Leads Marketwide ETF Speculation Rally]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203515</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203515/this-week-in-coins-bitcoin-ethereum-chainlink-price"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T18:54:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin and other leading coins have now been rallying for a fortnight.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin's 14% Weekly Gain Signals 'End of an Era' as Big Tech Dumps, Analyst Says]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74ae1c9809</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/10/27/bitcoins-14-weekly-gain-signals-end-of-an-era-as-big-tech-dumps-analyst-says/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T18:44:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin's advance this week coupled with gains across all digital asset sectors, highlighting the breadth of the crypto rally.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gemini Sues Genesis for Control of $1.6 Billion in Grayscale Bitcoin Trust Shares]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203506</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203506/gemini-genesis-lawsuit-grayscale-bitcoin-gbtc"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T18:38:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Genesis-Gemini saga continues, with a new twist.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Urges Crypto Asset Firms To Intensify Efforts Against Illicit Financing]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74ae1e6f8c</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/us-urges-crypto-asset-firms-to-intensify-efforts/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T18:30:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amid the ongoing global crackdown on financial crimes and terrorism funding, the US government recently highlighted concerns regarding the alleged inadequate efforts of some companies operating in the crypto asset space.
 
The US government particularly points to the potential role of digital assets in facilitating illicit financial transactions, urging companies to take proactive steps in curbing such activities.
 
 
Illicit Finance In The Digital Realm? 
 
While addressing an audience in London, US Deputy Treasury Secretary Wally Adeyemo emphasized that most financial institutions share an interest in eliminating terrorist financing. This collaborative spirit, however, doesn’t spread to “all sectors equally.”
 
Adeyemo pointedly noted concerns regarding certain players in the digital ass…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken Warns Users: Your Bitcoin Trading Data Is Headed to the IRS]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203507</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203507/kraken-warns-users-bitcoin-trading-data-irs"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T18:13:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken sent an email to customers on Wednesday to let them know it plans to share data on crypto trades of more than $20,000 by November.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Market Expert Gareth Soloway Explores Bitcoin’s Future Amidst Rising Treasury Yields and ETF Speculation]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74ae19b9db</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/market-expert-gareth-soloway-explores-bitcoins-future-amidst-rising-treasury-yields-and-etf-speculation/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T18:04:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Year-to-date, bitcoin (BTC), the leading digital currency by market cap, has witnessed a staggering increase of over 100%, sparking curiosity about the duration of its upward trajectory. In a Thursday interview with Gareth Soloway, the head market strategist at inthemoneystocks.com, the expert delved into the potential longevity of this rally. Soloway also touched upon the upcoming gathering of the U.S. Federal Reserve and the ascent of 10-year treasury yields to a pinnacle unmatched in the last 16 years.
 
Bitcoin’s Longevity Examined by Market Strategist Gareth Soloway; Anticipates Gold Surge
 

 
On a Thursday marked by a downturn in U.S. equities, resulting in a sea of red across the stock market, precious metals, and the crypto markets stood resilient, weathering the storm with grace.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken Bolsters UK Presence with Appointment of New Managing Director]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74ae1af21d</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/kraken-bolsters-uk-presence-with-the-appointment-of-new-managing-director/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T17:55:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken has appointed Bivu Das as the Managing  
Director for the UK. He brings nearly two decades of experience in commercial  
enterprise and fintech strategy development to his new role. His appointment  
happens when the cryptocurrency exchange is expanding its services in the  
region. 
Before joining Kraken, Das co-founded a crypto  
startup that focused on creating an accessible payment gateway for users to  
enter and exit the digital asset ecosystem. His expertise also extends to  
navigating hyper-growth stages at Starling Bank, a popular neobank. 
Kraken Expands Workforce in the UK
Das said: "Kraken has long advocated for the  
potential crypto assets have to transform how everyday people interact with  
financial services. There are millions of people in the  
UK, as well as glo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Price Forecast: Can DOGE Breach $0.1 Barrier Amid Meme Coin Surge?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74ae06a7a1</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-price-forecast-can-doge-breach-0-1/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T17:28:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin (DOGE) is riding the bullish wave once again, experiencing a substantial rally with double-digit gains. Notably, selected tokens such as Pepe Coin and Floki Inu have also joined the meme coin rally, surging by double digits within a week. 
 
Market analysts and enthusiasts are attributing this surge to the ongoing excitement surrounding exchange-traded funds (ETFs), and the price momentum shows no signs of slowing down.
 
Kaiko, a prominent figure in the crypto market, was quick to draw attention to the impressive price hikes in the meme coin sector. Pepe Coin and Floki Inu, along with Dogecoin, have been leading this charge. The excitement surrounding these meme coins has created a positive atmosphere in the crypto sphere. 
 
 
$AVAX and $DOGE are up 10% while $AAVE is down .25% …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Lido Finance, Ethereum's Largest Liquid Staking Project?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202774</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-lido-finance-ethereums-largest-liquid-staking-project"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T14:57:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lido Finance has long held the lion’s share of the liquid staking market on Ethereum, but what is it and how does it work?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SBF Trial Live Updates: Sam Bankman-Fried Wanted to Sell FTX]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=199892</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/199892/trial-sam-bankman-fried-live-blog-latest-news-insights"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T14:18:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried faces seven criminal charges related to the dramatic collapse of his crypto empire. Here's the latest on his trial.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New dYdX Chain Denominates Trading Fees in USDC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203480</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203480/new-dydx-chain-denominate-trading-fees-usdc"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T13:57:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stakers and validators will also earn all of the newly launched chain's fees for helping to secure the dYdX Chain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto ‘Not the Vast Majority’ of Terrorism Funding, Says US Treasury Deputy Secretary]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203481</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203481/crypto-not-the-vast-majority-terrorism-funding-says-us-treasury-deputy-secretary"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T12:59:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin is just a natural next step to fund illicit activities, coming after PayPal and the traditional banking system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov,Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LayerZero Hit With Hefty Backlash After ‘Frontrunning’ Lido Governance]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203475</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203475/layerzero-hit-with-hefty-backlash-after-frontrunning-lido-governance"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T11:38:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LayerZero announced a new integration to the rejoice of three different blockchains and the chagrin of one DeFi project in particular.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Must Be 'Harnessed Responsibly' to Curtail Doomsday Scenarios, Says UN Secretary-General]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203473</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203473/ai-must-be-harnessed-responsibly-curtail-doomsday-scenarios-says-un-secretary-general"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T10:29:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While AI may offer key opportunities, the UN is concerned that just "a handful of companies and countries" will have expertise with the tech.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Invisible Ink: Researchers Probe the Weaknesses of Watermarking AI-Generated Content]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203455</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203455/disadvantages-of-watermarking-ai-generated-images"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T03:30:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New research suggests watermarking may not be enough to ensure that we can identify deepfakes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Inside of Mars Is ‘Surprisingly Soft’, A New Survey Says]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203456</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203456/northwestern-study-probes-deep-into-the-red-planets-core"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T03:03:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NASA's InSight rover has been collecting seismic data on Mars for three years, offering a snapshot of the planet's internal structure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried Testifies During Special Hearing—After The Jury Is Sent Home]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203450</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203450/sam-bankman-fried-testifies-during-special-hearing-after-the-jury-is-sent-home"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T23:55:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The former CEO of the failed FTX exchange took the stand for an audience of one, so Judge Lewis Kaplan could vet the admissibility of his statements.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bitcoin ETF Could Soon Finally Launch. What If It Flops?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203441</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203441/bitcoin-etf-launch-flop-market-demand"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T22:40:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin hopefuls are crossing their fingers for the approval of a spot crypto ETF. But will demand match the hype?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ryder Ripps Must Pay Yuga Labs $1.5 Million for Bored Ape Trademark Infringement]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203445</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203445/ryder-ripps-must-pay-yuga-labs-1-5-million-for-bored-ape-copyright-infringement"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T22:39:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A U.S. District Judge orders Ryder Ripps and Jeremy Cahen to cease all NFT sales and relinquish its blockchain assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Senator Urges ‘Swift Action’ Against Binance, Tether for Links to Terrorist Groups]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203416</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203416/us-lawmakers-urge-doj-to-choke-off-terrorist-funding-by-targeting-binance-and-tether"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T20:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bipartisan letter comes after lawmakers flagged the use of crypto in terrorism to the Biden Administration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Future Fashion Summit Connects Luxury Houses, Digital Platforms in Paris]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203414</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203414/future-fashion-summit-connects-luxury-houses-digital-platforms-in-paris"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T19:52:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“There’s definitely a shift happening from mobile devices to wearables,” said Snapchat’s global head of luxury.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephanie Hirschmiller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain Will Be ‘Standard’ for Gaming in Asia: Bandai Namco Exec]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203391</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203391/blockchain-will-be-standard-in-gaming-in-asia"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T18:36:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Asia, says the game publisher's SVP of corporate development, Web3 doesn't have the that stigma it does in the West.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[God Mode: 7 Twisted 'Thomas the Tank Engine' Game Mods—From Starfield to Skyrim]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203333</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203333/god-mode-7-twisted-thomas-tank-engine-game-mods-starfield-skyrim"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T15:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thomas the Tank Engine isn't in Grand Theft Auto V, Elden Ring, or Starfield—unless you want him to be. Check out these must-play mods.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Frederiksen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New UK Bill Strengthens Authorities Ability to Seize Illicit Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203380</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203380/uk-bill-strengthens-authorities-ability-seize-illicit-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T15:27:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bill's passing means police will have a more leeway when it comes to seizing cryptocurrencies involved in crimes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More Tokens Than Ever Are Being Staked, Says New Research]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203356</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203356/more-tokens-than-ever-are-being-staked-says-new-research"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T13:34:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aptos and SUI were the most staked networks by the percentage of circulating supply that had been locked in, new research revealed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trezor Safe 3 Review: A Hardware Wallet for Bitcoin Newcomers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202808</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202808/trezor-safe-3-review-hardware-wallet-bitcoin-newcomers"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T12:50:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest addition to Trezor’s lineup is aimed at “new entrants to crypto.” Does it make getting started simple?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Memecoin Madness: PEPE, Dogecoin and SHIB Surge Amid Crypto Rally]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203348</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203348/memecoin-madness-pepe-dogecoin-shib-ride-crypto-rally"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T11:26:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The memecoins haven't been forgotten in the latest rally, with PEPE, DOGE, and SHIB all soaring double-digits over the week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI-Generated Child Abuse Material Could ‘Overwhelm’ the Internet, UK Group Warns]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203327</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203327/ai-child-sexual-abuse-material-overwhelm-web-uk-internet-watch"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T02:48:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Internet Watch Foundation says over 20,000 AI-generated images were found on a single darkweb forum in just one month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Takes on AI Rivals With Child-Friendly Alexa Features]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203313</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203313/amazon-takes-on-ai-rivals-with-child-friendly-alexa-features"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T23:32:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon's Alexa now offers Explore with Alexa, a feature that gives kids personalized and trusted educational responses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I’m Finally Getting Some Opposition On My Bitcoin Bill', Says Mexican Senator]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203312</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203312/mexico-senator-indira-kempis-bitcoin-cbdc-bill"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T23:11:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Indira Kempis has been leading the legislative conversation towards establishing Bitcoin as legal tender in Mexico.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tech Titans Microsoft and Google Make AI Moves Down Under]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203305</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203305/tech-titans-microsoft-and-google-set-their-sights-down-under"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T21:10:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While the appeal of a largely untapped market is clear, some say the move could also reflect a regulatory chill in the U.S.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are You Playing Starfield? Over 11 Million Gamers Are, Says Microsoft CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203299</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203299/starfield-11-million-players-best-selling-game-microsoft"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T19:27:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first new universe for Bethesda in 25 years was the top-selling video game last month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stocks Are Down, Bitcoin Is Way Up—Will This Time Be Different?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203287</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203287/stocks-are-down-bitcoin-is-way-up-will-this-time-be-different"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T18:49:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF hype can explain a lot about why BTC appears to have decoupled from stocks. But analysts say that's not the only reason.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Selling the Pump? Estate Moves $8.6M Ethereum, Chainlink, Aave and Maker to Binance]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203262</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203262/ftx-moves-8-6-million-ethereum-chainlink-aave-maker-to-binance"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T16:58:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The funds are on the move again—this time to the collapsed exchange’s rival]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amanda Cassatt on Web3 Marketing and the early days of Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5Cm0ENyc/amanda-cassatt-on-web3-marketing-and-the-early-days-of-ethereum</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5Cm0ENyc/amanda-cassatt-on-web3-marketing-and-the-early-days-of-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T16:40:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week's episode, our host is joined by Amanda Cassatt! 

Amanda is the founder of Serotonin, a web3 marketing agency, the author of the first book ever published on web3 marketing, and led the marketing team that helped bring Ethereum to market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Hits $35,000, Reaching 16-Month High Amid ETF Hype]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203274</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203274/bitcoin-hits-35000-reaching-16-month-high-amid-spot-etf-hype"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T16:36:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin continues its climb amid speculation of an imminent ETF approval, this time breaching a key milestone not seen since May 2022.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Parallel' Game Adds Over 120 New NFT Cards in Planetfall Expansion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203199</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203199/parallel-game-adds-over-120-new-nft-cards-planetfall-expansion"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T15:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Parallel is releasing new cards for its game via blind bundles. While little is known about the cards so far, some new art has been revealed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Midnight Society's Rob Bowling on Deadrop's New Cars and User-Generated Modes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/A0auyZzn/midnight-societys-rob-bowling-on-deadrops-new-cars-and-user-generated-modes</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/A0auyZzn/midnight-societys-rob-bowling-on-deadrops-new-cars-and-user-generated-modes"/>
        <updated>2023-10-22T01:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt reporter and GG producer Kate Irwin interviews Midnight Society Studio Head Rob Bowling about Deadrop's development and Snapshot VII.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Game Review: 'Raini: The Lords of Light' Brands Itself With Memes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/32YyJHCJ/game-review-raini-the-lords-of-light-brands-itself-with-memes</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/32YyJHCJ/game-review-raini-the-lords-of-light-brands-itself-with-memes"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T19:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Raini: Lords of Light is an NFT-optional card game bursting with crypto memes. From SBF to CZ and Elon, this free-to-play game has some truly wild animations. Decrypt contributor Ryan S. Gladwin shares his honest thoughts on the game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Art Blocks Marfa Weekend Recap]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/QaTBP6eO/art-blocks-marfa-weekend-recap</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/QaTBP6eO/art-blocks-marfa-weekend-recap"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T19:19:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Relive the Art Blocks Marfa Weekend 2023 event with this highlights video, produced by Vincent Roazzi Jr. for Decrypt Studios in partnership with Art Blocks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Phantom Galaxies: A Look Inside the Mech Shooter NFT Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QI1uDwQv/phantom-galaxies-a-look-inside-the-mech-shooter-nft-game</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QI1uDwQv/phantom-galaxies-a-look-inside-the-mech-shooter-nft-game"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T21:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animoca Brands and game studio Blowfish are developing Phantom Galaxies, an upcoming sci-fi mech shooter game inspired by mech battlers like Transformers. Decrypt's Kate Irwin asks Blowfish Studios Cofounder and Managing Director Ben Lee about what it's like to play the game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Clip: DeepMedia's DeepID Deepfake Detection Tool at Work]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/m4Vy4vhC/clip-deepmedias-deepid-deepfake-detection-tool-at-work</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/m4Vy4vhC/clip-deepmedias-deepid-deepfake-detection-tool-at-work"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T16:48:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A clip showcasing how DeepMedia's DeepID deepfake detection tool works. Courtesy: DeepMedia]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentraland AI World Fair Trailer]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/3tUb56Fv/decentraland-ai-world-fair-trailer</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/3tUb56Fv/decentraland-ai-world-fair-trailer"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A trailer for the AI World Fair event in metaverse game Decentraland, taking place from October 25-27. Courtesy: Decentraland.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BackTheBunny - Money, Conspiracy, Milady]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BRoKZzer/backthebunny-money-conspiracy-milady</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BRoKZzer/backthebunny-money-conspiracy-milady"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T19:48:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our host Reza Jafery sits down with BackTheBunny to dive deep into money, the fight against crypto that we're witnessing in real-time, and milady culture. 

Our Host: https://twitter.com/rezajafery
Our Guest: https://twitter.com/BackTheBunny

Our Sponsors
https://decrypt.co/1000x]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['A Grand Experiment': Shrapnel Studio Head Don Norbury Talks Game Economics]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Z2OMMsC5/a-grand-experiment-shrapnel-studio-head-don-norbury-talks-game-economics</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Z2OMMsC5/a-grand-experiment-shrapnel-studio-head-don-norbury-talks-game-economics"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T17:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How much of Shrapnel's in-game items are tradeable NFTs? Don Norbury, Studio Head at Shrapnel and CTO at game studio NEON, tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about Shrapnel's approach to game economics, including different game pricing models and how NFT game economies create different challenges for developers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trezor Safe 3 and Trezor Keep Metal Unboxing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/IjqnO9pR/trezor-safe-3-and-trezor-keep-metal-unboxing</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/IjqnO9pR/trezor-safe-3-and-trezor-keep-metal-unboxing"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T14:45:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trezor has launched the Safe 3, a hardware wallet aimed at "new entrants to crypto," alongside the new Keep Metal recovery seed storage device. We take a first look at what comes in the box.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why AI Arena is Building on Arbitrum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Gl80TQOm/why-ai-arena-is-building-on-arbitrum</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Gl80TQOm/why-ai-arena-is-building-on-arbitrum"/>
        <updated>2023-10-12T14:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI Arena CEO Brandon Da Silva and COO Wei Xie discuss the challenges that come with building on Ethereum, ETH sidechains, and layer-two blockchains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pet3rPan_ on venture DAOs and blockchain games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DawNLI3O/pet3rpan-on-venture-daos-and-blockchain-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DawNLI3O/pet3rpan-on-venture-daos-and-blockchain-games"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T18:24:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the 4th episode of this time will be different.

Our guest for today's episode is Pet3rpan_ from Metacartel, 1kx, HydraVentures, and more!

https://twitter.com/pet3rpan_

This Time Will Be Different is sponsored by 1000x
https://decrypt.co/1000x]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Shrapnel's Marketplace, New Map, and 'AI Director' Feature]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/F5RQCmvH/inside-shrapnels-marketplace-new-map-and-ai-director-feature</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/F5RQCmvH/inside-shrapnels-marketplace-new-map-and-ai-director-feature"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T16:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin chats with Shrapnel's Head of Studio Don Norbury to get the latest updates on how the NFT-powered first-person sci-fi extraction shooter's development is progressing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Art of the Times': Art Blocks Founder Erick Calderon on the State of Generative Art]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zSjfRrl5/art-of-the-times-art-blocks-founder-erick-calderon-on-the-state-of-generative-art</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zSjfRrl5/art-of-the-times-art-blocks-founder-erick-calderon-on-the-state-of-generative-art"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T18:10:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Art Blocks founder and CEO Erick Calderon sat down with Sander Lutz, lead culture reporter at Decrypt's SCENE, at Art Blocks Marfa Weekend 2023. They discuss the evolution of the company and the generative art world, along with what draws art enthusiasts to be an active part of the community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt Learn: Digital Ownership Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/6udZCotB/decrypt-learn-digital-ownership-explained</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/6udZCotB/decrypt-learn-digital-ownership-explained"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T10:57:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most powerful aspects of blockchain technology is its ability to provide us genuine ownership of our digital assets. This is called digital ownership. In this video, we’ll deep dive into digital ownership, why it matters, and how web3 makes owning digital assets like our social networks, music libraries, personal data, and beyond possible. Author: Clarissa Watson, Senior Writer at Consensys.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Martin Shkreli on E/ACC and SBF in Prison]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QONaWXKZ/martin-shkreli-on-e-acc-and-sbf-in-prison</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QONaWXKZ/martin-shkreli-on-e-acc-and-sbf-in-prison"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T22:03:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reza Jafery and Martin Shkreli sit down for a casual conversation about the growing movement that is E/ACC, what songs they could recite at gunpoint, and whether or not SBF will thrive or just survive during his time in prison.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Can AI Do in Gaming?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JKuqCMao/what-can-ai-do-in-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JKuqCMao/what-can-ai-do-in-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T17:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI Arena CEO Brandon Da Silva and COO Wei Xie discuss how artificial intelligence can shape the video game experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['There Are No Real Standards': Ready Player Me CEO Timmu Tõke on Building for an Open Gaming Ecosystem]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TH3KEAI0/there-are-no-real-standards-ready-player-me-ceo-timmu-tke-on-building-for-an-open-gaming-ecosystem</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TH3KEAI0/there-are-no-real-standards-ready-player-me-ceo-timmu-tke-on-building-for-an-open-gaming-ecosystem"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T17:29:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Timmu Tõke, co-founder and CEO of Ready Player Me, joins Decrypt contributor Ryan Gladwin to discuss the startup's approach to powering avatars that are interoperable across games and metaverse platforms—and what's needed to convince the industry to adopt standards and open up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain Is 'Only Way' Forward for Gaming, Says Shrapnel Studio Head]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/fhoy7Z8f/blockchain-is-only-way-forward-for-gaming-says-shrapnel-studio-head</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/fhoy7Z8f/blockchain-is-only-way-forward-for-gaming-says-shrapnel-studio-head"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T21:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shrapnel Studio Head Don Norbury tells Kate Irwin the reasons why the upcoming first-person shooter game will offer a wide range of NFTs. He also reveals team-based gameplay plans and shares how game maps have already changed this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>