<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-07-06T01:10:18.602Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-07-06T01:10:18.602Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[German MP Strongly Opposes Government’s Bitcoin Sale Amid Market Uncertainty]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7407690de4</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/german-mp-strongly-opposes-governments-bitcoin-sale/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-06T01:03:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a scathing critique of the recent Bitcoin management strategy of the German government, Joana Cotar, a member of parliament has openly expressed her disapproval of the plan to sell off its BTC holdings during a volatile time in the market. 
 
Cotar, a well-known supporter of innovation and digital assets in the Bundestag, contended that this action not only comes at a bad time but also calls into question the long-term advantages of holding onto digital assets like Bitcoin.
 
Cotar Urges German Government To Rethink Bitcoin Sell-Off
 
On Thursday, the German parliament member Joana Cotar taking to the X (formerly Twitter) platform highlighted that the government liquidating Bitcoin holdings during a period of market uncertainty is not a strategic move. She criticized the approach saying…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Godspower Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Goldman Sachs Analyst Blasts Cardano And XRP, Calls Them ‘Cult Meme Coins’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7407690ddf</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/cardano-xrp-cult-meme-coins/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-06T01:03:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Goldman Sachs analyst, Murad Mahmudov has unexpectedly criticized two prominent cryptocurrencies, Cardano (ADA) and XRP. The analyst has labeled both altcoins as cult meme coins, sparking heated debate within the crypto community. 
 
Analyst Claims XRP And Cardano Are Cult Meme Coins
 
In an X (formerly Twitter) post on June 4, Mahmudov declared that XRP and Cardano were cult meme coins, implying that they have no intrinsic value and their price was driven more by community hype. The criticism came as a surprise to Cardano community members who rebuffed the analyst’s controversial claims.
 
 
“This is the cycle when people are finally realizing that XRP and ADA were nothing other than Cult Meme Coins all along,” Mahmudov stated. 
 
As a meme coin analyst and trader, Mahmudov has con…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI did not reveal security breach in 2023 – NYT]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19659226/OpenAI-did-not-reveal-security-breach-in-2023-NYT</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19659226/OpenAI-did-not-reveal-security-breach-in-2023-NYT"/>
        <updated>2024-07-06T01:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI experienced a security breach in 2023 but did not disclose the incident outside the company, the New York Times reported on July 4. OpenAI executives allegedly disclosed the incident internally during an April 2023 meeting but did not reveal it publicly because the attacker did not access...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Theft Surge: Hackers Steal $1.38 Billion in First Half of 2024, Doubling 2023 Figures]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74076b1bd0</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/crypto-theft-surge-hackers-steal-1-38-billion-in-first-half-of-2024-doubling-2023-figures/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-06T00:35:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new report by blockchain intelligence firm TRM reveals that crypto thefts in the first half of 2024 have doubled compared to 2023, with $1.38 billion stolen by June 24. Major hacks constitute 70% of losses, with private key compromises and smart contract exploits as top attack vectors. Crypto projects are advised to adopt comprehensive […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 New Bitcoin (BTC) Support Levels to Watch, Toncoin (TON) Saw Biggest Price Drop Ever, Solana (SOL) on Strong 8% Rise as Ethereum Plummets]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19659206/3-New-Bitcoin-BTC-Support-Levels-to-Watch-Toncoin-TON-Saw-Biggest-Price-Drop-Ever-Solana-SOL-on-Strong-8-Rise-as-Ethereum-Plummets</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19659206/3-New-Bitcoin-BTC-Support-Levels-to-Watch-Toncoin-TON-Saw-Biggest-Price-Drop-Ever-Solana-SOL-on-Strong-8-Rise-as-Ethereum-Plummets"/>
        <updated>2024-07-06T00:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Surprisingly, things have gotten even worse than they were]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New AI Training Technique Is Drastically Faster, Says Google]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=238730</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/238730/new-ai-training-technique-is-drastically-faster-says-google"/>
        <updated>2024-07-06T00:01:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The so-called JEST approach is up to 13 times faster and 10 times more efficient—which could mean lower energy demands.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New AI Training Technique Is Drastically Faster, Says Google]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19659160/New-AI-Training-Technique-Is-Drastically-Faster-Says-Google</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19659160/New-AI-Training-Technique-Is-Drastically-Faster-Says-Google"/>
        <updated>2024-07-06T00:01:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The so-called JEST approach is up to 13 times faster and 10 times more efficient—which could mean lower energy demands.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP drops 12.24%, but analysts rally for $27: What happens now?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19659158/XRP-drops-1224-but-analysts-rally-for-27-What-happens-now</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19659158/XRP-drops-1224-but-analysts-rally-for-27-What-happens-now"/>
        <updated>2024-07-06T00:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XRP drops 12.24% amid broader market declines, with the ongoing Ripple v SEC lawsuit influencing future movements.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chainlink on the Cusp of ‘Good Times Ahead,’ Says Analyst Michaël van de Poppe – Here Are His Targets]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19659134/Chainlink-on-the-Cusp-of-Good-Times-Ahead-Says-Analyst-Michael-van-de-Poppe-Here-Are-His-Targets</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19659134/Chainlink-on-the-Cusp-of-Good-Times-Ahead-Says-Analyst-Michael-van-de-Poppe-Here-Are-His-Targets"/>
        <updated>2024-07-06T00:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One widely followed crypto analyst is turning bullish on decentralized oracle network Chainlink (LINK) after a massive correction. Crypto trader Michaël van de Poppe tells his 722,800 followers on the social media platform X that based on a historical pattern, Chainlink could enter an uptrend...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu’s Shytoshi Kusama Makes Rare Public Appearance at IVS 2024 in Japan]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19659175/Shiba-Inus-Shytoshi-Kusama-Makes-Rare-Public-Appearance-at-IVS-2024-in-Japan</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19659175/Shiba-Inus-Shytoshi-Kusama-Makes-Rare-Public-Appearance-at-IVS-2024-in-Japan"/>
        <updated>2024-07-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The pseudonymous leader of Shiba Inu, Shytoshi Kusama, made a rare public appearance at the 2024 Infinity Venture Summit in Kyoto, Japan, where he met with a local politician and members of the Shiba Inu community to discuss the potential of Web3 technology in Japan. Interestingly, Kusama met...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum and Altcoins Hit Historic Lows in RSI, Signaling Market Capitulation]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19659124/Ethereum-and-Altcoins-Hit-Historic-Lows-in-RSI-Signaling-Market-Capitulation</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19659124/Ethereum-and-Altcoins-Hit-Historic-Lows-in-RSI-Signaling-Market-Capitulation"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T23:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum’s price has tumbled, reaching its lowest Relative Strength Index (RSI) level since August 2023 and signaling a potential market bottom. This extreme oversold condition, mirrored across numerous altcoins, suggests widespread capitulation among investors and raises questions about the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung expects a 15-fold jump in profitability, thanks to AI]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19659110/Samsung-expects-a-15-fold-jump-in-profitability-thanks-to-AI</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19659110/Samsung-expects-a-15-fold-jump-in-profitability-thanks-to-AI"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T23:22:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung Electronics on Friday announced it is expecting a 15-fold increase in operating profit for the second quarter of 2024, driven by AI. The firm revealed the demand for semiconductors helped to increase earnings. Also read: Samsung Reclaims Software Update Lead Amid Growing Competition The...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain Projects Tackle DeFi’s Biggest Hurdle: Consumer Confidence]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19659118/Blockchain-Projects-Tackle-DeFis-Biggest-Hurdle-Consumer-Confidence</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19659118/Blockchain-Projects-Tackle-DeFis-Biggest-Hurdle-Consumer-Confidence"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T23:09:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi promises to revolutionize financial services, but challenges surrounding accessibility and security remain. Discover how blockchain projects are working to bridge the gap and build trust with consumers seeking alternative financial solutions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Vs. Shiba Inu Vs. PEPE: Comparing The Profitability Of The Top Meme Coins]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19659100/Dogecoin-Vs-Shiba-Inu-Vs-PEPE-Comparing-The-Profitability-Of-The-Top-Meme-Coins</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19659100/Dogecoin-Vs-Shiba-Inu-Vs-PEPE-Comparing-The-Profitability-Of-The-Top-Meme-Coins"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T23:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Holders of the top meme coins have witnessed rough price action in the past few weeks. The majority of meme cryptos have crashed hard during the last week, with losses of over 20% in each asset across the board. Particularly, holders of the top meme coins Dogecoin, PEPE, and Shiba Inu have been...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s price dump to $45K would simply be a ‘normal market pullback’]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19659096/Bitcoins-price-dump-to-45K-would-simply-be-a-normal-market-pullback</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19659096/Bitcoins-price-dump-to-45K-would-simply-be-a-normal-market-pullback"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T23:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite Bitcoin's extended price pullback above 25%, on-chain metrics suggest that some growth was still possible.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s Future: Analyzing the Impact of Government-Held BTC]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19659107/Bitcoins-Future-Analyzing-the-Impact-of-Government-Held-BTC</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19659107/Bitcoins-Future-Analyzing-the-Impact-of-Government-Held-BTC"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data analytics firm Arkham revealed that several governments hold a combined $17.8 billion worth of Bitcoin, raising concerns about potential liquidations and their impact on the crypto market. The United States, the United Kingdom, Germany, and El Salvador are among the governments holding...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nigerian Kucoin users to pay 7.5% VAT on all transactions]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19659081/Nigerian-Kucoin-users-to-pay-75-VAT-on-all-transactions</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19659081/Nigerian-Kucoin-users-to-pay-75-VAT-on-all-transactions"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T22:45:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting Monday, July 8th, Kucoin will charge a 7.5% tax on all transactions made by users registered in Nigeria. This decision comes from a regulatory update from the Nigerian SEC. Kucoin exchange took to Twitter (X) to announce that starting Monday, July 8th, Nigerian users will be charged a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analyst: Mt Gox Repayment Event Will Cause 4x the Selling Pressure for BCH Compared to BTC]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74075c9acd</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/analyst-mt-gox-repayment-event-will-cause-4x-the-selling-pressure-for-bch-compared-to-btc/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T22:43:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Chung, an analyst of Presto Research, has examined the intensity of the selloff that ostensibly will be caused by the repayment of Mt Gox creditors, set to flood the market with close to 142,000 BTC between July and October. According to Chung, BCH will hurt the most with this selloff, given its weaker investor […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Faces Continuous Decline Despite Legal Clarity]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19659086/XRP-Faces-Continuous-Decline-Despite-Legal-Clarity</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19659086/XRP-Faces-Continuous-Decline-Despite-Legal-Clarity"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T22:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple’s XRP has faced a challenging year, with its value steadily declining against Bitcoin for the past 12 months. The prolonged slump is evident in its record-breaking 12th consecutive monthly red candle against Bitcoin. This decline has occurred even though XRP stands out as one of the few...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu’s Shytoshi Kusama Makes Public Debut – But Not As Expected]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74075fe5d8</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-shytoshi-kusama-public-debut/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T22:09:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shytoshi Kusama, the enigmatic lead developer of the Shiba Inu cryptocurrency project, made his first public appearance today at the Infinity Venture Summit (IVS) 2024 held in Kyoto. The venue, abuzz with Web3 enthusiasts and developers, served as the backdrop for what many expected to be a revelatory moment. However, Kusama’s choice of attire—a dual-masked ensemble complete with a hood—ensured his physical features remained hidden, thereby preserving his anonymity.
 
Shiba Inu Lead Dev Remains Anonymous
 
Kusama’s outfit drew immediate attention for its dramatic flair: the primary mask resembled that of a plague doctor, covering the upper face, while a secondary mask obscured the lower facial features, leaving only his eyes visible through narrow slits. This costume mirrored his previousl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFTs Rise From The Ashes: Market Sees Unexpected Boom In 2024]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74075fe5cd</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/nfts-rising-market-sees-unexpected-boom/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T22:09:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The once-frigid market for NFTs has thawed in a surprising turn of events, defying the recent slump in Bitcoin prices. Data from DappRadar reveals a robust Q2 2024, with a 28% increase in NFT sales compared to the previous quarter, reaching levels last seen in early 2023. This surge comes as Bitcoin experiences its fourth consecutive day of decline, leaving many scratching their heads about the resilience of digital collectibles.
 
 
Blur Muscles Past OpenSea In A Changing Marketplace Landscape
 
The NFT landscape itself is undergoing a transformation. OpenSea, the former king of the castle, has been dethroned by a new contender – Blur. With its focus on professional traders and lower fees, Blur has captured a dominant 31% market share, leaving OpenSea with the bronze medal at $369 million…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana-Based Memecoin Defies Market Downturn, Jumps Over 30% in 24 Hours Amid Listing on Multiple Exchanges]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19659042/Solana-Based-Memecoin-Defies-Market-Downturn-Jumps-Over-30-in-24-Hours-Amid-Listing-on-Multiple-Exchanges</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19659042/Solana-Based-Memecoin-Defies-Market-Downturn-Jumps-Over-30-in-24-Hours-Amid-Listing-on-Multiple-Exchanges"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T22:01:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One Solana-based (SOL) meme asset is defying market doldrums and rallying after being listed on numerous crypto exchange platforms. New data reveals that Billy (BILLY), a dog-themed memecoin built over Solana, has jumped over 30% during the last 24 hours after multiple crypto exchange platforms...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Toncoin: Examining what the future holds after TON’s 20% dip]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19659044/Toncoin-Examining-what-the-future-holds-after-TONs-20-dip</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19659044/Toncoin-Examining-what-the-future-holds-after-TONs-20-dip"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T22:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TON's price stands at a crossroads after a breakout of the rising wedge pattern.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu’s Shytoshi Kusama Makes Public Debut – But Not As Expected]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19659007/Shiba-Inus-Shytoshi-Kusama-Makes-Public-Debut-But-Not-As-Expected</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19659007/Shiba-Inus-Shytoshi-Kusama-Makes-Public-Debut-But-Not-As-Expected"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T22:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shytoshi Kusama, the enigmatic lead developer of the Shiba Inu cryptocurrency project, made his first public appearance today at the Infinity Venture Summit (IVS) 2024 held in Kyoto. The venue, abuzz with Web3 enthusiasts and developers, served as the backdrop for what many expected to be a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Korea Delays Crypto Tax Implementation to 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19659052/South-Korea-Delays-Crypto-Tax-Implementation-to-2025</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19659052/South-Korea-Delays-Crypto-Tax-Implementation-to-2025"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[South Korea’s cryptocurrency investors can breathe a sigh of relief as the government has delayed the implementation of new virtual asset tax regulations until January 2025. The new rules, which were initially planned for early 2023, have been pushed back to address concerns about their impact...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fetch.ai (FET) Attracts Whales Ahead of ASI Transformation]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19659070/Fetchai-FET-Attracts-Whales-Ahead-of-ASI-Transformation</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19659070/Fetchai-FET-Attracts-Whales-Ahead-of-ASI-Transformation"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fetch.ai’s (FET) price is no longer Fetch.ai’s price; it is the price of the Artificial Superintelligence Alliance.  As Ocean Protocol (OCEAN) and SingularityNET (AGIX) merged into Fetch.ai (FET), their collective identity has been converted into ASI. Whales Welcome Fetch.Ai’s Conversion Into...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$26 XRP Price Still in View as Ripple CTO Cites its Practical Utility in the Trillion-Dollar Payments Market]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19659014/26-XRP-Price-Still-in-View-as-Ripple-CTO-Cites-its-Practical-Utility-in-the-Trillion-Dollar-Payments-Market</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19659014/26-XRP-Price-Still-in-View-as-Ripple-CTO-Cites-its-Practical-Utility-in-the-Trillion-Dollar-Payments-Market"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T21:56:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple's XRP faced a tumultuous week as its price plummeted 11% to a 15-month low of $0.38 on Friday, exacerbating concerns among investors amidst a broader market decline.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop Stock Still Sinking, Now Down 23% Over Past Month]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=238725</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/238725/gamestop-stock-still-sinking-down-23-past-month"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T21:15:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Where’s Roaring Kitty? GameStop (GME) just finished another week down as meme stock momentum continues to fade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden Flips Kamala: Crypto Markets Expect President to Be Nominee]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=238719</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/238719/biden-flips-kamala-crypto-markets-democratic-nominee"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T20:58:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto bettors on the popular prediction market Polymarket again favor incumbent Joe Biden for the Democratic nomination. For now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Kawailani Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram CEO Calls Crypto Game Hamster Kombat World's 'Fastest-Growing Digital Service']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=238702</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/238702/telegram-ceo-hamster-kombat-worlds-fastest-growing"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T20:32:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pavel Durov, Telegram’s founder and CEO, also said that viral game Hamster Kombat has reached 239 million users ahead of its token launch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Events That Could Shift the Crypto Market Landscape in an Instant]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740742b2de</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/7-events-that-could-shift-the-crypto-market-landscape-in-an-instant/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T20:21:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cryptocurrency market finds itself in a challenging situation, with a mix of obstacles and potential opportunities that could influence its future positively. This editorial examines the elements that the crypto community might encounter and highlights key points to consider amid the current market volatility. 7 Distinct Things That Could Instantly Change Everything Bitcoin has […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why HV-MTL Ethereum Mechs Are Coming to Arena Shooter ‘Shatterline’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=238706</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/238706/why-hv-mtl-ethereum-mechs-arena-shooter-shatterline"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T20:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After acquiring the IP from Yuga Labs, Faraway is bringing HV-MTL and Legends of the Mara into other games—starting with this one.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Federal Reserve, Custodia Bank, and the Battle over Sovereignty]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74074d0dab</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/legal/the-federal-reserve-custodia-bank-and-the-battle-for-constitutional-sovereignty"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T20:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction
As it moves into the active appeal stage at the Tenth Circuit, the ongoing legal battle between Custodia Bank and the Federal Reserve has garnered significant attention, especially given the involvement of various amicus briefs. A total of seven briefs were filed on July 3rd, the last day for supporting, or neutral, briefs to be filed.1 This case has attracted significant interest from top-flight appellate attorneys, drawing three former Solicitors General, two representing amici and Ian Gershengorn who represents Custodia itself.
In Federal appellate practice, an amicus curiae (“friend of the court”) brief allows non-parties to provide the court with additional perspectives, expertise, or insights. These briefs, submitted by states, individuals, organizations, or entities wit…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Colin Crossman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Team To Host First-Ever Meet And Greet In Kyoto, Japan]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74074d93c6</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-team-meet-greet/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T19:54:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Shiba Inu team has announced their first-ever meet and greet, offering the Shibarmy a rare opportunity to connect with key members of the Shiba Inu development and promotion team. The community is filled with excitement and anticipation for the upcoming event set to take place in the city of Kyoto, Japan. 
 
Shytoshi Kusama Announces First Ever Meet And Greet
 
On July 1, pseudonymous Shiba Inu lead developer, Shytoshi Kusama took to X (formerly Twitter) to announce the community’s first meet-and-greet event. The Shiba Inu developer expressed excitement for the upcoming event, declaring his anticipation to meet and connect with the Shibarmy community. 
 
 
Kusama disclosed that the event will take place on July 5, around noon at the IVS official Shiba Inu booth based in the city of Kyo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[True Bitcoin HODLers Unfazed: Over 30% Of Supply Dormant Since 5 Years+]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74074d93bc</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-hodlers-unfazed-30-supply-dormant-5-years/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T19:54:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data shows the Bitcoin diamond hands holding since more than five years ago have continued to be stalwart despite the latest crash.
 
Over 30% Of The Entire Bitcoin Supply Hasn’t Moved In 5 Years Or More
 
In a new post on X, the market intelligence platform IntoTheBlock talked about what the percentage of the total circulating Bitcoin supply held by the investors who bought more than five years ago looked like recently.
 
Statistically, the longer a holder keeps their coins (or, to be more precise, UTXOs) dormant, the less likely they become to transfer or sell them on the network. As such, the “long-term holder” (LTH) cohort is considered to carry the relentless hands of the market.
 
 
IntoTheBlock defines LTHs as the investors who bought at least a year ago, so the holders who…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 152 - JOINED BY DEEZE!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/oLurNfIh/fomo-hour-152-joined-by-deeze</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/oLurNfIh/fomo-hour-152-joined-by-deeze"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T18:57:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC hits $54k, set for worst week in over year. Mt. Gox begins to move BTC & make distributions. German government continues to sell holdings. Worst day for BTC liquidations since FTX. Justin Sun says he is willing to buy German BTC. German MP calls on it to stop selling BTC. $52k super-trend support line eyed for BTC. Funding rates turn extremely negative across majors. Only 6 mining machines profitable below $56k. Coinbase spot buyers emerge to counter drop. Total3 hits RSI lows only hit 4 times in last 4 years. Fear & Greed index hits lowest since Jan 2023. Capo remains bullish. Real selling begins at $38k: Schiff. Coinbase continue to fight for Gensler’s emails. Circle mints $250m USDC on SOL. Symbiotic hits $1bn TVL. Taiwan Mobile may open crypto exchange. Unisat completes funding round with Binance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multicoin to Match Up to $1 Million in Solana Donations to Pro-Crypto Candidates]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=238684</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/238684/multicoin-1-million-solana-political-candidates-pac"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T18:43:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ten-day campaign will raise funds for a political action committee focused on the U.S. Senate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Andrew Tate Teases DADDY Meme Coin 'Global Tour' After Being Cleared to Travel]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=238673</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/238673/andrew-tate-daddy-meme-coin-tour-cleared-travel"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T18:13:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Andrew Tate is free to travel the EU as he awaits trail in Romania—and plans to use this time for a “global” tour around the DADDY meme coin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Economist Highlights Possible ‘Hidden Recession’: Official Figures May Understate Inflation Impact]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740731e1de</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/economist-highlights-possible-hidden-recession-official-figures-may-understate-inflation-impact/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T18:10:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent editorial, economist Peter St Onge explores the potential of a hidden economic recession, suggesting that official figures might not reveal the full extent of the decline. St Onge raises concerns about the accuracy of U.S. inflation data and its implications for measuring true economic growth. Peter St Onge, Official Figures May Understate […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[If Biden Drops Out, Is Crypto Villain Gary Gensler Out Too?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=238680</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/238680/if-biden-drops-out-crypto-villain-gary-gensler-out-too"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T17:57:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If Democrats force president Joe Biden to stop running or even resign, is crypto still stuck with his infamous SEC head, Gary Gensler?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[9 Dormant Bitcoin Wallets Reactivate, Moving $7.5M Amid BTC Price Drop]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74073f04b2</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/9-dormant-bitcoin-wallets-reactivate-moving-7-5m-amid-btc-price-drop/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T17:31:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While bitcoin’s price was at $60,382 on July 3, it dropped significantly to $53,550 two days later before rebounding back to $56,642 by 12:50 p.m. EDT on July 5. Notably, nine dormant bitcoin wallets created in 2013, 2016, and 2017 became active on Friday, moving 133.41 BTC valued at $7.5 million. The initial three wallets, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto As A Weapon? Russia Considers Stablecoins To Fight Sanctions]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74073fa9c1</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/russia-considers-stablecoins-to-fight-sanctions/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T17:25:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Russia’s pivot towards stablecoins comes against the backdrop of its chairmanship of the BRICS group (Brazil, Russia, India, China, and South Africa). The BRICS nations have previously discussed the creation of a digital currency-based payment system, the BRICS Bridge, to reduce reliance on the US dollar-dominated global financial system.
 
 
However, sanctions imposed on Russia have thrown a wrench into these plans. A Russian central bank official admitted that the current geopolitical climate makes collaboration on the BRICS Bridge extremely challenging.
 
Ditching The Dollar? Ruble Wobbles As Russia Eyes Stablecoins
 
Traditionally, Russia has maintained a cautious stance towards cryptocurrencies. However, the SWIFT ban and subsequent financial isolation have forced a rethink, propellin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sacked Northern Data Execs File Suit Against Tether-Backed Company, Alleging Fraud]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74073a9f57</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/07/05/sacked-northern-data-execs-file-suit-against-tether-backed-company-alleging-fraud/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T17:04:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two former executives of Tether-backed German tech company Northern Data have filed suit against the firm, alleging that they were wrongfully terminated after raising concerns about the company’s financial health and alleging tax evasion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cheyenne Ligon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Exchange Hack Leads Surging Tally of Crypto Stolen in 2024: TRM Labs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=238668</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/238668/bitcoin-exchange-hack-leads-surging-crypto-stolen-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T16:52:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TRM Labs says $1.38 billion in crypto assets have been stolen so far in 2024, double the tally from this time last year. Here's why.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Reiff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[German MP Criticizes Bitcoin Sales, Urges Government to Hold BTC as Reserve Asset]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7407214600</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/german-mp-criticizes-bitcoin-sales-urges-government-to-hold-btc-as-reserve-asset/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T16:20:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A German parliament member, Joana Cotar, has criticized the government’s decision to sell seized bitcoin on a large scale, advocating for the cryptocurrency’s use as a strategic reserve. She invited key political figures, including Chancellor Olaf Scholz, to a lecture on bitcoin’s advantages for nation-states, aiming to shift policy toward embracing cryptocurrency as a reserve […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protocol Village: Valora Introduces 'Mobile Stack' to Simplify Web3 Apps on iOS, Android]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7407233461</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2024/07/05/protocol-village/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T16:08:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest in blockchain tech upgrades, funding announcements and deals. For the period of July 5-10.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bradley Keoun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale Ethereum Trust Hits Premium for First Time Since 2021]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74072df9db</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/grayscale-ethereum-trust-hits-premium-for-first-time-since-2021/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T15:51:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale’s Ethereum Trust (ETHE) has shifted from a discount to a premium in its net asset value (NAV) for the first time since November 2021, as reported by ycharts.com metrics. This adjustment comes just before the expected debut of spot ether exchange-traded fund listings expected to launch later this month. On July 2, 2024, ycharts.com […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Private Equity Giants Are Circling Bitcoin Miners on AI Allure]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74072ea54c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2024/07/05/private-equity-giants-are-circling-bitcoin-miners-on-ai-allure/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T15:47:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Private equity firms are now looking at bitcoin miners in a much more different way after Core Scientific signed 200MW deal with CoreWeave in June, the company’s CEO said in an exclusive interview with CoinDesk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Canny, Aoyon Ashraf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Crash Pushes Fear & Greed Index to Lowest Since Bitcoin Traded at $17K in Early 2023]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74072ea540</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/07/05/crypto-crash-pushes-fear-greed-index-to-lowest-since-bitcoin-traded-at-17k-in-early-2023/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T15:47:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The widely-followed sentiment metric hit extreme greed levels earlier in March near the local top of the crypto market, but now is pushing its limits in the opposite direction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nintendo Switch 2 Preview: Everything You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197793</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197793/nintendo-switch-2-rumors-leaks-latest-news"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T15:42:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATED: Nintendo says it's already thinking about how to avoid shortages with the Switch 2 launch. Here's everything you need to know.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nigerian Officials Claim Detained Binance Exec Is 'Fine' Amid Health Concerns]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=238641</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/238641/nigerian-officials-detained-binance-exec-fine-health-concerns"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T15:20:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The family of Binance executive Tigran Gambaryan said that he is "suffering immensely" in detention—but Nigerian officials don't agree.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chidirim Ndeche</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multicoin Pledges up to $1M for Pro-Crypto Senate Candidates]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740716061c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/07/05/multicoin-pledges-up-to-1m-for-pro-crypto-senate-candidates/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T15:01:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The investment firm is eager to flip the Senate for Republicans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[German Politician Criticizes the Government's Bitcoin Sell-Off Strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=238623</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/238623/german-politician-challenges-governments-bitcoin-sell-off"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T13:12:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[She would rather see the government keep "Bitcoin in the state treasury, issuing Bitcoin bonds, or creating a favorable regulatory environment."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notcoin Drops 14% as Fresh Start Shows Signs of Unraveling]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=238612</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/238612/notcoin-drops-14-as-fresh-start-shows-signs-of-unraveling"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T12:31:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Viral Telegram game, Notcoin, has taken a major hit as its fresh start begins to reveal itself and the wider crypto industry sees a downturn.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Could Face Volatility From US Payroll and Unemployment Reports—But Not Much, Say Analysts]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=238611</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/238611/bitcoin-volatility-us-payroll-unemployment"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T12:19:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Employment and non-farm payroll data are more indicative of how strong the U.S. economy is despite the higher rates," said a BRN analyst.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Isn't Germany Selling Its Seized Bitcoin at Auction?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=238585</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/238585/germany-seized-bitcoin-auction"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T11:31:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Institutions generally prefer to acquire clean Bitcoin," said Darren Franceschini, co-founder of Fideum.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$17.8 Billion Bitcoin Is Still Sitting in These Government Wallets: Arkham]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=238587</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/238587/17-8-billion-bitcoin-is-still-sitting-in-these-government-wallets-arkham"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T11:12:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data from Arkham shows that countries including Germany, the U.S. and the UK hold substantial amounts of Bitcoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[End of Germany, Mt. Gox Sales 'Likely' to Mark Bitcoin Bottom, Experts Say]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=238581</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/238581/end-of-germany-mt-gox-sales-likely-to-mark-bitcoin-bottom-experts-say"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T07:10:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto is facing its toughest headwind in months, with an end of selling from Mt. Gox and Germany expected to mark a Bitcoin bottom.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Sinclair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Slides to $55,000 as Liquidations Top $600 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=238579</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/238579/bitcoin-55000-liquidations-cross-600-million"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T03:41:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin has fallen to its lowest point since February, triggering a cascade of liquidations worth hundreds of millions of dollars.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Sinclair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mt. Gox Transfers $2.7 Billion in Bitcoin From Cold Storage Amid Market Rout]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=238575</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/238575/mt-gox-transfers-2-7-billion-cold-storage-market-rout"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T02:38:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mt. Gox has transferred $2.7 billion worth of Bitcoin to an unidentified wallet, further exacerbating concerns over declining crypto prices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Sinclair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blocking AI Bots From Scraping Websites Gets Boost From Cloudflare]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=238548</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/238548/ai-bot-web-crawler-blocking-cloudflare"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T00:01:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Along with adding an “easy button” to stop AI developers from training their models on web content, the security firm shared  its findings on AI bot activity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UFC Star Launches Meme Coin, Falls to Zero in Minutes Amid Insider Trading Claims]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=238539</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/238539/ufc-khamzat-chimaev-smash-meme-coin"/>
        <updated>2024-07-04T20:50:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Khamzat Chimaev’s SMASH token crashed to zero after he promoted it on Twitter—and he’s since deleted his tweets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Exchange KuCoin Adds 7.5% Tax for Nigeria Users, Citing 'Regulatory Update']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=238532</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/238532/kucoin-vat-tax-nigeria-sec"/>
        <updated>2024-07-04T20:18:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The tax applies to “all transaction types on KuCoin platform,” the exchange told Decrypt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chidirim Ndeche</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Is Falling—How Low Will It Go?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=238535</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/238535/bitcoin-falling-how-low-will-it-go"/>
        <updated>2024-07-04T19:47:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We still haven’t hit the bottom, analysts say. But they also expect plenty of upside left before the end of the year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Novice Bitcoin Traders Are Selling the Dip, Data Shows]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=238530</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/238530/new-bitcoin-traders-selling-dip"/>
        <updated>2024-07-04T19:05:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CryptoQuant analysts say newer holders seem unable to stomach the volatility, dumping $2.4 billion in BTC this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fake Iggy Azalea Token Buyers Await Refunds as Celeb Handler Sahil Appears to Cash Out]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=238523</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/238523/fake-iggy-azalea-token-airdrop-refunds-sahil-arora"/>
        <updated>2024-07-04T18:47:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celebrity crypto coin promoter Sahil Arora has started to move funds out of the presale wallet that raised over $380,000 in May. What happened to the airdrop?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Justin Sun Offers to Buy $2 Billion in Bitcoin From Germany to 'Minimize' Market Impact]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=238492</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/238492/justin-sun-2-billion-bitcoin-germany-market-impact"/>
        <updated>2024-07-04T15:11:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's unclear just how serious Sun really is, as usual.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maincard.io to Reach ‘A Billion Potential Users’ With The Open Network Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235907</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235907/maincard-io-to-reach-a-billion-potential-users-with-the-open-network-launch"/>
        <updated>2024-07-04T14:01:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maincard is one of the first handful of companies accepted into TON’s accelerator program, out of over 170 applicants.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Falls Below $57,000 as Mt. Gox Trustee Sends Test Transactions: Arkham]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=238487</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/238487/bitcoin-falls-below-57000-as-mt-gox-trustee-sends-test-transactions-arkham"/>
        <updated>2024-07-04T12:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Only ill-informed traders are willing to buy here," wrote 10x Research. "Breaking this support could cause a sharp decline to the low $50,000s."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are Layer 3 Networks? Improving Functionality and Interoperability]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=238486</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-are-layer-3-networks-improving-functionality-and-interoperability"/>
        <updated>2024-07-04T12:13:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Layer 3 networks sit atop the infrastructure of layer 1 and layer 2 blockchains, enhancing functionality and interoperability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Tumbles as German Government Moves Another $75 Million to Exchanges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=238463</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/238463/bitcoin-tumbles-as-german-government-moves-another-75-million-to-exchanges"/>
        <updated>2024-07-04T11:28:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Yet another day of heavy selling pressure, causing BTC to fall below the 60k support level and reaching lows of 57,875," noted QCP Capital.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is ‘Gemz’? It’s Telegram Game ‘Hamster Kombat’ But With Sloths]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=238395</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-gemz-telegram-game-hamster-kombat-sloths"/>
        <updated>2024-07-04T10:01:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gemz is basically Hamster Kombat, but with a few tweaks. And it’s another polished tap-to-earn Telegram game that’s gaining steam.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friend.tech Plunges 25%, Hits All-Time Low After Saying It'll Stay on Base L2]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=238460</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/238460/friend-tech-plunges-25-hits-all-time-low-after-saying-itll-stay-on-base-l2"/>
        <updated>2024-07-04T09:58:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Friend.tech team's decision not to migrate off the Coinbase incubated Base L2 sent its token plummeting to an all-time low.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No, Nintendo Will Not Use AI in its Upcoming Titles, President Says]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=238458</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/238458/no-nintendo-will-not-use-ai-in-its-upcoming-titles-president-says"/>
        <updated>2024-07-04T06:15:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nintendo's president said his company would not use AI technology for upcoming titles due to concerns over intellectual property rights.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Sinclair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fed Sees Inflation Declining But Not Fast Enough, Here’s Why That Matters for Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=238456</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/238456/fed-inflation-declining-not-fast-enough-why-matters-for-crypto"/>
        <updated>2024-07-04T04:20:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Falling inflation benefits risk assets, including crypto, as it would give the Fed confidence to begin lowering interest rates this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Sinclair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 151 - BTC TAPS THE 60K LINE]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/HP5x5DDr/fomo-hour-151-btc-taps-the-60k-line</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/HP5x5DDr/fomo-hour-151-btc-taps-the-60k-line"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T18:27:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETF Flows: -$14m. BTC drops to $60k, CME gap filed again. $1bn shorts liquidated if we rally to $62.6k. Pump(.)fun surpasses ETH for revenue. ETH will outperform BTC after ETF launch: K33. ETH ETF may be delayed even further. BTC heading to $150k: Fundstrat. Chainlink & Fidelity partner for fund data on-chain. USDC protects the dollar: Circle ad. Robinhood considers crypto futures in US & EU. Another BTC miner looks to IPO in US. Vitalik bullish on prediction markets. Sentient Labs raises $85m for AI on SOL. Mantra to tokenise $500m of real estate. TAO falls 15% after security breach. Crypto scams & hacks hit $572m in Q2.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 150 - BILLY TO A BILLY?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/lyMeJEHY/fomo-hour-150-billy-to-a-billy</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/lyMeJEHY/fomo-hour-150-billy-to-a-billy"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T15:58:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETF inflows hit highest in a month. ETH ETF inflows to hit $5bn in 6 months: Gemini. ETH public funds see largest outflow since 2022. SOL hits new ATH for monthly economic value. Sellers starting to look exhausted: Crypto Quant. Silvergate sued by SEC, settles for $63m. Circle gets stablecoin license for USDC in EU. US DoJ ironically chooses Coinbase for custody. Bitcoin miner aims for $16bn IPO. Bitfarms increases BTC mining amid takeover attempt. DOT has 2 year runway amid large burn. DOT ecosystem builders turn against team. PENDLE TVL falls $3bn as restaking rewards end. PayPal stablecoin goes live on Jupiter. At least $600m altcoin unlocks this month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 149 - LUCA NETZ LIVE!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/VwszUB8K/fomo-hour-149-luca-netz-live</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/VwszUB8K/fomo-hour-149-luca-netz-live"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T07:39:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC bounces back above $61k after nosedive. SOL leads majors, BTC dominance falls. BTC RSI hit 18, largest net selling day in over a year. $174m ETF outflow led by GBTC. German government sells $24m more more BTC. Mt Gox info probably ‘leaked to insiders’. Mr 100 buys dip for first time in 34 days. SOL leads Moonpay transactions for 5th week. Trump may speak at Bitcoin Nashville. Biden rehires crypto advisor. Crypto & AI complement each other: Balaji. Bitcoin will protect AI’s wealth: Pomp. Tether stops minting on Algorand & EOS. Jupiter launches v3 swaps. ETH Foundation mailing list gets leaked. Jump CEO resigns after CFTC investigation. 54% of Japanese institutional investors want BTC. Strike launches in UK. MiCA approved EUR stablecoins coming in 6 days.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Transhumanism and the Quest for Immortality with SingularityNET CEO Dr. Ben Goertzel]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/k7x3OCKI/transhumanism-and-the-quest-for-immortality-with-singularitynet-ceo-dr-ben-goertzel</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/k7x3OCKI/transhumanism-and-the-quest-for-immortality-with-singularitynet-ceo-dr-ben-goertzel"/>
        <updated>2024-06-29T16:26:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Transhumanism is a philosophical and intellectual movement that advocates the enhancement of the human condition using technologies that can increase longevity, cognition, and well-being. In this interview, SingularityNET founder and CEO Dr. Ben Goertzel discusses his background in the transhumanist movement and how AI, and AGI will play a part.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vivendi Web3 Lead: 'There's No Ethical GenAI if You Don't Protect Content']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DlaGWo2U/vivendi-web3-lead-theres-no-ethical-genai-if-you-dont-protect-content</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DlaGWo2U/vivendi-web3-lead-theres-no-ethical-genai-if-you-dont-protect-content"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T16:01:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fabien Aufrechter, VP of Web 3.0 at Vivendi, joined Rug Radio's Farokh aboard the Joker Odyssey at Cannes Lions to discuss the media group's plans for a global digital copyright, and how token-gated media will lead to the end of third-party cookies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 148 - SOL ETF NARRATIVE DOMINATES]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/6vtl91oI/fomo-hour-148-sol-etf-narrative-dominates</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/6vtl91oI/fomo-hour-148-sol-etf-narrative-dominates"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T15:35:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SOL leads majors as Van Eck files for ETF. Bitwise hints at SOL ETF filing. SOL will get ETF, ADA & XRP won’t: GSR. SOL price may rise 8.9x with ETF: GSR. Coinbase & Stripe team up for onboarding. BTC miner sell pressure weakens. BTC activity drops to lowest level in 10 years. Steve Cohen shuts down crypto arm of hedge fund. Crypto unmentioned in Presidential debate. Kraken co-founder donates $1m to Trump. Bolivia lifts BTC ban. MegaLabs raises $20m, aims for 100k TPS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 147 - THE BLAST FALLOUT]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/3C8awS5v/fomo-hour-147-the-blast-fallout</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/3C8awS5v/fomo-hour-147-the-blast-fallout"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T19:15:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto bounces, ETFs see another small net inflow. The US government sends 3940 BTC to exchanges. Spot ETH ETFs may be coming July 4th. Coinbase sues SEC over FOIA inquiries. Most ‘obvious & attractive’ buying opp possible. US man convicted of home invasions to steal BTC. Blast launches at $2.5bn FDV, disappoints many. ADA faces DDoS attacks with 200 transactions. Losses from deep fakes could hit $24bn in 2024. Miners face M&A boom on AI retrofitting. Marathon mines $16M KAS. Vitalik introduces ZK voting company Rarimo. Animoca Brands considers public listing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 146 - IT'S BLAST DAY!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pGQCmjhT/fomo-hour-146-its-blast-day</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pGQCmjhT/fomo-hour-146-its-blast-day"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T19:09:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETFs reverse 7-day outflow. Geverman government to sell $35m more BTC. SOL Blinks allows transactions from any website. Jupiter allows you to swap tokens from X. Helius allows SOL staking from X. Drift allows you to leverage trade from X. ETH supply increases for 73 days straight. ETF review going smoothly: Gensler. Expect $15bn net inflows for ETH ETF: Bitwise. VanEck to waive ETH ETF fee until 2025. UAE new regulations could limit stablecoins. Court convicts two men for crypto ‘securities fraud’. BTC ETFs to be approved by Morgan Stanley. Vanguard CEO calls BTC ‘a stable asset like gold’. Blast launches today, 16.5% as community airdrop. $2.9bn FDV for Blast on Aevo, others predict higher. Top Blast holders to see vesting over 6 months. Nubank to integrate Bitcoin Lightning Network. FTX creditors to vote on cash or crypto repayment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 145 - WE SURVIVED!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/812Lhy0g/fomo-hour-145-we-survived</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/812Lhy0g/fomo-hour-145-we-survived"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T21:18:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC bounces back above $61k after nosedive. SOL leads majors, BTC dominance falls. BTC RSI hit 18, largest net selling day in over a year. $174m ETF outflow led by GBTC. German government sells $24m more more BTC. Mt Gox info probably ‘leaked to insiders’. Mr 100 buys dip for first time in 34 days. SOL leads Moonpay transactions for 5th week. Trump may speak at Bitcoin Nashville. Biden rehires crypto advisor. Crypto & AI complement each other: Balaji. Bitcoin will protect AI’s wealth: Pomp. Tether stops minting on Algorand & EOS. Jupiter launches v3 swaps. ETH Foundation mailing list gets leaked. Jump CEO resigns after CFTC investigation. 54% of Japanese institutional investors want BTC. Strike launches in UK. MiCA approved EUR stablecoins coming in 6 days.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mika Shares How to Send and Receive Crypto Using Kraken Wallet]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/Dg5Xjel7/mika-shares-how-to-send-and-receive-crypto-using-kraken-wallet</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/Dg5Xjel7/mika-shares-how-to-send-and-receive-crypto-using-kraken-wallet"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T07:55:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join Rug Radio creator and crypto influencer Mika as she guides you through the process of sending and receiving cryptocurrency using the Kraken wallet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 144 - A VERY RED DAY]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tDG5cHBN/fomo-hour-144-a-very-red-day</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tDG5cHBN/fomo-hour-144-a-very-red-day"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T19:48:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC hits 6-week lows, $215m liquidations in fall. Mt Gox set to start BTC repayments in July. Fear & Greed index nears 2024 lows. Bitfinex whales’ long positioning rebounds. Open Interest rises as shorts grow, funding negative. BTC is economic immortality, going to $10m: Saylor. Moment of truth for BTC to rebound: Ansem. Expect $61-62k BTC to hold: Emperor BTC. SOL upgrade is big step-change: Raoul Pal. Expect slow melt-up from ETH ETF: DC Investor. MKR falls 11% as delegate gets phished. TON ecosystem sees phishing attacks spread.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 143 - CRYPTO TRENDS LOWER]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/dvJof6CV/fomo-hour-143-crypto-trends-lower</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/dvJof6CV/fomo-hour-143-crypto-trends-lower"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T15:38:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto sinks, ETFs see another $140m outflow. German government likely sells $195m more BTC. 100 day BTC break-out coming: Don Alt. SOL ETF applied for in Canada. Rumours SEC case vs Coinbase also dropped. Standard Chatered setup spot trading desk. ARB has record daily revenue on LayerZero claims. CFTC investigating Jump Crypto. FTM outperforms ahead of Sonic upgrade. Binance integrates USDT on TON. Onchain prediction market TVL continues to soar.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 142 - ETH LEADS THE RALLY]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/teZMC9Tb/fomo-hour-142-eth-leads-the-rally</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/teZMC9Tb/fomo-hour-142-eth-leads-the-rally"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T15:46:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH continues to lead gains, SOL underperforms. BTC may rebound as Fed liquidity rips higher. ETH sees large amount of bullish call activity. LayerZero launches today, 25% unlock. Funding level the lowest in 3 months. German government sends 1000 BTC to exchanges. Stablecoins to become 10% of money: Circle CEO. Stabelcoin transfers up 16x in 4 years. BTC exchanges balances hit 3 year low. SOL again flips ETH for DEX volumes. Kraken reports $3m bug exploit found by CertiK. Debate about whether CertiK were whitehats. Jump Crypto gives $10m to crypto PAC. Binance launches HODLer airdrops. TipLink allows SOL transfers by email. ETHFI proposes 50% revenue for buybacks. JTO teases LSD backed stablecoin. JUP team proposes to reduce 30% of supply.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Robotics Company Aims to Solve a Labor Shortage in Manufacturing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ub9yvCXi/this-robotics-company-aims-to-solve-a-labor-shortage-in-manufacturing</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ub9yvCXi/this-robotics-company-aims-to-solve-a-labor-shortage-in-manufacturing"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GrayMatter Robotics Co-founder and CEO Ariyan Kabir explains the origin of the company, the need for artificial intelligence and robotics to offset a growing labor shortage, and takes Decrypt on a tour of its AI-powered facility.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 141 - SEC DROPS ETH PROBE]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zFpVKbtL/fomo-hour-141-sec-drops-eth-probe</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zFpVKbtL/fomo-hour-141-sec-drops-eth-probe"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T22:41:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC: 65.4k (0%), ETH: 3545 (+3%), SOL: 139 (+2%). Top Gainers: LDO, BRETT, PEPE, AR. ETH & beta lead gains after SEC headline. SEC drops probe into ETH as a security. BTC ETFs see another $152m outflow. Pantera show $100m buying interest in ETH ETF. Pantera aims to raise new $1bn fund. Lack of staking won’t harm ETH ETF: 21 Shares. LayerZero airdrop coming June 20th. SEC concerns on USDC may delay Circle IPO. Hayes increasing PENDLE & DOGE positions. Fox News to build L2 with Polygon. EIGEN trades at $10bn pre-market. Drift & Ondo partner on RWAs. Commercial real estate coming on-chain: KPMG.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 140 - MARKETS DOWN BAD]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/7BwSoeRf/fomo-hour-140-markets-down-bad</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/7BwSoeRf/fomo-hour-140-markets-down-bad"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T17:35:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC touches 1-month lows, dominance hits 56%. $500m of liquidations in fall, $146m ETF outflows. VanEck to launch first ETF in Australia. Coinbase to launch pre-market trading. 56% of Fortune 500 building in web3. Uphold to delist USDT in EU due to MiCA. TON flips DOGE in sell-off. Base DEX users now 2nd place after SOL. Ethena launches staking & restaking with Symbiotic. Lens aiming to raise $50m at $500m valuation. Two ‘crazy’ MATIC announcements coming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 139 - WHATS THE NEXT META?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zEW6uY5Z/fomo-hour-139-whats-the-next-meta</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zEW6uY5Z/fomo-hour-139-whats-the-next-meta"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T17:32:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC again breaks $66k, dominance rises. Fear & Greed index hits 3 month low. Whales continue to be in accumulation mode. Miners 33 days into capitulation, average 41 days. Financial advisors not buying BTC yet: BlackRock. Crypto funds saw $600m outflows last week. ZKsync airdrop live, prices at $5bn FDV. ZKsync defend sybil measures. Low float, high FDV coins get hammered again. Tether launches product backed by Gold. Korean exchanges reviewing 600 coins for delisting. ETH ETF ‘sell the rumour, buy the news event’. BTC ETF basis buyers roughly 15% of demand. CVX bounces 100% after loan liquidation. TON sees fastest user growth in crypto history. APT may flip SOL in 1-3 years: Hayes. Crypto lifetime funding eclipses $100bn. SEC claims $876m Ripple fine still fair. Gensler could cost Biden election: Cuban.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 138 - MORE CELEB COINS!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/KzCZzgqx/fomo-hour-138-more-celeb-coins</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/KzCZzgqx/fomo-hour-138-more-celeb-coins"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T18:05:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Altcoins bleed out heavy, BTC dominance rises towards 60%. Miners continue to be large BTC sellers, whales accumulate. ETF inflows slow, hedge fund allocations point to basis trades. ETH ETFs approvals see little movement, coming 'in the summer’. Stocks continue to hit ATHs as CPI & PPI both come in soft. TON performs best in L1s, active wallets eclipse ETH. Andrew Tate joins celebrity memecoin meta, DADDY hits $350m. SOL DEX volumes eclipse ETH in memecoin frenzy. Curve founder defaults on CRV debt as DeFi coins tumble. Terraform Labs & Do Kwon to pay $4.5bn fine to SEC. BAMK hits $350m in Runes as it issues BTC stablecoin. Gaming tokens face huge sell-off, PRIME changes tokenomics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 137 - CRYPTO DIPS FURTHER]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mJ28rAx5/fomo-hour-137-crypto-dips-further</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mJ28rAx5/fomo-hour-137-crypto-dips-further"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T15:46:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto falls after slightly hawkish Fed speech. BTC whales buy $1.4bn in 24hrs. Miners continue to be large sellers of BTC. BTC ETFs see $100m inflows. MicroStrategy to raise $500m to buy BTC. Egorov CRV debt positions begin to liquidate  . Circle to support SOL for wallets. 4% of Turkey GDP used to buy stablecoins. QuantMatter say $11m stolen from OKX account. Biden to use Coinbase for crypto donations. Terraform Labs & Do Kwon set to pay $4.5bn fine. Franklin Templeton write report on SOL DePin. TON flips ETH for active addresses. Moonpay & Paypal integration goes live in EU & UK.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>