<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-12-29T07:13:41.860Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-12-29T07:13:41.860Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Markets Brace for Epic $11 Billion Crypto Options Expiry Event]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19138887/Markets-Brace-for-Epic-11-Billion-Crypto-Options-Expiry-Event</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19138887/Markets-Brace-for-Epic-11-Billion-Crypto-Options-Expiry-Event"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T07:05:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Friday is Bitcoin options expiration day, and today is a mammoth end-of-month and end-of-year event. With billions in BTC derivatives expiring today, crypto markets may have one final movement before the end of the year. More than 178,000 Bitcoin options contracts are set to expire on December...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LM Funding America Announces Sale of Symbiont’s Blockchain Technology to Platonic Holdings Inc.]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19138889/LM-Funding-America-Announces-Sale-of-Symbionts-Blockchain-Technology-to-Platonic-Holdings-Inc</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19138889/LM-Funding-America-Announces-Sale-of-Symbionts-Blockchain-Technology-to-Platonic-Holdings-Inc"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T07:03:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LM Funding America, Inc. (NASDAQ: LMFA), a cryptocurrency mining and technology-based specialty finance company, has made a significant move in the blockchain industry by selling Symbiont’s blockchain technology to Platonic Holdings Inc. for $2 million.  The strategic sale is set to strengthen...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[India to Block Websites of Binance, Kraken, and 7 Other Crypto Exchanges]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7487169863</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/india-to-block-websites-of-binance-kraken-and-7-other-crypto-exchanges/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T06:59:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Indian government has issued show cause notice to nine popular offshore virtual digital assets service providers (VDASPs) under the local anti-money laundering laws. The announcement yesterday (Thursday) further detailed that the Financial Intelligence Unit (FIU) ordered to blacklist the domains of the nine crypto exchanges as they are illegally operating in the country.
India to Block Top Crypto Exchanges
The names of the crypto exchanges in the notice are Binance, Kucoin, Huobi, Kraken, Gate.io, Bittrex, Bitstamp, MEXC Global, and Bitfinex. All these exchanges are ranked at the top in terms of global crypto trading volume but do not have any authorization to operate in India.
“Director FIU IND has written to Secretary, Ministry of Electronics and Information Technology to block the U…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arnab Shome</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Exchange Bitzlato Halts Withdrawals Following Co-founder’s Guilty Plea in $700M Case]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19138862/Crypto-Exchange-Bitzlato-Halts-Withdrawals-Following-Co-founders-Guilty-Plea-in-700M-Case</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19138862/Crypto-Exchange-Bitzlato-Halts-Withdrawals-Following-Co-founders-Guilty-Plea-in-700M-Case"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T06:55:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitzlato's temporary withdrawal suspension comes a few weeks after its co-founder, Anatoly Legkodymov, pleaded guilty to money laundering charges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Economist Warns the Demise of US Dollar Hegemony Is ‘Really Upon Us’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7487108e19</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/economist-warns-the-demise-of-us-dollar-hegemony-is-really-upon-us/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T06:39:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Economist Stephanie Pomboy has warned that the “demise of the U.S. hegemony is really upon us,” emphasizing that the Biden administration and many U.S. policymakers in Washington “are just sleeping right through it.” She pointed out that a growing number of nations are reducing their reliance on the U.S. dollar and opting to use local currencies in international trade.
 
‘The Demise of the US Hegemony Is Really Upon Us’
 
Economist Stephanie Pomboy discussed the future of the U.S. dollar in an interview with Tucker Carlson last week. Pomboy is a financial analyst, market strategist, and economist, who founded Macromavens, a research firm specializing in emerging global economic trends. Before launching her firm, she worked as a managing director at an independent economic research firm ISI…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will India Ban These Nine Offshore Crypto Exchanges?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19138888/Will-India-Ban-These-Nine-Offshore-Crypto-Exchanges</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19138888/Will-India-Ban-These-Nine-Offshore-Crypto-Exchanges"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T06:39:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The financial regulator in India has released a document detailing actions against nine prominent cryptocurrency exchanges, indicating the possibility of additional measures against them. “Financial Intelligence Unit India (FIU IND) has issued compliance Show Cause Notices to following nine...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI-Powered DreamWire Revolutionizes Multi-View Wire Art Creation]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19138840/AI-Powered-DreamWire-Revolutionizes-Multi-View-Wire-Art-Creation</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19138840/AI-Powered-DreamWire-Revolutionizes-Multi-View-Wire-Art-Creation"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T06:36:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a remarkable stride toward democratizing the world of Multi-View Wire Art (MVWA), researchers from the University of Surrey and Beijing University of Posts and Telecommunications have unveiled a groundbreaking AI system called DreamWire. This pioneering system introduces an innovative...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Canadian crypto exchange Catalyx faces security breach and client asset loss]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19138824/Canadian-crypto-exchange-Catalyx-faces-security-breach-and-client-asset-loss</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19138824/Canadian-crypto-exchange-Catalyx-faces-security-breach-and-client-asset-loss"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T06:28:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CatalX CTS Ltd., the operator of the Canadian crypto trading platform Catalyx, has reported a security breach that resulted in the loss of a portion of crypto assets held on behalf of clients. The company’s management suspects the involvement of an employee in this incident. The breach prompted...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeFiance Capital’s Yeou Jie Goh Joins Chromia as Head of APAC Region]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19138825/DeFiance-Capitals-Yeou-Jie-Goh-Joins-Chromia-as-Head-of-APAC-Region</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19138825/DeFiance-Capitals-Yeou-Jie-Goh-Joins-Chromia-as-Head-of-APAC-Region"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T06:25:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DeFiance Capital, a leading crypto investment firm led by Arthur Cheong, is experiencing a significant change in its team composition. Yeou Jie Goh, the firm’s head of portfolio growth, has resigned from his position at DeFiance and is set to join the blockchain project Chromia as the head of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Labs Faces the SEC on Trial, Is Jump Trading Involved?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19138836/Terraform-Labs-Faces-the-SEC-on-Trial-Is-Jump-Trading-Involved</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19138836/Terraform-Labs-Faces-the-SEC-on-Trial-Is-Jump-Trading-Involved"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T06:22:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent development in the legal tussle between Terraform Labs and the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), the court has ordered a trial, scheduled for January 29, 2024, in the Manhattan federal court. The decision follows the court’s recent ruling in favor of the regulators that...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Breakthrough: Revolutionizing Early Detection of Liver Cancer]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19138813/AI-Breakthrough-Revolutionizing-Early-Detection-of-Liver-Cancer</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19138813/AI-Breakthrough-Revolutionizing-Early-Detection-of-Liver-Cancer"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T06:18:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a groundbreaking development, artificial intelligence (AI) technology is poised to transform the landscape of hepatocellular carcinoma (HCC) diagnosis. Hepatocellular carcinoma, the most common form of liver cancer, has long been a global health concern with rising incidence rates,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybercriminal group “Pink Drainer” strikes again: $4.4 million theft in Chainlink]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19138804/Cybercriminal-group-Pink-Drainer-strikes-again-44-million-theft-in-Chainlink</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19138804/Cybercriminal-group-Pink-Drainer-strikes-again-44-million-theft-in-Chainlink"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T06:07:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The notorious cyber-criminal group known as “Pink Drainer” has orchestrated a significant theft, making off with a staggering $4.4 million in Chainlink (LINK). The victim enticed into initiating an “Increase Approval” functionality, fell prey to a swift and calculated attack. Swift execution of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Buterin Takes a Nostalgic Dive Into Ethereum’s Early Days]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19138800/Buterin-Takes-a-Nostalgic-Dive-Into-Ethereums-Early-Days</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19138800/Buterin-Takes-a-Nostalgic-Dive-Into-Ethereums-Early-Days"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T06:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent blog post, Ethereum co-founder Vitalik Buterin took a stroll down memory lane, reminiscing about the early days of cryptocurrency adoption. Titled “Make Ethereum Cypherpunk Again,” Tron founder Justin Sun also responded to Buterin’s tweet, expressing Tron’s admiration for Ethereum....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UAE’s Pioneering Role in Healthcare Transformation Through Data and AI]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19138791/UAEs-Pioneering-Role-in-Healthcare-Transformation-Through-Data-and-AI</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19138791/UAEs-Pioneering-Role-in-Healthcare-Transformation-Through-Data-and-AI"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T05:59:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The United Arab Emirates (UAE) is emerging as a pivotal player in healthcare transformation. Led by Abu Dhabi’s Adia Lab, the UAE’s pioneering efforts in data research and artificial intelligence (AI) are poised to revolutionize healthcare globally. Horst Simon, an esteemed expert in computer...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche Foundation is about to start buying memecoins for the ‘culture’]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19138789/Avalanche-Foundation-is-about-to-start-buying-memecoins-for-the-culture</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19138789/Avalanche-Foundation-is-about-to-start-buying-memecoins-for-the-culture"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T05:53:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche says it will utilize its $100 million NFT incubator initiative to start investing in select memecoins, which it says encourages the “culture and fun” brought about by meme-derived tokens.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monex Group expands crypto portfolio with majority stake in 3iQ Digital Holdings]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19138783/Monex-Group-expands-crypto-portfolio-with-majority-stake-in-3iQ-Digital-Holdings</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19138783/Monex-Group-expands-crypto-portfolio-with-majority-stake-in-3iQ-Digital-Holdings"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T05:44:07.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BRC20.com Secures $1.5 Million Funding to Enhance Bitcoin Token Infrastructure]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19138784/BRC20com-Secures-15-Million-Funding-to-Enhance-Bitcoin-Token-Infrastructure</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19138784/BRC20com-Secures-15-Million-Funding-to-Enhance-Bitcoin-Token-Infrastructure"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T05:41:41.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FIU IND Sends Notice to 9 Foreign-Based Crypto Exchanges]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19138815/FIU-IND-Sends-Notice-to-9-Foreign-Based-Crypto-Exchanges</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19138815/FIU-IND-Sends-Notice-to-9-Foreign-Based-Crypto-Exchanges"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T05:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Clamps Down On 'Self-Styled Entrepreneur' For Using $364K Crypto Investor Funds For Personal Expenses]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19138781/SEC-Clamps-Down-On-Self-Styled-Entrepreneur-For-Using-364K-Crypto-Investor-Funds-For-Personal-Expenses</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19138781/SEC-Clamps-Down-On-Self-Styled-Entrepreneur-For-Using-364K-Crypto-Investor-Funds-For-Personal-Expenses"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T05:28:14.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche Foundation Boosts Meme Sector with Culture Catalyst Funding]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19138760/Avalanche-Foundation-Boosts-Meme-Sector-with-Culture-Catalyst-Funding</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19138760/Avalanche-Foundation-Boosts-Meme-Sector-with-Culture-Catalyst-Funding"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T05:24:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Avalanche Foundation has taken a significant step by announcing its support for the Meme sector through the Culture Catalyst funding program. The initiative marks a strategic move to recognize and nurture the unique culture and creativity the Meme ecosystem embodies. By purchasing selected...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin climbs the currency ranks, now 16th largest by market cap globally]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19138752/Bitcoin-climbs-the-currency-ranks-now-16th-largest-by-market-cap-globally</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19138752/Bitcoin-climbs-the-currency-ranks-now-16th-largest-by-market-cap-globally"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T05:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin says original Web3 visions have ‘faded into the background’]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19138748/Vitalik-Buterin-says-original-Web3-visions-have-faded-into-the-background</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19138748/Vitalik-Buterin-says-original-Web3-visions-have-faded-into-the-background"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T04:54:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Buterin said in a blog post that there’s a large ideological rift where the non-blockchain world sees the crypto space as a distraction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ark Invest CEO Cathie Wood Expects Spot Bitcoin ETFs to Boost BTC Price ‘Significantly’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74871b8f58</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ark-invest-ceo-cathie-wood-expects-spot-bitcoin-etfs-to-boost-btc-price-significantly/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T04:35:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cathie Wood, CEO of Ark Investment Management, foresees widespread institutional involvement in spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) following anticipated approval by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). “All we need is for the trillions of dollars in institutional assets out there to allocate maybe 0.1% or 0.2% to an ETF, which will be one of the easiest ways to gain exposure and one of the most efficient ways to gain exposure to bitcoin,” she explained, adding: “That will move the price significantly.”
 
Ark Invest CEO Cathie Wood on Spot Bitcoin ETF Approval
 
The CEO of Ark Investment Management (Ark Invest), Cathie Wood, shared her perspective regarding spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) in an interview with Yahoo Finance on Tuesday. Ark Invest is among the a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Schiff Says ‘Big Surprise’ Awaits in 2024 — Warns of Crash, Recession, High Inflation Returning With Vengeance]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74870d971d</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/peter-schiff-says-big-surprise-awaits-in-2024-warns-of-crash-recession-high-inflation-returning-with-vengeance/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T02:34:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Economist Peter Schiff has shared some predictions for 2024. “The big surprise in 2024 will not only be that the economy crashes into recession, but that high inflation returns with a vengeance,” he described. The technicals are breaking down for the U.S. Dollar Index, he added, emphasizing: “This couldn’t come at a worse time. The Fed is planning interest rate cuts, which will not only accelerate the decline, but put renewed upward pressure on inflation.”
 
Peter Schiff’s 2024 Economic Predictions
 
Gold bug and economist Peter Schiff shared his predictions for 2024 in a series of posts on social media platform X Wednesday.
 
“Investors are convinced the Fed has succeeded in restoring price stability without causing a recession, pulling off a miraculous soft landing,” Schiff described, wa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Ernie Bot from Baidu Reaches 100 Million Users in China]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211138</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211138/baidu-ernie-bot-ai-chatbot-china"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T02:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Baidu's conversational AI demonstrates swift traction at home, even as it looks to close the gap globally.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Most Powerful Generative AI Text Tools of 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211128</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211128/decrypt-emerge-best-large-language-models-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T01:02:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whatever your style, there will always be a Large Language Model (LLM) out there for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former US President Donald Trump Selling ETH Worth Millions of Dollars, Analysis Indicates]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7480f77d11</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/former-us-president-donald-trump-selling-eth-worth-millions-of-dollars-analysis-indicates/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T00:33:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An analysis by crypto intelligence firm Arkham indicates that Donald Trump, the 45th President of the United States, is selling millions of dollars in ether acquired from selling his non-fungible token (NFT) collections. The analytics firm also revealed that Trump’s highest crypto balance reached $4 million. Based on deposit analysis to date, the former U.S. president has sold 1,325 ETH, totaling over $3 million.
 
Donald Trump Selling Ether, Analysis Suggests
 
Crypto intelligence firm Arkham shared an analysis on social media platform X on Thursday, revealing the amount of ether former U.S. President Donald Trump appears to have sold.
 
“Looks like Donald Trump is selling his ETH,” the firm wrote, adding that three weeks ago, the former U.S. president started sending his cryptocurrencies…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Judge Sides With SEC Over Do Kwon, Says UST, LUNA Are Securities]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211129</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211129/judge-sides-with-sec-over-do-kwon-says-ust-luna-are-securities"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T23:49:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The summary judgment removes one of the biggest questions looming over Kwon’s trial, which will now focus solely on allegations of fraud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Labs' LUNA and MIR Tokens are Securities, Judge Rules]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7480fd999f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/12/28/terraform-labs-luna-and-mir-tokens-are-securities-judge-rules/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T23:24:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A federal judge issued summary judgements siding with the SEC's arguments that Terraform had illegally sold unregistered crypto securities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Napolitano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Exchange Catalyx Suspends Trading, Withdrawals Following 'Security Breach']]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7480ff05c1</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/12/28/crypto-exchange-catalyx-suspends-trading-withdrawals-following-security-breach/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T23:08:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Canadian exchange suffered a security break earlier this month, resulting in the loss of an unknown amount of customer funds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Napolitano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano Founding Entity EMURGO Maps Out Growth Strategy For 2024]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7480ff4a48</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/cardano-founding-entity-emurgo-maps-out-2024/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T23:05:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EMURGO, a founding entity of the Cardano blockchain, has recently reflected on the achievements of 2023 and unveiled a roadmap for the ecosystem in 2024. 
 
With a focus on sustainable community governance, technical advancements, interoperability, and ecosystem expansion, Cardano aims to improve its position in terms of decentralized applications (DApps) and real-world Web3 solutions in 2024.
 
Cardano Roadmap Unveiled
 
As EMURGO highlights in its roadmap, in 2023, Cardano took steps toward establishing sustainable community governance through initiatives such as CIP1694 and the launch of Intersect, a member-based organization. 
 
According to the founding entity, these developments laid the foundation for the blockchain’s minimum-viable community-run government. 
 
With a vision of 2024…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Criticizes NFTs, Gives Nod to Inscriptions: ‘At Least Encode the Jpeg on the Blockchain’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7480fa2fd2</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/elon-musk-criticizes-nfts-gives-nod-to-inscriptions-at-least-encode-the-jpeg-on-the-blockchain/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T22:32:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk, the chairman of X, has referred to non-fungible tokens (NFTs) and the defects of their implementation, indirectly making the case for inscriptions. Answering a post on X on the topic of NFTs, Musk suggested saving the jpeg (an image format) of the NFT on the blockchain, like inscriptions are currently saved on Bitcoin.
Elon Musk Indirectly Nods at Ordinal Inscriptions
Elon Musk has given indirect support to Ordinal inscriptions, a series of images and other data saved on the BTC blockchain. In an X post commenting on the issue of non-fungible token (NFT) data, and how it can be linked to content not owned by the issuers, that can be removed, Musk declared:
Yeah, at least encode the jpeg on the blockchain!
Musk’s complaints about how standard NFTs work are not new. On the Joe Rogan Experience podcast, Musk stated:
The funny thing is the NFT is not even on the blockchain — it’s just a URL to the JPEG.
As Musk explained, earlier NFT implementations featured a link to the content highlighted in the file that led to a website, something that was pointed out by critics of the NFT mania back in the day. However, Ordinal inscriptions and Stamps, two recently introduced protocols, allow users to save the desired media directly on top of the Bitcoin blockchain, securing the longevity of the file.
The rise of these inscriptions has raised discussions on what constitutes a “fair use” of the blockchain space, with some mining pools even opting to filter transactions containing them, considering these inscriptions “spam.”
The post that started the discussion featured a video and a song about NFTs that Musk also posted in 2021. Leonidas, a co-founder of Ord.io, later reported this video was inscribed on Bitcoin by an unknown user who paid $7,223 in fees to this end. The file, identified as Inscription 51,887,020, has a size of 366.57 KB.
What do you think about Elon Musk’s views on NFTs? Tell us in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GG's 2023 Year in Review: Stories That Rocked the Gaming World]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211122</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211122/ggs-2023-year-review-stories-rocked-gaming-world"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T22:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From layoffs to GTA 6 and Microsoft acquiring Activision, these are the stories that defined 2023 in gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bankrupt FTX Stirs Controversy With Repayment Plan: Bitcoin Valued At $16,000 For Customers]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7480e7c8c5</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ftx-repayment-plan-bitcoin-valued-at-16000/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T21:33:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent filing on December 27, bankrupt cryptocurrency exchange FTX unveiled its repayment plan, triggering customer outrage and discontent. The plan, which values customers’ digital assets at the time of FTX’s collapse, offers a value significantly lower than prevailing market prices.
 
FTX Under Fire
 
The filing by FTX stated that the repayment plan aims to make substantial progress towards confirming a Chapter 11 plan and returning the value of the assets to customers and other creditors. 
 
However, the unique nature of these Chapter 11 cases, involving claims based on digital assets, has posed challenges in determining fair and reasonable values for these unliquidated claims.
 
 
According to the filing, to estimate the value of the digital assets owed to customers, FTX compiled …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Study Observes Consolidation of Bitcoin Mining Rewards With Antpool]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7480ecd706</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/study-observes-consolidation-of-bitcoin-mining-rewards-with-antpool/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T20:40:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a significant shift within the bitcoin mining landscape, Antpool’s resurgence in 2023 has marked a notable trend in the consolidation of bitcoin rewards, surpassing Foundry USA in blocks mined. The Miner Mag’s recent analysis reveals that Antpool, along with other major pools, has centralized coinbase block rewards, reflecting a deeper, more interconnected mining ecosystem. This consolidation hints at unknown and strategic financial arrangements and evolving power dynamics among leading mining pools.
 
Report Highlights Rising Consolidation in Bitcoin Mining Pool Rewards
 

 
According to The Miner Mag, ten of the fifteen largest mining pools have been merging their coinbase block rewards since early 2022. This trend includes prominent names like Binance Pool, BTC.com, and Braiins Pool,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[India Will Block Binance, Kraken, and Other Exchanges in Crypto Crackdown]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211114</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211114/india-block-binance-kraken-other-exchanges-crypto-crackdown"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T20:32:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[India's Financial Intelligence Unit said the crypto exchanges were operating illegally in the country. Now their websites will be blocked.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin No Longer Cheap: Fees Jumped 35x In 2023]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7480e8055a</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-no-longer-cheap-fees-jumped-35x-in-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T20:07:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data shows the Bitcoin daily transaction fees jumped 35x during 2023, leading to BTC flipping Ethereum in the metric.
 
Bitcoin Daily Transaction Fees Has Shot Up Recently
 
According to data from the market intelligence platform IntoTheBlock, the BTC transaction fees have hit new highs in 2023. The “transaction fees” here naturally refer to the amount that any sender has to attach with their transfers on the Bitcoin blockchain as payment for the miners.
 
The average fees that the users would be willing to put on their transactions depend on the network conditions. When a large number of users make transactions at once, some transfers can get stuck waiting in the mempool, as the chain only has a limited capacity to process moves.
 
 
If a sender doesn’t want to risk having to wai…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bloomberg ETF Analyst Reassures Spot Bitcoin ETFs Will Hold Actual BTC, Amidst Concerns]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7480e8310e</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/markets/bloomberg-etf-analyst-reassures-spot-bitcoin-etfs-will-hold-actual-btc-amidst-concerns"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T20:06:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amid rapidly growing anticipation for the launch of Spot Bitcoin Exchange-Traded Funds (ETFs) in the United States, concerns have arisen from many in the Bitcoin community regarding if these funds will truly hold spot Bitcoin or not. 
In response to these worries, Bloomberg Intelligence ETF analyst James Seyffart has stepped forward to allay fears, assuring investors that the current pool of spot Bitcoin ETFs will indeed hold real, spot BTC, if approved.



This assurance comes in the wake of posts by many in the online Bitcoin community, raising skepticism about whether the impending ETFs will maintain actual Bitcoin reserves. Spot Bitcoin ETF filers were told by the SEC that their applications needed to include clear language of cash creations and redemptions, with no mentions of in-kind creations and redemptions, according to FOX Businesses' Eleanor Terrett.



This has caused many to think that this would allow a loophole for issuers to start fractionally reserving the ETF, which is not the case. "There are a lot of bad Bitcoin ETF takes. People are simply uninformed (being nice) and wayyyy too gullible," Seyffart said yesterday. "Say it with me: 'Spot Bitcoin ETFs WILL hold Bitcoin.'"
The imminent launch of Spot Bitcoin ETFs has been a hotly debated topic within the financial sphere, heralded as a potential game-changer for both institutional and retail investors. As the anticipation for Spot Bitcoin ETFs continues to mount, investors remain vigilant, eagerly awaiting their introduction into the market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nik Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[India Cracks Down On 9 Overseas Crypto Exchanges, Binance And Kraken Among Targets]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7480e8f557</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/india-cracks-down-on-9-overseas-crypto-exchanges/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T19:58:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[India has intensified its efforts to regulate the crypto sector by clamping down on overseas exchanges, including Binance, that are allegedly operating illegally within the country.
 
The Financial Intelligence Unit (FIU) has issued compliance show-cause notices to several platforms, urging them to demonstrate adherence to Indian laws. Additionally, the information ministry has been requested to block the uniform resource locators (URLs) or web addresses of nine entities, restricting local access to their websites. 
 
These measures come as the Indian government strengthens its oversight of digital assets, implementing anti-money laundering (AML) provisions and imposing taxes on crypto transactions. 
 
Offshore Crypto Exchanges Under Scrutiny
 
According to a Bloomberg report, The FIU, res…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$14 Billion in Bitcoin Options Expire Tomorrow—Here’s Why It Matters]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211113</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211113/14-billion-bitcoin-options-expire-tomorrow-why-it-matters"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T19:40:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's $14 billion worth of Bitcoin options expiring on Friday. The split between puts and call shows investors are feeling bullish.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[L2 Protocol Blast Soars Past $1 Billion in Locked Crypto Value]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7480d14cf4</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/l2-protocol-blast-soars-past-1-billion-in-locked-crypto-value/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T18:39:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Statistics reveal that the Ethereum layer two (L2) platform Blast now secures over $1 billion within its protocol. The total value locked (TVL) in Blast has expanded more than twelvefold since its launch in late November.
 
Blast’s TVL Hits $1 Billion
 

 
Initially, on Nov. 22, 2023, Blast’s value locked was recorded at $89.59 million, but as of today, it has surged to $1.135 billion. Currently, Blast ranks as the 17th largest decentralized finance (defi) protocol in terms of TVL, nestled between Juststables and Marinade Finance, according to data collected by defillama.com.
 

 
The platform is distinguished by its native staking and strategies to amplify yield through ether (ETH) staking and real-world assets (RWAs). Pacman, the creator behind the non-fungible token (NFT) marketplace Bl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Expert’s Bold Prediction: Stablecoins Set To Eclipse ETFs, Forging A Multi-Trillion Dollar Market]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7480d16081</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/experts-prediction-stablecoins-etfs-trillion-dollar/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T18:38:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoins are poised to become the next multi-trillion-dollar market, according to a prediction by Gabor Gurbacs, an advisor to Tether, one of the leading stablecoin issuers. Gurbac’s assertion places stablecoins at a pivotal juncture in the evolution of financial markets, drawing parallels to the monumental growth of exchange-traded funds (ETFs).
 
As the stablecoin market currently stands at over $130 billion, led by heavyweights like USDT, USDC, DAI, and TrueUSD, Gurbacs’s perspective presents an intriguing forecast for the future of finance.
 
 
Disruptive Potential Of Stablecoins: A Financial Paradigm Shift
 
Gurbacs recently articulated his vision on the X platform, detailing how stablecoins, much like their predecessors – stocks, hedge funds, mutual funds, and ETFs – have the pote…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Traders May Be Lining Up to 'Sell the News' on ETF Approval]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211108</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211108/bitcoin-traders-sell-news-etf-approval"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T18:37:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price of Bitcoin could plunge if a spot exchange-traded fund (ETF) is approved in the U.S. in January, CryptoQuant claims.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Marks Record Year with 40 Million New Users in 2023]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7480d21d83</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/binance-marks-record-year-with-40-million-new-users-in-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T18:32:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency  
exchange Binance saw significant growth in its user base in 2023, according to  
its recently released year-end report. The company added over 40 million  
registered users this year, representing a 30% increase compared to 2022. It  
now has a total of 170 million registered users globally.
Crypto Exchange Binance  
Sees User Growth in 2023
Binance  
highlighted the steady adoption growth of its crypto payments, peer-to-peer  
trading, and earning products. Its P2P platform saw an 18% increase in trading  
volume and a 39% rise in active users.
"By 2023-end, Binance amassed 170 million registered users and offered 1785 trading pairs across 431 different assets," the company commented in the report.

The #Binance 2023 End-of-Year Report has landed!This year, we remained de…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Damian Chmiel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana's SOL Dips Below $100, Slips Back Behind BNB in Crypto Ranking]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7480dc4816</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/12/28/solanas-sol-dips-below-100-slips-back-behind-bnb-in-crypto-ranking/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T18:14:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Traders were moving capital from SOL to stablecoins suggesting profit taking, one analyst said in an interview.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blast Deposits Top $1.1 Billion Ahead of Ethereum L2 Launch and Airdrop]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211107</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211107/blast-deposits-top-1-1-billion-ahead-ethereum-l2-launch-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T18:11:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Paradigm-backed Ethereum scaler’s rollout has been controversial, but that isn’t stopping users from buying in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance User Base Grew 30% This Year, Expanding Even After U.S. Legal Settlements]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7480debc9d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/12/28/binance-user-base-grew-30-this-year-expanding-even-after-us-legal-settlements/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T17:54:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The largest cryptocurrency trading venue added 40 million accounts to 170 million.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A List of Every Wall Street Giant Seeking to Launch a Bitcoin ETF]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7480d9695e</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/markets/every-wall-street-giant-applying-launch-spot-bitcoin-etf"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T17:32:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As soon as January, a Bitcoin spot ETF could be live in the U.S. – but while that much appears likely, it remains to be seen which specific investment vehicles will be approved.
Indeed, in advance of the January 10 deadline, anticipation is high, with over 12 applicants ranging from disruptive Bitcoin companies to some of the most well-known names in global finance.
The prize is the potential to provide investors with a regulated and accessible vehicle to the world's leading cryptocurrency. 
Unlike traditional investment routes, such as direct ownership or futures trading, a Bitcoin ETF simplifies the process, allowing a broader range of investors, both institutional and retail, to participate in the crypto market.
This article delves into the intense competition among prominent players in…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reed Macdonald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Dips Below $100 as Meme Coin Trading Reverses Course]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211101</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211101/solana-dips-below-100-meme-coin-trading-bonk"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T16:51:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SOL may have burned a little too hot a little too fast, now falling 7% in 24 hours.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cathie Wood's ARK Sells Remaining GBTC Shares, Buys $100M in Bitcoin Futures ETF]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211088</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211088/cathie-woods-ark-sells-remaining-gbtc-shares-buys-100m-in-bitcoin-futures-etf"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T13:52:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The asset manager offloaded 2.25 million GBTC shares and purchased 4.32 million shares of the ProShares Bitcoin Strategy ETF.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PancakeSwap's CAKE Jumps 7% on Proposal to Slash Token Supply by 300 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211085</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211085/pancakeswaps-cake-jumps-5-on-proposal-to-slash-token-supply-by-300-million"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T10:45:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PancakeSwap's CAKE token jumped by 4% following the proposal, which would see its maximum supply reduced from 750 million to 450 million.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Dumps Millions in Ethereum After Disastrous NFT Redux]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211064</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211064/trump-dumps-millions-in-eth-after-disastrous-nft-redux"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T00:53:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The former president has cashed out $2.4 million worth of ETH in the last three weeks, Arkham reports.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Biggest Space Stories of 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211059</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211059/the-biggest-space-stories-of-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T23:53:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even amid an avalanche of AI news, space exploration still managed to make headlines this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Biggest Crypto Airdrops of 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211031</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211031/biggest-crypto-airdrops-2023-arbitrum-blur-celestia-jito"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T23:03:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The top token handouts of the year netted users over $4.5 billion worth of free crypto. Here are 2023's biggest crypto airdrops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Gaming Predictions: Will 2024 Be the Breakout Year?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210772</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210772/crypto-gaming-predictions-2024-breakout-year"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T22:29:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto industry leaders remain optimistic about the future of blockchain gaming. Here's what they expect in 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brakes on Bonk: Solana Meme Coin Down 56% From All-Time High]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211030</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211030/bonk-solana-based-meme-coin-slows-down"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T21:41:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The meme token is now well below the all-time high it touched two weeks ago.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Game On: The Hottest Upcoming Gaming Token Airdrops]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211029</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211029/game-on-hottest-upcoming-gaming-token-airdrops"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T21:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From Portal to Saga, these are the token airdrops that crypto gamers should be paying close attention to right now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI Trained AI Models on Copyrighted Work, Says NYT Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211006</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211006/openai-trained-ai-models-on-copyrighted-work-says-nyt-lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T19:02:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Current methods for training AI on copyrighted work means “less journalism will be produced, and the cost to society will be enormous,” says the NYT.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PlayStation Plus: Latest Free PS5 Games to Download]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207958</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207958/playstation-plus-latest-free-ps5-games-download"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATED: Sony's next batch of free PS5 games for PlayStation Plus subscribers has been announced. Here's what you can grab soon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Jumps, But the Real Winners Are Optimism, Arbitrum, and Polygon]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210990</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210990/ethereum-jumps-real-winners-optimism-arbitrum-polygon"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T18:18:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum is up significantly today, but the tokens behind projects that make the ecosystem faster and cheaper to use are doing even better.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Year in Bitcoin: ETFs, Ordinals and What Comes Next]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210926</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210926/year-in-bitcoin-etfs-ordinals-what-comes-next"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T18:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin was in survival mode at the start of the year and then made a massive comeback.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's 2023 NFT Project of the Year: Pudgy Penguins]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210727</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210727/decrypts-nft-project-year-2023-pudgy-penguins"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T17:34:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum collection Pudgy Penguins thrived in Crypto Winter and now is gliding to new heights on the back of mainstream market toys.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xai Gaming Token Airdrop Delayed—Here's When It's Coming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210989</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210989/xai-gaming-token-airdrop-delayed-heres-when-coming"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T17:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arbitrum's "layer-3" gaming network is pushing back its XAI airdrop. Here's why, and who’s eligible for the rescheduled launch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy Boosts Its Bitcoin Holdings to $8 Billion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210969</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210969/microstrategy-boosts-its-bitcoin-holdings-to-8-billion"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T16:11:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company has spent $5.9 billion to build its BTC treasury.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Got a Solana Saga Before They Sold Out? Here Are All the Airdrops You Can Claim]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210634</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210634/solana-saga-airdrops-tokens-nfts-you-can-claim"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T15:49:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATED: Our list has been updated with even more airdrops, NFTs, and other perks for Solana Saga owners. Check out the latest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘We’re Living Longer, But We’re Living Longer, Sicker’: Rejuve CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210928</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210928/were-living-longer-but-were-living-longer-sicker-rejuve-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-12-26T22:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A SingularityNET spinoff hopes to leverage AI and blockchain to crowdsource better health and longevity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Slips Standalone Copilot AI App Into Android Store]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210918</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210918/microsoft-slips-standalone-copilot-app-for-android-into-google-app-store"/>
        <updated>2023-12-26T22:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a late Christmas gift to generative AI fans, the Redmond-based tech giant released a free mobile app to rival popular paid options.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Barry Silbert Out as Grayscale Chairman While Bitcoin ETF Decision Looms]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210919</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210919/barry-silbert-out-as-grayscale-chairman-while-bitcoin-etf-decision-looms"/>
        <updated>2023-12-26T19:59:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Silbert will be replaced by Grayscale parent Digital Currency Group’s CFO, Mark Shifke.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Cools Slightly as Bitcoin and Ethereum See Prices Slump]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210911</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210911/solana-cools-slightly-as-bitcoin-and-ethereum-see-prices-slump"/>
        <updated>2023-12-26T18:59:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana, which soared past the $100 mark over the weekend, has cooled slightly. SOL is trading for $109.20—down 11% in the past day.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biggest Crypto Exploits and Hacks of 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210802</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210802/biggest-crypto-hacks-of-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-12-26T16:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers made away with a lot of cash in 2023. But not as much as last year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's 2023 Project of the Year: Base]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210661</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210661/decrypt-project-year-2023-coinbase-ethereum-base"/>
        <updated>2023-12-26T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase's Ethereum layer-2 network took crypto by storm, and may have permanently redefined the company in the process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's 2023 Story of the Year: The War on Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210725</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210725/2023-story-of-the-year-war-on-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-12-25T20:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Regulators really went after the crypto industry this year. But did they go too far? Here's a recap of the battles fought in 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emerge Weirdest News Stories of 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210807</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210807/weirdest-emerging-tech-stories-of-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-12-25T18:01:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From beer made of vaginal yeast to toilets that know more about you than your doctor, these bizarre trends kept us from getting bored this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Products of the Year 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210267</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210267/crypto-products-of-the-year-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-12-25T16:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 gets physical with this selection of Decrypt's favorite crypto products of 2023, from hardware wallets to NFT art frames.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFT Gag Gifts: From Rugrats to Stoner Cats (and Trump Too)]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210855</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210855/nft-gag-gifts-from-rugrats-to-stoner-cats-and-trump-too"/>
        <updated>2023-12-25T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Need a quick, memorable gift? These wacky—and infamous—NFTs are sure to make an impression this holiday season.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Socrates Beginner's Guide: The 'Cultural Nexus' Offering Debate-to-Earn Rewards]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210604</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210604/socrates-beginners-guide-the-cultural-nexus-offering-debate-to-earn-rewards"/>
        <updated>2023-12-24T21:25:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Social media and entertainment platform Socrates combines elements of GameFi and SocialFi. Here’s how to get started.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GG's 2023 Game of the Year: Parallel]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210693</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210693/gg-2023-game-of-the-year-parallel"/>
        <updated>2023-12-24T17:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The dark sci-fi card game is in closed beta, but already offers stunning character art, deep strategy, and rewarding gameplay.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week on Crypto Twitter: New Dog, Old Tricks]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210840</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210840/this-week-on-crypto-twitter-new-dog-old-tricks"/>
        <updated>2023-12-24T16:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As one dog-themed meme coin sets, another rises.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wildcard's Plans for 2024 with Founders Paul and Katy Bettner]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/TI3aFBhO/wildcards-plans-for-2024-with-founders-paul-and-katy-bettner</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/TI3aFBhO/wildcards-plans-for-2024-with-founders-paul-and-katy-bettner"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T21:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wildcard developers Paul and Katy Bettner tell Decrypt's Kate Irwin about why they see their game as a "Web3 game," not a crypto game, and share why they've stuck with their initial vision despite the challenging broader market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt and Rug Radio Merge to Create Global Web3 Publishing Company]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/VTEBYFD8/decrypt-and-rug-radio-merge-to-create-global-web3-publishing-company</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/VTEBYFD8/decrypt-and-rug-radio-merge-to-create-global-web3-publishing-company"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T17:04:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt and Rug Radio have announced their intent to merge, creating the world’s biggest decentralized publishing company. Codenamed [REDACTED], the alliance is aimed at revolutionizing tech-media, bringing together the forces of content creation and consumption.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['If You Play Well, You're Gonna be Rewarded': How FPS Web3War is Bringing 'Skill-to-Earn' to Crypto Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Jl5AEFuD/if-you-play-well-youre-gonna-be-rewarded-how-fps-web3war-is-bringing-skill-to-earn-to-crypto-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Jl5AEFuD/if-you-play-well-youre-gonna-be-rewarded-how-fps-web3war-is-bringing-skill-to-earn-to-crypto-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T10:20:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roll1ng Thund3rz co-founder Valentin Cobelea and Zilliqa CEO Matt Dyer joined Decrypt to discuss how the new FPS game Web3War is shaking up the crypto gaming space with a novel "skill to earn" mechanic that rewards players for high-quality gameplay.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating peaceful money & taking over your local government w/ Joseph Schiarizzi]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zb0VG27G/creating-peaceful-money-taking-over-your-local-government-w-joseph-schiarizzi</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zb0VG27G/creating-peaceful-money-taking-over-your-local-government-w-joseph-schiarizzi"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T23:23:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week our host Reza Jafery is joined by Joseph Schiarizzi, founder of OpenDollar and prolific solidity developer. 


We discuss: 
- Onchain beer
- Taking over your local government
- His Emmy and 3 patents?!?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INTERVIEW: Ember Sword CEO Says NFT Games Are More 'Transparent']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/M9OHCVpA/interview-ember-sword-ceo-says-nft-games-are-more-transparent</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/M9OHCVpA/interview-ember-sword-ceo-says-nft-games-are-more-transparent"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T21:58:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ember Sword CEO Mark Laursen shares why some big game studios "irk" him—and why he got into game development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Director Jordan Bayne on the State of Film3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZLoEDkL9/director-jordan-bayne-on-the-state-of-film3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZLoEDkL9/director-jordan-bayne-on-the-state-of-film3"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T00:11:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the 2023 Film3 Summit, Jordan Bayne—director and founder of The Squad—spoke with Decrypt's Sander Lutz about how the Film3 world has progressed over the last year and what decentralized technologies can offer to creators that want to buck the Hollywood system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Questions With SCENE: Phil Mohun]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TwOjXfOR/5-questions-with-scene-phil-mohun</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TwOjXfOR/5-questions-with-scene-phil-mohun"/>
        <updated>2023-12-01T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bright Moments co-founder Phil Mohun joins 5 Questions With SCENE to recount some favorite moments from the road, including negotiating with Patagonian gauchos, falling in love with Tokyo, and gaining a newfound appreciation for shrooms chocolate bars.

Shot and edited by Vincent Roazzi Jr.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>