<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-06-22T17:12:48.919Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-06-22T17:12:48.919Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin.com News Is the Best Place to Advertise Your Crypto Project]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7572f3ca1f</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-com-news-is-the-best-place-to-advertise-your-crypto-project/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T17:06:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are looking for a way to promote your crypto project to a large and engaged audience, you should first consider advertising on Bitcoin.com News. This is one of the leading sources of information and analysis on the cryptocurrency industry, covering everything from token prices to DeFi to NFTs. Here are some reasons why Bitcoin.com News is the best place to advertise your crypto project:
 
– Reach millions of readers worldwide. Bitcoin.com news has a global reach, with visitors from over 200 countries and over 3 million followers on social media. You can target your ads to specific regions or languages, or run them across the entire network.
 
– Enjoy flexible and affordable pricing options. Bitcoin.com news offers various advertising formats and packages to suit your needs and budget. You can choose from press releases, banner ads, sponsored articles, short video ads, podcasts, newsletters, and more. You can also customize your campaign duration, frequency, and targeting.
 
– Get support from a dedicated team of experts. Bitcoin.com news has a professional and experienced team of marketers who will help you create and run your campaign. You will get guidance on how to craft your message, optimize your ads, and measure your results.
 
– Get 10% off by paying with Verse, Bitcoin.com’s own utility token!
 
Bitcoin.com news is the best place to advertise your crypto project because it gives you access to a large and loyal audience of crypto enthusiasts who are eager to learn about new and innovative projects. By advertising on Bitcoin.com News, you can increase your brand awareness, improve SEO, generate leads, and drive conversions. Don’t miss this opportunity to grow your crypto project with Bitcoin.com news!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Financial Advisors Can Navigate Crypto’s Turbulent Waters]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7572f3f8b7</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/06/22/how-financial-advisors-can-navigate-cryptos-turbulent-waters/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T17:05:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FAs and RIAs shouldn’t run from crypto and digital assets, as long as they have the right playbook.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Ervin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PEPE Pumps 55% Following Whale’s Massive Purchase]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18633974/PEPE-Pumps-55-Following-Whales-Massive-Purchase</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18633974/PEPE-Pumps-55-Following-Whales-Massive-Purchase"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T17:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PEPE has been seeing enormous growth in the past several days.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase CEO sees 2024 election playing key role in crypto regulation]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18633978/Coinbase-CEO-sees-2024-election-playing-key-role-in-crypto-regulation</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18633978/Coinbase-CEO-sees-2024-election-playing-key-role-in-crypto-regulation"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T17:04:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong thinks the upcoming U.S. presidential election next year could be a potential turning point for the crypto industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance.US Initiates Lawsuit, Alleging SEC’s Misleading Statements]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18633968/BinanceUS-Initiates-Lawsuit-Alleging-SECs-Misleading-Statements</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18633968/BinanceUS-Initiates-Lawsuit-Alleging-SECs-Misleading-Statements"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T17:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A motion has been filed by lawyers representing Binance.US, Binance Holdings Limited (the global exchange), and Binance CEO Changpeng “CZ” Zhao. The motion alleges that the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) provided misleading statements regarding an ongoing securities...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fun Fact [Actually Mind-blowing]]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18633979/Fun-Fact-Actually-Mind-blowing</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18633979/Fun-Fact-Actually-Mind-blowing"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T17:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This fact is insane when you think about crypto, AI, and tech stocks.🔥 GET MY FREE NEWSLETTER 👉 https://cryptolark.co/WEALTHMASTERY💸 BYBIT $30,030 BONUS & FEE DISCOUNT 👉 https://cryptolark.co/BYBIT💡💡💡 ESSENTIAL CRYPTO KNOWLEDGE 💡💡💡🔥 GET MY FREE NEWSLETTER 👉 https://cryptolark.co/WEALTHMASTERY👨‍🎓...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BitMEX CEO Suggests Crypto Exchanges Should Eliminate Internal Market Makers – Here's Why]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18633973/BitMEX-CEO-Suggests-Crypto-Exchanges-Should-Eliminate-Internal-Market-Makers-Heres-Why</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18633973/BitMEX-CEO-Suggests-Crypto-Exchanges-Should-Eliminate-Internal-Market-Makers-Heres-Why"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T16:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BitMEX CEO Stephan Lutz has stated that crypto exchanges do not need to run internal market makers after it was revealed Crypto.com has internal trading teams that trade crypto.  The revelation raised concerns about a potential conflict of interest at Crypto.com. In an interview with The Block,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance in Efforts To Enable Bitcoin (BTC) Deposits and Withdrawals via Lightning Network]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18633950/Binance-in-Efforts-To-Enable-Bitcoin-BTC-Deposits-and-Withdrawals-via-Lightning-Network</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18633950/Binance-in-Efforts-To-Enable-Bitcoin-BTC-Deposits-and-Withdrawals-via-Lightning-Network"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T16:55:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top global crypto exchange Binance is now officially working on integrating Bitcoin (BTC) deposits and withdrawals via the Lightning Network. The Lightning Network is a layer-2 scaling solution built on top of Bitcoin that aims to enable instant and cost-effective transactions for BTC. Binance...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Financial Advisors Can Navigate Crypto’s Turbulent Waters]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18633969/How-Financial-Advisors-Can-Navigate-Cryptos-Turbulent-Waters</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18633969/How-Financial-Advisors-Can-Navigate-Cryptos-Turbulent-Waters"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T16:55:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FAs and RIAs shouldn’t run from crypto and digital assets, as long as they have the right playbook.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s Ferocious ETF-Fueled Rally Puts Ether at Weakest Price Versus BTC in 2 Months]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7572fe6850</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/06/22/bitcoins-ferocious-etf-fueled-rally-puts-ether-at-weakest-price-versus-btc-in-months/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T16:51:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The largest cryptocurrency by market cap has benefited from rising investor optimism following multiple filings for spot bitcoin ETFs and its omission from tokens listed in SEC lawsuits earlier this month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lyllah Ledesma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TrueUSD Says TUSD Stablecoin Has ‘No Exposure’ to Embattled Prime Trust]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7572fe6847</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/06/22/trueusd-says-tusd-stablecoin-has-no-exposure-to-embattled-prime-trust/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T16:51:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoin project TrueUSD said Thursday it had “no exposure” to embattled crypto services company Prime Trust as it raced to shore up confidence in its dollar-backed TUSD.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Introduces Zero Maker Fees for TUSD Trading Pairs – The Next Tether Stablecoin?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18633938/Binance-Introduces-Zero-Maker-Fees-for-TUSD-Trading-Pairs-The-Next-Tether-Stablecoin</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18633938/Binance-Introduces-Zero-Maker-Fees-for-TUSD-Trading-Pairs-The-Next-Tether-Stablecoin"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T16:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto exchange giant Binance has announced a new zero-maker fee promotion for stablecoin TUSD. Starting from 30th June, the promotional offer covers both spot and margin trading for TrueUSD.  The zero trading fee promotion for USD stablecoin applies to all existing and new USD stablecoin pairs...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Catawba Nation Is Seeking Seasoned Banking Regulators To Help Grow Their Bitcoin-Friendly Jurisdiction]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7572fe935d</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/legal/catawba-nation-is-seeking-seasoned-banking-regulators-for-bitcoin-friendly-jurisdiction"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T16:50:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Catawba Nation, a sovereign federally recognized tribal government, has established the Catawba Digital Economic Zone (CDEZ), a special jurisdiction within the Catawba Reservation in South Carolina, aimed at empowering emerging digital technology companies, including Bitcoin companies. The CDEZ has recently achieved a significant milestone with the enactment of the Banking and Financial Services Code, a comprehensive legal framework that combines the best practices from the financial codes of South Dakota, North Dakota and Wyoming.
The CDEZ Banking Commission, an integral part of the regulatory landscape within the jurisdiction, is now seeking experienced banking regulators and financial experts to shape the future of the zone's banking practices. The commission's responsibilities incl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BtcCasey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shibarium in July? Shiba Inu (SHIB) Executive Sends Mysterious Message]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18633934/Shibarium-in-July-Shiba-Inu-SHIB-Executive-Sends-Mysterious-Message</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18633934/Shibarium-in-July-Shiba-Inu-SHIB-Executive-Sends-Mysterious-Message"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T16:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shytoshi Kusama's announcement ignites SHIB army's craze]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alien Expedition Fund With Users’ Money? Cardano Founder Denies Accusations]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7572ff9294</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/cardano-founder-defends-himself-over-allegations/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T16:44:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano founder Charles Hoskinson recently got entangled in debate after sharing snapshots of his expedition to the ocean in search of an interstellar meteor. The snapshots from his search for the interstellar meteor brought mixed reactions from the crypto community, with some claiming Hoskinson was harming Cardano and ADA  deployment.
 
A critic responded to his post with a sarcastic remark, suggesting Hoskinson was spending others’ money, prompting the entrepreneur to defend himself in a series of tweets.
 
Hoskinson’s Defense
 
The commentator jested the Cardano founder in his comment, saying: “Hey everybody, check out how I’m spending your money.” And Hoskinson, offended by the jest, rebuked the fellow for implying that his money belonged to his followers. 
 
Related Reading: What is B…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kent Glory</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brazilian Lawmaker Seeks Binance Probe over Links to Pyramid Schemes]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7572ffe901</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/brazilian-lawmaker-seeks-binance-probe-over-links-to-pyramid-schemes/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T16:41:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance’s troubles with  
public authorities may compound in the coming days as  
Alfredo Gaspar, a Brazilian lawmaker, has requested that the country’s lower  
parliamentary house probe the cryptocurrency exchange over alleged connections  
to pyramid schemes in the country. Gaspar asked that  
Guilherme Nazar, Binance’s Country Manager in Brazil, be summoned before the  
chamber to testify as a witness in a Commission of Inquiry (CPI) investigation.
Lawmaker Justifies Probing Binance
According to Gaspar,  
Binance operates in Brazil through a representative firm, B Fintech Serviços de  
Tecnologia LTDA. Defending the request to summon Nazar, the lawmaker cited the  
media report of a pyramid scheme, Ever Operations and Investment, whose funds  
were held in a Binance account and blocked …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Solomon Oladipupo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beware of Fake Regulatory Claims by Crypto Firms, Warns Canadian Securities Administrators]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18633930/Beware-of-Fake-Regulatory-Claims-by-Crypto-Firms-Warns-Canadian-Securities-Administrators</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18633930/Beware-of-Fake-Regulatory-Claims-by-Crypto-Firms-Warns-Canadian-Securities-Administrators"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Canada’s crypto sector has seen a rise in the number of companies that falsely claim to be authorized to offer their services in the country, according to the Canadian Securities Administrators (CSA).  The authorities stated that several firms claimed to be affiliated with fictitious regulatory...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pepecoin Becomes Biggest Meme Coin Gainer With 70% Weekly Jump]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7572f835f8</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/06/22/pepecoin-becomes-biggest-meme-coin-gainer-with-70-weekly-jump/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T16:39:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The tokens racked up $800 million in trading volumes over the past 24 hours, data shows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s Ferocious ETF-Fueled Rally Puts Ether at Weakest Price Versus BTC in 2 Months]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18633928/Bitcoins-Ferocious-ETF-Fueled-Rally-Puts-Ether-at-Weakest-Price-Versus-BTC-in-2-Months</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18633928/Bitcoins-Ferocious-ETF-Fueled-Rally-Puts-Ether-at-Weakest-Price-Versus-BTC-in-2-Months"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T16:38:28.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TrueUSD Says TUSD Stablecoin Has ‘No Exposure’ to Embattled Prime Trust]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18633929/TrueUSD-Says-TUSD-Stablecoin-Has-No-Exposure-to-Embattled-Prime-Trust</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18633929/TrueUSD-Says-TUSD-Stablecoin-Has-No-Exposure-to-Embattled-Prime-Trust"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T16:37:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoin project TrueUSD said Thursday it had “no exposure” to embattled crypto services company Prime Trust as it raced to shore up confidence in its dollar-backed TUSD.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PEPE Outperforms SHIB, DOGE in Double-Digit Rebound Rally]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18633912/PEPE-Outperforms-SHIB-DOGE-in-Double-Digit-Rebound-Rally</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18633912/PEPE-Outperforms-SHIB-DOGE-in-Double-Digit-Rebound-Rally"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T16:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SHIB Jumps By 14% In A Single Day, As Shiba Inu “Worldpaper” Gets Closer]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18633916/SHIB-Jumps-By-14-In-A-Single-Day-As-Shiba-Inu-Worldpaper-Gets-Closer</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18633916/SHIB-Jumps-By-14-In-A-Single-Day-As-Shiba-Inu-Worldpaper-Gets-Closer"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T16:30:45.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Short-term Bitcoin holders signal positive market momentum as BTC breaks $30K]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18633910/Short-term-Bitcoin-holders-signal-positive-market-momentum-as-BTC-breaks-30K</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18633910/Short-term-Bitcoin-holders-signal-positive-market-momentum-as-BTC-breaks-30K"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T16:30:05.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Is How Scammers Can Drain Your Crypto Wallet]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7572f9ec20</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/06/22/social-engineering-ice-phishing-and-more-how-scammers-can-drain-your-crypto-wallet/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T16:27:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scammers use a variety of techniques to steal users’ money, some of which only require knowing your wallet address, a Forta Network researcher said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anna Baydakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Catawba Nation Is Seeking Seasoned Banking Regulators To Help Grow Their Bitcoin-Friendly Jurisdiction]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18633876/The-Catawba-Nation-Is-Seeking-Seasoned-Banking-Regulators-To-Help-Grow-Their-Bitcoin-Friendly-Jurisdiction</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18633876/The-Catawba-Nation-Is-Seeking-Seasoned-Banking-Regulators-To-Help-Grow-Their-Bitcoin-Friendly-Jurisdiction"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T16:27:17.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pepecoin Becomes Biggest Meme Coin Gainer With 70% Weekly Jump]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18633908/Pepecoin-Becomes-Biggest-Meme-Coin-Gainer-With-70-Weekly-Jump</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18633908/Pepecoin-Becomes-Biggest-Meme-Coin-Gainer-With-70-Weekly-Jump"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T16:25:42.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Arrows Co-Founders Are Back With a New VC Fund. Is Anyone Buying?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145792</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145792/three-arrows-co-founders-are-back-with-a-new-vc-fund-is-anyone-buying"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T16:24:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The co-founders of the bankrupt crypto hedge fund Three Arrows Capital (3AC) are launching a new investment venture.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SHIB Burn Sparks Up 6,936%, Boosting SHIB Above Key Support]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18633870/SHIB-Burn-Sparks-Up-6936-Boosting-SHIB-Above-Key-Support</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18633870/SHIB-Burn-Sparks-Up-6936-Boosting-SHIB-Above-Key-Support"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T16:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Micropayments Solution Volition Says It'll Make 'Crypto for Coffee Transactions Viable']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145598</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145598/ethereum-micropayments-solution-volition-says-itll-make-crypto-for-coffee-transactions-viable"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T16:15:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[StarkWare’s novel scaling functionality, Volition, promises to make it possible to reduce Ethereum gas fees by up to 90%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Micropayments Solution Volition Says It'll Make 'Crypto for Coffee Transactions Viable']]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18633869/Ethereum-Micropayments-Solution-Volition-Says-Itll-Make-Crypto-for-Coffee-Transactions-Viable</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18633869/Ethereum-Micropayments-Solution-Volition-Says-Itll-Make-Crypto-for-Coffee-Transactions-Viable"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T16:15:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[StarkWare’s novel scaling functionality, Volition, promises to make it possible to reduce Ethereum gas fees by up to 90%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Just Recorded Major Bullish Signal]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18633874/Bitcoin-BTC-Just-Recorded-Major-Bullish-Signal</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18633874/Bitcoin-BTC-Just-Recorded-Major-Bullish-Signal"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T16:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) has sent its moving average convergence divergence (MACD) cross into bullish territory for first time since late 2021]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uncertainty Returns After BitGo Cancels Prime Trust Acquisition]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7572e4bd76</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/uncertainty-returns-after-bitgo-cancels-prime-trust-acquisition"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T16:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BitGo's plans to acquire Prime Trust, a prominent custody firm, have taken an unexpected turn as BitGo recently announced on Twitter the cancellation of the acquisition. The initial announcement had generated excitement within the industry, as the consolidation of these two major custodians was expected to have a significant impact on the industry landscape.
In the preliminary announcement, BitGo highlighted its intentions to provide business continuity, long-term stability and secure services to Prime Trust clients. Prime Trust, expressing its enthusiasm for the partnership, believed that the combined company would revolutionize the future of custody services. Jor Law, Prime Trust's Interim CEO and President, stated, "No other company will have the breadth of product and services nor depth of experience that this combined company would have."
However, after considerable efforts and discussions, BitGo made the “hard decision” to terminate the acquisition. Although BitGo did not provide specific reasons for this change of course, the company emphasized its commitment to delivering trust in digital assets. The termination of the deal raises questions about the future trajectory of Prime Trust, as there were many rumors about the firm’s liquidity prior to the acquisition announcement.
The original acquisition decision came amidst developments in the custody landscape, with Bitcoin-only exchanges Strike and Swan both announcing their departure from custody services provided by Prime Trust. Strike switched to utilizing its own custody services, while Swan transitioned to BitGo and Fortress Trust, which was founded by Scott Purcell, the former founder of Prime Trust.
While the termination of the acquisition raises speculation about the financial health of Prime Trust, the recent announcement did not address or confirm these rumors. The industry will now eagerly await further details and clarifications from both BitGo and Prime Trust regarding their future plans and strategies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BtcCasey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitgo Abandons Acquisition of Prime Trust Amidst Nevada-Based Custodian’s Ongoing Uncertainty]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7572e55e56</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitgo-abandons-acquisition-of-prime-trust-amidst-nevada-based-custodians-ongoing-uncertainty/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T16:05:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On June 22, 2023, Bitgo, a digital assets firm and crypto custodian, declared the termination of its planned acquisition of custodian Prime Trust. The company cited a “considerable effort” in attempting to chart a course for Prime Trust’s future.
 
Bitgo Cancels Prime Trust Acquisition
 
A fortnight prior, Bitgo announced its intention to acquire Nevada-based crypto custodian Prime Trust through a letter of intent. However, Bitgo has now called off the acquisition and will not proceed with the Prime Trust agreement.
 
“After considerable effort and work to find a path forward with Prime Trust, Bitgo has made the hard decision to terminate its acquisition of Prime Trust,” Bitgo said on Thursday. “This decision was not made lightly and Bitgo remains committed to our mission to deliver trust …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arbitrum Devs Release Orbit Framework In Push For Ethereum L3’s]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7572e0dd71</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/arbitrum-release-orbit-in-push-for-ethereum-l3s/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T15:44:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arbitrum development team Offchain Labs tweeted today that it has released the Orbit framework to make it easier for developers to build applications. Orbit is a development framework for creating and launching layer-3 (L3) networks. Via Twitter, Offchain Labs announced:
 

Today, we’re releasing tooling that will make building your own Arbitrum Orbit chain easier than ever. To start, we’re providing a quickstart guide & tools to help you with building your Orbit DevNet chain!
 
Why Are L3’s Needed On Arbitrum?
 
Layer-3 networks are often referred to as AppChains. These are specialized networks that host a single distributed application. They are secured by layer-2 networks and take on the security guarantees of an underlying layer-1 Ethereum network.
 
With Arbitrum Orbit, developers can…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BitMEX’s CEO Calls For Crypto Exchanges To Ditch Internal Market Makers]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7572e9f7e2</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitmexs-calls-crypto-exchanges-ditch-market-makers/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T14:42:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the crypto landscape evolves, BitMEX’s acting CEO Stephan Lutz suggests that a change be made in the operational model of exchanges, specifically concerning their internal market-making teams.
 
Internal trading teams, often under the spotlight for possible conflict of interest, are now being questioned about their role in the modern cryptocurrency exchange structure. And Stephan Lutz, acting CEO and group CFO at BitMEX’s parent company, 100x Group, sees a shift in the landscape where the necessity for these teams is dwindling.
 
The Changing Role Of Internal Market Makers
 
According to Lutz, the abundance of High-Frequency Traders (HFTs) and proprietary trading firms currently operating could adequately replace the function of internal market-making teams. These external entities can …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Rise Of Crypto Giants: 4 Cryptocurrency Companies Make TIME 100 List]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7572e9f7db</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/the-rise-of-crypto-giants/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T14:42:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto takes the lead in the highly anticipated annual compilation of The TIME100 Most Influential Companies, which highlights the foremost innovators and disruptors in the global technology arena.
 
These companies, known for their transformative influence, represent the cutting edge of advancement, challenging limits and molding the future. Among this esteemed roster, the recognition of cryptocurrency stands out prominently, as this year’s edition features four distinguished cryptocurrency companies, along with numerous businesses that embrace the asset class.
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
By incorporating these digital pioneers, TIME100 acknowledges the profound influence and potential of the crypto industry in reshaping traditional financial systems and revolutionizing various sectors worldwide.
 
 

…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miner CleanSpark Claims Two Georgia Facilities For $9.3 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145779</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145779/bitcoin-miner-cleanspark-claims-two-georgia-facilities-for-9-3-million"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T14:18:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The facilities are expected to add nearly 1 exahash per second to CleanSpark's bitcoin mining capacity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Northstake Raises $3M to Boost Institutional Crypto Staking]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7572d5bc9b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/06/22/northstake-raises-3m-to-boost-institutional-crypto-staking/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T14:15:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2.8 million-euro fundraise comes from PreSeed Ventures, Morph Capital, The Aventures Fund, Funfair Ventures and Delta Blockchain Fund.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Startup Kaito Gets $87.5M Valuation in New Funding to Build AI Search Engine for Crypto]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7572d5bc95</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/06/22/startup-kaito-gets-875m-valuation-in-new-funding-to-build-ai-search-engine-for-crypto/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T14:15:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The search engine combines real-time data with large language models like ChatGPT.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliza Gkritsi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Custody Firm BitGo Cancels Acquisition of Rival Prime Trust]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7572d5bc8f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/06/22/cryptp-custody-firm-bitgo-cancels-prime-trust-acquisition/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T14:15:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prime Trust has been losing clients and deposits to competitors for weeks amid mounting concerns over its business, a source at one former client told CoinDesk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley, Danny Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pepe Surges Amidst Meme Coin Market Gains; Whales Accumulated Significant PEPE During Price Dip]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7572d5de91</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/pepe-surges-amidst-meme-coin-market-gains-whales-accumulated-significant-pepe-during-price-dip/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T14:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While the crypto economy has reached a value of $1.2 trillion, meme coin markets have experienced substantial gains this week, with the top five meme tokens recording both 24-hour and seven-day gains. According to recent data, pepe is leading the pack with a 34% increase in the last 24 hours and a 66% increase over the past week.
 
Whales Capitalize on Price Dip as Pepe Surges in Meme Coin Market
 
The meme coin economy witnessed a surge in value on June 22, 2023, with a 6.9% increase over 24 hours, bringing the current market valuation to $15.5 billion at 8:03 a.m. Eastern Time, June 22. Leading the market in terms of market cap, dogecoin (DOGE) has risen by 3% today and 8.3% over the past seven days. Following closely is shiba inu (SHIB), which experienced a 7.5% jump in 24 hours and a 1…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wintermute Backs DEX Vertex Protocol in Strategic Investment]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7572d7d470</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/06/22/wintermute-backs-dex-vertex-protocol-in-strategic-investment/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T14:01:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The amount of the investment wasn’t disclosed, and Wintermute will provide liquidity services to the decentralized exchange.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandy Betz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spot Bitcoin ETF Buzz: Valkyrie And Bitwise Make Headlines As Latest Applicants]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7572d2ee4d</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/spot-bitcoin-etf-buzz-valkyrie-and-bitwise/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T13:41:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Valkyrie intends to list its Bitcoin ETF fund on the Nasdaq with the ticker BRRR, with Bitwise also jumping on board.
 
 
Financial giants Valkyrie and Bitwise have joined the wave of applicants seeking approval for a spot Bitcoin Exchange-traded fund in the U.S.
 
BlackRock’s filing for a spot Bitcoin ETF has caused a significant market shift, resulting in a reversal of Bitcoin’s downward trajectory and a price surge of over 20%.
 
Bitcoin’s resurgence has led to increased market dominance, accounting for 50% of the overall cryptocurrency market, and has triggered heightened activity from large-scale investors known as whales.
 
 
Financial Giants Join The ETF Bandwagon
 
Valkyrie, a prominent player in the Bitcoin derivative products market, took a significant step toward introducing a s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ebo Victor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anichess Raises $1.5 Million to Put Magical Twist on Chess]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145770</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145770/anichess-raises-1-5-million-put-magical-twist-chess"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T13:01:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animoca Brands’ inventive play-and-earn riff on chess is supported by Chess.com and due to roll out in 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ali Shutler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Atomic Wallet Claims 'Less Than 0.1%' of Users Affected by $100M Hack]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145765</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145765/atomic-wallet-claims-less-than-0-1-of-users-affected-by-100m-hack"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T12:19:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Atomic Wallet team reported that they are working to recover the funds, but would not confirm how much money was stolen in the attack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Has Played Its Hinman Hand—Could It Help Coinbase?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145310</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145310/ripple-hinman-emails-coinbase"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T12:01:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How will the revelations in the Hinman emails play out for Ripple and Coinbase in their SEC court battles? Legal experts weigh in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PEPE's 79% Weekly Gains Lead Meme Coin Surge as DOGE, SHIB, FLOKI Up Double Digits]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145754</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145754/pepes-79-weekly-gains-lead-meme-coin-surge-as-doge-shib-floki-up-double-digits"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T11:05:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The meme coin sector posted impressive gains as market sentiment turned positive with Bitcoin’s breakout above $30,000.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Gains In-Principle Payments License in Singapore]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145750</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145750/ripple-gains-in-principle-payments-license-in-singapore"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T10:20:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse said the approval reaffirmed the company’s commitment to the Asia-Pacific region.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alys Key</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gods Unchained Hits Epic Games Store Ahead of Mobile Expansion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145727</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145727/gods-unchained-hits-epic-games-store-ahead-mobile-expansion"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T00:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The long-running NFT card game is now available in Epic’s popular marketplace, as part of a year of expansion for Gods Unchained.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gods Unchained Executive Producer Discusses Epic Games Store Move]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/hjLymzUL/gods-unchained-executive-producer-discusses-epic-games-store-move</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/hjLymzUL/gods-unchained-executive-producer-discusses-epic-games-store-move"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daniel Paez, Executive Producer on Immutable X-based card-battler Gods Unchained, discusses the long-running NFT game's launch on the Epic Games Store and the opportunity it provides.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New York City Spa Gets Heat for Heating with Bitcoin Mining]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145714</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145714/new-york-city-spa-gets-heat-for-heating-with-bitcoin-mining"/>
        <updated>2023-06-21T21:45:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bathhouse shared how the process works, inviting people to “enjoy a hot pool while supporting the Bitcoin network.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex- Barclays CEO Praises BlackRock Bitcoin ETF Filing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145713</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145713/blackrock-bitcoin-etf-filing-barclays-ceo-praise"/>
        <updated>2023-06-21T21:43:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto’s growth is just a natural part of an increasingly digitized world, says Bob Diamond.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF Printer Goes ‘BRRR’ as Valkyrie Refiles With SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145708</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145708/bitcoin-etf-valkyrie-updated-sec-filing-brrr-fund"/>
        <updated>2023-06-21T21:16:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A clever name for a proposed Bitcoin fund affirms recent trends in institutional adoption.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fed Chair Powell Says Bitcoin Has 'Staying Power' as an Asset Class]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145703</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145703/fed-chair-powell-says-bitcoin-has-staying-power-as-an-asset-class"/>
        <updated>2023-06-21T20:56:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“We do see payments stablecoins as a form of money," Powell said, adding that "the ultimate source of credibility in money is the central bank."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jeff Staple, Gmoney Drop 'Pigeon Shit' Cap Collab at Paris Fashion Week]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145690</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145690/jeff-staple-gmoney-drop-pigeon-shit-cap-collab-paris-fashion-week"/>
        <updated>2023-06-21T20:16:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 9dcc x Stapleverse baseball cap is sold via a redeemable NFT and can be digitally signed. The co-creators spoke to Decrypt in Paris.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Euny Hong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Congress Presses Forward on AI Regulation With Proposed Commission]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145685</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145685/ai-commission-proposed-us-congress"/>
        <updated>2023-06-21T19:54:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new bipartisan bid emerges to set a regulatory framework amid a global race to control how AI takes part in the society of the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Exec May Be Called to Testify in Brazil Over Alleged Pyramid Schemes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145666</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145666/binance-exec-may-be-called-to-testify-in-brazil-over-alleged-pyramid-schemes"/>
        <updated>2023-06-21T19:35:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Another day, another country signaling it has questions for its local Binance subsidiary.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zora Launches Layer-2 NFT Network to Battle Ethereum Gas Fees]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145650</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145650/zora-launches-layer-2-nft-netowrk-battle-ethereum-gas-fees"/>
        <updated>2023-06-21T19:34:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Co-founder Jacob Horne said Ethereum gas fees are a "systemic inhibitor" to Web3 adoption. The Zora Network aims to help.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lucy Harley-McKeown</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon Launches Its Own Copilot, a ChatGPT AI Assistant Chatbot]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145668</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145668/polygon-launches-chatgpt-ai-assistant-chatbot"/>
        <updated>2023-06-21T19:02:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ethereum scaling solution developer integrates OpenAI's ChatGPT to launch Polygon Copilot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Founder Vitalik Buterin Has Ties to SEC Darling Prometheum—Here's How]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145654</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145654/ethereum-founder-vitalik-buterin-prometheum-ties"/>
        <updated>2023-06-21T18:15:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It began when Feng Xiao, then-CEO of Wanxiang Blockchain Labs, befriended Buterin and purchased $500,000 worth of Ethereum in 2015.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Shoots Past $30,000 as Wall Street Eyes Up 'Digital Gold']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145628</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145628/bitcoin-hits-30000-wall-street-digital-gold"/>
        <updated>2023-06-21T16:20:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Big investors are feeling bullish about the biggest cryptocurrency—and the rest of the crypto market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Grammys Will Allow Songs Created With AI Help]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145561</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145561/grammys-will-allow-songs-created-ai-help"/>
        <updated>2023-06-21T16:10:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence can play a part in creating eligible music, but ultimately only a human can accept a Grammy award.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ali Shutler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Neutron Raises $10 Million to Develop Smart Contracts on Cosmos]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145599</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145599/neutron-raises-10-million-to-develop-smart-contracts-on-cosmos"/>
        <updated>2023-06-21T16:01:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neutron, a CosmWasm smart contract platform for the Cosmos "internet of blockchains," has raised $10 million in a funding round.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Startup Casa Expands Beyond BTC With Ethereum Vaults]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145642</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145642/bitcoin-startup-casa-expands-beyond-btc-ethereum-vaults"/>
        <updated>2023-06-21T16:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bitcoin-centric startup has embraced Ethereum, offering ETH holders self-custody vaults that require multiple signatures to transact.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alyssa Hertig</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Marvel's 'Secret Invasion' Show Uses Generative AI—And Fans and Creators Are Livid]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145613</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145613/marvels-secret-invasion-show-uses-generative-ai-and-fans-and-creators-are-livid"/>
        <updated>2023-06-21T14:56:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["It's utterly horrifying," said one artist of the realization that Marvel's latest comic book adaptation tapped AI tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ali Shutler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash, Stacks, and Pepe Lead Alts Parade as Bitcoin Breaks Above $29,000]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145590</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145590/bitcoin-cash-stacks-and-other-alts-jump-as-bitcoin-breaks-above-29000"/>
        <updated>2023-06-21T14:47:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin has brought the rest of the market with it as it closes in on $30,000, as altcoins follow in its wake.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Hits $29,000 Following BlackRock, WisdomTree, Invesco ETF Filings]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145586</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145586/bitcoin-hits-29000-following-blackrock-wisdomtree-invesco-etf-filings"/>
        <updated>2023-06-21T12:07:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The largest cryptocurrency has reclaimed $29,000 amid a wave of ETF filings in the U.S. and rising interest from institutional investors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ledger Investor Bpifrance Exploring ZK Proofs, AI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145570</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145570/ledger-investor-bpifrance-exploring-zk-proofs-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-06-21T11:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Publicly funded investment bank Bpifrance looms large in the French crypto scene. The firm’s crypto lead shared insights on its Web3 fund with Decrypt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wimbledon 2023 to Feature AI-Generated Highlights Commentary]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145572</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145572/wimbledon-2023-to-feature-ai-generated-highlights-commentary"/>
        <updated>2023-06-21T11:03:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Grand Slam tennis championship will use IBM’s artificial intelligence tech to produce audio commentary for highlights packages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alys Key</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Federal Agencies Form New U.S. Crypto Crime Task Force]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145569</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145569/federal-agencies-form-new-u-s-crypto-crime-task-force"/>
        <updated>2023-06-21T10:40:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Darknet Marketplace and Digital Currency Crimes Task Force formalizes a prior collaboration between five law enforcement agencies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WisdomTree, Invesco Follow BlackRock With Spot Bitcoin ETF Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145566</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145566/wisdomtree-invesco-follow-blackrock-with-spot-bitcoin-etf-applications"/>
        <updated>2023-06-21T09:11:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC is facing a fresh wave of spot Bitcoin ETF applications from major investment firms, in the wake of BlackRock's filing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Chatbots Like ChatGPT and Google Bard Don’t Meet EU Law Standards: Study]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145548</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145548/every-chatbot-chatgpt-google-bard-fail-eu-ai-law-standards"/>
        <updated>2023-06-21T00:44:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Stanford study also confirmed that open source models are much more transparent than the more popular—and profitable—models like ChatGPT and Bard.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bored Ape Creator's 'HV-MTL Forge' Mech Game Revealed]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145538</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145538/bored-ape-creators-hv-mtl-forge-mech-game-revealed"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T23:33:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The workshop-building game will launch on June 29 and use HV-MTL robot NFTs that previous Sewer Pass holders claimed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ava Labs Is the Latest Crypto Company to Launch an AI Chatbot]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145533</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145533/ava-labs-ai-chatbot-avagpt-crypto-network"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T23:20:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AvaGPT uses ChatGPT's API to quickly answer Avalanche network queries with immediate access to the source material.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Breaks $28K for the First Time Since May]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145528</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145528/bitcoin-above-28000-first-time-since-may-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T22:52:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[News of BlackRock's upcoming Bitcoin ETF filing sparked optimism in an otherwise battered and bruised crypto market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the Circus: Top 5 Absurd AI Tools You Should Try in 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145480</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145480/top-5-absurd-ai-tools-you-should-try-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T21:14:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We've got Twitter bots roasting humans, your photos turned into memes, AI cats, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Metaverse is Coming to Bitcoin, Declares Bitmap Theory]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145510</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145510/the-metaverse-is-coming-to-bitcoin-declares-bitmap-theory"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T21:10:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The project revolves around the idea that people can own individual blocks, leading to an inscription frenzy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miner Iris Energy Shares Pop 21% After Major Hash Rate Expansion Plans]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145479</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145479/iris-energy-shares-pop-21-after-major-hash-rate-expansion-plans"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T20:59:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After shrinking briefly in November, Iris Energy’s mining capacity is making a rapid comeback.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Snap Into the 'Meataverse'—Slim Jim Gives Away Free 'GigaJims' NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145476</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145476/snap-into-meataverse-slim-jim-gives-away-free-gigajims-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T20:58:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Snack brand Slim Jim's oddball Web3 play includes 10,000 free "GigaJims" NFTs on Polygon, which are available now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ali Shutler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Play-to-Earn Is Not Dead. It Will Never Die' Says Words with Friends Creator Paul Bettner]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/znmOo9vp/play-to-earn-is-not-dead-it-will-never-die-says-words-with-friends-creator-paul-bettner</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/znmOo9vp/play-to-earn-is-not-dead-it-will-never-die-says-words-with-friends-creator-paul-bettner"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T14:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Words With Friends and Wildcard Creator Paul Bettner tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about his perspective on Axie Infinity and Web3 games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cross the Ages Game Review: A Tough But Rewarding Card Battler]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/2PfzFDVY/cross-the-ages-game-review-a-tough-but-rewarding-card-battler</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/2PfzFDVY/cross-the-ages-game-review-a-tough-but-rewarding-card-battler"/>
        <updated>2023-06-18T12:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cross the Ages is a digital collectible card game that challenges players to duel online opponents—and you can even mint your cards as tradable NFTs. It's complex and difficult to grasp at first, but this mobile-first game has some serious strategic upside. GG contributor Ryan Gladwin puts Cross the Ages through its paces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["AI Is Game-Changing But Needs Fact-Checking": AlchemyAI Project Lead]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/HXlThlXv/ai-is-game-changing-but-needs-fact-checking-alchemyai-project-lead</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/HXlThlXv/ai-is-game-changing-but-needs-fact-checking-alchemyai-project-lead"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this interview, Decrypt's Jason Nelson chats with Alchemy product manager and AlchemyAI project lead Elan Halpern on blockchain analysis using ChatGPT, what AI means for better user experience, and the need to fact-check AI. Halpern also gives a demo of the new AlchemyAI ChatGPT plugin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fractal Is Like an Arcade, Says Twitch Co-Founder Justin Kan]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/6r6Mdwt6/fractal-is-like-an-arcade-says-twitch-co-founder-justin-kan</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/6r6Mdwt6/fractal-is-like-an-arcade-says-twitch-co-founder-justin-kan"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Justin Kan was a co-founder of Twitch and now works on Fractal, a Web3 gaming startup. Kan tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about his new company and what he's up to.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are NFTs the Next SEC Target?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/YaGgY87J/are-nfts-the-next-sec-target</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/YaGgY87J/are-nfts-the-next-sec-target"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T20:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin discusses the current regulatory climate in the U.S. with Gala Games' President of Blockchain Jason Brink.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Collab.Land Co-Founder Said There Was No ‘Aha Moment’ When Launching DAO Toolkit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/kcBRKFGk/collabland-co-founder-said-there-was-no-aha-moment-when-launching-dao-toolkit</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/kcBRKFGk/collabland-co-founder-said-there-was-no-aha-moment-when-launching-dao-toolkit"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T09:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CCO and co-founder of Collab.Land Anjali Young explained at this year’s NFC Lisbon the origins of the crypto community tool kit, which industry niches are turning to its suite of products, and what’s next for the project since its token distribution event last February.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Buying a Slice of H.R. Giger's 'Alien' Is Fine Art, Not Memorabilia: Particle CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/VACG0WVg/buying-a-slice-of-hr-gigers-alien-is-fine-art-not-memorabilia-particle-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/VACG0WVg/buying-a-slice-of-hr-gigers-alien-is-fine-art-not-memorabilia-particle-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T08:49:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With H.R. Giger's original "Alien" statue on full display at this year's NFC Lisbon, Particle CEO Harold Eytan told Decrypt that owning an NFT-ified slice of the piece isn't just for fans of the iconic creature and movie series but also for fine art collectors. Interested in owning a piece? Be prepared to cough up half an ETH for one of the 500 tranches of the digitized sculpture.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Community Co-Creation 'Is a Big Step for Fashion Brands' Entering the Metaverse: BNV Founder and CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/z6NSMnNm/community-co-creation-is-a-big-step-for-fashion-brands-entering-the-metaverse-bnv-founder-and-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/z6NSMnNm/community-co-creation-is-a-big-step-for-fashion-brands-entering-the-metaverse-bnv-founder-and-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T08:49:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The founder and CEO of metaverse fashion platform BNV Richard Hobbs said big brands are still nervous to let fans and community members customize their favorite garments. Still, he believes that as long as you can meet a firm's commercial bottom lines while stirring engagement, there's nothing to lose.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Standard Crypto VC Co-Founder on NFTs and Their Stigma in Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/bmtrrLio/standard-crypto-vc-co-founder-on-nfts-and-their-stigma-in-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/bmtrrLio/standard-crypto-vc-co-founder-on-nfts-and-their-stigma-in-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T18:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alok Vasudev is a co-founder of venture capital firm Standard Crypto. In an interview with Decrypt's Kate Irwin, he shares his thoughts on NFT marketing, NFT utility in gaming, and the stigma that pervades the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ava Labs Announces Avalanche Arcad3 for Game Developers at 3XP]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XPHp9r4j/ava-labs-announces-avalanche-arcad3-for-game-developers-at-3xp</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XPHp9r4j/ava-labs-announces-avalanche-arcad3-for-game-developers-at-3xp"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T15:21:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ava Labs Head of Gaming Ed Chang shares news with Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the crypto firm's latest push to help traditional game developers break into blockchain gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Like a Middle Finger to Western Culture’: YuYu Unpacks Inspiration Behind NFT Expo GAG]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Vuoplr6a/like-a-middle-finger-to-western-culture-yuyu-unpacks-inspiration-behind-nft-expo-gag</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Vuoplr6a/like-a-middle-finger-to-western-culture-yuyu-unpacks-inspiration-behind-nft-expo-gag"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T13:33:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At this year’s NFC Lisbon, multimedia artist and photographer YuLiang "YuYu" Liu broke down how themes from traditional painting and BDSM informed his latest NFT exhibition called “GAG.” He also shared exclusively with Decrypt a yet-to-be-launched drop for fans of his work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Competition Was Rather Low' in Mobile Wallet Space, Says Zerion Head of Growth]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/vCg8O2oy/competition-was-rather-low-in-mobile-wallet-space-says-zerion-head-of-growth</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/vCg8O2oy/competition-was-rather-low-in-mobile-wallet-space-says-zerion-head-of-growth"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T13:33:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zerion's move to launch a mobile-first crypto wallet not only helped NFT users swap jpegs on the go but was also a play to get away from crypto's desktop-centric user experience. And with such little competition, Zerion's head of growth Alexander Guy told Decrypt at NFC Lisbon it's managed to rake in 150,000 funded wallets. Next step? Taking on MetaMask and contending as a browser-extension wallet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘We’ve Never Seen Anything Like This in VR’, Says The Sandbox COO on Apple’s Vision Pro Headset]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/GQ29RaHw/weve-never-seen-anything-like-this-in-vr-says-the-sandbox-coo-on-apples-vision-pro-headset</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/GQ29RaHw/weve-never-seen-anything-like-this-in-vr-says-the-sandbox-coo-on-apples-vision-pro-headset"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T13:33:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Sandbox COO Sebastien Borget told Decrypt at this year’s NFC Lisbon that despite the high price point, Apple’s new VR headset is nonetheless “groundbreaking.” And though the tech giant never used the term “metaverse” in its reveal, Borget is sure that the technology will be key in growing participation in various digital worlds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Gala Safe? Gala Games Head of Blockchain on GALA, Crypto, and SEC Regulatory Turmoil]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5bcrE8nL/is-gala-safe-gala-games-head-of-blockchain-on-gala-crypto-and-sec-regulatory-turmoil</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5bcrE8nL/is-gala-safe-gala-games-head-of-blockchain-on-gala-crypto-and-sec-regulatory-turmoil"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T15:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gala Games President of Blockchain shares his thoughts on the GALA token upgrade and the latest SEC turmoil with Decrypt's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Artists Adopting NFTs Has Been ‘Really Market Dependent’, Says NFT Club Berlin’s Rebekka Revel]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/QKlIVlj3/artists-adopting-nfts-has-been-really-market-dependent-says-nft-club-berlins-rebekka-revel</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/QKlIVlj3/artists-adopting-nfts-has-been-really-market-dependent-says-nft-club-berlins-rebekka-revel"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T15:07:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Getting non-crypto artists to make the leap into Web3 comes in ebbs and flows according to the market’s bear and bull waves, says co-founder of NFT Club Berlin and Superteam Germany Rebekka Revel. But she’s hoping to change that by changing the narrative around digital collectibles, regardless of the market, one word at a time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big Brands Exploring Web3 to ‘Scale Up Their Super-fan Base’: Superduper Co-founder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/he6UzJwz/big-brands-exploring-web3-to-scale-up-their-super-fan-base-superduper-co-founder</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/he6UzJwz/big-brands-exploring-web3-to-scale-up-their-super-fan-base-superduper-co-founder"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T14:49:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Co-founder and co-CEO of Web3 media brand Superduper Dom Smith says big brands are eager to enter the space—they just don’t know how. Still, they all maintain a thesis of turning their communities into “super fans” that generate value for users as well as a firm’s bottom line.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How 1 Simple Question Kickstarted Performance Artist Foodmasku's Plunge Into NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/w86DMn3p/how-1-simple-question-kickstarted-performance-artist-foodmaskus-plunge-into-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/w86DMn3p/how-1-simple-question-kickstarted-performance-artist-foodmaskus-plunge-into-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T10:10:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As his food mask creations went viral on the Internet during the COVID lockdowns, reposted on TikTok and Instagram without his consent, he soon asked: "How do I protect my digital files?" Performance artist Foodmasku describes at this year's NFC Lisbon how that simple question spiraled into a minting collection after collection of his edible works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arianee CEO Pegs Wine and Spirits as Next 'Exciting' Industry to Make Web3 Leap]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Bo2NeG9Z/arianee-ceo-pegs-wine-and-spirits-as-next-exciting-industry-to-make-web3-leap</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Bo2NeG9Z/arianee-ceo-pegs-wine-and-spirits-as-next-exciting-industry-to-make-web3-leap"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T09:28:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CEO and co-founder of Arianee Pierre Nicolas Hurstel unpacks the wide spectrum of digital collectibles from 10,000 PFP collections to access passes for exclusive events. And with an unannounced big brand soon joining, Hurstel revealed at NFC Lisbon which kind of NFTs big brands are moving towards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why 'Words With Friends' Creator Paul Bettner is 'Allergic' to Pay-to-Win NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JkfOleb4/why-words-with-friends-creator-paul-bettner-is-allergic-to-pay-to-win-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JkfOleb4/why-words-with-friends-creator-paul-bettner-is-allergic-to-pay-to-win-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T20:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Words With Friends and Wildcard creator Paul Bettner tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about his perspective on what to do when NFTs become in-game characters and assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>