<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-11-22T19:12:23.495Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-11-22T19:12:23.495Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple CTO Explores XRP Impact In Context Of Forgoing IPO]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e749ec47aaa</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ripple-cto-xrp-impact-ipo/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T19:06:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent conversation on X, David “JoelKatz” Schwartz, the Chief Technology Officer of Ripple, delved into the intricate dynamics between XRP and the company’s decision to move away from a traditional Initial Public Offering (IPO). This discussion offers a deep dive into the strategic choices and financial nuances.
 
Ripple Is Like Amazon
 
Schwartz, who is known for his straightforward nature and open communication with the XRP community, initiated a thought-provoking dialogue about corporate governance in the context of the drama around OpenAI and Sam Altman.
 
He questioned the effectiveness of traditional corporate structures in big tech companies, remarking, “I was just thinking, maybe a board that’s not accountable to investors and leaving the CEO and employees out of the upside i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple CTO Explores XRP Impact In Context Of Forgoing IPO]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19056998/Ripple-CTO-Explores-XRP-Impact-In-Context-Of-Forgoing-IPO</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19056998/Ripple-CTO-Explores-XRP-Impact-In-Context-Of-Forgoing-IPO"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T19:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent conversation on X, David “JoelKatz” Schwartz, the Chief Technology Officer of Ripple, delved into the intricate dynamics between XRP and the company’s decision to move away from a traditional Initial Public Offering (IPO). This discussion offers a deep dive into the strategic choices...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock and the SEC Recently Met for Bitcoin Spot ETF Approval, It Has Been Revealed]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19056989/BlackRock-and-the-SEC-Recently-Met-for-Bitcoin-Spot-ETF-Approval-It-Has-Been-Revealed</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19056989/BlackRock-and-the-SEC-Recently-Met-for-Bitcoin-Spot-ETF-Approval-It-Has-Been-Revealed"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T18:54:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bloomberg analysts revealed that BlackRock and the SEC met on Monday to discuss the Bitcoin Spot ETF product. Continue Reading: BlackRock and the SEC Recently Met for Bitcoin Spot ETF Approval, It Has Been Revealed]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former SEC Branch Chief Lisa Braganca Analyzes Binance Probe and Crypto Industry Impact]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19056976/Former-SEC-Branch-Chief-Lisa-Braganca-Analyzes-Binance-Probe-and-Crypto-Industry-Impact</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19056976/Former-SEC-Branch-Chief-Lisa-Braganca-Analyzes-Binance-Probe-and-Crypto-Industry-Impact"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T18:48:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lisa Braganca, a former U.S. SEC branch chief, appeared on CNBC’s “Squawk Box” to discuss the criminal investigation into Binance following founder Changpeng Zhao’s guilty plea to money laundering charges. She explored the implications of this case for the broader cryptocurrency industry....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Whales load up on BLUR after Season 2 airdrop]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19056958/Whales-load-up-on-BLUR-after-Season-2-airdrop</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19056958/Whales-load-up-on-BLUR-after-Season-2-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T18:44:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BLUR has outperformed other altcoins with 35% upside Data shows increased whale buying after the end of the NFT marketplace’s season 2 airdrop. BLUR price reached a high of $0.52, its highest level since late May. Blur (BLUR) was outperforming with a massive 35% upside at the time of writing....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rare SMA20 Golden Cross Imminent on Altcoin; Is This a Bullish Sign?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19056950/Rare-SMA20-Golden-Cross-Imminent-on-Altcoin-Is-This-a-Bullish-Sign</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19056950/Rare-SMA20-Golden-Cross-Imminent-on-Altcoin-Is-This-a-Bullish-Sign"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T18:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amid the bearish trend that rocked the crypto market in the last 24 hours, with digital assets such as BNB taking a major hit, a prominent Bitcoin trader has argued that the overall altcoin market is on the verge of a parabolic breakout. In a recent tweet, a Bitcoin trader with the X username...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[S&P 500 Flirts With Key Resistance, VIX Drops, Nvidia In Focus: What's Driving Markets Wednesday?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19056957/SP-500-Flirts-With-Key-Resistance-VIX-Drops-Nvidia-In-Focus-Whats-Driving-Markets-Wednesday</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19056957/SP-500-Flirts-With-Key-Resistance-VIX-Drops-Nvidia-In-Focus-Whats-Driving-Markets-Wednesday"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T18:34:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wall Street is cloaked in green in the session leading up to Thanksgiving, with the S&P 500 index reaching 4,560 points, a level closely watched by analysts, at midday trading in New York. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple CLO optimistic following Binance settlement, lambasts SEC’s ‘juvenile behavior’]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19056944/Ripple-CLO-optimistic-following-Binance-settlement-lambasts-SECs-juvenile-behavior</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19056944/Ripple-CLO-optimistic-following-Binance-settlement-lambasts-SECs-juvenile-behavior"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T18:30:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Chief Legal Officer Stuart Alderoty believes the recent resolution of anti-money laundering violations by Binance via a settlement with the U.S. Department of Justice (DOJ) is a significant step towards aligning the crypto industry with essential legal and safety standards. Alderoty noted...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Worldcoin became a bit too volatile recently]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19056910/Why-Worldcoin-became-a-bit-too-volatile-recently</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19056910/Why-Worldcoin-became-a-bit-too-volatile-recently"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T18:30:01.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[1 out of 3 Cardano holders are in profit]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19056919/1-out-of-3-Cardano-holders-are-in-profit</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19056919/1-out-of-3-Cardano-holders-are-in-profit"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T18:29:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA) is one of the most popular layer-1 blockchains for decentralized apps (DApps), decentralized finance (DeFi), and Web3. Recently, … Continued]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Binance-CZ Deal Positive For The Crypto Sector? How Will 2024 Be For Bitcoin? When Will CZ Make a Comeback? Matrixport Answered]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19056934/Is-Binance-CZ-Deal-Positive-For-The-Crypto-Sector-How-Will-2024-Be-For-Bitcoin-When-Will-CZ-Make-a-Comeback-Matrixport-Answered</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19056934/Is-Binance-CZ-Deal-Positive-For-The-Crypto-Sector-How-Will-2024-Be-For-Bitcoin-When-Will-CZ-Make-a-Comeback-Matrixport-Answered"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T18:29:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the largest settlement in cryptocurrency history, Binance and CZ admitted their guilt. What will happen next? Continue Reading: Is Binance-CZ Deal Positive For The Crypto Sector? How Will 2024 Be For Bitcoin? When Will CZ Make a Comeback? Matrixport Answered]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mt.Gox Creditors Set To Start Receiving Repayments in 2023-2024]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19056932/MtGox-Creditors-Set-To-Start-Receiving-Repayments-in-2023-2024</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19056932/MtGox-Creditors-Set-To-Start-Receiving-Repayments-in-2023-2024"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T18:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2014, Mt.Gox suffered from the largest Bitcoin hack up to that point in time. Wu Blockchain announced on X today that Mt.Gox creditors received emails from the bankruptcy trustee. Due to the email, repayments of Mt.Gox creditors are expected to start this year, continuing into 2024. Wu...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THIS Is What CZ Will Be Investing In Soon]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19056913/THIS-Is-What-CZ-Will-Be-Investing-In-Soon</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19056913/THIS-Is-What-CZ-Will-Be-Investing-In-Soon"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T18:26:07.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s What You Need to Know About Binance’s New CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19056918/Heres-What-You-Need-to-Know-About-Binances-New-CEO</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19056918/Heres-What-You-Need-to-Know-About-Binances-New-CEO"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T18:25:24.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Court denies Sam Bankman-Fried’s latest request for release]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19056909/Court-denies-Sam-Bankman-Frieds-latest-request-for-release</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19056909/Court-denies-Sam-Bankman-Frieds-latest-request-for-release"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T18:20:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A fresh request from former FTX CEO Sam Bankman-Fried to get out of jail was denied by a court of appeals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Protocol: CZ's out, Altman's in, and Kraken's Sued]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e749ec2b896</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/11/22/the-protocol-czs-out-altmans-in-and-krakens-sued/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T18:19:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week's edition of The Protocol newsletter, we share a few trends stand out to close 2023: the proliferation of Ethereum layer-2 networks, the ascendancy of zero-knowledge cryptography and the appearance of tokens, smart contracts and now file hosting on the Bitcoin blockchain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bradley Keoun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) Sees “Systemic Buying,” Analyst Claims]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19056962/Ethereum-ETH-Sees-Systemic-Buying-Analyst-Claims</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19056962/Ethereum-ETH-Sees-Systemic-Buying-Analyst-Claims"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T18:15:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maarten Regterschot, a CryptoQuant contributing analyst, has identified a notable "systemic buying" trend in Ethereum (ETH) futures]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ordinals startup Taproot Wizards hires CTO after seed raise]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19056900/Bitcoin-ordinals-startup-Taproot-Wizards-hires-CTO-after-seed-raise</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19056900/Bitcoin-ordinals-startup-Taproot-Wizards-hires-CTO-after-seed-raise"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T18:08:37.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Audiobook Production Takes a Leap with AI Integration]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19056948/Audiobook-Production-Takes-a-Leap-with-AI-Integration</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19056948/Audiobook-Production-Takes-a-Leap-with-AI-Integration"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T18:07:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a significant development for the publishing industry, Project Gutenberg, in collaboration with Microsoft and MIT, has recently unveiled a groundbreaking project involving the production of 5,000 AI-generated audiobooks. This collaboration utilizes advanced neural text-to-speech technology to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Spot ETF: Grayscale Meets With SEC Division Responsible For Approvals]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e749eccaf74</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-spot-etf-grayscale/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T18:05:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent development, the asset manager Grayscale recently met with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) in a move that could suggest that the approval of a Spot Bitcoin ETF is on the horizon. 
 
Why Grayscale’s Meeting With SEC Is Significant
 
In a post on his X (formerly Twitter) platform, Bloomberg analyst James Seyffart made this development known and specifically stated that the meeting was with the SEC’s division of trading and markets, which took place on November 20. This development is significant as this division of the SEC is in charge of approving or denying proposed rule changes (in this case, as it relates to Grayscale’s Bitcoin Trust). 
 
 
Many had continued to speculate on the next steps following the SEC’s decision not to appeal the US Court of Appeals’ ruling…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Protocol: CZ's out, Altman's in, and Kraken's Sued]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19056901/The-Protocol-CZs-out-Altmans-in-and-Krakens-Sued</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19056901/The-Protocol-CZs-out-Altmans-in-and-Krakens-Sued"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T18:05:04.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon Whale Moves 15M MATIC As Traders Identify Arc Bottom]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19056879/Polygon-Whale-Moves-15M-MATIC-As-Traders-Identify-Arc-Bottom</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19056879/Polygon-Whale-Moves-15M-MATIC-As-Traders-Identify-Arc-Bottom"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T18:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency aficionados are thrilled over the flippening of 14,998,378 MATIC tokens, but is the bottom really in?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celebrating Kaspa’s 2nd Birthday: $1M Airdrop Campaign With OKX, Coinpal.io]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e749ecd417b</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/celebrating-kaspas-2nd-birthday-1m-airdrop-campaign-with-okx-coinpal-io/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T18:01:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. Massachusetts, USA, November 22nd, 2023, Chainwire. Kaspa, the revolutionary open-source, decentralized, and fully scalable Layer-1 blockchain network, is thrilled to announce its 2nd birthday celebration. To commemorate this significant milestone, together with industry leaders Coinpal.io, OKX Web3, ICERIVER, IGV, and Rhubarb Media to launch a spectacular 1 Million Airdrop Campaign. This campaign will take place exclusively on OKX Cryptopedia, offering participants the chance to receive $1 million USD worth of $KAS and the exclusive, custom-designed NFT – KASBOTS with no cost!
 
Kaspa – Fast, Safe, and Decentralized – The cradle of a true peer-to-peer blockchain payment system
 
Kaspa is not just any blockchain; it stands as a groundbreaking achievement in the world of dece…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hope for Future Generations: How Bitcoin is Shaping a Unified Global Community]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19056868/Hope-for-Future-Generations-How-Bitcoin-is-Shaping-a-Unified-Global-Community</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19056868/Hope-for-Future-Generations-How-Bitcoin-is-Shaping-a-Unified-Global-Community"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T18:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin represents a beacon of hope for future generations, offering more than just a financial revolution. It embodies the essence of community and shared belief, uniting people across the globe with a common vision. As Bitcoin's culture expands, it fosters a sense of belonging and purpose,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is A Bitcoiner?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e749ec9e409</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/what-is-a-bitcoiner"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T17:29:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When bitcoin adoption reaches a global scale, it is likely there will no longer be bitcoin podcasts, bitcoin conferences or even, sorry to say this, a need for a Bitcoin Magazine. However, until this point, people interested in bitcoin will be differentiated from those who are yet to begin their journey down the bitcoin rabbit hole. The question is then raised, how does a bitcoiner describe themselves to others, that may help bridge the chasm between their own understanding and those still plugged into The Matrix?
Given the inflationary policies of successive governments, globally (see Rune Østgård excellent book Fraudcoin for more information), nearly everyone with resources has had to become an “investor” simply to attempt to maintain purchasing power overtime. 
People who want to own th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rupert Matthews</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin and Ethereum Trade Sideways as Binance Turmoil Drops BNB 11%]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207034</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207034/bitcoin-and-ethereum-trade-sideways-as-binance-turmoil-drops-bnb-11"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T17:22:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance's BNB token continued to drop hard Wednesday following the U.S. Department of Justice's announcement yesterday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why On-Chain Transaction Is the Key Blockchain Indicator]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e749eb5b052</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/11/22/why-on-chain-transaction-is-the-key-blockchain-indicator/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T17:04:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The metric helps investors and users to understand whether a blockchain is going to merely survive, or thrive, says Todd Groth, head of research at CoinDesk Indices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Todd Groth, CFA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tokenization and Real-World Assets Take Center Stage]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e749eb5b022</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/11/22/tokenization-and-real-world-assets-take-center-stage/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T17:04:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blue-chip institutions including Goldman Sachs and J.P. Morgan are trialing digital asset offerings, seeking cost savings and efficiencies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Gaffney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Active Addresses Spike, What Does It Mean?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e749eb5d783</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-active-addresses-spike-what-does-it-mean/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T17:03:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data shows the Ethereum active addresses have observed a large spike recently. Here’s what this could mean for ETH’s price.
 
Ethereum Daily Active Addresses Have Seen A Surge Recently
 
According to data from the on-chain analytics firm Santiment, the ETH active addresses are currently at their second-highest level since the middle of September. The “active addresses” here refer to those addresses on the Ethereum blockchain that are taking part in some sort of transaction activity.
 
In the context of the current discussion, the unique number of these active addresses is of interest. Note that this metric takes into account both the senders and receivers.
 
The active addresses may be considered analogous to the unique users present on the network, so their number can provide hin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Genesis Alleges Multi-Million Dollar Preferential Transfers by Gemini Amidst Crypto Turmoil]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e749eb602f6</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/genesis-alleges-multi-million-dollar-preferential-transfers-by-gemini-amidst-crypto-turmoil/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T17:02:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent legal move, Digital Currency Group’s (DCG) subsidiary Genesis Global Capital LLC has filed a complaint against the crypto exchange platform and custodian Gemini. Genesis hopes to claw back $689 million from the centralized crypto trading platform founded by Cameron and Tyler Winklevoss in 2014. 
 
Genesis Targets Gemini in $689M Legal Battle Over Alleged Preferential Crypto Withdrawals
 
The court filing, filed on November 21, 2023, accuses Gemini of withdrawing over $689 million in the months leading to Genesis’ Chapter 11 bankruptcy proceedings. This action, according to Genesis, unfairly benefited Gemini at the expense of other creditors.
 
The complaint, filed in the wake of significant crypto market instability that began in 2022, targets transactions occurring in the 90 days preceding Genesis’ bankruptcy declaration. According to the document, Gemini’s withdrawals totaled approximately $689.30 million, a move Genesis describes as preferential and detrimental to the broader creditor base.
 
This situation arose during a period marked by notable fluctuations and uncertainty within the cryptocurrency sector, further complicating the financial dynamics at play. Genesis’ legal strategy aims to invoke the provisions of the Bankruptcy Code to rectify what it perceives as an inequitable situation.
 
 
By doing so, they intend to recover the withdrawn funds in a clawback, thereby restoring a level playing field among all of Genesis’ creditors. The lawyers insist the focus is not just on the monetary aspect but also on the principles of fairness and equitable treatment in bankruptcy proceedings.
 
The complaint details the significant withdrawals by Gemini, characterizing them as preferential transfers. These actions, as per the filing, allowed Gemini to allegedly gain an advantage over other creditors, an advantage that Genesis seeks to nullify.
 
What do you think about the Genesis court filing against Gemini? Share your thoughts and opinions about this subject in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bit.Store Introduces Privacy-First Virtual Crypto Mastercard and Unveils Website’s New Look]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e749eb3edb0</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bit-store-introduces-privacy-first-virtual-crypto-mastercard-and-unveils-websites-new-look/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T16:24:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. Bit.Store, a pioneer in the Web3 revolution, is delighted to introduce its freshly redesigned website and the official release of the Bit.Store Virtual Crypto Card. With an unwavering commitment to facilitating seamless crypto transactions, Bit.Store is actively shaping the future of digital payments, making it more accessible to all through its innovative card solutions.
 
Embrace the new face of Bit.Store, where the website’s transformation reflects a user-first philosophy. The redesign crystallizes Bit.Store’s commitment to a superior user journey, marrying sleek modernity with the brand’s pioneering essence.
 
The website overhaul showcases a sleek layout that prioritizes ease and efficiency. Users are greeted with clean lines, simplified content, and adaptive design, en…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance’s $4.3 Billion Fine: Trigger For Massive Bitcoin And Crypto Sell-Off?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e749ebde8e8</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/binance-fine-trigger-bitcoin-crypto-sell-off/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T16:11:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday, November 21, Binance, the world’s largest cryptocurrency exchange, and its CEO Changpeng Zhao (CZ) consented to a $4.3 billion settlement with the US Department of Justice. This decision follows charges of money laundering, unlicensed money transmitting, and US sanctions violations. As part of the settlement, Binance will pay $4.3 billion, while CZ personally agreed to a $50 million fine, as Bitcoinist reported.
 
Massive Bitcoin And Crypto Sell-Off Incoming?
 
Following the news, the crypto community buzzed with a flurry of speculations and insights. Matrixport, a prominent digital asset platform, noted that before the settlement, on-chain data indicated Binance had moved a substantial $3.9 billion in USDT across its various wallets.
 
Mike Alfred, a vocal critic of Binance and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[1 Way to Revive Dead NFT Wallets]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e749ebe15a5</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/11/22/1-way-to-revive-dead-nft-wallets/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T16:10:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Conceptual artist and legal scholar Brian Frye says inaccessible crypto tokens cannot be sold, but can be donated — with potentially significant tax benefits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian  Frye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[State Adoption: A Trojan Horse Challenging Core Tenet's Of Personal Liberty]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e749ebe71bd</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/state-adoption-a-trojan-horse-challenging-core-tenets-of-personal-liberty"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T16:07:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The saying “government will ban Bitcoin” is one of the most frequently used pieces of FUD. It is something that every Bitcoiner intellectually wrestles with on their journey down the Bitcoin rabbit hole. It is a frequently cited reason by those skeptical of Bitcoin to justify their reluctance to explore further education. Thankfully many excellent writers have written extensively debunking this piece of FUD. Bitcoiners often emphasize the logistical challenges, intense resource costs, game-theoretical complexities, and the sheer implausibility of any attempt by the State to outlaw Bitcoin. While Bitcoiners hail these writings as compelling evidence of the inevitable advent of hyperbitcoinization, the subsequent logical question is frequently unexamined or hastily dismissed: If the governme…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Matulef</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Heco Bridge Breach Drains $86 Million — Justin Sun’s HTX-Linked Venture Faces Major Security Setback]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e749ea79eac</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/heco-bridge-breach-drains-86-million-justin-suns-htx-linked-venture-faces-major-security-setback/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T15:11:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Numerous sources have reported that the Heco Bridge, a cross-chain conduit linking Ethereum with the Heco blockchain, has suffered a security breach, resulting in a loss of $86 million. Subsequent to the heist, the stolen funds were redirected to various decentralized exchange (dex) platforms.
 
Major $86 Million Theft Hits Heco Bridge
 
In a recent setback for a venture linked to Tron’s creator, Justin Sun, it’s estimated that $85 to $86 million has been drained from the Heco Bridge. Blockchain security firms Cyvers and Peckshield raised the alarm about this breach, stating, “Our initial analysis indicates the suspicious $86.6m outflow from Heco Chain bridge was from a compromised operator, which was operational since [October 8, 2022].”
 
In a strategic move in 2022, Sun combined HTX’s Heco Chain with the Tron and Bittorrent blockchains, aiming to foster a more integrated platform and promote cooperation between developers from Heco, Tron, and Bittorrent. Recently, Sun’s ventures have been recurrent targets of significant cyber attacks, including the HTX (formerly Huobi) hack, the Poloniex breach, and the latest Heco Chain incident.
 
 
Currently, the perpetrator’s wallet holds 30,949 ether, valued at $62.83 million, which is only a portion of the total stolen amount. As of 9:00 a.m. Eastern Time on November 22, 2023, there has been no update from Heco Chain’s X account regarding the situation. However, Sun has addressed the issue on social media, revealing that HTX is preparing to compensate for the lost funds.
 
“HTX will fully compensate for HTX’s hot wallet Losses,” Sun wrote. “Deposits and withdrawals [are] temporarily suspended. All funds in HTX are secure, and the community can rest assured. We are investigating the specific reasons for the hacker attack. Once we complete the investigation and identify the cause, we will resume services.”
 
Why do you think Justin Sun-linked projects are being attacked? Share your thoughts and opinions about this subject in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple CLO Raises Pertinent Questions About The $4 Billion Binance Deal]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e749ea7e7a8</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ripple-clo-questions-binance-deal/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T15:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the wake of Binance’s settlement with the Department of Justice (DOJ), Ripple’s Chief Legal Officer (CLO) Stuart Alderoty has highlighted an important point as it relates to crypto regulation in the country. 
 
Crypto Tokens Are Not Securities
 
In a post on his X (formerly Twitter) platform, Alderoty questioned the Securities and Exchange Commission’s (SEC) stance on crypto tokens. He noted that neither did the DOJ mention anything about Binance violating securities laws or that the crypto tokens on the exchange were securities in the charges it brought against the foremost crypto exchange in the world. 
 
 
As he rightly mentioned, the DOJ didn’t make any statement to suggest that crypto tokens were securities in line with the view that the SEC already holds. This is despite the fact …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Mover Americas: Binance, Binance, Binance]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e749eac2b08</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/11/22/first-mover-americas-binance-binance-binance/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T14:41:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest price moves in bitcoin [BTC] and crypto markets in context for Nov. 22, 2023. First Mover is CoinDesk’s daily newsletter that contextualizes the latest actions in the crypto markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lyllah Ledesma, Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Justin Sun Confirms HTX, Heco Chain Exploited After $100M in Suspicious Transfers]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e749eac2ac7</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/11/22/justin-sun-confirms-htx-heco-chain-exploited-after-100m-in-suspicious-transfers/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T14:41:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HTX withdrawals and deposits have been temporarily suspended, and all losses will be covered by the exchange, Sun said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond Borders: The Intricacies of CBDCs and CFMs]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e749eacfcff</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/beyond-borders-the-intricacies-of-cbdcs-and-cfms/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T14:35:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the pursuit of modernizing 
payment systems and future-proofing central banking in the digital age, central 
banks worldwide are exploring Central Bank Digital Currencies (CBDCs). 
CBDCs, as digital liabilities of central banks, hold the potential to 
revolutionize cross-border transactions, reshaping the dynamics of global 
finance. In that regard, the intricate relationship between CBDCs, capital flow 
management measures (CFMs), and the evolving landscape of cross-border 
transactions are well worthy of exploring.
 
CBDCs Paving the Way 
for Cross-Border Advancements
 
Cross-border payments, 
especially at the retail level, face inherent challenges such as sluggish 
processes and high costs. CBDCs, viewed as a "clean slate," have the 
potential to act as a catalyst for seamless cross…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Ferreira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bizarre Twist: Sam Altman Makes A Surprise Return To OpenAI As CEO]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e749e944909</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/sam-altman-makes-a-surprise-return-to-openai-as-ceo/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T13:48:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following a tumultuous five-day power struggle within OpenAI’s board, Sam Altman stages a triumphant return, joining forces once again with co-founder Greg Brockman amidst the unfolding drama.
 
In a startling turn of events, Altman has made a decisive agreement to reclaim the helm at OpenAI, as revealed in a Wednesday post on X. His unexpected removal as CEO triggered a fierce backlash from employees, casting shadows over the once-pioneering company in the burgeoning artificial intelligence industry.
 
 
Unexpected Turn Of Events
 
 
i love openai, and everything i’ve done over the past few days has been in service of keeping this team and its mission together. when i decided to join msft on sun evening, it was clear that was the best path for me and the team. with the new board and w sat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin in Bundestag: Germany's Bold Leap into Cryptocurrency Recognition]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e749e94875e</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/bitcoin-in-bundestag-germanys-bold-leap-into-cryptocurrency-recognition/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T13:46:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an unexpected move that 
could reshape the financial terrain, Joana Cotar, a member of the German 
Bundestag, has put forward the idea of recognizing Bitcoin as legal tender in 
Germany. This revelation, occurring amid a global surge in cryptocurrency interest, 
suggests Germany's potential leadership in adopting decentralized digital 
currency at a governmental level. The implications extend beyond 
cryptocurrency, indicating a broader shift in economic ideology—one that aligns 
with the principles of proactive economic policies.
 
 

 
A Distinct Focus on 
Bitcoin: Shaping a New Financial Narrative
 
Cotar's initiative, labeled 
"Bitcoin in the Bundestag," seeks not only to integrate Bitcoin into 
mainstream financial processes but also to educate parliamentary peers on its 
benefits.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Ferreira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale Met With SEC to Discuss Spot Bitcoin ETF Bid]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207009</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207009/grayscale-met-with-sec-to-discuss-spot-bitcoin-etf-bid"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T11:06:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to a memo published by the SEC, officials from the Division of Trading and Markets met with Grayscale's CEO and other principals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Altman Reinstated as OpenAI CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=207003</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/207003/sam-altman-reinstated-as-openai-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T09:52:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following a week of turmoil at OpenAI that saw Sam Altman leave the ChatGPT developer, Altman will return as CEO of the firm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Needs ‘Rules of the Road’: Apple CEO Tim Cook]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206985</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206985/tim-cook-on-ai-regulation-apple-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T02:40:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple's Tim Cook spoke with Dua Lipa about AI's potential and the necessity for regulatory frameworks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cruise CEO Steps Down Amid Self-Driving Car Safety Crisis]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206979</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206979/cruise-autonomous-self-driving-car-safety-ceo-resignation"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T02:02:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kyle Vogt said he was optimistic about his business, but regulatory actions may have made moving forward untenable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic Upgrades Claude With Nearly Twice The Capabilities of GPT-4 Turbo]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206966</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206966/anthropic-upgrades-claude-with-nearly-twice-the-capabilities-of-gpt-4-turbo"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T01:01:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While the drama at OpenAI captures most of the attention, OpenAI challenger Anthropic delivers the latest version of its capable chatbot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ubisoft's 'Champions Tactics' NFT Game Is Coming to Animoca's 'Mocaverse']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206941</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206941/ubisoft-champions-tactics-nft-game-coming-animoca-mocaverse"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T00:26:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animoca Brands and Ubisoft are teaming up to add Champions Tactics to the Mocaverse Frequent Player Program.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why 'Cyberpunk 2077: Ultimate Edition' Needs 3 Discs on Xbox]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206946</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206946/why-cyberpunk-2077-ultimate-edition-needs-3-discs-xbox"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T23:51:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The expanded version of Cyberpunk 2077 is coming to PC, PS5, and Xbox—but only one version ships with three discs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Bitcoin Better Off Without CZ Helming Binance?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206919</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206919/is-bitcoin-better-off-without-cz-helming-binance"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T23:31:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The exit of its CEO suggests a resurgence in U.S. regulatory pressure, but how relevant is the development to borderless cryptocurrencies?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Will a Post-CZ Binance Look Like?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206931</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206931/what-will-binance-be-like-without-ceo-cz"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T23:01:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Market experts weigh in on how the embattled exchange moves forward—will Binance’s status fall without CZ at the helm?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Crypto Isn't Going Anywhere': Industry Leaders Weigh In on Binance Crackdown]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206918</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206918/crypto-isnt-going-anywhere-industry-leaders-react-binance-crackdown"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T22:39:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Industry response to CZ’s guilty plea and Binance’s shakeup has been mixed, with some arguing that the news is actually good for crypto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Binance Founder Changpeng Zhao Go to Prison?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206905</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206905/will-binance-founder-changpeng-zhao-go-to-prison"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T22:21:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What are the odds the fallen Binance CEO will join Sam Bankman-Fried on the prison yard? Here's a look at what Changpeng "CZ" Zhao is facing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Allie Eve Knox on Spankchain and the life of a Crypto Financial Dominatrix]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/16rVeg6o/allie-eve-knox-on-spankchain-and-the-life-of-a-crypto-financial-dominatrix</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/16rVeg6o/allie-eve-knox-on-spankchain-and-the-life-of-a-crypto-financial-dominatrix"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T21:20:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the first IRL episode of This Time Will Be Different!

In this week's episode, our host, Reza Jafery, is joined by Allie Eve Knox, the Spankchain Chief of Staff and FinDomme. 

They discuss
- How to sell feet pics
- If crypto is really as permissionless as it seems
- the intersections between crypto and sex work]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Must 'Completely Exit' From US as It Settles Years-Long Criminal Investigation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206904</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206904/binance-must-completely-exit-from-us-as-it-settles-years-long-criminal-investigation"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T20:55:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The $4.3 billion settlement is one of the largest corporate penalties in U.S. history, says DOJ.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance's CZ: 'I Made Mistakes', Confirms Richard Teng Will Take Over as CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206907</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206907/binances-cz-i-made-mistakes-confirms-richard-teng-will-takeover-as-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T20:44:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance founder Changpeng Zhao has resigned as CEO, and confirmed that Richard Teng will take over the role.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Someone Got $8.4 Million in Blur NFT Marketplace's Latest Airdrop]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206893</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206893/someone-got-8-4-million-blur-nft-marketplace-latest-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T19:45:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One JPEG flipper saw millions of dollars in rewards from Blur's Season 2 airdrop. Now the marketplace is teasing its own Ethereum layer-2 network, Blast.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Degens Have Already Found a Way to Make Money on CZ Stepping Down]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206885</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206885/degens-make-money-ethereum-token-cz-stepping-down"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T18:42:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A freshly launched token called "CZ" is already trading on Ethereum DeFi exchange Uniswap—and up 18,000%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BNB Plunges as Crypto Market Reacts to Binance CEO Stunner]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206884</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206884/bnb-plunges-crypto-market-reacts-binance-ceo-stunner"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T18:14:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance and CEO Changpeng Zhao will reportedly plead guilty today amid a settlement with the U.S. DOJ. BNB quickly tumbled on the news.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao to Step Down, Plead Guilty to Money Laundering]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206873</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206873/binance-ceo-changpeng-zhao-step-down-plead-guilty"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T17:47:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CZ is out, but Binance survives as part of a DOJ settlement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bounces as DOJ Preps to Make Binance Settlement Official]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206840</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206840/bitcoin-bounces-doj-binance-settlement"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T16:55:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Binance settlement bullish for Bitcoin? The market seems to think so.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fortnite's Big Bang Event Marks 'New Beginning' for Epic’s Smash Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206827</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206827/fortnite-big-bang-event-marks-new-beginning"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T15:11:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The current Fortnite OG season will end in early December, and Epic Games is teasing massive new developments for the free-to-play shooter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken Co-Founder Jesse Powell: SEC 'USA's Top Decel']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206814</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206814/kraken-co-founder-jesse-powell-sec-usas-top-decel"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T12:17:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Powell accused the SEC of extortion after the regulator leveled new charges at the crypto exchange, including commingling customer funds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI In 'Intense Discussions' to Prevent Staff Exodus: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206804</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206804/openai-in-intense-discussions-to-prevent-staff-exodus-report"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T10:43:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With 90% of OpenAI staff threatening to follow ousted CEO Sam Altman to Microsoft, investors are reportedly exploring legal options.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Drug Giant AstraZeneca Launches Evinova to Quicken Clinical Trials]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206789</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206789/astrazeneca-launches-evinova-faster-clinical-trials"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T01:03:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Evinova aims to use AI to design studies, automate cost calculations, and determine feasibility for drug testing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ubisoft Halts Twitter Ads, Joining IBM, Apple, Disney, Warner Bros.]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206780</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206780/ubisoft-halts-twitter-ads-joining-ibm-apple-disney-warner-bros"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T00:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ads are reportedly being placed next to antisemitic posts on Twitter, and some of the biggest entertainment and tech firms—like Ubisoft—want out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BONK Goes Boom: Solana Meme Coin Soars 1,700% in 30 Days to Hit All-Time High]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206788</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206788/bonk-goes-boom-solana-meme-token-soars-1700-30-days-hit-all-time-high"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T23:57:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Granted, BONK promptly fell 29% after hitting that peak, but the Solana meme coin has still doubled in price over the past week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WLD Had a Wild Weekend—What's Next for Sam Altman's Worldcoin?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206758</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206758/wld-wild-weekend-whats-next-sam-altman-worldcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T23:38:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the Altman and OpenAI drama unfolds, Worldcoin remains quiet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pyth Airdrop Puts $77 Million in the Wallets of Crypto Users]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206754</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206754/pyth-airdrop-puts-77-million-wallets-crypto-users"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T23:16:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Upstart crypto exchange Backpack also airdropped the Solana-based PYTH token to tens of thousands of new users as a reward.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[As ‘Decels’ Rise, Meta Dissolves Its Responsible AI Team]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206777</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206777/meta-dissolves-responsible-ai-team"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T23:12:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As calls to slow development of artificial intelligence to ensure safety grow louder, Meta is broadening its efforts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Files Charges Against Crypto Exchange Kraken—Again]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206775</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206775/sec-files-charges-against-crypto-exchange-kraken-again"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T22:40:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The United States regulator has filed fresh charges against Kraken, just nine months after settling previous charges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Exchange Bittrex Global Shuts Down Following Battle With SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206761</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206761/crypto-bittrex-global-shuts-down-sec"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T22:26:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Another crypto business has bit the dust. Bittrex Global is winding down operations following the closure of its U.S. exchange in March.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Argentina's Next President Says It's OK to Sell Babies—Here's Why Bitcoin Lovers Love Him]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206724</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206724/argentina-next-president-says-ok-sell-babies-why-bitcoin-lovers-love-him"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T20:41:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin maximalists and crypto industry leaders are celebrating the rise of Javier Milei, in the hopes the controversial politician will benefit crypto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will AI Use Crypto? Here’s What’s Driving AI Token FOMO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206730</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206730/ai-crypto-whats-driving-ai-token-fomo"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T20:05:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Will crypto be the currency of choice for the AI of the future? Crypto investors are betting on it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Hover Near Yearly Highs as ETF Hopes Stay Alive]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206705</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206705/bitcoin-ethereum-near-yearly-highs-on-etf-hopes"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T19:55:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin is hovering near $38,000 and Ethereum has been able to stay above $2,000 as the global crypto market cap nears $1.5 trillion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who Is Emmett Shear? New OpenAI CEO Is an AI 'Doomer' Who Thinks It Might Kill Us All]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206718</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206718/who-emmett-shear-new-openai-ceo-ai-doomer-thinks-might-kill-us-all"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T19:27:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Emmett Shear has a long history in tech, primarily focused on livestreaming platform Twitch. But what is Shear's approach to AI development?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Oops, You Stepped Into the Future': Nike Drops Sneakers With NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206706</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206706/oops-you-stepped-future-nike-drops-sneakers-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T18:31:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You don't need to own an expensive NFT to buy the latest Nike x RTFKT sneakers—and they actually come with NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOJ Is Seeking $4 Billion From Binance, Criminal Charges Against CZ]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206716</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206716/doj-seeking-4-billion-binance-settlement-cz-criminal-charges"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T18:23:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The DOJ's negotiations include possible criminal charges against Binance's founder and CEO Changpeng Zhao, but would allow Binance to keep operating.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Questions With SCENE: Jeff Davis]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PChJu1R8/5-questions-with-scene-jeff-davis</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PChJu1R8/5-questions-with-scene-jeff-davis"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artist Jeff Davis joins 5 Questions with SCENE to answer burning questions about his artistic practice, the path that brought him to Art Blocks, and his quietly sophisticated DJ abilities.

Video shot and edited by Vincent Roazzi Jr.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Heatbit Founder Alex Busarov on the Bitcoin Miner That Heats Your Home]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DJuHqcGT/heatbit-founder-alex-busarov-on-the-bitcoin-miner-that-heats-your-home</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DJuHqcGT/heatbit-founder-alex-busarov-on-the-bitcoin-miner-that-heats-your-home"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T18:12:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt joined Heatbit founder Alex Busarov at Web Summit for a walkthrough of the firm's flagship product, a Bitcoin miner that acts as a domestic space heater—aimed at the casual user.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nym CEO Harry Halpin on Privacy, Decentralized VPNs and Tornado Cash]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/aLTtY2aq/nym-ceo-harry-halpin-on-privacy-decentralized-vpns-and-tornado-cash</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/aLTtY2aq/nym-ceo-harry-halpin-on-privacy-decentralized-vpns-and-tornado-cash"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T18:08:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The founder of privacy-preserving mixnet Nym sat down with Decrypt at Web Summit to talk about its new decentralized VPN, the Web3 privacy landscape and why "devs should be defended" in the wake of the Tornado Cash crackdown.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pat Felder - The worst is over [Macro Deep Dive Episode]]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MdcKPVo0/pat-felder-the-worst-is-over-macro-deep-dive-episode</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MdcKPVo0/pat-felder-the-worst-is-over-macro-deep-dive-episode"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T17:10:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the first Markets Edition of This Time Will Be Different! In this episode we dive into the current macroeconomic conditions around crypto and look at the data behind the price action. 


Reza sits down with Pat Felder, founder of Prismatic Capital to discuss the current macro environment, and to answer the question on everyone's mind-- is the bear market really over?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Sandbox Co-Founder Sebastien Borget: 'We're Already Integrating AI']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/HlARjhG1/the-sandbox-co-founder-sebastien-borget-were-already-integrating-ai</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/HlARjhG1/the-sandbox-co-founder-sebastien-borget-were-already-integrating-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T16:09:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt sat down with The Sandbox co-founder Sebastien Borget at Web Summit to talk about AI, the open metaverse and the creative challenges of interoperability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dacoco CEO Saro McKenna: How Alien Worlds is Creating an AI-Powered 'Lore DAO' with Kevin J Anderson]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QrQTrsjH/dacoco-ceo-saro-mckenna-how-alien-worlds-is-creating-an-ai-powered-lore-dao-with-kevin-j-anderson</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QrQTrsjH/dacoco-ceo-saro-mckenna-how-alien-worlds-is-creating-an-ai-powered-lore-dao-with-kevin-j-anderson"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T16:06:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt joined Dacoco CEO Sarojini McKenna at Web Summit 2023 to talk about Alien Worlds' new Lore DAO and its AI-powered collaboration with sci-fi author Kevin J Anderson.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avalon's Jeffrey Butler on Designing a Metaverse MMO That Lets Players Co-Create]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XDz9vsvT/avalons-jeffrey-butler-on-designing-a-metaverse-mmo-that-lets-players-co-create</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XDz9vsvT/avalons-jeffrey-butler-on-designing-a-metaverse-mmo-that-lets-players-co-create"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T00:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avalon Chief Product Officer Jeffrey Butler speaks with Decrypt reporter Jason Nelson and details his studio's new MMO game with interoperable assets—and how it will enable players to create and monetize their own content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Gen Z Is Different: OTK Chief Strategy Officer Talks Creator Economy Shift and Rise of Kick]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PieshbpH/how-gen-z-is-different-otk-chief-strategy-officer-talks-creator-economy-shift-and-rise-of-kick</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PieshbpH/how-gen-z-is-different-otk-chief-strategy-officer-talks-creator-economy-shift-and-rise-of-kick"/>
        <updated>2023-11-10T18:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One True King, an esports and gaming lifestyle brand and media company, was founded by creators like Asmongold and Mizkif. OTK's Chief Strategy Officer Zachary Diaz, who previously worked at TikTok and Twitch, shares with Decrypt's Kate Irwin about how the creator economy is changing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moisés Zamora on Videomart and Bucking the Hollywood System]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kyjQCle8/moises-zamora-on-videomart-and-bucking-the-hollywood-system</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kyjQCle8/moises-zamora-on-videomart-and-bucking-the-hollywood-system"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T17:11:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Selena: The Series" creator and co-showrunner Moisés Zamora joins Decrypt's Sander Lutz at the Film3 Summit 2023 to discuss why the Hollywood system is broken and why he founded the Videomart NFT digital film marketplace to give creators more power.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why OTK Is Making Video Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/1NCV4Fk0/why-otk-is-making-video-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/1NCV4Fk0/why-otk-is-making-video-games"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One True King (OTK) Chief Strategy Officer Zachary Diaz tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about OTK's long-term strategy and vision to become a content creator-powered media and video games company.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Questions With SCENE: LoVid]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/E8BZZBWX/5-questions-with-scene-lovid</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/E8BZZBWX/5-questions-with-scene-lovid"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T21:47:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artistic duo LoVid, aka Tali Hinkis and Kyle Lapidus, joins 5 Questions with SCENE to answer burning questions about art, lettuce, and the hellscape (in someone’s opinion) that is Miami.

Video shot and edited by Vincent Roazzi Jr.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Barney on DeFi, Privacy, and Vega]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/hgDzjboU/barney-on-defi-privacy-and-vega</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/hgDzjboU/barney-on-defi-privacy-and-vega"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T18:27:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week our host is joined by Barney the founder of Vega Protocol. 

They discuss the current state of DeFi, what's wrong with the apps being built today, whether or not privacy matters when its only applied to an L2, and most importantly-- which form of sales tax is the sexiest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Is Phantom Galaxies Releasing Two Versions of Its Game?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QtnWGSSJ/why-is-phantom-galaxies-releasing-two-versions-of-its-game</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QtnWGSSJ/why-is-phantom-galaxies-releasing-two-versions-of-its-game"/>
        <updated>2023-11-06T17:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animoca Brands-owned Blowfish Studios is building a space mech pilot game called Phantom Galaxies. Blowfish Cofounder Ben Lee tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about his plans for the game's release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sophie Maxx on NFTs, Augmented Reality, and Fashion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/VByufHjn/sophie-maxx-on-nfts-augmented-reality-and-fashion</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/VByufHjn/sophie-maxx-on-nfts-augmented-reality-and-fashion"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T23:37:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week our host is joined by Sophie Maxx (Web3Maxx) to discuss NFTs, augmented reality, the metaverse, how blockchain is sneaking into the fashion world, and more!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Questions With SCENE: Kevin Rose]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/u9LDX8Vr/5-questions-with-scene-kevin-rose</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/u9LDX8Vr/5-questions-with-scene-kevin-rose"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kevin Rose, co-founder and CEO of PROOF and co-creator of the hit Moonbirds NFT collection, joins 5 Questions with SCENE to answer some hard-hitting questions about his childhood dreams, his wife’s candy preferences, and his undying love of rap music.

Video shot and edited by Vincent Roazzi Jr.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Happened to Atari's Token? Inside Atari's Blockchain Plans]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/7OtQIdqa/what-happened-to-ataris-token-inside-ataris-blockchain-plans</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/7OtQIdqa/what-happened-to-ataris-token-inside-ataris-blockchain-plans"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T18:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin chats with Atari X director Tyler Drewitz about what happened with Atari's token plans, whether a token is coming, and what Atari games might be getting the blockchain treatment. Oh, and there's lots of Easter eggs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitch CEO Dan Clancy Is a 'Wild Card,' Says Marketing Director]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/qCOCtPKe/twitch-ceo-dan-clancy-is-a-wild-card-says-marketing-director</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/qCOCtPKe/twitch-ceo-dan-clancy-is-a-wild-card-says-marketing-director"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T20:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twitch Senior Director of Community Marketing Mary Kish speaks with Decrypt's Kate Irwin about Twitch CEO Dan Clancy, Ninja, Twitch's new simulcasting rules, the biggest differences between Twitch and rival platform Kick, and the role of esports on the streaming platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why NFT Paris has Launched a Loyalty Token]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/91tPVJff/why-nft-paris-has-launched-a-loyalty-token</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/91tPVJff/why-nft-paris-has-launched-a-loyalty-token"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T13:26:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NFT Paris founder Alexandre Tsydenkov told Decrypt what to expect from the upcoming 2024 edition of the conference, the launch of its loyalty token and its plans to create a Web3 loyalty program that rewards the most engaged members of the community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Game Review—Formula E: High Voltage Is a Fun Play-to-Earn Racer That Lacks Direction]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/hzkx0TDg/game-reviewformula-e-high-voltage-is-a-fun-play-to-earn-racer-that-lacks-direction</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/hzkx0TDg/game-reviewformula-e-high-voltage-is-a-fun-play-to-earn-racer-that-lacks-direction"/>
        <updated>2023-10-29T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Formula E: High Voltage is a play-to-earn racing game with a distinctive strategic approach. Decrypt contributor Ryan Gladwin put Animoca's web-based game through its paces in this review, highlighting the unique gameplay design, the role of NFTs and crypto, and where the game currently comes up short.

Follow Decrypt's GG on Twitter: https://twitter.com/ggdecrypt 

Check out GG for daily gaming news: https://decrypt.co/gg 

Subscribe to our GG newsletter with over 50,000 subscribers: https://decrypt.co/newsletters/gg 

Join our official Discord: https://discord.com/invite/3bc4QpA57C]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>