<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-08-22T06:18:05.934Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-08-22T06:18:05.934Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitmain Dispatches Initial KS3 Antminers Amid Surge in Kaspa’s Hashrate]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755706771c</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitmain-dispatches-initial-ks3-antminers-amid-surge-in-kaspas-hashrate/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T06:03:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to Bitmain, the well known crypto ASIC mining rig manufacturer, the company has shipped its first batch of KS3 Antminer machines. Despite each rig costing $49,800, Bitmain sold out of the first batch and announced another batch of KS3 Antminers would be available soon.
 
As Kaspa’s Hashrate Climbs, Bitmain Ships KS3 Antminer Series
 
Bitmain disclosed on Monday that it had shipped its initial batch of KS3 Antminer machines. These rigs mine the crypto asset kaspa (KAS), a digital currency that ranks 45th in market capitalization. Current data suggest the KS3 miner is the most profitable mining ASIC available. The website asicminervalue.com reports that the machine can earn an estimated $440 daily by mining KAS.
 
However, Bitmain’s machine quickly sold out, making it the company’s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Debtors to Seek Justice in Class-Action Suit Against Grayscale]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18851971/FTX-Debtors-to-Seek-Justice-in-Class-Action-Suit-Against-Grayscale</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18851971/FTX-Debtors-to-Seek-Justice-in-Class-Action-Suit-Against-Grayscale"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T06:01:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent announcement, Alameda Research, UTXO Management, and Balch & Bingham LLP unveiled GrayscaleLitigation.com. According to the notification, the platform seeks to unite the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust and Grayscale Ethereum Trust shareholders for collective legal action against Grayscale...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Lead Dev Reveals When Shibarium Will Relaunch For Public]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18851981/Shiba-Inu-Lead-Dev-Reveals-When-Shibarium-Will-Relaunch-For-Public</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18851981/Shiba-Inu-Lead-Dev-Reveals-When-Shibarium-Will-Relaunch-For-Public"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T06:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following the abrupt halt in operations due to unanticipated high traffic immediately after its mainnet launch, the layer-2 network of Shiba Inu, Shibarium, is reportedly making its way towards a public relaunch tomorrow. The details were revealed in a recent blog post by Shiba Inu’s lead...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Takes Stake in USDC-Issuer Circle, Shuts Centre Consortium]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755706cd2f</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/coinbase-takes-stake-in-usdc-issuer-circle-shuts-centre-consortium/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T06:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase (NASDAQ: COIN), the top crypto exchange in the United States, has taken an unknown amount of equity stake in stablecoin issuer Circle Internet Financial. Further, the two companies will shutter the jointly managed Centre Consortium, the self-governance consortium for USDC.  

Restructuring of USDC Governance  

Announced yesterday (Monday), the decisions were taken with the growing regulatory clarity around stablecoins in the United States. A blog post co-authored by Coinbase’s CEO Brian Armstrong and Circle’s CEO Jeremy Allaire highlighted that a separate governance body of USDC is no longer needed. Instead, Circle, which only issued USDC earlier, will now fully control the governance and issuance of USD-pegged stablecoin.  

“The new structure will streamline the operations and …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arnab Shome</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Komainu becomes latest crypto firm to gain full license in Dubai]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18851968/Komainu-becomes-latest-crypto-firm-to-gain-full-license-in-Dubai</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18851968/Komainu-becomes-latest-crypto-firm-to-gain-full-license-in-Dubai"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto custodian is set to offer institutional staking and collateral management in the region via its Komainu Connect platform]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mysterious Bitcoin wallet becomes 3rd largest BTC holder in 3 months]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18851967/Mysterious-Bitcoin-wallet-becomes-3rd-largest-BTC-holder-in-3-months</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18851967/Mysterious-Bitcoin-wallet-becomes-3rd-largest-BTC-holder-in-3-months"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T05:50:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An unknown wallet has accrued more than $3 billion worth of Bitcoin in the last three months, sparking a wave of theories about the potential owner.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Lawyer Demands SEC Audit After Binance Suspends EUR Withdrawals]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18851957/Crypto-Lawyer-Demands-SEC-Audit-After-Binance-Suspends-EUR-Withdrawals</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18851957/Crypto-Lawyer-Demands-SEC-Audit-After-Binance-Suspends-EUR-Withdrawals"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T05:45:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto lawyer John Reed Stark has called on the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and the Financial Industry Regulatory Authority (FINRA) to send auditors, inspectors, and examiners to investigate Binance. Stark’s latest comments were in response to the suspension of EU withdrawals from...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gold-backed BRICS currency will be 'very hard' to deliver: Lyn Alden]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18851953/Gold-backed-BRICS-currency-will-be-very-hard-to-deliver-Lyn-Alden</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18851953/Gold-backed-BRICS-currency-will-be-very-hard-to-deliver-Lyn-Alden"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T05:45:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A BRICS common currency will be challenging to initiate and maintain, though efforts to dethrone the US dollar could have an impact on Bitcoin, says investment strategist Lyn Alden.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Burn Rate Skyrockets 850% In A Day — SHIB Becomes Most Traded Token Among Top Ethereum Whales]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18851966/Shiba-Inu-Burn-Rate-Skyrockets-850-In-A-Day-SHIB-Becomes-Most-Traded-Token-Among-Top-Ethereum-Whales</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18851966/Shiba-Inu-Burn-Rate-Skyrockets-850-In-A-Day-SHIB-Becomes-Most-Traded-Token-Among-Top-Ethereum-Whales"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T05:44:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The self-proclaimed “Dogecoin (CRYPTO: DOGE) killer,” Shiba Inu (CRYPTO: SHIB), experienced an 850% surge in its burn rate within the span of just 24 hours. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Looks Most Oversold Since Covid Crash, Key Indicator Suggests]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7557011ea2</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/08/22/bitcoin-looks-most-oversold-since-covid-crash-key-indicator-suggests/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T05:33:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin's relative strength index has dropped well below 30 to its strongest oversold reading since March 2020.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Looks Most Oversold Since Covid Crash, Key Indicator Suggests]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18851936/Bitcoin-Looks-Most-Oversold-Since-Covid-Crash-Key-Indicator-Suggests</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18851936/Bitcoin-Looks-Most-Oversold-Since-Covid-Crash-Key-Indicator-Suggests"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T05:23:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin's relative strength index has dropped well below 30 to its strongest oversold reading since March 2020.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Coin (BNB) Woes Continue as Liquidation Fears Mount]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18851948/Binance-Coin-BNB-Woes-Continue-as-Liquidation-Fears-Mount</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18851948/Binance-Coin-BNB-Woes-Continue-as-Liquidation-Fears-Mount"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T05:15:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The pressure on the world’s largest crypto exchange continues to mount, which can be visualized through the performance of its native asset, Binance Coin (BNB). The continued decline of BNB has some speculating that a larger liquidation could be on the horizon.  Crypto social media is reacting...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Scams and Fraud Ads: Thailand Threatens to Shut Down Facebook]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75570ccdfc</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/crypto-scams-and-fraud-ads-thailand-threatens-to-shut-down-facebook/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T04:50:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The authorities in Thailand are taking a tough stance against the rampant menace of cryptocurrency scams and fraudulent ads on Facebook and are seeking to bring a court-issued shutdown order against the social media giant if it fails to curb these illegal activities.  

Thailand Seeks Legal Action against Facebook  

The proposed action came as, according to the Ministry of Digital Economy and Society (MDES), fraudulent Facebook ads, including cryptocurrency scams and investments into fake businesses, duped more than 200,000 Thai people.  

To lure victims, the fraudulent ads offered daily returns of up to 30 percent and even illegally used the photos of celebrities and well-known financial industry figures as fake endorsements. Some advertisements even used the name and symbol of Thailand…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arnab Shome</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Price Shows Confluence Of Bearish Factors and Could Decline Again]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18851908/XRP-Price-Shows-Confluence-Of-Bearish-Factors-and-Could-Decline-Again</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18851908/XRP-Price-Shows-Confluence-Of-Bearish-Factors-and-Could-Decline-Again"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T04:50:08.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Ordinals’ volume impresses despite these hurdles. Assessing…]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18851880/Bitcoin-Ordinals-volume-impresses-despite-these-hurdles-Assessing</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18851880/Bitcoin-Ordinals-volume-impresses-despite-these-hurdles-Assessing"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T04:30:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The speculation about the demise of Bitcoin Ordinals was definitively addressed over the weekend as Inscription numbers surged to a record high.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BRICS Not Focusing on Creating Common Currency, Indian Official Says]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7557087c7e</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/brics-not-focusing-on-creating-common-currency-indian-official-says/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T04:07:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A top Indian official has downplayed the creation of a shared BRICS currency. Emphasizing that “common currency discussions have several prerequisites before you can even talk about a common currency framework,” the official stressed that the BRICS nations have focused on boosting settlements in national currencies.
 
Indian Foreign Secretary on BRICS Currency
 
India’s Foreign Secretary Vinay Mohan Kwatra explained in a media briefing on Monday that the BRICS economic bloc is not focusing on the proposed common currency for member states, Indian news outlet Mint reported. The BRICS nations are Brazil, Russia, India, China, and South Africa.
 
“The substantive part of trade and economic exchanges and discussions that have been a part of BRICS discussions have so far, in a major way, focuse…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mysterious Whale Acquires $3B Worth Bitcoin In 3 Months, Guess How Much The Ultimate HODLR Satoshi Nakamoto Have In His Stash]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18851869/Mysterious-Whale-Acquires-3B-Worth-Bitcoin-In-3-Months-Guess-How-Much-The-Ultimate-HODLR-Satoshi-Nakamoto-Have-In-His-Stash</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18851869/Mysterious-Whale-Acquires-3B-Worth-Bitcoin-In-3-Months-Guess-How-Much-The-Ultimate-HODLR-Satoshi-Nakamoto-Have-In-His-Stash"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T03:47:26.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI unlikely to destroy jobs, but cost to certain workers may be ‘brutal’ — UN study]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18851842/AI-unlikely-to-destroy-jobs-but-cost-to-certain-workers-may-be-brutal-UN-study</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18851842/AI-unlikely-to-destroy-jobs-but-cost-to-certain-workers-may-be-brutal-UN-study"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T03:32:26.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Layer 2 Throughput Hits Record High]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18851835/Ethereum-Layer-2-Throughput-Hits-Record-High</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18851835/Ethereum-Layer-2-Throughput-Hits-Record-High"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T03:26:36.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why FTX deserves a second chance]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18851829/Why-FTX-deserves-a-second-chance</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18851829/Why-FTX-deserves-a-second-chance"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T03:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite the outrage against Sam Bankman-Fried and the now-bankrupt exchange, everyone would be better off with a relaunched FTX 2.0, writes Rachel Lin, CEO of SynFutures.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum, Dogecoin Drop After Vitalik Buterin Transfers ETH Worth $1M To Coinbase: Analyst Warns BNB Is Casually Dragging Down Entire Crypto Market]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18851817/Bitcoin-Ethereum-Dogecoin-Drop-After-Vitalik-Buterin-Transfers-ETH-Worth-1M-To-Coinbase-Analyst-Warns-BNB-Is-Casually-Dragging-Down-Entire-Crypto-Market</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18851817/Bitcoin-Ethereum-Dogecoin-Drop-After-Vitalik-Buterin-Transfers-ETH-Worth-1M-To-Coinbase-Analyst-Warns-BNB-Is-Casually-Dragging-Down-Entire-Crypto-Market"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T02:31:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Major cryptocurrencies experienced a decline on Monday evening, while altcoins displayed minimal price fluctuations. This occurred as the markets appeared to regain stability after a significant liquidation event, which stands as one of the largest in recent months. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Crashes Below 8-Month Support Line, More Pain Incoming?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7550f087d8</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-crashes-8-month-support-more-pain-incoming/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T02:25:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the first time since early January, Bitcoin is changing hands below a critical support band and the 20-week moving average, evident in the weekly chart.
 
An analyst on X, formerly Twitter, pointed out this formation and has since raised questions about the coin’s prospects in the days and weeks ahead. Bitcoin is trading at around $26,000, down 18% from July 2023 peak. The situation remains tense for coin holders as the price pressures continue to mount.
 
 
Bitcoin Breaks Below Critical Support Levels
 
Looking at price action in the weekly chart, sellers are in control and actively aiming to erase gains posted between June and July 2023. At this pace, it won’t not only mean more pressure on holders but more liquidations for long positions in derivatives exchanges, impacting sentiment…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dalmas Ngetich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prosecutors File Proposed Jury Instructions for Sam Bankman-Fried Trial]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7550f0a4e1</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/08/22/prosecutors-file-proposed-jury-instructions-for-sam-bankman-fried-trial/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T02:23:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Department of Justice filed its proposed set of jury instructions for Sam Bankman-Fried's October trial a day before he is set to be arraigned on a new superseding indictment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried Granted 6.5-Hour Temporary Leave From Jail]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18851806/Sam-Bankman-Fried-Granted-65-Hour-Temporary-Leave-From-Jail</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18851806/Sam-Bankman-Fried-Granted-65-Hour-Temporary-Leave-From-Jail"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T02:23:33.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[friend.tech Closes In On Ethereum With $1.7M In Daily Fees]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18851802/friendtech-Closes-In-On-Ethereum-With-17M-In-Daily-Fees</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18851802/friendtech-Closes-In-On-Ethereum-With-17M-In-Daily-Fees"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T02:17:39.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Over 40 Heads of State Will Attend BRICS Summit, South Africa Confirms]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7550f207f4</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/over-40-heads-of-state-will-attend-brics-summit-south-africa-confirms/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T02:06:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[South Africa, the host of the BRICS summit this year, has confirmed that more than 40 heads of state will participate in the summit that will take place on Aug. 22-24. South Africa has also claimed that 23 countries have formally applied for BRICS membership.
 
40+ Heads of State to Participate in BRICS Summit
 
Nelson Kgwete, the South African foreign ministry’s media liaison officer, told Russian news outlet Tass that more than 40 heads of state have confirmed that they will participate in the BRICS summit that will take place on Aug. 22-24 in Johannesburg. South Africa is the host of the BRICS summit this year. He was quoted as saying:
 

Yes, confirmed, the summit will be attended by over 40 heads of state.
 
All leaders of the BRICS nations (Brazil, Russia, India, China, and South Afr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Crashes Below 8-Month Support Line, More Pain Incoming?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18851782/Bitcoin-Crashes-Below-8-Month-Support-Line-More-Pain-Incoming</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18851782/Bitcoin-Crashes-Below-8-Month-Support-Line-More-Pain-Incoming"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T02:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prosecutors File Proposed Jury Instructions for Sam Bankman-Fried Trial]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18851783/Prosecutors-File-Proposed-Jury-Instructions-for-Sam-Bankman-Fried-Trial</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18851783/Prosecutors-File-Proposed-Jury-Instructions-for-Sam-Bankman-Fried-Trial"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T01:55:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Department of Justice filed its proposed set of jury instructions for Sam Bankman-Fried's October trial a day before he is set to be arraigned on a new superseding indictment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friend.tech Renames Its Token—But Is It Even Legal?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=153287</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/153287/friend-tech-shares-renamed-keys-securities"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T01:32:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Regulatory red flags likely prompted the red-hot social crypto app to drop the term “shares.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Starknet’s TVL Drops Nearly 50%, What’s Going On?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7550fd1758</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/starknets-tvl-drops-nearly-50-whats-going-on/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T01:26:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The total value locked (TVL) in Starknet, a layer-2 scaling solution for Ethereum using ZK-Rollup, is down nearly 50%, L2Beat data on August 21 shows.
 
At this pace, the contraction in Starknet’s TVL is among the fastest in the layer-2 scene and stands at around $98 million. As of August 16, Starknet had a TVL of over $203 million and remained in the top 10 of the most popular layer-2 scaling options in Ethereum.
 
 
StarkNet’s TVL Dropping
 
Starknet uses zero-knowledge (ZK) in its rollups, meaning while the platform bundles transactions before confirming them on-chain, using zero-knowledge translates to better privacy. StarkWare, the team behind Starknet, also notes that the layer-2 solution is not ZK-EVM, meaning users must deploy all general-purpose smart contracts built using Cairo, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dalmas Ngetich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Developers Say Craig Wright May Be Admitting That He Stole 80,000 Bitcoin from Mt. Gox]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=153279</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/153279/bitcoin-developers-say-craig-wright-admits-to-stealing-millions-in-bitcoin-from-mt-gox"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T00:39:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Defense attorneys say the ownership claim by the man who says he is Bitcoin creator Satoshi Nakamoto implies he stole 80,000 BTC from the exchange.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Debtors Pivot: Revised Settlement Proposal Emerges Amid US Trustee Objection]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7550f9931a</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ftx-revised-settlement-proposal-amid-objection/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T00:27:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent court filing on Sunday, bankrupt cryptocurrency exchange FTX disclosed that it had revised its motion for settlement after facing objections from the US Trustee. 
 
Despite criticizing the US Department of Justice (DOJ) representatives for intervening in what they considered a routine settlement process safeguarded by two creditor committees, FTX debtors acknowledged the concerns raised and proposed revisions to address them.
 
FTX Seeks Efficient Resolution Of Small Estate Claims
 
According to the court filing, establishing omnibus settlement procedures in complex cases is a “routine, appropriate, and authorized” practice. 
 
 
Contrary to the US Trustee’s suggestion, such procedures are often permitted by courts, enabling the settlement of claims by category and granting rel…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Market Strategist Draws Parallels Between Bitcoin and 1930 Stock Market Crash]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7550fa5762</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/market-strategist-draws-parallels-between-bitcoin-and-1930-stock-market-crash/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T00:16:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bloomberg Intelligence’s senior commodity strategist, Mike McGlone, has explained that bitcoin appears similar to the stock market in 1930. At that time, elevated equity prices led to the stock market losing almost 90%. The crash of 1929, also called the Great Crash, contributed to the Great Depression which lasted approximately 10 years.
 
Bitcoin v Stock Market in 1930s
 
Mike McGlone, a senior commodity strategist for Bloomberg Intelligence (BI), the research arm of Bloomberg, has pointed out the similarity between bitcoin and the stock market in 1930. He tweeted on Monday:
 

One of the best-performing assets in history and a leading indicator — bitcoin — appears similar to the stock market in 1930.
 
“Statistician and entrepreneur Roger Babson began warning about elevated equity price…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[K-Pop Titans Blackpink Launch Roblox Metaverse Experience]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=153251</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/153251/k-pop-titans-blackpink-launch-roblox-metaverse-experience"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T00:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blackpink: The Palace launches this week in Roblox and will evolve over the next year with metaverse experiences for K-pop fans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ali Shutler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Developers Push Back Against Craig Wright’s Claim to Billions of Dollars in Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7550e41508</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/08/21/bitcoin-developers-push-back-against-craig-wrights-claim-to-billions-of-dollars-in-bitcoin/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T23:54:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A group of bitcoin developers is fighting a lawsuit in the UK alleging they wrongfully refused to help Craig Wright’s crypto company retrieve billions of dollars worth of bitcoin that the company allegedly lost in a hack, a Monday court filing shows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Napolitano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gaming Influencers FaZe Banks, Nadeshot Among Friend.tech's Top Earners]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=153243</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/153243/gaming-influencers-faze-banks-nadeshot-among-friend-tech-top-earners"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T23:51:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The esports and gaming titans behind FaZe Clan and 100 Thieves respectively are making bank on buzzy social token app Friend.tech.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friend.tech Founders Say Viral Crypto App Is Surprising Them Too: 'We Want to Catch Our Breath']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=153270</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/153270/friend-tech-founders-say-viral-crypto-app-is-surprising-them-too-we-want-to-catch-our-breath"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T23:35:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The founders of Friend.tech tell Decrypt what's next for the tokenized social media platform—and where their heads are at following the boom.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friend.tech Is Crypto’s Latest Obsession—But Critics Say It Won’t End Well]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=153248</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/153248/friend-tech-is-cryptos-latest-obsession-but-critics-say-it-wont-end-well"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T23:12:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celebrities are signing up on the protocol, which is already bigger than Tron and Uniswap. But is it sustainable?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This GMX Whale Trader Has An 80% Win Rate, What Crypto Did They Buy?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7550e3a4fb</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/gmx-whale-trader-has-80-win-rate/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T22:27:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto market was thoroughly shaken up last week when the prices of assets in the space crashed rapidly. As a result, over 170,000 traders lost their positions, amounting to more than $1 billion in losses. However, not all crypto traders suffered due to the crash as one GMX whale trader made almost 7-figures in profit. On a closer look, the whale seems to be on a streak with an impressive 80% win rate over the last two months.
 
GMX Whale Trader Makes Almost $1 Million
 
When the crypto market crashed last week and the price of Ethereum fell from above $1,800 to below $1,600, most of the market was caught aware. But one GMX whale trader was properly positioned to profit from such a crash and they were rewarded handsomely for their foresight.
 
 
By the time the crash rolled around, the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Best Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Federal Reserve CBDC Would Threaten Privacy and Freedom, Report Warns]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7550ed6645</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/federal-reserve-cbdc-would-threaten-privacy-and-freedom-report-warns/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T22:08:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The America First Policy Institute (AFPI) recently sounded the alarm on the potential dangers of transitioning to a central bank digital currency (CBDC). This revelation, in a report penned by Michael Faulkender and David Vasquez, highlights the probable perils associated with the Federal Reserve’s direct issuance of a digital dollar.
 
AFPI: A CBDC ‘Would Represent the Greatest Threat to What Little Financial Privacy and Data Security Americans Enjoy’
 
According to the AFPI’s report, introducing a CBDC could grant the government unparalleled access to all financial transactions, eroding citizens’ privacy. They reference the IRS’s recent data exposures as an indication that federal agencies might not be equipped to handle Americans’ transaction data safely.
 
Moreover, the report cautions…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BREAKING: Coinbase Acquires Stake In Circle As Centre Consortium Fades Away]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7550e929e1</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/breaking-coinbase-acquires-stake-in-circle/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T21:28:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a significant development for USD Coin (USDC), Coinbase and Circle, the two companies behind the stablecoin, have reached a new agreement that brings changes to its governance and funding. 
 
This move comes at a crucial juncture as USDC faces evolving global regulatory challenges and intensifying competition from other stablecoins, including Tether and the recently announced PayPal stablecoin (PYUSD). 
 
According to a Fortune Magazine report, the updated agreement involves Coinbase acquiring an equity stake in Circle for the first time and the closure of the Centre Consortium, which previously governed USDC.
 
Coinbase And Circle Revamp Governance For USDC
 
Under the previous revenue-sharing arrangement, Coinbase and Circle split revenue based on the amount of USDC distributed and he…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bears Regain Control Over Bitcoin For First Time In 2023, Signal Reveals]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7550e929da</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bears-regain-control-over-bitcoin-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T21:28:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Up until this past week, bulls have been in charge of Bitcoin price action, maintaining a series of higher high and higher lows.
 
While that uptrend structure isn’t yet broken, a tool that reveals the underlying strength of a trend points to bears having the upper hand for the first time in 2023.
 
Sideways Bitcoin Breaks Down Leaving Bulls Vulnerable
 
A recent distinct lack of volatility and prolonged sideways trading range suggested that a big move in BTCUSD was on the way. The outcome ultimately saw bears swatting down Bitcoin price by 10% in a single day. The breakdown immediately put the 2023 uptrend in jeopardy.
 
An uptrend is defined as a series of higher lows and higher highs, which is still structurally intact in BTCUSD charts. But there is often more to a trend than structure …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tony &amp;quot;The Bull&amp;quot;</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried Due Back in Court as He Asks for Daily Releases]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7550e94b2c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/08/21/sam-bankman-fried-due-back-in-court-as-he-asks-for-daily-releases/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T21:27:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried will have five and a half hours with his attorneys, minus any time spent being arraigned yet again Tuesday on his latest indictment, which folded campaign finance allegations into existing charges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Acquires Stake in Circle, Dissolving USDC Issuer Centre]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=153229</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/153229/coinbase-buys-stake-circle-dissolving-usdc-centre"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T21:19:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Circle will now be the only issuer of the USDC stablecoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Gets a Stake in Stablecoin Operator Circle and USDC Adds 6 New Blockchains]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7550ebc13a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/08/21/coinbase-buys-a-stake-in-stablecoin-operator-circle-and-usdc-adds-6-new-blockchains/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T21:01:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Centre Consortium, jointly managed by Circle and Coinbase, is being shut down and Circle is bringing issuance and governance of the USDC stablecoin in-house.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto and NFT Games Are Still Launching on Steam Despite Ongoing Ban]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=153196</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/153196/crypto-nft-games-still-launching-steam-despite-ongoing-ban"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T20:49:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Popular PC marketplace Steam banned blockchain games in 2021, but developers are finding various ways to work around—or within—the rules.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Disappointing’ ETF Decisions By SEC Blamed for Bitcoin Selloff]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=153230</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/153230/disappointing-etf-decisions-by-sec-blamed-for-bitcoin-selloff"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T20:47:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amid a widespread crypto sell-off and SEC stalling, CoinShares reports that institutional investors sold $55 million worth of Bitcoin in the past week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Volatility Returns With 15% Drop]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7550d5f7f3</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/markets/bitcoin-volatility-returns-with-massive-bitcoin-price-drop"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T20:38:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The article below is an excerpt from a recent edition of Bitcoin Magazine PRO, Bitcoin Magazine's premium markets newsletter. To be among the first to receive these insights and other on-chain bitcoin market analysis straight to your inbox, subscribe now.

 
         
         
         
        Bitcoin volatility returns with an exchange rate crash. 
    
Aug. 17, marked the return of the much-awaited and notorious bitcoin volatility. After several months of consolidating around the $30,000 level with historically low realized and implied volatility in the bitcoin market, the price finally awakened, bringing about the biggest liquidation event bitcoin has seen in years. Contrary to some opinions by reporters and analysts, the bitcoin crash was not triggered by rumors of SpaceX selling bit…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dylan LeClair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Open Interest Continues To Climb, Another Violent Move Incoming?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7550d6e311</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-open-interest-climb-violent-move-incoming/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T20:29:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data shows the Bitcoin open interest has continued to climb recently, a sign that another violent move may be brewing for the asset.
 
Bitcoin Open Interest Is Steadily Going Up Right Now
 
In a new post on X, Maartunn, the community manager at CryptoQuant Netherlands, has looked into how the derivative metrics for Bitcoin right now compare against those seen before the recent crash.
 
There are mainly two indicators of interest here: the open interest and the funding rate. The former measures the total number of BTC positions on the derivative platforms.
 
When this metric’s value goes up, investors are opening up new market positions. Generally, such a trend leads to higher volatility for the cryptocurrency, as the total leverage in the market also increases with the indicator’s rise.
 
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hououin Kyouma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Fund Misled Clients With Promises of 2,700% Returns, SEC Claims]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=153190</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/153190/crypto-fund-misled-investors-promised-2700-returns"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T19:52:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Titan promised investors annual returns of over 2,700% with its crypto product—but the SEC alleges it was a con.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Won't Lead to an Unemployment Crisis, but Jobs Are at Risk: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=153209</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/153209/ai-wont-bring-an-unemployment-crisis-but-jobs-are-at-risk-ilo-report"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T19:40:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The International Labor Organization says artificial intelligence threatens working women more than men.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Market Is Sleeping on These AI Investments, Says Ark]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=153202</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/153202/market-is-sleeping-on-these-ai-investments-says-ark"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T18:17:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cathie Wood's investment firm urges caution before looking to mega cap tech giants for AI exposure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Euro Transfers ‘Still Available’, Says Paysafe After Erroneous Tweet]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=153191</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/153191/binance-euro-transfers-still-available-says-paysafe"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T17:36:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance’s users have until September 25 to conduct euro transactions via SEPA, according to Paysafe and Binance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who’s Who in Global Crypto Regulation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=153195</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/whos-who-in-global-crypto-regulation"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T17:09:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is difficult to properly assess cryptocurrencies through the lenses of traditional finance—it is even challenging to determine which agencies may be responsible for their oversight.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Reiff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kenyan Government Launches Committee to Examine Worldcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=153186</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/153186/kenyan-government-launches-committee-examine-worldcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T16:57:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The move comes just three weeks after the African nation's authorities suspended Worldcoin’s activities in the country.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Wagner's 'Controversial Take' on Crypto in Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tc2nKeqA/michael-wagners-controversial-take-on-crypto-in-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tc2nKeqA/michael-wagners-controversial-take-on-crypto-in-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T16:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Solana's PlayGG, Star Atlas CEO Michael Wagner shares his "controversial take" on crypto in games, shares the challenges of developing the upcoming scifi game, and how crypto's volatility has changed his perspective with Decrypt's Jason Nelson.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ETH Linked to Ethereum ICO Participant, Vitalik Buterin Is on the Move]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=153184</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/153184/eth-linked-ethereum-ico-participant-vitalik-buterin-are-move"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T14:26:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roughly $1.3 million in Ethereum between an eight-year-old address and Vitalik Buterin has bought up altcoins or been sent to Coinbase.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China Is Taking Its Social Credit System to the Metaverse: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=153163</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/153163/china-is-taking-social-credit-system-metaverse"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T13:09:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Officials in China have reportedly put forth a set of proposals for a “government-controlled internet” to a UN metaverse focus group.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another Lucky Solo Miner Nabs $160,000 Bitcoin Block Reward]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=153150</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/153150/another-lucky-solo-miner-nabs-160000-bitcoin-block-reward"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T09:59:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With a mere 1 PH/s in hash power, the lucky miner enjoys vastly fewer resources than what major industrial-scale Bitcoin mining pools boast.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meme Coins PEPE, SHIB Plummet More Than 20% Over the Week]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=153135</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/153135/meme-coins-pepe-shib-plummet-more-week"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T09:22:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Markets are down bad and meme coins—the riskier assets—are bearing the brunt. Last week’s chaotic Shibarium launch also helped sink the price of SHIB.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Base Network Sees Activity Soar Past Arbitrum, Optimism Amid Friend.tech Frenzy]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=153133</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/153133/base-network-sees-activity-soar-past-arbitrum-optimism-friend-tech-frenzy"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T09:07:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Twitter-linked crypto app has taken off, lifting activity and the amount in fees accrued by the Coinbase-incubated Base network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFT Platform Recur to Shut Down Despite $50M Raise and Big Name Backers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=153124</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/153124/nft-platform-recur-to-shut-down-despite-50-million-raise-and-big-name-backers"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T23:13:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recur is the latest NFT-centered firm with big-name partnerships to announce its platform is shutting down.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Failure to State a Claim': Gemini Pushes to Get SEC Case Dismissed]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=153123</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/153123/failure-to-state-a-claim-gemini-pushes-to-get-sec-case-dismissed"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T22:38:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lawyers for Gemini say the SEC can’t prove the company was selling securities to customers, and wants the lawsuit thrown out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tornado Cash Sanctions Affirmed by Federal Court]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=153118</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/153118/tornado-cash-sanctions-affirmed-by-federal-court"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T20:35:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The judge dismissed claims that the sanctions violated the First Amendment rights of Tornado Cash users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt AI, Edited by Ryan Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week on Crypto Twitter: Gitcoin Admits Shell Deal Was a Mistake, Trump’s Crypto Wallet Gets Outed]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=153103</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/153103/this-week-on-crypto-twitter-donald-trump-crypto-wallet-shell-oil-gitcoin-evergrande-tether"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T19:57:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twitter was full of unsubstantiated rumors about Tether’s exposure to bankrupt Chinese property giant Evergrande.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Token Founder Loses $250,000 and His House in Scam, Sues Crypto.com]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=153097</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/153097/token-founder-loses-250000-and-his-house-in-scam-sues-crypto-com"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T19:33:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Glow Token CEO says he was duped by scam artists posing as representatives of the major digital currency exchange.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt AI, Edited by Ryan Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried Wants Regular Release From Jail, May Blame Lawyers In His Defense]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=153092</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/153092/sam-bankman-fried-wants-regular-release-from-jail-may-blame-lawyers-in-his-defense"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T18:16:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The FTX founder needs better access to evidence, his lawyers argue, even as his defense may be that his lawyers made him do it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can Robots Be Beatniks? An AI-Powered Allen Ginsberg Finds Out]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=153027</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/153027/can-robots-beatniks-ai-powered-allen-ginsberg-finds-out"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T16:33:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new exhibition in Los Angeles features Ginsberg-esque poems crafted by AI, inspired by the artist’s photographs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Believe In God? You Might Believe In AI, Too]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=153068</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/153068/believe-in-god-you-might-believe-in-ai-too"/>
        <updated>2023-08-19T19:46:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A joint university study suggests that people with a strong belief in God are more willing to trust advice from AI over humans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scientists Uncover Biological Echoes in Powerful AI Transformer Models]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=153069</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/153069/scientists-uncover-biological-echoes-in-powerful-ai-transformer-models"/>
        <updated>2023-08-19T19:33:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unassuming astrocytes, thought to merely be helper brain cells, are more than meets the eye.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean Hackers Have Stolen $200 Million So Far This Year: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=153063</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/153063/north-korean-hackers-stolen-over-200-million-in-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-08-19T18:38:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybercriminals have raked in over $2 Billion over the last five years, TRM Labs says.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Flash Crash! Bitcoin and Ethereum Shed 10% as Altcoins Tumble]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=153053</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/153053/this-week-in-coins-flash-crash-bitcoin-ethereum-altcoins-down"/>
        <updated>2023-08-19T17:29:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A major selloff this week sent the prices of all leading cryptocurrencies spiraling down.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto's Oldest Use Case Is Back in the Spotlight. But Why Now?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152936</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152936/cryptos-oldest-use-case-is-back-spotlight-why-now"/>
        <updated>2023-08-19T11:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tokenization is back in a big way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mark Cuban, Yuga Labs Lead Backlash Over OpenSea's NFT Royalties Change]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=153043</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/153043/mark-cuban-yuga-labs-lead-backlash-over-opensea-nft-royalties-change"/>
        <updated>2023-08-19T00:11:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenSea investor Mark Cuban expressed disappointment in the marketplace's move as creators plot potential boycotts and restrictions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Is Down Bad Again—Here's Why and What Comes Next]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=153024</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/153024/bitcoin-down-bad-again-why-what-comes-next"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T22:40:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elon or Evergrande—or something else entirely? Experts share what caused Bitcoin's flash crash Thursday, and what to expect ahead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roblox Enables 'Illicit Gambling' for Kids, Lawsuit Alleges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152990</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152990/roblox-enables-illicit-gambling-kids-lawsuit-alleges"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T22:02:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roblox is being blamed for third-party online casinos that use its currency, Robux, and facilitate underage gambling. Will the case stick?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Says He's Killing Twitter's Block Feature, Sparking Outcry]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152980</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152980/elon-musk-says-hes-killing-twitters-block-feature-sparking-outcry"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T20:40:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Twitter owner revealed plans to axe the block feature, igniting swift backlash among users citing safety concerns on the platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another Crypto Bridge Collapses as DeFi Lender on Optimism Suffers $7 Million Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152966</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152966/defi-lender-optimism-exactly-suffers-7-million-hack"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T20:01:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Exactly, a credit market on the Optimism network, was hacked on Friday as thieves exploited its bridge to swipe a stash of ETH.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet the DJ Who Wears a CryptoPunk Helmet While He Spins]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152947</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152947/meet-seedphrase-dj-who-wears-cryptopunk-helmet"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T19:28:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With his debut single "Angels" out today, Seedphrase says he understands skepticism but wants to "let the music do the talking."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ali Shutler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Billionaire Biohacker Who Wants to Live Forever Just Started 'Penis Rejuvenation' Therapy]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152950</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152950/billionaire-biohacker-wants-live-forever-just-started-penis-rejuvenation-therapy"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T18:28:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 45-year-old Bryan Johnson is undergoing therapy using sound waves to help him attempt to achieve the erections of a healthy 18-year-old.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interview: Angelic CEO on Building the Sci-Fi RPG on Solana and Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/uCzW3K7P/interview-angelic-ceo-on-building-the-sci-fi-rpg-on-solana-and-ethereum</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/uCzW3K7P/interview-angelic-ceo-on-building-the-sci-fi-rpg-on-solana-and-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T15:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Angelic is a sci-fi roleplay game in development that will be free-to-play and offer optional, opt-in crypto features on Solana and Ethereum and a governance token. Metaverse Game Studios CEO and Founder Erkan Bayol tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how he sees AAA traditional games as Angelic's main competitors and shares his vision for the game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apex Legends Voice Actor on AI's Impact on Video Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IOIrmb0N/apex-legends-voice-actor-on-ais-impact-on-video-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IOIrmb0N/apex-legends-voice-actor-on-ais-impact-on-video-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T17:28:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ben Prendergast is an actor who has voiced characters like Apex Legends' Fuse, God of War Ragnarok's Tyr, and Patroclus in Hades. But as debates swirl around the use of artificial intelligence in entertainment in light of the SAG-AFTRA and WGA strikes, Prendergast gives Decrypt's Kate Irwin his honest take on the potential use of AI actors in games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Star Atlas CEO on Developing an MMO Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/WQCaahmH/star-atlas-ceo-on-developing-an-mmo-game</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/WQCaahmH/star-atlas-ceo-on-developing-an-mmo-game"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T13:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Jason Nelson speaks with Star Atlas Founder and CEO Michael Wagner about the MMO game's approach to development, marketing, and blockchain integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aurory's Origin Story: How JRPGs Inspired the Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/O0S201TB/aurorys-origin-story-how-jrpgs-inspired-the-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/O0S201TB/aurorys-origin-story-how-jrpgs-inspired-the-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T16:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Jason Nelson talks to Aurory's Head of Marketing and Business Development Michael Natoli about the origins of the Aurory crypto games at the Solana PlayGG event.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Parallel TCG: Inside the Sci-Fi Card Game’s Closed Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/q8YVWJh4/parallel-tcg-inside-the-sci-fi-card-games-closed-beta</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/q8YVWJh4/parallel-tcg-inside-the-sci-fi-card-games-closed-beta"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T15:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin goes hands-on with Parallel’s closed beta on Windows PC to find out what sets it apart from other crypto card-battlers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 Games Need to Compete with All Games, Says Solana Foundation GM]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ud9wTd4s/web3-games-need-to-compete-with-all-games-says-solana-foundation-gm</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ud9wTd4s/web3-games-need-to-compete-with-all-games-says-solana-foundation-gm"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T19:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Foundation's General Manager of Games Johnny Lee tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about Solana's PlayGG conference and shares his take on crypto gaming and the "play-to-earn" concept.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Many Early Blockchain Games Were 'Cash Grabs,' Says Twitch Streamer Alliestrasza]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BA4yE45A/many-early-blockchain-games-were-cash-grabs-says-twitch-streamer-alliestrasza</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BA4yE45A/many-early-blockchain-games-were-cash-grabs-says-twitch-streamer-alliestrasza"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T16:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["I wrote them off," Twitch streamer Alliestrasza said of her initial thoughts on many early blockchain games. She tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how her perspective on Web3 games has evolved over time and now sees blockchain games getting significantly better.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['MetalCore' Game Preview: Hands-on With the 'Titanfall' Meets 'Destiny' NFT Mashup]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/tjK6i7lv/metalcore-game-preview-hands-on-with-the-titanfall-meets-destiny-nft-mashup</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/tjK6i7lv/metalcore-game-preview-hands-on-with-the-titanfall-meets-destiny-nft-mashup"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T19:46:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MetalCore is an upcoming mech shooter developed by Studio 369, and it's being developed on Ethereum scaling network Immutable zkEVM. Decrypt contributor Ryan Gladwin played through the prologue and tested out the recent Alpha 3 online experience to get a sense of the NFT-infused mashup of Titanfall and Destiny.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Give Projects a Chance,' Says Aurory's Michael Natoli on NFT Game Challenges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/nBNKKZdK/give-projects-a-chance-says-aurorys-michael-natoli-on-nft-game-challenges</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/nBNKKZdK/give-projects-a-chance-says-aurorys-michael-natoli-on-nft-game-challenges"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aurory is an NFT-driven game franchise that started life on Solana and is expanding to other chains. Decrypt's Jason Nelson spoke with Aurory Head of Marketing Michael Natoli at Solana's PlayGG event, where Natoli shared his thoughts on the challenges that blockchain games face in reaching players.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Is Only Network Ready for Gaming: Solana Foundation's Johnny Lee]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5OvV3ZXn/solana-is-only-network-ready-for-gaming-solana-foundations-johnny-lee</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5OvV3ZXn/solana-is-only-network-ready-for-gaming-solana-foundations-johnny-lee"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T17:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Foundation General Manager Johnny Lee tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how the Solana network will tackle the scaling problem that blockchain games pose for the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Com2uS Is Going "Full Speed" on Crypto Gaming: Kyu Lee]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pYMZRoYy/com2us-is-going-full-speed-on-crypto-gaming-kyu-lee</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pYMZRoYy/com2us-is-going-full-speed-on-crypto-gaming-kyu-lee"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kyu Lee is the President of game studio Com2uS USA. In an interview, he shares the studio's approach to Web3 and crypto gaming with Decrypt GG's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Discord Game with AI and Blockchain: 'Alchemy: Battle for Ankhos' Creative Lead Alex Finden]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mF18GHGo/building-a-discord-game-with-ai-and-blockchain-alchemy-battle-for-ankhos-creative-lead-alex-finden</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mF18GHGo/building-a-discord-game-with-ai-and-blockchain-alchemy-battle-for-ankhos-creative-lead-alex-finden"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T21:55:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Jason Nelson interviews Alchemy: Battle for Ankhos Creative Director Alex Finden at the Solana PlayGG event in San Diego, California.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Big Respect Between Ethereum and Cosmos Developer Communities': dYdX Foundation CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/XU5MbCGE/big-respect-between-ethereum-and-cosmos-developer-communities-dydx-foundation-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/XU5MbCGE/big-respect-between-ethereum-and-cosmos-developer-communities-dydx-foundation-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T13:24:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CEO of the dYdX Foundation Charles d'Haussy unpacks the decision behind moving one of the largest decentralized exchange protocol's over to its very own chain built on Cosmos. A key driver, he told Decrypt at this year's EthCC event, was that instead of launching on a rollup or another layer-1, launching a fully customized chain will allow dYdX to fine tune the network for its product's needs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Staking Solution Lido 'Had Perfect Product Market Fit' at Launch, Says DAO's Biz Dev Contributor]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/fUHhelhV/ethereum-staking-solution-lido-had-perfect-product-market-fit-at-launch-says-daos-biz-dev-contributor</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/fUHhelhV/ethereum-staking-solution-lido-had-perfect-product-market-fit-at-launch-says-daos-biz-dev-contributor"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T08:43:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marin Tvrdić, a business development contributor to the Lido DAO, sat down with Decrypt during this year's EthCC to break down how the liquid staking protocol has managed such a massive lead, how it plans to keep that lead, and the protocol's new dual-governance tokenomics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's Going to Stop All the DeFi Hacks? 'Standards,' Says OpenZepplin Security Architect]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/aYNuFdAi/whats-going-to-stop-all-the-defi-hacks-standards-says-openzepplin-security-architect</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/aYNuFdAi/whats-going-to-stop-all-the-defi-hacks-standards-says-openzepplin-security-architect"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T08:04:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenZeppelin's security solutions architect Michael Lewellen sat down with Decrypt to discuss how the industry can become a little safer for users at this year's EthCC Paris. The key? Introducing security standards across the industry so folks know what an audit actually means and where risks lie, be it bad faith actors or poor implementation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Ev.io' Game Review: Earn Solana While Blasting Enemies]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/2ZmkuhL2/evio-game-review-earn-solana-while-blasting-enemies</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/2ZmkuhL2/evio-game-review-earn-solana-while-blasting-enemies"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T22:21:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ev.io is a web-based first-person shooter that's free to play, but lets NFT holders earn in-game currency that can be redeemed for Solana (SOL). Decrypt contributor Ryan Gladwin shares his review of the fun throwback to Quake-style blasting, albeit with a modern crypto twist.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Moving Fast and Breaking Things Isn't the Web3 Ethos': MetaMask Product Lead]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/l1EbLgl3/moving-fast-and-breaking-things-isnt-the-web3-ethos-metamask-product-lead</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/l1EbLgl3/moving-fast-and-breaking-things-isnt-the-web3-ethos-metamask-product-lead"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T15:45:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Account abstraction this, smart wallets that. Discussions at EthCC Paris about improving user experience have pointed at industry leader MetaMask as an example of what not to do. But that may soon change, with a host of updates and optimizations coming to crypto's number one wallet, said its product lead Alex Jupiter. It still may take some time, though, before these changes take effect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling Smart Wallets on Starknet 'Was The Winning Combination', Says Argent Co-Founder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/gnBsxw4D/scaling-smart-wallets-on-starknet-was-the-winning-combination-says-argent-co-founder</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/gnBsxw4D/scaling-smart-wallets-on-starknet-was-the-winning-combination-says-argent-co-founder"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T07:35:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Argent co-founder Julien Niset told Decrypt at EthCC Paris that he wants to make crypto wallets disappear. Or at least how they're currently conceived. From clunky seed phrases to a stiff user experience, Argent hopes to make using crypto a little less intimidating and a whole lot more fun.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>