<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-10-19T18:23:23.752Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-10-19T18:23:23.752Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bringing Inheritance Firms and Professionals to Manage Assets on Cardano]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20050964/Bringing-Inheritance-Firms-and-Professionals-to-Manage-Assets-on-Cardano</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20050964/Bringing-Inheritance-Firms-and-Professionals-to-Manage-Assets-on-Cardano"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T18:18:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano needs its Dapps and Projects to make an effort to onboard more firms and individuals into Cardano and even to help onboard more real-world assets to be managed on Blockchain. That is what GenWealth is searching to do. From conversations with Inheritance professionals, GenWealth has a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Scam Operator Sentenced to 20 Years, Ordered to Forfeit $3.6M]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20050950/Crypto-Scam-Operator-Sentenced-to-20-Years-Ordered-to-Forfeit-36M</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20050950/Crypto-Scam-Operator-Sentenced-to-20-Years-Ordered-to-Forfeit-36M"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T18:15:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Victims tracked fake profits via an online portal; the perpetrator delayed payouts with excuses and hidden fees.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GRVT Announces Major 2024 Airdrop for DeFi Users]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20050953/GRVT-Announces-Major-2024-Airdrop-for-DeFi-Users</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20050953/GRVT-Announces-Major-2024-Airdrop-for-DeFi-Users"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T18:15:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GRVT is launching a major 2024 airdrop, offering 12% of its token supply to regular users as part of its upcoming regulated DeFi hybrid exchange.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yellow Network Prepares for ICO]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20050945/Yellow-Network-Prepares-for-ICO</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20050945/Yellow-Network-Prepares-for-ICO"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T18:11:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yellow Network is set to launch its ICO in late 2024, offering innovative cross-chain trading solutions with strong backing from major investors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum's Price Target Slips Amid Investor Shift]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20050876/Ethereums-Price-Target-Slips-Amid-Investor-Shift</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20050876/Ethereums-Price-Target-Slips-Amid-Investor-Shift"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T18:04:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum's price goal has faded as dropping ETF inflows and increased selling pressure push analysts to lower expectations for the token.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Banking Trojan Compromises 13,000 Android Users, Security Experts Warn]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20050861/New-Banking-Trojan-Compromises-13000-Android-Users-Security-Experts-Warn</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20050861/New-Banking-Trojan-Compromises-13000-Android-Users-Security-Experts-Warn"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T18:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security specialists have discovered a new variant of the TrickMo banking Trojan, which has compromised approximately 13,000 Android devices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Toncoin (TON) Price Faces Potential Drop Below $5: Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20050942/Toncoin-TON-Price-Faces-Potential-Drop-Below-5-Heres-Why</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20050942/Toncoin-TON-Price-Faces-Potential-Drop-Below-5-Heres-Why"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For most of the week, the Toncoin (TON) price remained range-bound at $5. This movement contradicts previous signals that the altcoin’s value would trade much higher. While TON still has the potential to go beyond the current levels, recent data shows that it could take some time as it could...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Moral Case for Bitcoin: Decentralized Currency as a Path to Freedom]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74455f3980</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/the-moral-case-for-bitcoin-decentralized-currency-as-a-path-to-freedom/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T17:58:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a world where state-backed currencies fund wars, inflate economies and deplete savings, digital alternatives like bitcoin offer a compelling ethical choice. By removing money from government control, bitcoin presents a route toward a freer and more just society. The Flaws of Fiat Currencies Government-issued fiat money, which lacks intrinsic value, is often manipulated through […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock Eyes BUIDL as New Crypto Collateral in Derivatives Market]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20050850/BlackRock-Eyes-BUIDL-as-New-Crypto-Collateral-in-Derivatives-Market</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20050850/BlackRock-Eyes-BUIDL-as-New-Crypto-Collateral-in-Derivatives-Market"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T17:55:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock is in talks with major crypto exchanges to use its BUIDL token as collateral for derivatives, aiming to compete with Tether in the crypto market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Smart Money is Betting Billions on Bitcoin & AI to WIN the Decade!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20050944/Why-Smart-Money-is-Betting-Billions-on-Bitcoin-AI-to-WIN-the-Decade</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20050944/Why-Smart-Money-is-Betting-Billions-on-Bitcoin-AI-to-WIN-the-Decade"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T17:53:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smart money like Microsoft, Google, Amazon, and the greatest investors in the world are telling us that Bitcoin and AI will dominate the next decade! Why are Stanley Druckenmiller and Financial Powerhouses pouring billions into Bitcoin infrastructure?! What does it mean? You don't want to miss...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can the meme coin craze ignite a Solana price rally?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20050849/Can-the-meme-coin-craze-ignite-a-Solana-price-rally</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20050849/Can-the-meme-coin-craze-ignite-a-Solana-price-rally"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T17:53:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Memecoins have once again captured the cryptocurrency spotlight, with Solana (SOL) emerging as a key network supporting this growing trend. … Continue reading]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angel Drainer Acquires Rival Crypto Phishing Service Inferno]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20050848/Angel-Drainer-Acquires-Rival-Crypto-Phishing-Service-Inferno</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20050848/Angel-Drainer-Acquires-Rival-Crypto-Phishing-Service-Inferno"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T17:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Angel Drainer reportedly acquired Inferno’s source code as the latter quit the crypto scamming business.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Meme Coin GOAT Soars as Crypto Whales Invest Big]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20050840/Solana-Meme-Coin-GOAT-Soars-as-Crypto-Whales-Invest-Big</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20050840/Solana-Meme-Coin-GOAT-Soars-as-Crypto-Whales-Invest-Big"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T17:44:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto whales are flocking to Solana meme coin GOAT after a 260% price surge, fueling speculation of further gains as social media buzz continues to grow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US legal officials push for hostage label for Binance executive held in Nigeria]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20050832/US-legal-officials-push-for-hostage-label-for-Binance-executive-held-in-Nigeria</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20050832/US-legal-officials-push-for-hostage-label-for-Binance-executive-held-in-Nigeria"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T17:37:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A coalition of U.S. attorneys general, spearheaded by Utah Attorney General Sean Reyes, has sent a letter to President Joe Biden and Secretary of State Antony Blinken. They are urging the administration to classify Binance executive Tigran Gambaryan, currently detained in Nigeria, as a hostage....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miners Are Embracing AI, Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20050831/Bitcoin-Miners-Are-Embracing-AI-Heres-Why</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20050831/Bitcoin-Miners-Are-Embracing-AI-Heres-Why"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T17:35:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For Bitcoin miners, the most recent halving event did not generate the anticipated profit, which is currently prompting them to pursue artificial intelligence. Some of the most critical actors in the Web3.0 ecosystem are Bitcoin miners. The changes in the network, particularly the halving...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitwise CIO Predicts Six-Figure Bitcoin is Certain]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20050810/Bitwise-CIO-Predicts-Six-Figure-Bitcoin-is-Certain</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20050810/Bitwise-CIO-Predicts-Six-Figure-Bitcoin-is-Certain"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T17:22:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to Bitwise CIO Matt Hougan, Bitcoin is anticipated to experience a substantial increase in value, which would propel its price into the six-figure range. Just recently, Bitwise CIO Matt Hougan expressed his optimism regarding Bitcoin. He stated that the cryptocurrency was on the brink...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China has not cracked encryption, at least not yet — Mental Outlaw]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20050790/China-has-not-cracked-encryption-at-least-not-yet-Mental-Outlaw</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20050790/China-has-not-cracked-encryption-at-least-not-yet-Mental-Outlaw"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T17:05:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quantum bits currently require temperatures between approximately -200 degrees Celsius to -270 degrees Celsius to operate properly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock Takes Aim at Tether With BUIDL Collateral Strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20050791/BlackRock-Takes-Aim-at-Tether-With-BUIDL-Collateral-Strategy</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20050791/BlackRock-Takes-Aim-at-Tether-With-BUIDL-Collateral-Strategy"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T17:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock’s BUIDL token could challenge Tether’s dominance in crypto derivatives, offering new collateral options and revenue streams.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Expert Predicts Bitcoin Could Soar Above $100,000 – Here is Why]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20050705/Crypto-Expert-Predicts-Bitcoin-Could-Soar-Above-100000-Here-is-Why</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20050705/Crypto-Expert-Predicts-Bitcoin-Could-Soar-Above-100000-Here-is-Why"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T17:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matt Hougan, Bitwise COO, is optimistic about Bitcoin’s prospects, predicting the potential for a substantial rally that could push its price into six figures.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is BONK ready for a price breakout? THIS level could be key!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20050726/Is-BONK-ready-for-a-price-breakout-THIS-level-could-be-key</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20050726/Is-BONK-ready-for-a-price-breakout-THIS-level-could-be-key"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T17:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A key resistance level is being tested and that could be good news for BONK.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Radiant Capital Working With US Law Enforcement To Freeze Stolen Crypto Assets After $50,000,000 Hack This Week]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20050695/Radiant-Capital-Working-With-US-Law-Enforcement-To-Freeze-Stolen-Crypto-Assets-After-50000000-Hack-This-Week</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20050695/Radiant-Capital-Working-With-US-Law-Enforcement-To-Freeze-Stolen-Crypto-Assets-After-50000000-Hack-This-Week"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T16:55:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The decentralized finance (DeFi) platform Radiant Capital (RDNT) is working with US law enforcement to freeze stolen assets after suffering a $50 million hack earlier this week. Hackers cracked multiple developers’ hardware wallets “through a highly advanced malware injection,” according to a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Is Today’s 'Tomarket' Telegram Game Daily Combo]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286780</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/here-is-todays-tomarket-telegram-game-daily-combo"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T16:20:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram game Tomarket is handing out free tomatoes and bonus items ahead of the airdrop. Here’s the combo for Saturday, October 19.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized Money Market Protocol Loses $4.3M in Social Engineering Attack]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7445413b9e</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/decentralized-money-market-protocol-loses-4-3m-in-social-engineering-attack/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T16:17:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tapioca DAO, has been the victim of a social engineering attack in which criminals exploited a vulnerability to compromise the ownership of the TAP token vesting contract. The breach led to the sale of 30 million vested tokens. A blockchain security firm detected suspicious activity involving Tapioca DAO. The attacker withdrew millions of TAP tokens, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock Seeks To Push BUIDL As Derivative Collateral In Crypto Market – Details]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74454d182c</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/blackrock-push-buidl-crypto-derivative-collateral/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T15:41:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The world’s largest asset manager, BlackRock, aims to expand its foray in the digital asset industry following the successful launch of spot Bitcoin and Ethereum ETFs in 2024. In a new venture, the American asset manager is attempting to push the adoption of its money-market token BUIDL as a collateral asset in the crypto derivative market. 
 
 
BlackRock’s BUIDL To Serve As Derivative Collateral: Report
 
According to a Friday report by Bloomberg, BlackRock has begun marketing BUIDL as collateral in the crypto derivative market. For context, BUIDL – which stands for BlackRock USD Institutional Digital Liquidity Fund – is a tokenized fund issued on the Ethereum blockchain offering institutional investors access to achieving US dollar yields.
 
Similar to stablecoins, BUIDL is pegged to a s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Semilore Faleti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Millionaire Picks His Favorite Altcoin For 2025, 12,000x Rally Looming]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7445482bb9</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-millionaire-picks-his-favorite-altcoin-for-2025-12000x-rally-looming/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T15:13:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As 2025 approaches, the excitement around RCO Finance (RCOF) rises, especially after the Dogecoin millionaire named it his top altcoin for next year, suggesting a potential 12,000x rally. 
 
With its ongoing presale attracting attention, investors are eager to seize the opportunity before RCOF takes off, positioning themselves for significant returns.
 
Dogecoin Millionaire Bets Big on RCO Finance: Next-Gen DeFi Platform Set to Explode 
RCO Finance is primed for a significant breakout, particularly after garnering attention from the Dogecoin millionaire. As the platform expands and attracts more users, RCO Finance (RCOF) is quickly gaining recognition for its innovative, AI-powered solutions that reshape the financial landscape.
 
Fueling this bullish momentum is the growing adoption of it…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friday’s Big Moves: Bitcoin ETFs Dominate With Fresh Inflows – Here’s What You Missed]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74454ac01c</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/fridays-big-moves-bitcoin-etfs-dominate-with-fresh-inflows-heres-what-you-missed/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T14:47:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spot bitcoin and ether exchange-traded funds (ETFs) in the U.S. had another winning day, with both categories seeing a steady flow of fresh investments. On Friday, the 12 bitcoin ETFs pulled in a combined $273.71 million, led by ARKB and IBIT at the front of the pack. Bitcoin ETFs Secure Inflows on Friday, Ether Funds […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Ordinal Sales Surge by 1,816%—And It’s Just Part of This Week’s NFT Shakeup]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e744530d137</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-ordinal-sales-surge-by-1816-and-its-just-part-of-this-weeks-nft-shakeup/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T13:47:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amid the broad uptick in crypto asset markets, non-fungible token (NFT) sales saw a 22.38% increase this past week. NFT sales managed to rake in $92.95 million this week and Ethereum and Bitcoin NFT sales led the way. Digital Collectibles Spike in Activity as Ethereum and Bitcoin Top the NFT Charts NFTs enjoyed an increase […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GOAT, the AI-Launched Meme Token—Navigating the Regulatory Uncertainty of Autonomous Agents]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74453cde5a</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/goat-the-ai-launched-meme-token-navigating-the-regulatory-uncertainty-of-autonomous-agents/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T13:06:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In recent developments, a notable instance occurred involving a tech titan, Marc Andreessen, and an AI bot named Truth Terminal. Andreessen’s decision to grant $50,000 in bitcoin to this semi-autonomous AI agent, to fund hardware upgrades and launch a cryptocurrency token named GOAT, illuminates potential regulatory challenges that lie ahead. This episode underscores the blurred […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kamala Harris Crypto Regulation Plans Spark Criticism—But Also Optimism]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287262</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287262/kamala-harris-crypto-regulation-criticism-optimism"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T13:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Kamala Harris campaign’s focus on Black male crypto investors sparks claims of pandering, but some still consider it a positive move.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Litecoin Jumps 11%: Here’s What’s Driving This Rally]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e744524a2b7</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/litecoin-jumps-11-heres-whats-driving-this-rally/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T11:46:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data suggests developments in these two Litecoin indicators could explain why the cryptocurrency has seen its latest price surge.
 
Litecoin Volume & Social Dominance Have Surged Recently
 
In a new post on X, the on-chain analytics firm Santiment has discussed about how the underlying metrics of Litecoin have looked during the latest surge in its price.
 
There are two indicators of relevance here: the Transaction Volume and the Social Dominance. The first of these, the Transaction Volume, keeps track of the total amount of tokens (in USD) that are becoming involved in transfers on the LTC network.
 
 
When the value of this metric is high, it means the investors are participating in a high amount of trading activity related to the asset. Such a trend can be a sign that the inter…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto ATMs Coming to 45 New Locations Across Five US States]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e744525ab46</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/crypto-atms-coming-to-45-new-locations-across-five-us-states/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T11:34:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency is becoming more accessible across the U.S. with the expansion of digital currency kiosks to 45 new locations in the Southwest and Midwest. Yesway, a fast-growing convenience store chain, is partnering with Coinflip to bring crypto ATMs to its customers, offering a seamless and secure way to buy and sell bitcoin and other digital […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Best Free Games to Play on Xbox Series X and S]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287076</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287076/best-free-games-xbox-series-x-s"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T11:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking for some great games to play on your Xbox Series X/S without paying a dime? Here are our favorite Xbox freebies right now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Frederiksen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Influence On 2024 US Presidential Election Bigger Than Expected, Survey Finds]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7445227683</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-influence-on-2024-us-presidential-election-bigger-than-expected-survey-finds/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T10:46:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to a recent survey by the pro-crypto trade group The Digital Chamber, the US presidential candidate’s stance on crypto could be more significant than initially anticipated.
 
26 Million Voters In The “Crypto Voting Bloc”
 
The “crypto voting bloc” refers to a group of voters – both Republicans and Democrats – who consider digital assets either “very” or “extremely” important in determining their vote. These voters are more likely to support a candidate with a pro-crypto stance.
 
 
Of the 1,004 respondents surveyed, about 16%, or one in seven individuals, opined that digital assets will play a crucial role in helping them determine which candidate to support.
 
Interestingly, 25% of Democratic and 21% of Republican voters said they would prefer a pro-crypto presidential candidate…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ash Tiwari</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Dookey Dash: Unclogged' Tips Guide: How to Dominate the Bored Ape Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287263</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/dookey-dash-unclogged-tips-guide-bored-ape-game"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T10:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bored Ape Yacht Club game Dookey Dash: Unclogged serves up an endless runner with real prizes. Here's how to rule the sewers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Stubbs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Grants Approval for 11 Spot Bitcoin ETFs to Trade Options on NYSE]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74452b4f31</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com/cryptocurrency/sec-grants-approval-for-11-spot-bitcoin-etfs-to-trade-options-on-nyse/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T09:13:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has granted  
accelerated approval to 11 exchange-traded funds (ETFs) for listing and trading  
options tied to spot Bitcoin prices on the New York Stock Exchange. 
This decision follows a regulatory filing made public. In  
January, the SEC had approved Bitcoin ETFs to track the cryptocurrency’s value,  
marking a significant development for Bitcoin and the broader cryptocurrency  
market.
Bitcoin ETFs Offer Hedging Options
The approved funds include the Fidelity Wise Origin Bitcoin  
Fund, ARK21Shares Bitcoin ETF, Invesco Galaxy Bitcoin ETF, Grayscale Bitcoin  
Trust BTC, and iShares Bitcoin Trust ETF. These options will provide  
institutional investors and traders with an alternative way to hedge their  
exposure to Bitcoin.
Options are d…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tareq Sikder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Scam Alert: EigenLayer’s X Account Hijacked To Promote Fraudulent Airdrop]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e744515e070</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-scam-alert-eigenlayers-x-account-hijacked/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T08:46:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the early hours of Friday, the official X (formerly Twitter) account of EigenLayer, a prominent restaking protocol, was compromised and used to promote a fraudulent airdrop, according to a confirmation from its developer, Eigen Labs.
 
The hackers exploited the account to share misleading posts about a fake reallocation of EIGEN tokens for Season 2 of EigenLayer’s airdrop. This malicious campaign attempted to lure users into engaging with suspicious links and submitting claims under pretenses.
 
 
The Aftermath And The Details
 
Following the hack, Eigen Labs immediately alerted users about the breach, urging them to avoid interacting with the posts and the fraudulent links.
 
The developer emphasized the importance of verifying any communication and ensuring that users were engaging wi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong’s Fraud Empire Collapses: How Triads, AI, and Fake Love Fuel Massive Crypto Heist]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e744516ef67</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/hong-kongs-fraud-empire-collapses-how-triads-ai-and-fake-love-fuel-massive-crypto-heist/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T08:35:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong police have dismantled a notorious fraud syndicate responsible for defrauding victims of HK$360 million using romance scams tied to fake cryptocurrency platforms. Arresting 27 individuals, some linked to triads, they revealed the sophisticated use of deepfake technology and digital media expertise to deceive victims across Asia. Massive Fraud Syndicate Busted: Deepfake Romance Scams, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin Drops ‘Coin’ In Major Rebrand To ‘World’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74451e12b2</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/worldcoin-drops-coin-in-major-rebrand-to-world/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T07:16:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Analysts are optimistic that cryptocurrency World, formerly known as Worldcoin, could potentially have a price rally despite experiencing a recent price drop.
 
Sam Altman’s Worldcoin said during a media event in San Francisco that it will now be branded as environment to expand its focus beyond digital asset ownership to identity verification in an AI-driven environment. Sam Altman and Alex Blania introduced the Orb 2.0, an upgraded iris-recognition system.
 
The positive outlook on the World coin indicates that its value is forecasted to increase significantly in the upcoming weeks on the back of the crypto’s strong growth potential.
 
 
World: Price Fluctuation Suggests A Reversal
 
The fluctuating prices that World crypto is experiencing could possibly signal a bullish reversal that co…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastermind Behind Fake Coinbase Website Scheme Sentenced To 5 Years In Prison]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74451e12af</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/mastermind-behind-fake-coinbase-website-scheme-sentenced-to-5-years-in-prison/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T07:16:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An Indian man received a 5-year sentence for a multi-million fraud involving a fake Coinbase website. The 2-year scheme took over $20 million in crypto from hundreds of victims, which was used to fund the fraudster’s lavish lifestyle.
 
 
Indian National To Serve 5-Year Sentence
 
On Thursday, the US Attorney’s Office for the Western District of North Carolina announced that an Indian man was sentenced to 5 years in prison for stealing over $20 million using a spoofed website imitating crypto exchange Coinbase’s platform.
 
US District Judge Kenneth D. Bell ordered Chirag Tomar, a 31-year-old Indian National, to serve 60 months in prison, followed by two years of supervised release. The sentence follows the defendant’s guilty plea to the wire fraud charge in May.
 
Tomar was charged with o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rubmar Garcia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fake Coinbase Sites Steal $20M — How Indian Man Led the Massive Crypto Fraud]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74450661fc</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/fake-coinbase-sites-steal-20m-how-indian-man-led-the-massive-crypto-fraud/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T05:33:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A cryptocurrency scam targeting Coinbase users has resulted in a significant theft of over $20 million. An Indian national, Chirag Tomar, was sentenced for orchestrating this scheme, where fake websites mimicking Coinbase led to victims surrendering credentials. U.S. authorities revealed how fraudsters used advanced tactics, including remote desktop access and posing as support agents, to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gold Tops Safe Haven Assets, According To Bank Of America—Can Bitcoin Compete?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74450c8f6f</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/gold-tops-safe-haven-assets-according-to-bank-of-america-can-bitcoin-compete/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T04:15:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For years, the financial community has debated on the best and safest investment during uncertain times. For most conservative traders and investors, bonds are an obvious choice. But for the younger set and tech-savvy individuals, Bitcoin is a better option. Despite fiscal challenges and current global economic trends, gold remains the best bet for analysts at Bank of America.
 
 
According to Bank of America, gold remains solid, regardless of falling or even higher interest rates. Interestingly, the bank is silent on Bitcoin’s role in the financial markets. However, many leading American banks are starting to get friendly, with Bank of America’s Merrill Lynch and Wells Fargo offering Bitcoin ETFs to their eligible clients.
 
 
 WOW: Bank of America today: Gold is the ‘last safe haven’ as …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Expands Mobile Money Across Africa — 6 More Countries Gain Access]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74450f137f</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/binance-expands-mobile-money-across-africa-6-more-countries-gain-access/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T03:41:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto exchange Binance has expanded its reach in West and Central Africa, integrating mobile money payments for cryptocurrency purchases in six countries. This move supports Binance’s goal to boost financial inclusion and make digital assets more accessible. By offering a secure, user-friendly entry into crypto, Binance aims to empower millions across Africa with greater access […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Bettor ‘Fredi’ Distorts Trump Odds On Polymarket, Researcher Claims]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74450aeb51</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-bettor-distorts-trump-odds-polymarket/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T02:44:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a story within the decentralized prediction market sphere, a researcher has accused a crypto bettor, operating under the pseudonym ‘Fredi9999’ or simply ‘Fredi,’ of significantly manipulating the odds for former President Donald Trump on the crypto platform Polymarket. Over the past fortnight, Trump’s probability of winning has surged from near parity with Vice President Kamala Harris to a substantial 60.7%, while Harris’s odds have dwindled to 39.3%.
 
The allegations were brought to light by Domer (@Domahhhh), a pseudonymous political crypto bettor, who detailed his findings in an extensive thread on X. Domer stated: “A long-winded and winding update on Fredi9999 — the person or entity — who is singlehandedly rocketing up the price of Trump on prediction markets around the world. Spoi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Digital Ruble and Sanctions: Expert Analyzes Russia’s Digital Currency Plan to Evade Western Control]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74450bb138</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/digital-ruble-and-sanctions-expert-analyzes-russias-digital-currency-plan-to-evade-western-control/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T02:32:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Fellow at the Carnegie Russia Eurasia Center and former adviser at the Central Bank of Russia has weighed in on the digital ruble, Russia’s central bank digital currency (CBDC), highlighting its potential role in reshaping Russia’s financial landscape amid sanctions. While the digital currency could offer new avenues for trade and reduce reliance on […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Is Today’s 'Major' Telegram Game Puzzle Durov Combo]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286896</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/here-is-todays-major-telegram-puzzle-durov-combo"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T01:15:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking to complete Major’s daily Pavel Durov puzzle on Telegram? Here’s the solution for Friday, October 18.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bluesky Signups Surge After Elon Musk's Twitter Says AI Can Be Trained on Tweets]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287241</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287241/bluesky-signups-surge-elon-musk-twitter-ai"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T20:31:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk's controversial moves at Twitter have sparked another user exodus, fueling explosive growth for decentralized rival Bluesky.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No, the SEC Isn't Backing Off Solana—Here's the Latest]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287253</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287253/sec-isnt-backing-off-solana-binance-latest"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T20:08:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New developments in the SEC’s lawsuit against Binance indicate the regulator is ratcheting up its case against SOL and other crypto tokens—not backing down, as some had hoped.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Huge week for BTC ETFs, Crypto now through Venmo, Memes Dominate Gainers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rLpBnnaQ/huge-week-for-btc-etfs-crypto-now-through-venmo-memes-dominate-gainers</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rLpBnnaQ/huge-week-for-btc-etfs-crypto-now-through-venmo-memes-dominate-gainers"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T19:24:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETFs see biggest inflow week since July. BlackRock ETF sees $1bn inflows in a week. Venmo can now be used to buy crypto on Moonpay. SEC’s XRP appeal doesn’t challenge security status. Worldcoin rebrands to World with new orb. EigenLayer X account compromised. FBI arrests hacker of SEC X account. SCB in Thailand adopts stablecoins for transfers. DBS in Singapore adopts ‘token services’. Trump family to get 75% of WLFL revenue. Scroll team accused of owning sybil addresses. STX Nakamoto upgrade to happen next week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Olympic Snowboarder Used Tether in Cocaine-Smuggling Murder Scheme, Feds Say]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287204</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287204/olympic-snowboarder-tether-cocaine-murders"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T19:20:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Canadian Olympic snowboarder and his gang used Tether (USDT) as part of its cocaine trafficking operation, U.S. authorities allege.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin 'Trump Trade' Returns as BlackRock's ETF Brings in Another $1 Billion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287209</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287209/bitcoin-trump-trade-blackrock-etf-billion"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T18:54:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF inflows have accelerated this week as the 2024 presidential election tightens in its final weeks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will 'Off the Grid' Take Crypto Games Mainstream?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287211</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287211/will-off-the-grid-take-crypto-games-mainstream"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T18:13:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche shooter Off the Grid has already made a huge splash in early access. We discuss the launch and potential impact on gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward,Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Let Him Come Home': Jailed Binance Exec’s Trial Postponed Due to Illness]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287207</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287207/jailed-binance-exec-trial-postponed-illness"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T17:42:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imprisoned Binance executive Tigran Gambaryan failed to attend a Nigerian court hearing due to his poor health, forcing a delay.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scammer Gets 5 Years in Prison After Swiping $20 Million via Fake Coinbase Websites]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287203</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287203/scammer-prison-fake-coinbase-websites"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T17:29:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chirag Tomar, an Indian national, drained the accounts of unsuspecting Coinbase customers in a scam built around impostor websites.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Is Booming—You Can Earn More by Playing These Free Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=205392</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/205392/bitcoin-booming-you-earn-more-playing-free-games"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T16:52:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATE: Bitcoin is making a move for $69,000 as "Uptober" takes root, and you can earn more BTC by playing these games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Radiant Capital’s $50M Breach Among ‘Most Sophisticated Hacks’ in DeFi History]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287162</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287162/radiant-capitals-50m-breach-among-most-sophisticated-hacks-in-defi-history"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T16:52:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The DeFi project claimed that hackers compromised the hardware wallets of its long-term developers and injected malware.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will McCurdy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[dGEN1 Mobile Device Launches for ‘Seamless’ Onchain Ethereum Transactions]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287120</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287120/dgen1-mobile-device-launches-for-seamless-onchain-ethereum-transactions"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T15:53:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Created by Freedom Factory, dGEN1 integrates Ethereum at the operating system level to streamline dapp interactions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy's Bitcoin Scheme Isn't an 'Infinite Money Glitch', Says Michael Saylor]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287163</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287163/microstrategy-bitcoin-scheme-isnt-infinite-money-glitch"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T15:18:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy founder Michael Saylor dismissed criticism over the firm's $16 billion Bitcoin haul, saying it's driving BTC scarcity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EigenLayer Twitter Account Hacked to Share Ethereum Airdrop Scam]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287159</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287159/eigenlayer-twitter-hack-airdrop-scam"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T14:37:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A hacker published a series of posts Friday from EigenLayer's Twitter account, urging users to click on an apparent phishing link.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Napolitano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Machine Learning AI Helped Detect $4 Billion Worth of Fraud in 2024, Says US Treasury]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287141</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287141/machine-learning-ai-us-treasury"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T12:54:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI models helped the department prevent $2.5 billion in fraud, while its check fraud detection systems facilitated the recovery of $1 billion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vismaya V</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Is Today’s 'Captain Tsubasa: Rivals' Telegram Game Daily Combo]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=250928</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/captain-tsubasa-rivals-telegram-game-daily-combo"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T12:50:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anime soccer game Captain Tsubasa: Rivals gives out 5 million free daily balls ahead of the TON token airdrop. Here’s the combo for Friday, October 18.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Craig Wright Says Bitcoin Devs 'Misled the Public' in New $1 Billion Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287138</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287138/craig-wright-bitcoin-new-lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T12:29:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After the SegWit and Taproot upgrades, Craig Wright claims Bitcoin “fundamentally deviated” from Satoshi Nakamoto’s vision and misled investors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Could Hit Turbulence From US Bond Yields, Fed Policy: Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287119</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287119/bitcoin-could-hit-turbulence-from-us-bond-yields-fed-policy-analyst"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T11:49:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin has climbed 11% in the past week, but there could be some macroeconomic headwinds on the horizon, say analysts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Moons Again After Musk Drops Token Mention During Pennsylvania Town Hall]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287079</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287079/dogecoin-moons-again-musk-drops-token-mention-during-pennsylvania-town-hall"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T05:29:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Someone asked Musk if he would head up a new “Department of Government Efficiency.” Musk responded with a lighthearted grin, “Yeah, Doge.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vismaya V</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Files Last-Minute Appeal in Ripple Case—Why the XRP Army is Outraged]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287069</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287069/sec-files-last-minute-appeal-in-ripple-case-why-xrp-army-outraged"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T02:15:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While the SEC isn't contesting the ruling that XRP sales to retail investors aren't securities, it is instead focusing on other key aspects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Sinclair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin Rebrands as World, Launches New Eyeball Scanning Orb]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287051</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287051/worldcoin-rebrands-as-world-launches-new-retina-scanning-orb"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T23:30:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[World's redesigned Orb has 30% fewer parts and triple the production capacity of its predecessor, powered by NVIDIA’s Jetson.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Researchers Hacked AI Robots Into Breaking Traffic Laws—And Worse]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286994</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286994/how-researchers-hacked-ai-robots-into-breaking-traffic-laws-and-worse"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T23:14:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers showed vulnerabilities in AI-powered robots being exploited to perform dangerous tasks, including detonating bombs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Worldcoin Built an Ethereum Network Specifically for Humans]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286983</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286983/world-chain-launches-mainnet-world-coin"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T22:34:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[World, previously called Worldcoin, has debuted an Ethereum layer-2 chain with an aim to onboard real humans—not bots.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Napolitano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Bulls Have Reason to Worry If L2s Remain Dominant, Says VanEck Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286970</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286970/ethereum-price-target-plunge-vaneck-analyst"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T22:16:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum's "changing fundamentals" and growing embrace of layer-2 networks could massively impact ETH's future price, a VanEck analyst said Thursday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk-Themed ‘X Empire’ Ends Telegram Gameplay Ahead of Airdrop]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286977</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286977/x-empire-ends-telegram-gameplay-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T21:12:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tap-to-earn game X Empire is gearing up for next week’s X token launch and airdrop on The Open Network (TON).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PayPal's Venmo Can Now Be Used to Buy Bitcoin and Ethereum via MoonPay]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286969</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286969/paypal-venmo-buy-crypto-moonpay"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T20:52:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PayPal's Venmo can now be used by U.S. customers to top up and make crypto purchases on MoonPay, according to a Thursday announcement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETFs Race Past $20 Billion Milestone in Just 10 Months]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286948</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286948/bitcoin-etf-20-billion-milestone-inflows-blackrock"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T19:06:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Approved in January, Bitcoin exchange-traded funds have experienced trading activity like no other ETF product.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Galaxis Teams Up With TV Show ‘Killer Whales’ to ‘Empower Creators’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285090</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285090/galaxis-teams-up-with-tv-show-killer-whales-to-empower-creators"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T19:05:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The partnership will see Galaxis showcased throughout the reality show, as well as “actively supporting” the Web3 projects featured.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wrapped Bitcoin Wars Ramp Up as Kraken Reveals kBTC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286934</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286934/wrapped-bitcoin-wars-kraken-kbtc"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T17:58:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto exchange Kraken has unveiled a new wrapped Bitcoin product dubbed kBTC, joining a growing battle with Coinbase, 21.co, and BitGo.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Presidential Election Tops $2 Billion in Betting Volume on Polymarket]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286923</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286923/us-presidential-election-2-billion-volume-polymarket"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T17:46:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trump is currently leading the Polymarket betting pool on the winner of the U.S. election, which has topped $2 billion in total volume.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Napolitano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Majors Fall 1 to 2%, A New Tiger takes to the Charts, Van Eck teases Big Web3 Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/a6Tm7OGW/majors-fall-1-to-2-a-new-tiger-takes-to-the-charts-van-eck-teases-big-web3-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/a6Tm7OGW/majors-fall-1-to-2-a-new-tiger-takes-to-the-charts-van-eck-teases-big-web3-gaming"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T17:42:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lucky GOAT memecoin trader turned $5,000 into $1.5M during GOAT's run to $300M. A new memecoin based on Disney Park's new baby tiger "Bakso" was a top mover on Wednesday, running to $10M (now $6M). Crypto majors fall 1-2%, memes red across board. a16z calls 2024 crypto's biggest year yet in "State of Crypto" report. Vitalik publishes part 2 of blog outlining ETH's future. Van Eck teases big bet on Parallel and web3 gaming. Huge day for digital art with 4 marquee mints seeing success.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hamster Kombat Season 2 Teaser]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/qcvjjJxN/hamster-kombat-season-2-teaser</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/qcvjjJxN/hamster-kombat-season-2-teaser"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T12:03:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here's a first look at Season 2 of Telegram tap-to-earn game Hamster Kombat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BTC hits $68K, Trump odds Continue to Rise, GOAT nears $300M]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/c88qN8eB/btc-hits-68k-trump-odds-continue-to-rise-goat-nears-300m</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/c88qN8eB/btc-hits-68k-trump-odds-continue-to-rise-goat-nears-300m"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T18:31:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC hits $68k as ETF inflows continue to soar. Open Interest at CME hits ATH, funding still low. Tesla moves $750m BTC to new wallet. Canary applies for Litcoin ETF, LTC up 8%. Grayscale asks SEC to convert altcoin fund to ETF. Kraken integrates with EigenLayer for restaking. ‘Network state’ Praxis raises $525m for new city. Trump project raises only $11m so far. a16z founders donate $2.5m to Trump PAC. TikTok accused of being crypto exchange in UK. Gotbit CEO arrested in Portugal. Perplexity AI launches finance platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ETF Inflows Soar, Kamala Courts Crypto, TURBO Nears $1BN!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zn2lboMV/etf-inflows-soar-kamala-courts-crypto-turbo-nears-1bn</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zn2lboMV/etf-inflows-soar-kamala-courts-crypto-turbo-nears-1bn"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T18:22:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETFs see $800m inflows in 2-days, huge volume. ETF inflows may be linked to Trump odds: CoinShares. Bitcoin will rival housing market as asset class: Fink. Vitalik proposes drop to 1ETH to become validator. Kamala reveals pro-crypto policies. Kamala mocked for linking crypto to race. Hyperliquid announces HYPE token coming. PUFFER airdrop claim goes live. Tether considering lending to commodities trader. Man takes $500m lost Bitcoin case to court. Google removes crypto prices from search. SUI Foundation denies $400m insider selling. UAE approves $AED stablecoin. Bitget wallet now only behind Binance for downloads.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BTC hits 2-week High, China Stocks Rally again, GOAT hits $120M]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/0V0rYhMX/btc-hits-2-week-high-china-stocks-rally-again-goat-hits-120m</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/0V0rYhMX/btc-hits-2-week-high-china-stocks-rally-again-goat-hits-120m"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T14:09:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC hits 2-week high as China stocks rise. SUI breaks into the top 15 coins. $1.3bn ETH might be sold from PlusToken scam. S. Korea may approve BTC & ETH ETFs this month. Australia launches first ETH ETF. Samara to buy BTC with $33m bond. Altcoins to see $500m unlocks this week. Vitalik writes blog on the future of ETH. Grayscale reveals 35 altcoins considered for funds. Ethena proposes SOL for USDe collateral. Only one Binance launchpad coin up this year. AVAX summit begins this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Todd ‘revealed’ as Satoshi, Google may be Broken-up, Murad’s Wallets Doxxed]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pLw8b2d2/todd-revealed-as-satoshi-google-may-be-broken-up-murads-wallets-doxxed</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pLw8b2d2/todd-revealed-as-satoshi-google-may-be-broken-up-murads-wallets-doxxed"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T07:29:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC will be range bound until election: Bernstein. TAO & memecoins dominate mindshare. Peter Todd ‘revealed’ as Satoshi by HBO. US government able to sell $4.4bn Silk Road BTC. Ireland unable to access $378m seized BTC. SOL could do 5x if Trump wins: StanChart. Coinbase integrates Taproot addresses for BTC. Canary Capital applies for XRP ETF. S. Korea to regulate stablecoin transfers. CryptoCom files countersuit against SEC. Babylon fills cap with 22k BTC. Scroll airdrop coming Oct 22nd. USDC goes live on SUI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Falls Ahead of CPI, Stripe Reinstates Crypto, Fed Charges Market-makers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/aYgFvZqj/crypto-falls-ahead-of-cpi-stripe-reinstates-crypto-fed-charges-market-makers</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/aYgFvZqj/crypto-falls-ahead-of-cpi-stripe-reinstates-crypto-fed-charges-market-makers"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T07:29:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Majors drop despite stocks hitting ATHs. Stripe reinstates crypto payments. Crypto settlements near $20bn in 2024. S. Korea to review ban on BTC ETFs. US charges market makers for market manipulation. FBI created their own coin to ensnare targets. Vitalik ‘outside pick’ for Nobel Prize. Trump family token to built on Aave stack. $16m OP tokens allocated to superchain users. Wisdomtree debuts debit card for on-chain fund. 47% of hedge funds have crypto exposure. Argentina overtakes Brazil for crypto inflows. Tucker interviews Ryan Salame over FTX.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bounces from $59K, Tesla unveils Robotaxis, Memecoins Outperform]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cyJj6tWj/bitcoin-bounces-from-59k-tesla-unveils-robotaxis-memecoins-outperform</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cyJj6tWj/bitcoin-bounces-from-59k-tesla-unveils-robotaxis-memecoins-outperform"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T07:29:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC briefly dips under $59k, $160m liquidations. Mt Gox extends repayment plan by 1 year. Uniswap plans L2 for DeFi. SEC sues crypto trading firm Cumberland. Binomial sues SEC over futures trading. SEC’s Uyeda criticises agency’s policy. Justin Sun named prime minister of Liberland. MicroStrategy wants to become BTC bank. Binance pre-market trading goes live. Nearly 50% of US investors want crypto ETFs. Whale phished for $35m crypto. Ethena invests $46m in RWA funds. Trump’s crypto project aims to raise $300m.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentraland Desktop Client Preview]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qqzvDcTC/decentraland-desktop-client-preview</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qqzvDcTC/decentraland-desktop-client-preview"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T15:53:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum metaverse game Decentraland has shared an exclusive look at the visual and performance upgrades coming via its new desktop client.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Trader Murad Mahmudov talks about the Supercycle and how he chooses Meme Coins.]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Hj3nDp7G/crypto-trader-murad-mahmudov-talks-about-the-supercycle-and-how-he-chooses-meme-coins</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Hj3nDp7G/crypto-trader-murad-mahmudov-talks-about-the-supercycle-and-how-he-chooses-meme-coins"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T21:47:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Trader Murad Mahmudov talks about the Supercycle and how he chooses Meme Coins. Crypto stable, had sold off after China stocks fall. Crypto adopted faster than other tech: BlackRock. Crypto adoption to hit 8% of world population. CryptoCom recieves Wells notice from SEC. HBO documentary on Satoshi airs tonight. FTX bankruptcy plan approved by judge. Scroll airdrop may be imminent. Jupiter goes live on mobile iOS. Phantom rolls out support for Base. AAVE launches GHO on Base. Gensler may be replaced by Robinhood CLO. 87% of new token launches on SOL. National Bank of Bahrain creates BTC fund. BedRock DeFi allows BTC staking on ARB.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Memecoins take off, funding stays low, China stocks keep on rising!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/703mAYhV/memecoins-take-off-funding-stays-low-china-stocks-keep-on-rising</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/703mAYhV/memecoins-take-off-funding-stays-low-china-stocks-keep-on-rising"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T08:27:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR EP213. Memecoins take off, funding stays low, China stocks keep on rising!
Many altcoins & memecoins soar despite stable BTC. Funding rates continue to be low or negative. Crypto funds saw $147m of outflows last week. BTC remains best performing major assets this year. SUI breaks into the top 20 coins again. TAO leads top 100 away from memes, sifu shorts. $100m bridge to SOL over the last 7 days. Metaplanet buys $6.7m more BTC. ETH proposal aims to improve throughput 50%. EIGEN, OP, APT lead token unlocks this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Walrus Protocol Unlocks New Applications for Decentralized Data Storage]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kwEYLYWj/how-walrus-protocol-unlocks-new-applications-for-decentralized-data-storage</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kwEYLYWj/how-walrus-protocol-unlocks-new-applications-for-decentralized-data-storage"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T11:19:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mysten Labs Chief Scientist George Danezis joined Decrypt to talk about its new decentralized storage protocol Walrus, which promises to unlock new applications such as AI and social media, thanks to its novel Red Stuff data encoding algorithm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Coinbase Sees Crypto as a Bipartisan, 'Purple' Political Issue]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/YR2YmmwR/why-coinbase-sees-crypto-as-a-bipartisan-purple-political-issue</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/YR2YmmwR/why-coinbase-sees-crypto-as-a-bipartisan-purple-political-issue"/>
        <updated>2024-10-05T22:18:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase VP of Corporate and Business Development, Shan Aggarwal, joined Decrypt's Sander Lutz and Liz Napolitano at Messari Mainnet 2024 to discuss the exchange's efforts to grow mainstream crypto adoption—and how the changing political conversation around digital assets is rapidly playing a major role in that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Is Playing Offense—Not Just Defense—Against Crypto Crime, Says Head of Financial Investigations]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DiJ8D2Qc/binance-is-playing-offensenot-just-defenseagainst-crypto-crime-says-head-of-financial-investigations</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DiJ8D2Qc/binance-is-playing-offensenot-just-defenseagainst-crypto-crime-says-head-of-financial-investigations"/>
        <updated>2024-10-05T01:58:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nils Anderson Röed, the exchange’s global head of financial investigations, sat down with Decrypt’s Sander Lutz at Messari Mainnet 2024 to discuss how Binance is proactively dismantling criminal networks around the world, the strategy with which the crypto exchange is approaching sensitive conflicts in the Middle East, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 212 - SEEDPHRASE TALKS ART!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PJfaJNkZ/fomo-hour-212-seedphrase-talks-art</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PJfaJNkZ/fomo-hour-212-seedphrase-talks-art"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T19:29:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Payrolls Higher than expected, Bitcoin reacts hard. Crypto sank early in the week as Middle East tensions spooked markets. Powell signals two more rate cuts this year. SUI leads L1s again, nears YTD high despite large unlock. Majority of FTX repayments still months away. EIGEN becomes non-transferable, hits $6bn FDV. SEC to appeal Ripple securities law ruling. Visa launches tokenization platform for banks. SWIFT plans digital asset trial in 2025. ByBit launched trading of global stock indices. SPX, GIGA & FWOG hit ATHs, most memes fall. XCOPY to release 250 piece collection on Shape. HBO documentary claims to have identified Satoshi.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Altcoins bleed, ByBit launches stock index trading, POCHITA soars]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kYjAt3nt/altcoins-bleed-bybit-launches-stock-index-trading-pochita-soars</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kYjAt3nt/altcoins-bleed-bybit-launches-stock-index-trading-pochita-soars"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T21:11:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Altcoins sink, BTC dominance nears cycle high. BTC in ‘three blind mice’ downtrend. Tron revenue hits record $577m in Q3. ByBit to launch trading of major stock indices. Franklin Templeton launch fund on APT. SWIFT banks to trial digital assets in 2025. Aerodrome hits $1bn TVL on Base. Cronje calls out Aerodrome for copyright. ETH ICO wallet sells $47m. SEC files appeal against Ripple ruling. EIGEN falls 20% on staking rewards FUD. FTX to auction off WLD position. Half of US voters think crypto ‘important’. North Korea ‘infiltrating’ crypto industry. Snowden challenged over SOL centralisation view. Top SEC official on crypto set to depart.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DACOM Summit: Fastex CLO Vardan Khachatryan on Crypto Compliance]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LGGnxkb6/dacom-summit-fastex-clo-vardan-khachatryan-on-crypto-compliance</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LGGnxkb6/dacom-summit-fastex-clo-vardan-khachatryan-on-crypto-compliance"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T14:32:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fastex Chief Legal Officer Vardan Khachatryan joined Rug Radio creator Mlow at DACOM Summit to discuss how the crypto exchange is advancing compliance, and the regulatory challenges that lie ahead for the sector.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 210 - MIDDLE EAST TENSIONS RISE]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Bcj37IF2/fomo-hour-210-middle-east-tensions-rise</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Bcj37IF2/fomo-hour-210-middle-east-tensions-rise"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T17:14:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto drops as Middle East tensions flare. $500m liquidations in drop. BTC ETFs see largest outflows in a month. Fidelity ETH ETF sees 2nd highest outflow ever. SUI hits 6-month highs, bridge goes live on mainnet. Hashdex set to launch XRP ETF. Wormhole leads altcoin gains after Upbit lists. BTC miners hit record low profits in September Crypto hackers stole $750m in Q3. Telegram has been disclosing IPs since 2018.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Arbitrum is Simplifying Web3 for Web2 Adopters]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Mm9OGAoG/how-arbitrum-is-simplifying-web3-for-web2-adopters</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Mm9OGAoG/how-arbitrum-is-simplifying-web3-for-web2-adopters"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T14:19:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arbitrum's Head of Korea, John Park, joined Rug Radio creator Pukerainbow at ArbiVerse to talk about the Ethereum layer-2's strategy in Asia, hackathons, and bringing enterprise clients to its ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>