<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-12-10T10:14:40.753Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-12-10T10:14:40.753Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA) Reaches Highest Level Since 2022, But There's Catch]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19098568/Cardano-ADA-Reaches-Highest-Level-Since-2022-But-Theres-Catch</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19098568/Cardano-ADA-Reaches-Highest-Level-Since-2022-But-Theres-Catch"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T09:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano breaking resistance after resistance, which made it one of strongest assets in top 10 of crypto market]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Bull Market in Danger? Top Analyst Warns of 422 Trillion SHIB Threat]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19098548/Shiba-Inu-Bull-Market-in-Danger-Top-Analyst-Warns-of-422-Trillion-SHIB-Threat</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19098548/Shiba-Inu-Bull-Market-in-Danger-Top-Analyst-Warns-of-422-Trillion-SHIB-Threat"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T09:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whale threat worth trillions of Shiba Inu tokens looms over SHIB's bull run, analyst warns]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI’s Accountability Crisis – OpenAI’s Leadership Struggle and the Moral Battle in Warfare]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19098545/AIs-Accountability-Crisis-OpenAIs-Leadership-Struggle-and-the-Moral-Battle-in-Warfare</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19098545/AIs-Accountability-Crisis-OpenAIs-Leadership-Struggle-and-the-Moral-Battle-in-Warfare"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T09:34:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an era where artificial intelligence’s (AI) impact on both warfare and corporate governance looms large, the ethical tightrope between innovation and accountability is more precarious than ever. The integration of AI in military operations has reached a critical juncture.  Recent conflicts,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Newly Unsealed DOJ Filings Could Mean End of Binance: Ex-SEC Chief]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19098538/Newly-Unsealed-DOJ-Filings-Could-Mean-End-of-Binance-Ex-SEC-Chief</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19098538/Newly-Unsealed-DOJ-Filings-Could-Mean-End-of-Binance-Ex-SEC-Chief"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T09:25:46.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Could Face More Charges: Former SEC Chief Predicts]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19098539/Binance-Could-Face-More-Charges-Former-SEC-Chief-Predicts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19098539/Binance-Could-Face-More-Charges-Former-SEC-Chief-Predicts"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T09:21:47.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Compound DAO Falls Short in Rewarding Developer for Critical Bug Fix]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19098529/Compound-DAO-Falls-Short-in-Rewarding-Developer-for-Critical-Bug-Fix</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19098529/Compound-DAO-Falls-Short-in-Rewarding-Developer-for-Critical-Bug-Fix"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T09:10:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Compound DAO’s recent vote to compensate a blockchain developer for addressing a significant vulnerability fell short by 15,000 votes, failing to reach the required 400,000 supporting vote quorum. The proposed reward was aimed at acknowledging the efforts of a pseudonymous developer, ‘KP,’ who...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boston Dynamics Unveils Bittle X: A Voice-Controlled Robot Companion]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19098521/Boston-Dynamics-Unveils-Bittle-X-A-Voice-Controlled-Robot-Companion</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19098521/Boston-Dynamics-Unveils-Bittle-X-A-Voice-Controlled-Robot-Companion"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T09:06:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Boston Dynamics, a leader in robotics and automation technology, has revealed its latest creation: Bittle X. This palm-sized robot, priced at $225, is designed to follow voice commands, offering a versatile and interactive experience for users. Introducing Bittle X: A Compact and Affordable...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Industry in Georgia: Contributions and Positioning within the Global Context]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19098502/Crypto-Industry-in-Georgia-Contributions-and-Positioning-within-the-Global-Context</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19098502/Crypto-Industry-in-Georgia-Contributions-and-Positioning-within-the-Global-Context"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T08:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Georgia, a vibrant epicenter of digital innovation, has emerged as a prominent player in the global cryptocurrency arena. Nestled at the crossroads of Eastern Europe and Western Asia, this nation has carved out a distinctive niche in the crypto world, distinguishing itself through a combination...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOJ Gains Extensive Oversight Over Binance Following Settlement – Details]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748bc17722</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/doj-to-acquire-extensive-oversight-over-binance/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T08:40:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently unveiled court documents from the US Department of Justice (DOJ) reveals a significant depth of oversight by the federal regulator into the operational activities of Binance, following the $4.3 billion settlement deal between both parties last month. This development comes as the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has now begun to incorporate facts from the popular plea deal into its lawsuit against the Seychelles-based exchange.
 
 
Binance’s Compliance Commitment With DOJ, Others
 
In a post on X on December 9, former SEC Chief of Internet Enforcement, John Reed Stark, shared an elaborating insight on Binance’s plea deal with the DOJ. Based on the freshly released DOJ filings, Stark claimed that the US government has now acquired an “extensive, robust and vigorous overs…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Semilore Faleti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two Institutional Investors and Three Giant Whales Are Showing High Activity in This Altcoin: They’re Selling Heavy]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19098498/Two-Institutional-Investors-and-Three-Giant-Whales-Are-Showing-High-Activity-in-This-Altcoin-Theyre-Selling-Heavy</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19098498/Two-Institutional-Investors-and-Three-Giant-Whales-Are-Showing-High-Activity-in-This-Altcoin-Theyre-Selling-Heavy"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T08:39:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Interestingly enough, big whales and institutional investors started making sudden sales in an altcoin today. Continue Reading: Two Institutional Investors and Three Giant Whales Are Showing High Activity in This Altcoin: They’re Selling Heavy]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS re:Invent 2023 Highlights: Key Takeaways and Insights]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19098495/AWS-reInvent-2023-Highlights-Key-Takeaways-and-Insights</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19098495/AWS-reInvent-2023-Highlights-Key-Takeaways-and-Insights"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T08:35:20.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOJ Gains Extensive Oversight Over Binance Following Settlement – Details]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19098494/DOJ-Gains-Extensive-Oversight-Over-Binance-Following-Settlement-Details</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19098494/DOJ-Gains-Extensive-Oversight-Over-Binance-Following-Settlement-Details"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T08:34:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently unveiled court documents from the US Department of Justice (DOJ) reveals a significant depth of oversight by the federal regulator into the operational activities of Binance, following the $4.3 billion settlement deal between both parties last month. This development comes as the US...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China and Singapore Team Up to Allow Tourists to Spend Digital Yuan]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748bc24659</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/china-and-singapore-team-up-to-allow-tourists-to-spend-digital-yuan/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T08:31:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Singapore and China have teamed up on a pilot to allow tourists in both countries to spend China’s central bank digital currency, the digital yuan. “This will enhance convenience for travelers when making purchases during their overseas travel,” Singapore’s central bank described.
 
Tourists in China and Singpoare Can Spend Digital Yuan
 
Singapore’s central bank, the Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS), announced Thursday “new digital finance and capital markets initiatives to expand its financial cooperation with China.”
 
One of the initiatives is a “cross-border e-CNY pilot between China and Singapore,” the MAS explained, adding that it and People’s Bank of China’s Digital Currency Institute (PBCDCI) signed a Memorandum of Understanding (MOU) on digital finance cooperation in 2020. The announcement details:
 

MAS and PBCDCI are embarking on a pilot that will allow travellers from both countries to use e-CNY for tourism spending in Singapore and China. This will enhance convenience for travellers when making purchases during their overseas travel.
 
 
China is at the forefront of central bank digital currency (CBDC) development, actively testing its e-CNY project. Since initiating digital yuan research, the People’s Bank of China (PBOC) has steadily expanded the pilot program’s reach. Presently, there are 26 pilot areas for digital yuan spread across China.
 
PBOC Governor Yi Gang disclosed in July that transactions utilizing China’s central bank digital currency reached 1.8 trillion yuan ($250 billion) at the end of June. In November, Standard Chartered Bank said that it had begun offering digital yuan exchange services in China. Moreover, the Chinese central bank and the Hong Kong Monetary Authority (HKMA) have entered the second phase of integrating digital yuan for payments and cross-border transactions within Hong Kong.
 
What do you think about the collaboration between China and Singapore to let tourists in both countries spend digital yuan? Let us know in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two More Cases of Highly Pathogenic Avian Influenza Detected in South Korea]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19098481/Two-More-Cases-of-Highly-Pathogenic-Avian-Influenza-Detected-in-South-Korea</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19098481/Two-More-Cases-of-Highly-Pathogenic-Avian-Influenza-Detected-in-South-Korea"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T08:27:09.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will the Federal Reserve Implement Further Tightening Policies?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19098475/Will-the-Federal-Reserve-Implement-Further-Tightening-Policies</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19098475/Will-the-Federal-Reserve-Implement-Further-Tightening-Policies"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T08:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche Web Wallet to Undergo Transformation with Launch of Core on January 23]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19098472/Avalanche-Web-Wallet-to-Undergo-Transformation-with-Launch-of-Core-on-January-23</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19098472/Avalanche-Web-Wallet-to-Undergo-Transformation-with-Launch-of-Core-on-January-23"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T08:16:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kieran McShane, a prominent figure associated with Ava Labs’ products, has revealed significant developments regarding the widely-used Avalanche Web Wallet. The platform is set to undergo a transformative shift with the retirement of the existing Web Wallet on January 23, marking a strategic...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Strategist Predicts Imminent Bitcoin Rally to $50,000 – Here’s His Timeline]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19098465/Crypto-Strategist-Predicts-Imminent-Bitcoin-Rally-to-50000-Heres-His-Timeline</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19098465/Crypto-Strategist-Predicts-Imminent-Bitcoin-Rally-to-50000-Heres-His-Timeline"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T08:04:22.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether Introduces New Initiative To Promote Stablecoin Adoption]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19098453/Tether-Introduces-New-Initiative-To-Promote-Stablecoin-Adoption</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19098453/Tether-Introduces-New-Initiative-To-Promote-Stablecoin-Adoption"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T07:43:52.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana’s JTO Coin Massive Rollercoaster: Here’s What You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19098444/Solanas-JTO-Coin-Massive-Rollercoaster-Heres-What-You-Need-to-Know</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19098444/Solanas-JTO-Coin-Massive-Rollercoaster-Heres-What-You-Need-to-Know"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T07:34:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jito's fully diluted market capitalization now exceeds $3 billion, taking Solana's center of attention.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the Crypto Industry in Gambia Offers Unbanked Populations Financial Inclusion]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19098437/How-the-Crypto-Industry-in-Gambia-Offers-Unbanked-Populations-Financial-Inclusion</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19098437/How-the-Crypto-Industry-in-Gambia-Offers-Unbanked-Populations-Financial-Inclusion"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T07:29:22.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Rally Continues But Concerns About Pullback Loom]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19098434/Bitcoin-Rally-Continues-But-Concerns-About-Pullback-Loom</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19098434/Bitcoin-Rally-Continues-But-Concerns-About-Pullback-Loom"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T07:19:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin made a remarkable move, surging to $44,000 following the Wall Street opening on December...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Market analysis of NFT in November]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19098451/Market-analysis-of-NFT-in-November</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19098451/Market-analysis-of-NFT-in-November"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Lawmakers Launch Bill to Counter Terrorism and Threats Involving Digital Assets]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748bcbe8cf</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/us-lawmakers-launch-bill-to-counter-terrorism-and-threats-involving-digital-assets/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T06:33:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several U.S. lawmakers have introduced a bipartisan bill to crack down on terrorist organizations by applying sanctions to foreign entities, including crypto platforms, that facilitate financial transactions for terrorists. The legislation would also “equip the Treasury Department with additional resources to counter terrorism and address emerging threats involving digital assets,” said one of the lawmakers who introduced the bill.
 
Terrorism Financing Prevention Act
 
U.S. Senators Mark Warner (D-VA), Mike Rounds (R-SD), Jack Reed (D-RI), and Mitt Romney (R-UT) announced Thursday that they have introduced bipartisan legislation titled Terrorist Financing Prevention Act of 2023 to “crack down on terrorist organizations like Hamas by applying sanctions to foreign parties that facilitate fi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russian President Putin: Western Financial System Dying, Major Western Banks Will Be Deprived of Their Monopoly]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748bbc3d03</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/russian-president-putin-western-financial-system-dying-major-western-banks-will-be-deprived-of-their-monopoly/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T04:40:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Russian President Vladimir Putin has stated that the Western financial system is “clearly becoming obsolete.” Furthermore, he said solutions involving blockchain and central bank digital currencies (CBDCs) “will pave the way for revolutionary shifts that will deprive the major Western banks of their monopoly.”
 
Putin on Western Financial System
 
Russian President Vladimir Putin shared his view about the Western financial system during the plenary session of the “Russia Calling” forum in Moscow on Thursday.
 
Describing the Western financial infrastructure as “decades-old” and largely controlled by the dollar and the euro, with transactions through Western banks and SWIFT, Putin stated: “Today, transactions in national currencies are effectively replacing this system. Of course, this is s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pudgy Penguins to Launch Webkinz-like Virtual World in 2024]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748bb97a6d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/12/10/pudgy-penguins-to-launch-webkinz-like-virtual-world-in-2024/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T03:24:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pudgy World, an interactive digital world available to Pudgy Penguin NFT holders, will become available in alpha mode sometime next year, according to the company’s CEO.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Napolitano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pudgy Penguins Reveal 'Pudgy World' NFT Game Rollout Plans]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209174</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209174/pudgy-penguins-reveals-pudgy-world-nft-game-rollout-plans"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T02:31:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Pudgy Penguins NFT empire is expanding and will open the gates for its metaverse experience Pudgy World sometime in 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Novogratz: JPMorgan CEO Jamie Dimon Is Wrong About Bitcoin, ‘Supreme Arrogance’ to Dismiss Value]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748ba549a7</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/novogratz-jpmorgan-ceo-jamie-dimon-is-wrong-about-bitcoin-supreme-arrogance-to-dismiss-value/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T02:30:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Galaxy Digital CEO Mike Novogratz says JPMorgan CEO Jamie Dimon has been proven wrong about bitcoin. “I think it’s supreme arrogance to think he knows what has value but all the rest of the people don’t,” said Novogratz after the JPMorgan executive slammed bitcoin as being used by criminals, emphasizing that he would shut it down if he were the government.
 
Jamie Dimon ‘Keeps Being Wrong’ About Bitcoin, Says Novogratz
 
Galaxy Digital CEO Mike Novogratz fiercely criticized JPMorgan CEO Jamie Dimon’s recent remarks about bitcoin and cryptocurrency. The JPMorgan boss said during a congressional hearing earlier this week that he would close down crypto and bitcoin if he were the government, claiming that they are primarily used by criminals, drug traffickers, money launderers, and tax evader…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vaneck Unveils 15 Crypto Predictions: Spot Bitcoin ETF Approvals, US Recession, BTC’s Historic Rally]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748bac8621</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/vaneck-unveils-15-crypto-predictions-spot-bitcoin-etf-approvals-us-recession-btcs-historic-rally/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T00:41:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Asset management firm Vaneck has unveiled its 15 crypto predictions for 2024. They include the U.S. recession’s arrival, the approvals of spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), and bitcoin’s historic rally, “potentially spurred by political events and regulatory shifts following a U.S. presidential election.”
 
15 Crypto Predictions for 2024
 
Asset management firm Vaneck published its 15 crypto predictions for 2024 on Thursday. The first prediction concerns the U.S. economy slipping into a recession and the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) approving spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs). Vaneck wrote on social media platform X:
 

The U.S. recession will finally arrive, but so will the first spot bitcoin ETFs. Over $2.4 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Outshines Gold: Digital Asset Surges 166% in 2023, Dwarfing Gold’s Modest 9% Gain]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748b94e4e1</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-outshines-gold-digital-asset-surges-166-in-2023-dwarfing-golds-modest-9-gain/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T22:42:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gold achieved a record high of $2,117 per troy ounce on Dec. 3, 2023, yet its price per ounce has decreased by 5.33% in the previous week. Despite hitting this unprecedented peak, its year-to-date increase against the U.S. dollar is relatively modest at 9.9%. In contrast, bitcoin, the leading crypto asset in terms of market capitalization, has experienced a significant surge of 166% since the beginning of 2023.
 
Gold Hits Record High, Yet Bitcoin Steals the Spotlight With Stellar 2023 Surge
 
Prominent gold supporter and economist Peter Schiff, along with several other gold enthusiasts, expressed satisfaction with gold’s recent ascent to $2,117 per ounce. Concurrently, Schiff remarked that bitcoin’s rise was not particularly noteworthy. However, objective analysis and factual data reveal …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether Freezes 41 Crypto Wallets Tied to Sanctions]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748b926428</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/12/09/tether-freezes-41-crypto-wallets-tied-to-sanctions/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T21:29:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stabelcoin issuer Tether blacklisted 41 wallets controlled by people on the Office of Foreign Assets Control (OFAC) Specially Designated Nationals (SDN) List on Saturday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meme Coins Surge in Value, Gaining $6.7 Billion in a Month With BONK, PEPE, and SHIB Leading the Rally]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748b9e9640</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/meme-coins-surge-in-value-gaining-6-7-billion-in-a-month-with-bonk-pepe-and-shib-leading-the-rally/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T20:37:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meme coins have been on a tear over the past month, increasing by $6.7 billion and 39.18% since Nov. 8. While bonk (BONK) led the pack this past week, rising 153% against the U.S. dollar, several other meme coins like dogecoin, shiba inu, and pepe recorded double-digit gains.
 
Explosive Growth in Meme Coin Sector as Market Cap Hits $23.8 Billion
 
The meme coin economy is currently valued at $23.8 billion, up $6.7 billion from the $17.1 billion mark recorded 30 days ago. Nine out of the top ten meme tokens have witnessed double-digit gains over the past week.
 
The top two leaders, in terms of market valuation, DOGE and SHIB, jumped 19.1% to 21.5%, respectively. The third-largest, pepe (Pepe), rose 43.5% against the greenback over the past week.
 
BONK is up 153%, while FLOKI increased by 24.2% this week. MEME saw a 34.3% gain, and BABYDOGE has increased by 30.8%. CORGIAI was the only member of the top ten without double-digit gains, but it did rise 4.5% over the past seven days.
 
The tenth largest meme coin, dubbed “harrypotterobamasonic10inu,” rose by 31.9% against the U.S. dollar. Other notable gainers in the world of meme coins were DOG, TOSHI, HUAHUA, and NFD.
 
 
In fact, including BONK, a total of 11 meme-based crypto assets recorded triple-digit gains. A total of 53 meme coin assets recorded double-digit gains against the U.S. dollar.
 
The top meme coin, dogecoin (DOGE), has a market valuation of $14.12 billion, which equates to 59.32% of the entire meme coin economy. Shiba inu (SHIB) has a $5.97 billion market cap on Dec. 9, 2023, accounting for just over 25% of the meme coin market’s $23.8 billion.
 
What do you think about the gains meme coins have seen over the past week? Let us know what you think in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jack Dorsey’s Block Launches Bitkey: A New Self-Custody Bitcoin Wallet With No Seed Phrases]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748b809d5a</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/jack-dorseys-block-launches-bitkey-a-new-self-custody-bitcoin-wallet-with-no-seed-phrases/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T18:37:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Block, Inc. has recently introduced Bitkey, its innovative self-custody bitcoin wallet, offering a unique approach to bitcoin management. Unlike traditional wallets which rely on passwords or seed phrases, Bitkey utilizes a distinctive 2-of-3 multi-signature mechanism for recovery.
 
Bitkey Wallet Approach Ditches Traditional Seed Phrases
 
Bitkey, conceived and built by Block, Inc. (formerly Square, Inc.), is a new bitcoin (BTC) wallet that encompasses a mobile app, a hardware device, and a suite of recovery tools. The non-custodial aspect of Bitkey’s design is different as it eliminates the traditional reliance on seed phrases. Instead, the wallet employs a 2-of-3 multi-signature scheme where the user is provided with two keys: one integrated within the mobile app for everyday transactio…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Analyst Identifies Cardano (ADA) Bullish Cross That Led To 6,000% Increase]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748b837513</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-analyst-identifies-cardano-ada-bullish-cross-that-led-to-6000-increase/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T18:06:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A crypto analyst has identified an indicator that could suggest that Cardano’s (ADA) price is set to enjoy a parabolic move. This comes just as the altcoin led others as the top gainer in the last 24 hours. 
 
 
ADA On The Way Up If This Happens
 
In a post on his X (formerly Twitter) platform, crypto analyst Tyler Strejilevich noted that ADA is about to get a bullish weekly cross for the first time since June 2020. The last time this happened, the crypto token was said to have climbed 6,000% in a period that lasted over a year. 
 

 
This indicator seems to spell a very bullish momentum for ADA, as Strejilevich sounded very optimistic about the new heights ADA could attain if this happens. He went as far as labeling ADA potentially seeing a bullish weekly cross as “Big.” According to him,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Bitcoin Rally Lends Meme Coins a Helping Hand]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209125</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209125/this-week-in-coins-bitcoin-rally-lends-meme-coins-a-helping-hand"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T16:33:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin continued to rally this week. And major altcoins—especially meme coins—blew up in value as a result.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[December Sparks NFT Sales Surge — Bitcoin Dominates as Market Recovers, Iconic Collections Realign]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748b74ac4c</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/december-sparks-nft-sales-surge-bitcoin-dominates-as-market-recovers-iconic-collections-realign/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T16:31:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the wake of a strong rise in non-fungible token (NFT) sales last November, the initial week of December continued this trend, with sales escalating by 57% compared to the previous week.
 
Bitcoin Outshines as NFT Sales Skyrocket in Early December
 
This past week’s NFT sales amounted to approximately $316 million. Despite this surge, the volume of buyers and sellers decreased considerably, dropping 90.09% and 88.31% respectively, as per the seven-day data from cryptoslam.io.
 
 
NFTs linked to Bitcoin maintained their leading position in sales volume in November, a trend that persisted into the first week of December. From December 1, 2023, Bitcoin-related NFTs garnered $121.34 million in sales over the week, outperforming Ethereum-based NFTs, which saw sales of $100.83 million.
 
 
Sal…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spot Bitcoin ETFs Are Coming Soon. How Will They Be Redeemed?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748b74f27b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/markets/spot-bitcoin-etfs-are-coming-soon-how-will-they-be-redeemed"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T16:30:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock and Grayscale recently met with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), presumably to discuss the approval requirements for their spot Bitcoin ETF applications.
Coinbase, which offers both Bitcoin custody and Bitcoin brokerage products, has emerged as the proposed custodian for the Bitcoin assets of several ETF applicants. Mike Belshe, CEO of BitGo, recently raised concerns about Coinbase's dual role as an exchange and custodian. Although his position is clearly aligned with his self-interest, since BitGo is a custodian that does not operate an exchange, Belshe warned that Coinbase’s dual role might lead to the SEC rejecting those applications.
Despite these concerns, analysts are confident that the SEC will approve some applications by January 10th, which is the deadline f…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Waugh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOGE Founder Calls Out Senator Warren For Anti-Crypto Stance, Elon Musk Agrees]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748b76c7bc</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/doge-founder-calls-out-senator-warren-for-anti-crypto-stance-elon-musk-agrees/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T16:12:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin’s founder, Shibetoshi Nakamoto has publicly challenged US Senator Elizabeth Warren for her anti-cryptocurrency stance. Adding weight to Nakamoto’s remarks, Tesla CEO Elon Musk has expressed his agreement. 
 
 
DOGE Founder Calls Out Senator’s Anti-Crypto Stance
 
Speaking on Squawk Newsmaker, Warren publicly declared her anti-crypto stance, citing potential threats of the exploitation of digital currencies for nefarious purposes.
 
“There’s a new threat out there, it’s crypto and it is being used for terrorist financing. It is being used for drug trafficking. North Korea is using it to pay for about half of its nuclear weapons program. We can’t allow that to continue,” Warren stated.
 
The senator’s statements were posted by Watcher Guru on X. In response to Warren’s remarks, the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Market Experts Predict When The Shiba Inu Price Will Reach $0.01]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748b794234</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-price-reach-0-01/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T14:32:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Information technology platform, Telegoan has made a series of price predictions for the Shiba Inu price, ranging from 2023 up to 2050. 
 
Shiba Inu 2023 To 2025 Price Prediction
 
Crypto analytics firm, Telegoan has published several optimistic predictions for the price of the Shiba Inu native token (SHIB). According to the information technology firm, Shiba Inu could have a steady price increase over the years until it reaches a maximum of $1 in a few decades. 
 
 
For the 2023 price prediction, Telegoan has forecasted the SHIB price to reach a maximum price level of $0.0000216 by the end of 2023. At the time of writing, the current price of the Shiba Inu token is $0.0000103 according to CoinMarketCap. The cryptocurrency has seen relatively slow growth despite the present hype of a poten…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Altcoin Surge Outshines Bitcoin’s Modest Gain Amid Anticipation of Potential Altcoin Season]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748b796a3d</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/altcoin-surge-outshines-bitcoins-modest-gain-amid-anticipation-of-potential-altcoin-season/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T14:30:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin saw a modest increase of 1.8% in the past 24 hours as of Dec. 9, 2023. Meanwhile, more than 17 crypto assets experienced much larger gains, ranging from 7% to over 35% in the same timeframe. Despite this rise in various altcoins against the U.S. dollar, current trends have yet to signal the start of an official ‘Altcoin Season,’ as suggested by the ‘Altcoin Season Index.’ Notably, such a season has not occurred since September 2022.
 
Despite Altcoins’ Impressive Gains, Altcoin Season Not Yet Declared
 
Several alternative digital currencies, or crypto tokens distinct from bitcoin, have registered notable increases in value over the previous day. Statistics indicate that the token bittorrent (BTT) surged by 35.48% in the past 24 hours, while bonk (BONK) climbed 24.62% against the U…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Free Money': These Are the Hottest Airdrops Around Right Now]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209179</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209179/free-money-hottest-airdrops-around-right-now"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T14:01:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jito just dropped bags of tokens to Solana users, and Starknet, Portal, and Jupiter airdrops are on the horizon. Here’s what you need to know.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood Launches Crypto Trading in EU, Aims for Global Accessibility]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748b6c41d6</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/robinhood-launches-crypto-trading-in-eu-aims-for-global-accessibility/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T12:40:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Financial services firm Robinhood has announced the launch of crypto trading in the European Union. “Like we did with the stock market, it’s our goal to make crypto more accessible and affordable to everyone, regardless of where they live,” the company explained.
 
Robinhood Expands Crypto Trading Services
 
Financial services firm Robinhood launched its crypto trading platform in the European Union on Thursday, offering investors the ability to buy and sell more than 25 cryptocurrencies. The announcement details:
 

Today, we are launching the Robinhood Crypto app to all eligible customers in the European Union (EU).
 
EU residents aged 18 and over with compatible iOS and Android devices can now access Robinhood Crypto, the company clarified. The announcement further details: “Support for…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nearly $900 Million In Bitcoin Sent To Exchanges – BTC Price Dip Incoming?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748b54461d</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/nearly-900-million-in-bitcoin-sent-to-exchanges-btc/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T11:19:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin put in another positive price performance over the past week, with its price rising by more than 14% in just seven days. However, the price of the premier cryptocurrency and the potential of the starting bull run might be under threat, as investors seem to be cashing in on their profits.
 
According to the latest on-chain data, significant amounts of Bitcoin have been on the move to cryptocurrency exchanges in the past few days.
 
BTC Traders Move Massive Amounts To Crypto Exchanges
 
Crypto analyst Ali Martinez revealed – via a post on X – that massive amounts of Bitcoin have been transferred to centralized exchanges in the past few days. This revelation is based on the “Exchange Inflow” data from the blockchain analytics platform Glassnode.
 
According to the post on X, around 20…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Opeyemi Sule</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong Regulator Warns of 2 Entities Suspected of Crypto Frauds]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748b504fc9</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/hong-kong-regulator-warns-of-2-entities-suspected-of-crypto-frauds/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T10:38:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong’s financial regulator has warned the public about two entities suspected of crypto frauds. In addition to issuing cease and desist letters to relevant website operators requesting them to cease offering crypto tokens for purchases, the regulator advises the public to “be cautious about too-good-to-be-true investment opportunities and advice posted on social media platforms and via instant messaging apps.”
 
Hong Kong Regulator’s Crypto Fraud Warning
 
The Hong Kong Securities and Futures Commission (SFC) issued a notice on Wednesday, warning the public of two entities suspected of involvement in virtual asset-related frauds. The two entities are Hong Kong Digital Research Institute, aka Hong Kong DAO, and Bitcuped. According to the notice:
 

At the SFC’s request, the Hong Kong P…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Undressing: Deepfake Nude Services Skyrocket in Popularity]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209181</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209181/ai-undressing-deepfake-nude-services-skyrocket-in-popularity"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T01:12:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Analytics firm Graphika says the amount of non-consensual intimate imagery online has grown 2,408% since January.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SOL Surges 13% as Solana NFTs Overtake Ethereum, BONK Up 26%]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209160</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209160/sol-surges-13-solana-nfts-overtake-ethereum-bonk-up-26"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T21:22:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana’s resurgence isn’t slowing, with SOL and Solana-based tokens still rising and NFT sales volume ruling the wider market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avail Hopes to Sell Hollywood on Using AI to Sort Through Scripts]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209135</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209135/ai-to-sort-summarize-movie-tv-scripts-avail"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T20:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The film and TV script summary platform says it can save time and effort with minimal AI hallucinations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI's Potential in Business Breakthroughs Is Overhyped, Says OpenAI COO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209143</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209143/ais-potential-in-business-breakthroughs-is-overhyped-says-openai-coo"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T20:10:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI won’t make you a millionaire, says Brad Lightcap, Sam Altman’s right hand man, calling the tech more of a “sidekick.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Says 'Not Your Keys, Not Your Wallet' in Butchered Attempt at Bitcoin Mantra]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209133</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209133/elon-musk-says-not-keys-not-wallet-butchered-bitcoin-mantra"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T19:47:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[World's richest man and alleged crypto fan Elon Musk took a swing at the classic Bitcoin "not your keys" mantra—and whiffed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Got $1 Million in Bitcoin or Tether? El Salvador Will Give You a 'Freedom Visa']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209122</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209122/el-salvador-passport-cough-up-1m-bitcoin-tether"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T19:06:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[El Salvador has announced a new “freedom visa” for rich people who want to live in the Central American nation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Prime Is Giving Out Free Items for NFT Game ‘Champions Ascension’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209121</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209121/amazon-prime-giving-out-free-items-nft-game-champions-ascension"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T18:57:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Got an Amazon Prime membership? You’ll be able to grab in-game items for NFT actioner Champions Ascension on PC for weeks to come.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Layer-2 Starknet Reveals STRK Token Airdrop]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209109</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209109/ethereum-layer-2-starknet-reveals-strk-token-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T18:01:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starknet, an Ethereum scaling network, is readying 1.8 billion STRK tokens between the airdrop and rebates, plus incentives for DeFi users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Dogecoin? The Original Meme Coin Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=5678</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/dogecoin-crypto-cryptocurrency-guide-how-to-buy-doge"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T17:50:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin is a peer-to-peer cryptocurrency based on a popular Internet meme. The token started off as a joke, but it's become a serious proposition.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward,Stephen Graves,Wendy Clack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Animoca Brands Boosts 'Mocaverse' Funding to $31.88 Million With Dapper, Polygon Onboard]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209096</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209096/animoca-brands-boosts-mocaverse-funding-31-88-million-dapper-polygon-onboard"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T17:27:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum NFT-based digital identity and loyalty platform Mocaverse will connect metaverse game worlds, apps, and other Web3 projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HODL: VanEck Bitcoin ETF Uses Laser-Eyed Lingo for Ticker]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209094</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209094/hodl-vaneck-bitcoin-etf-uses-laser-eyed-lingo-for-ticker"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T17:26:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fund manager is one of the biggest contenders in the spot Bitcoin ETF race.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Novel Wallet Is a Book That Hides Your Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209113</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209113/novel-wallet-is-a-book-that-hides-your-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T17:16:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This low-tech tome puts every possible passphrase word in print, providing a creative way to safely store your seed phrase.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Withdraws Abu Dhabi Investment Fund Licence Application]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209069</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209069/binance-withdraws-abu-dhabi-investment-fund-licence-application"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T12:30:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The license, which Binance voluntarily canceled, would have permitted the exchange to manage a collective investment fund in the country.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elizabeth Warren: Update Bank Secrecy Act to Address Crypto 'Threat']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209068</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209068/elizabeth-warren-update-bank-secrecy-act-to-address-crypto-threat"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T11:02:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Senator linked crypto to terrorist financing, drug trafficking, and North Korea's nuclear weapons programme.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Judge Bans Changpeng ‘CZ’ Zhao from Leaving the Country]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209060</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209060/us-judge-bans-changpeng-cz-zhao-from-leaving-the-country"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T02:51:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["The defendant has enormous wealth and property abroad," wrote Judge Richard Jones, "and no ties to the United States."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Early Bitcoin Ordinals Art Sells for Record $450,000]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209032</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209032/early-bitcoin-ordinals-art-sells-for-record-450000"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T02:21:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Honey Badger inscription number eight, created on Jan. 15, sold on Magic Eden on Thursday for 10.4 BTC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft May Be Working On an AI Edition of Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209025</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209025/microsoft-ai-windows-2024-germanium-copilot"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T02:06:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 Windows release is rumored to have AI in everything from its graphical user interface to its command line.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jito Airdrop Hands Out $225 Million to Solana Users]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209010</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209010/jito-airdrop-hands-out-225-million-solana-users"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T23:22:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana DeFi users are celebrating after Jito launched JTO, with 90 million tokens up for grabs for eligible users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INTERVIEW: Ember Sword CEO Says NFT Games Are More 'Transparent']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/M9OHCVpA/interview-ember-sword-ceo-says-nft-games-are-more-transparent</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/M9OHCVpA/interview-ember-sword-ceo-says-nft-games-are-more-transparent"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T21:58:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ember Sword CEO Mark Laursen shares why some big game studios "irk" him—and why he got into game development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Unveils Open-Source Path for AI Development on Its Silicon Chips]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209003</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209003/apple-ai-ml-development-mlx-silicon"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T21:07:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MLX speeds AI development on Apple hardware, connecting its users with the broader AI development community on other platforms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What the Bitcoin Halving Means for Investors]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208164</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208164/bitcoin-halving-what-it-means-investors"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T19:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The next Bitcoin halving takes place in April—but this time is different, insiders say. Here's what retail investors should know.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reebok Follows Nike Into Digital Fashion and Gaming, With an AI Twist]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208993</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208993/reebok-follows-nike-into-digital-wearables-gaming-with-ai-twist"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T19:31:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Footwear brand Reebok will debut an on-chain gaming experience next year that it promises will be “mind-bending.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meme Coins Dogecoin, SHIB Slip—But Solana's BONK Continues to Soar]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208973</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208973/meme-coin-dogecoin-shib-solana-bonk"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T18:38:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bullish traders are once again eyeing up risky assets for quick gains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ronin and Beam Gaming Tokens Surge, Outpacing Bitcoin and Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208986</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208986/ronin-beam-gaming-tokens-surge-outpacing-bitcoin-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T18:16:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gaming tokens remain hot, with RON and BEAM the biggest winners this week with huge double-digit weekly percentage jumps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gamers Can Now Livestream to Twitter via Streamlabs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208972</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208972/gamers-can-now-livestream-twitter-streamlabs"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T17:01:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Streamlabs’ new X feature allows gamers to go live on Twitter from a phone or computer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Montenegro Set to Extradite Terra Co-Founder Do Kwon to US: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208983</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208983/montenegro-extradite-terra-co-founder-do-kwon-us"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T17:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Terraform Labs co-founder has been caught in a jurisdictional tug-of-war between the U.S. and his native South Korea.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These Are the High-Profile Spot Bitcoin ETF Applications Currently in Play]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=62912</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/62912/high-profile-bitcoin-etf-applications"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T15:06:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. SEC has dragged its heels on approval of a Bitcoin spot ETF—but analysts are optimistic that there's light at the end of the tunnel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Auction House Sotheby's Announces First Sale of Bitcoin Ordinals Collection]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208961</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208961/auction-house-sothebys-announces-first-sale-of-bitcoin-ordinals-collection"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T13:22:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The sale marks the first occasion on which works from the BitcoinShrooms collection will be made available to the public, Sotheby's said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood Crypto Launches in EU With 'Crypto Back' Bitcoin Rewards Program]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208954</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208954/robinhood-crypto-launches-in-eu-with-crypto-back-bitcoin-rewards-program"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T10:06:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood Crypto's EU users will receive a percentage of trading volume back in Bitcoin, as well as Bitcoin rewards for referrals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rising Bitcoin Fees Prompt Renewed Battle Over Ordinals, BRC-20 Tokens]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208945</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208945/rising-bitcoin-fees-prompt-renewed-battle-over-ordinals-brc-20-tokens"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T02:01:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While some call for purging the NFT-like inscriptions, others say they are good for the network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t ‘AI Wash’ Investment Pitches: SEC Chair Gary Gensler]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208944</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208944/dont-ai-wash-investment-pitches-sec-chair-gary-gensler"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T01:33:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While excited by AI technology, Gensler highlighted its potential biases and conflicts of interest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Adds AI Across Its Apps, Launches Standalone Image Generator]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208935</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208935/meta-adds-ai-across-its-apps-launches-standalone-image-generator"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T01:02:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Facebook, Instagram, Messenger, and WhatsApp get new AI features, and the Meta Imagine tool lets users create AI art.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Set to List Jito Following Airdrop of Solana Token]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208923</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208923/coinbase-set-list-jito-following-airdrop-solana-token"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T00:07:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase has announced it will list Solana-based DeFi project Jito's token on its platform following the JTO airdrop Thursday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Merit Circle Brings Immutable zkEVM Into Beam Crypto Gaming Ecosystem]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208912</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208912/merit-circle-brings-immutable-zkevm-into-beam-crypto-gaming-ecosystem"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T23:31:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Merit Circle’s Beam tech is expanding beyond Avalanche to the Immutable zkEVM as a part of the DAO's "chain agnostic" approach.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Director Jordan Bayne on the State of Film3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZLoEDkL9/director-jordan-bayne-on-the-state-of-film3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZLoEDkL9/director-jordan-bayne-on-the-state-of-film3"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T00:11:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the 2023 Film3 Summit, Jordan Bayne—director and founder of The Squad—spoke with Decrypt's Sander Lutz about how the Film3 world has progressed over the last year and what decentralized technologies can offer to creators that want to buck the Hollywood system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Questions With SCENE: Phil Mohun]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TwOjXfOR/5-questions-with-scene-phil-mohun</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TwOjXfOR/5-questions-with-scene-phil-mohun"/>
        <updated>2023-12-01T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bright Moments co-founder Phil Mohun joins 5 Questions With SCENE to recount some favorite moments from the road, including negotiating with Patagonian gauchos, falling in love with Tokyo, and gaining a newfound appreciation for shrooms chocolate bars.

Shot and edited by Vincent Roazzi Jr.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are NFTs Ever Coming Back?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qLmFpNKE/are-nfts-ever-coming-back</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qLmFpNKE/are-nfts-ever-coming-back"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T18:38:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this weeks episode we sit down with Cashtro from Arcade.xyz to discuss NFTs, shitcoins, what collections have held onto their floor prices, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Summit: Will Web3 Gaming Ever be Mainstream?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OvVWhGbW/web-summit-will-web3-gaming-ever-be-mainstream</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OvVWhGbW/web-summit-will-web3-gaming-ever-be-mainstream"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T19:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animoca Brands CEO Robby Yung, EndeavorXR CEO Amy Peck and Gamee co-founder CEO Bozena Rezab joined Decrypt's Stephen Graves on stage at Web Summit to talk about the future of Web3 gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Allie Eve Knox on Spankchain and the life of a Crypto Financial Dominatrix]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/16rVeg6o/allie-eve-knox-on-spankchain-and-the-life-of-a-crypto-financial-dominatrix</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/16rVeg6o/allie-eve-knox-on-spankchain-and-the-life-of-a-crypto-financial-dominatrix"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T21:20:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the first IRL episode of This Time Will Be Different!

In this week's episode, our host, Reza Jafery, is joined by Allie Eve Knox, the Spankchain Chief of Staff and FinDomme. 

They discuss
- How to sell feet pics
- If crypto is really as permissionless as it seems
- the intersections between crypto and sex work]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Questions With SCENE: Jeff Davis]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PChJu1R8/5-questions-with-scene-jeff-davis</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PChJu1R8/5-questions-with-scene-jeff-davis"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artist Jeff Davis joins 5 Questions with SCENE to answer burning questions about his artistic practice, the path that brought him to Art Blocks, and his quietly sophisticated DJ abilities.

Video shot and edited by Vincent Roazzi Jr.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Heatbit Founder Alex Busarov on the Bitcoin Miner That Heats Your Home]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DJuHqcGT/heatbit-founder-alex-busarov-on-the-bitcoin-miner-that-heats-your-home</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DJuHqcGT/heatbit-founder-alex-busarov-on-the-bitcoin-miner-that-heats-your-home"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T18:12:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt joined Heatbit founder Alex Busarov at Web Summit for a walkthrough of the firm's flagship product, a Bitcoin miner that acts as a domestic space heater—aimed at the casual user.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nym CEO Harry Halpin on Privacy, Decentralized VPNs and Tornado Cash]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/aLTtY2aq/nym-ceo-harry-halpin-on-privacy-decentralized-vpns-and-tornado-cash</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/aLTtY2aq/nym-ceo-harry-halpin-on-privacy-decentralized-vpns-and-tornado-cash"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T18:08:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The founder of privacy-preserving mixnet Nym sat down with Decrypt at Web Summit to talk about its new decentralized VPN, the Web3 privacy landscape and why "devs should be defended" in the wake of the Tornado Cash crackdown.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pat Felder - The worst is over [Macro Deep Dive Episode]]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MdcKPVo0/pat-felder-the-worst-is-over-macro-deep-dive-episode</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MdcKPVo0/pat-felder-the-worst-is-over-macro-deep-dive-episode"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T17:10:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the first Markets Edition of This Time Will Be Different! In this episode we dive into the current macroeconomic conditions around crypto and look at the data behind the price action. 


Reza sits down with Pat Felder, founder of Prismatic Capital to discuss the current macro environment, and to answer the question on everyone's mind-- is the bear market really over?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Sandbox Co-Founder Sebastien Borget: 'We're Already Integrating AI']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/HlARjhG1/the-sandbox-co-founder-sebastien-borget-were-already-integrating-ai</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/HlARjhG1/the-sandbox-co-founder-sebastien-borget-were-already-integrating-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T16:09:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt sat down with The Sandbox co-founder Sebastien Borget at Web Summit to talk about AI, the open metaverse and the creative challenges of interoperability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dacoco CEO Saro McKenna: How Alien Worlds is Creating an AI-Powered 'Lore DAO' with Kevin J Anderson]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QrQTrsjH/dacoco-ceo-saro-mckenna-how-alien-worlds-is-creating-an-ai-powered-lore-dao-with-kevin-j-anderson</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QrQTrsjH/dacoco-ceo-saro-mckenna-how-alien-worlds-is-creating-an-ai-powered-lore-dao-with-kevin-j-anderson"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T16:06:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt joined Dacoco CEO Sarojini McKenna at Web Summit 2023 to talk about Alien Worlds' new Lore DAO and its AI-powered collaboration with sci-fi author Kevin J Anderson.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avalon's Jeffrey Butler on Designing a Metaverse MMO That Lets Players Co-Create]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XDz9vsvT/avalons-jeffrey-butler-on-designing-a-metaverse-mmo-that-lets-players-co-create</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XDz9vsvT/avalons-jeffrey-butler-on-designing-a-metaverse-mmo-that-lets-players-co-create"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T00:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avalon Chief Product Officer Jeffrey Butler speaks with Decrypt reporter Jason Nelson and details his studio's new MMO game with interoperable assets—and how it will enable players to create and monetize their own content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>