<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-05-07T21:13:56.285Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-05-07T21:13:56.285Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CFTC Chair Predicts Tsunami Of Crypto Enforcement Actions In Next 2 Years]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742f565898</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/cftc-predicts-tsunami-of-crypto-enforcement-actions/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T21:06:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) continues to scrutinize crypto industry players, including Robinhood, Binance, Coinbase, and Ripple, the Chair of the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC), Rostin Behnam, warns of an impending surge in enforcement actions. 
 
Crypto Faces Inevitable Wave Of Enforcement Actions
 
At the Milken Institute’s 27th annual Global Conference, Behnam emphasized the lack of regulatory framework and transparency within the growing crypto industry, which he believes will inevitably lead to more fraud and manipulation cases.
 
Behnam anticipates a “cycle of enforcement actions” within the next six months to two years, driven by the rapid appreciation of digital assets and heightened interest from retail investors. 
 
 
As a regulator, Behnam exp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Polygon Miden Brings to the Table as Testnet Goes Live]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468371/What-Polygon-Miden-Brings-to-the-Table-as-Testnet-Goes-Live</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468371/What-Polygon-Miden-Brings-to-the-Table-as-Testnet-Goes-Live"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T21:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Miden goes live on testnet; what does it bring to the Polygon ecosystem?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CFTC Chair Predicts Tsunami Of Crypto Enforcement Actions In Next 2 Years]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468360/CFTC-Chair-Predicts-Tsunami-Of-Crypto-Enforcement-Actions-In-Next-2-Years</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468360/CFTC-Chair-Predicts-Tsunami-Of-Crypto-Enforcement-Actions-In-Next-2-Years"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T21:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) continues to scrutinize crypto industry players, including Robinhood, Binance, Coinbase, and Ripple, the Chair of the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC), Rostin Behnam, warns of an impending surge in enforcement actions.  Crypto Faces...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Saves Central Banks During Global Crisis?!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468370/Bitcoin-Saves-Central-Banks-During-Global-Crisis</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468370/Bitcoin-Saves-Central-Banks-During-Global-Crisis"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T21:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marko Papic is a macro strategist who incorporates geopolitics into his investment analysis. He is also the author of "Geopolitical Alpha: An Investment Framework for Predicting the Future." In this conversation, we talk about geopolitical alpha, how to apply it to your investment process,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock, Ondo, Superstate: The Biggest Movers in the RWA Sector in Q1]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468361/BlackRock-Ondo-Superstate-The-Biggest-Movers-in-the-RWA-Sector-in-Q1</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468361/BlackRock-Ondo-Superstate-The-Biggest-Movers-in-the-RWA-Sector-in-Q1"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T20:55:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Catching up on the biggest news from the real-world asset space.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Big Short’ Investor Calls Crypto One of the ‘Great Themes of Our Time,’ But He’s Not a Believer]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742f50967d</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/big-short-investor-calls-crypto-one-of-the-great-themes-of-our-time-but-hes-not-a-believer/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T20:49:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent interview on Bloomberg Television, Steve Eisman of Neuberger Berman, who gained prominence from “The Big Short,” shared insights on the impending U.S. election and his investment strategies. Eisman identified three significant current themes, including cryptocurrency, about which he expressed skepticism. Steve Eisman’s Take: Trump’s Re-Election and the So-Called Crypto Conundrum Steve Eisman, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Is A Key Issue For 1 in 5 Voters In The 2024 US Elections, Digital Currency Group Says]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468311/Crypto-Is-A-Key-Issue-For-1-in-5-Voters-In-The-2024-US-Elections-Digital-Currency-Group-Says</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468311/Crypto-Is-A-Key-Issue-For-1-in-5-Voters-In-The-2024-US-Elections-Digital-Currency-Group-Says"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T20:44:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One in five voters in key battleground states believe digital assets are a key issue in the upcoming 2024 elections, data released Tuesday by the Digital Currency Group (DCG) reveals. The survey results come amidst the increasingly tense presidential race between Joe Biden and Donald Trump, with...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michelle Obama and RFK Jr. Have Equal Odds of Becoming Next President on Polymarket]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229803</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229803/michelle-obama-rfk-jr-presidential-win-odds-polymarket"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T20:43:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The former first lady has no plans to run for U.S. President, but oddsmakers are backing her as enthusiastically as the actual, crypto-friendly candidate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michelle Obama and RFK Jr. Have Equal Odds of Becoming Next President on Polymarket]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468310/Michelle-Obama-and-RFK-Jr-Have-Equal-Odds-of-Becoming-Next-President-on-Polymarket</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468310/Michelle-Obama-and-RFK-Jr-Have-Equal-Odds-of-Becoming-Next-President-on-Polymarket"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T20:43:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The former first lady has no plans to run for U.S. President, but oddsmakers are backing her as enthusiastically as the actual, crypto-friendly candidate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Huge Transaction from the PEPE Whale: Deeply Impacts Price]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468308/Huge-Transaction-from-the-PEPE-Whale-Deeply-Impacts-Price</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468308/Huge-Transaction-from-the-PEPE-Whale-Deeply-Impacts-Price"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T20:41:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to onchain data, a whale made a high-volume transaction in PEPE, one of the popular memecoins. Here are the details. Continue Reading: Huge Transaction from the PEPE Whale: Deeply Impacts Price]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum price lags due to ‘weaker capital rotation,’ but crypto macro uptrend remains]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468309/Ethereum-price-lags-due-to-weaker-capital-rotation-but-crypto-macro-uptrend-remains</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468309/Ethereum-price-lags-due-to-weaker-capital-rotation-but-crypto-macro-uptrend-remains"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T20:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH price has underperformed Bitcoin, but Glassnode analysts say data suggests the crypto market remains in the “early stages of a macro uptrend.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Investment Firm Discloses Over $1.8 Billion in Bitcoin ETF Holdings in SEC Filing]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742f525163</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/markets/investment-firm-discloses-over-1-8-billion-in-bitcoin-etf-holdings-in-sec-filing"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T20:36:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Susquehanna International Group, LLP (SIG), a global trading, technology, and investment firm, disclosed that it holds over $1.8 billion in Bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) through a 13F-HR filing submitted to the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), providing a detailed breakdown of SIG's investment portfolio.
The filing reveals the investment firms biggest positions were in Grayscales Bitcoin ETF GBTC, totaling $1,091,029,663.
 
                         
                         
                         
                     
                    
The documents also revealed that SIG holds positions in ARK 21SHARES BITCOIN ETF, BITWISE BITCOIN ETF TR, BITWISE FUNDS TRUST (BITCOIN AND ETHER), FIDELITY WISE ORIGIN BITCOIN, FRANKLIN TEMPLETON DIGITAL BITCOIN ETF, GLOBAL X BITCOIN T…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nik Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitget Trains Over 6,000 Students: Here's How to Get Certified]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468303/Bitget-Trains-Over-6000-Students-Heres-How-to-Get-Certified</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468303/Bitget-Trains-Over-6000-Students-Heres-How-to-Get-Certified"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T20:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitget's Blockchain4Youth initiative provides free blockchain certificates to over 6,000 students, equipping them with fundamental blockchain literacy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Experts Bulk Up on New Web3 Utility Coin – Next Big Bitcoin Challenger?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468305/Crypto-Experts-Bulk-Up-on-New-Web3-Utility-Coin-Next-Big-Bitcoin-Challenger</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468305/Crypto-Experts-Bulk-Up-on-New-Web3-Utility-Coin-Next-Big-Bitcoin-Challenger"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T20:29:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto experts are bulking up on what could be crypto’s best new web3 utility coin ICO Mega Dice (DICE), a fast-growing crypto casino platform that combines aspects of GambleFi, GameFi, is a passive income gem, and has one of web3’s most exciting airdrops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Crypto to Buy Now May 7 – Bitcoin, AIOZ Network, Ethena]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468304/Best-Crypto-to-Buy-Now-May-7-Bitcoin-AIOZ-Network-Ethena</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468304/Best-Crypto-to-Buy-Now-May-7-Bitcoin-AIOZ-Network-Ethena"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T20:25:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the Bitcoin (BTC) price consolidates just to the north of $63,000, investors are weighing up whether it could be the best crypto to buy now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance-Listed Altcoin Makes a Big New Announcement: Price Reacts]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468262/Binance-Listed-Altcoin-Makes-a-Big-New-Announcement-Price-Reacts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468262/Binance-Listed-Altcoin-Makes-a-Big-New-Announcement-Price-Reacts"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T20:14:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The developers of an altcoin that is also listed on Binance announced in their latest statement that they will establish a new Ethereum layer 2 chain. Continue Reading: Binance-Listed Altcoin Makes a Big New Announcement: Price Reacts]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Independent Presidential Candidate Robert F. Kennedy Jr. Joins Consensus as a Headline Speaker]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742f5dd7b6</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/independent-presidential-candidate-robert-f-kennedy-jr-joins-consensus-as-a-headline-speaker/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T20:08:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. May 7, 2024, Austin, TX – In less than four weeks, independent presidential candidate Robert F. Kennedy Jr. will take the stage in Austin, TX, at Consensus 2024, the world’s largest, longest-running, and most influential gathering that brings together all sides of the crypto and Web3 community. As an environmental lawyer, scion of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Swiss National Bank Prefers Tokenized Assets Over CBDCs]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468279/Swiss-National-Bank-Prefers-Tokenized-Assets-Over-CBDCs</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468279/Swiss-National-Bank-Prefers-Tokenized-Assets-Over-CBDCs"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T20:05:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Swiss National Bank (SNB) is at the forefront of integrating cutting-edge technology in the financial sector. At a recent summit in Basel, SNB Chairman Thomas Jordan unveiled the bank’s strategic move towards asset tokenization. Jordan outlined that the SNB assesses various methods to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nigeria Mulls Crypto P2P Ban in Fintech Conflict Escalation]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468255/Nigeria-Mulls-Crypto-P2P-Ban-in-Fintech-Conflict-Escalation</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468255/Nigeria-Mulls-Crypto-P2P-Ban-in-Fintech-Conflict-Escalation"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T20:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Nigerian SEC Director-General announced an imminent ban on naira P2P services across all crypto trading and exchange platforms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Holders In Profit across 82%, What About Shiba Inu?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742f5e5a45</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-holders-profit-shiba-inu/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T20:04:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Major cryptocurrencies have exhibited an interesting price dynamic in the past few days. According to data from Coinmarketcap, the majority of cryptocurrencies, including Dogecoin, have posted losses in the past 24 hours. On the other hand, some of these cryptocurrencies are still on a price increase when looking at a larger timeframe and many more addresses have crossed into the profitability zone in the past seven days. 
 
Dogecoin, for instance, is still up by 9% in a 7-day timeframe. As a result, the number of DOGE addresses in profitability has now been pushed to 83%, with 163,000 more addresses waiting to be pushed into profit if DOGE crosses over $0.1657.
 
Holders of Shiba Inu, Dogecoin’s meme counterpart, haven’t been treated to the same effect. At the time of writing, the number …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Republican congressman challenges SEC’s approach to market oversight]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468243/Republican-congressman-challenges-SECs-approach-to-market-oversight</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468243/Republican-congressman-challenges-SECs-approach-to-market-oversight"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T20:02:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Republican Congressman Tom Emmer, who also serves as majority whip in the House of Republicans, has been lashing out at Securities and Exchange Commission Chair Gary Gensler for implementing Staff Accounting Bulletin (SAB) 121. Emmer stands against regulatory overreach by SEC Emmer laments that...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Holders In Profit across 82%, What About Shiba Inu?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468241/Dogecoin-Holders-In-Profit-across-82-What-About-Shiba-Inu</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468241/Dogecoin-Holders-In-Profit-across-82-What-About-Shiba-Inu"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T20:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Major cryptocurrencies have exhibited an interesting price dynamic in the past few days. According to data from Coinmarketcap, the majority of cryptocurrencies, including Dogecoin, have posted losses in the past 24 hours. On the other hand, some of these cryptocurrencies are still on a price...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin miner Marathon Digital’s MARA hikes 17% after S&P 600 listing]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468238/Bitcoin-miner-Marathon-Digitals-MARA-hikes-17-after-SP-600-listing</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468238/Bitcoin-miner-Marathon-Digitals-MARA-hikes-17-after-SP-600-listing"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T20:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marathon Digital’s stock (MARA) rallied and reversed its April losses after its latest listing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Rally Could Be Short-Lived if BTC Follows Stock Market, According to Analyst Benjamin Cowen]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468227/Bitcoin-Rally-Could-Be-Short-Lived-if-BTC-Follows-Stock-Market-According-to-Analyst-Benjamin-Cowen</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468227/Bitcoin-Rally-Could-Be-Short-Lived-if-BTC-Follows-Stock-Market-According-to-Analyst-Benjamin-Cowen"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T20:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A widely followed crypto analyst says that Bitcoin (BTC) may be acting as a “more volatile version” of the stock market. In a new video update, crypto strategist Benjamin Cowen tells his 801,000 YouTube subscribers that Bitcoin may be following in the footsteps of the Russell 2000 Index, NASDAQ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance CEO Richard Teng Demands Nigeria Release Imprisoned Employee, Offers Help in Resolving Tax Issues]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468218/Binance-CEO-Richard-Teng-Demands-Nigeria-Release-Imprisoned-Employee-Offers-Help-in-Resolving-Tax-Issues</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468218/Binance-CEO-Richard-Teng-Demands-Nigeria-Release-Imprisoned-Employee-Offers-Help-in-Resolving-Tax-Issues"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T19:55:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance CEO Richard Teng is demanding the release of a top executive imprisoned in Nigeria for alleged money laundering crimes. In a new Binance blog post, Teng calls on Nigerian authorities to release Tigran Gambaryan, head of the crypto exchange’s Financial Crime Compliance team, who has been...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coincheck's Nasdaq Listing Gains Traction as SPAC Submits Proposal to SEC]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742f5fb08d</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/coinchecks-nasdaq-listing-gains-traction-as-spac-submits-proposal-to-sec/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T19:54:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coincheck and Spacial Purpose Acquisition Company Thunder Bridge Capital Partners IV is progressing with their merger deal, which will enable the Japanese cryptocurrency exchange to list on Nasdaq. This action signifies a significant step for both companies and has implications for investors seeking exposure to the burgeoning crypto  
industry.
Gateway to Nasdaq
Coincheck is a renowned digital asset exchange in Japan, with a market share of over 1.98 million accounts. Thunder Bridge Capital Partners IV is an SPAC that facilitates mergers and acquisitions within the finance sector. The proposed merger signifies Coincheck's ambition to expand its global footprint and  
gain access to the Nasdaq market. The combined entity, to be named Coincheck Group  
N.V.,  is pending regulatory approvals …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu's Whale Transactions Spike 383% And New Account Creations Soar 15X On Nexo Listing Announcement]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468252/Shiba-Inus-Whale-Transactions-Spike-383-And-New-Account-Creations-Soar-15X-On-Nexo-Listing-Announcement</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468252/Shiba-Inus-Whale-Transactions-Spike-383-And-New-Account-Creations-Soar-15X-On-Nexo-Listing-Announcement"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T19:51:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (CRYPTO: SHIB) has experienced a surge in large transaction volume and new accounts following a network upgrade that has made Shibarium even f read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitpay Partners With Moonpay to Enhance Crypto Selling Experience on App]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742f59c44f</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitpay-partners-with-moonpay-to-enhance-crypto-selling-experience-on-app/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T19:38:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Tuesday, the crypto payments processor based in Atlanta, Bitpay, revealed its collaboration with Moonpay. The partnership, Bitpay emphasized, enables users to sell bitcoin and other crypto assets directly through the Bitpay app. Bitpay Now Allows Direct Sales via Moonpay Partnership Users of the Bitpay app can now sell their crypto assets through Bitpay’s integration […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[House Republicans Move To Crush SEC's Anti-Crypto Banking Policy]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229786</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229786/us-house-resolution-sec-bank-bulletin-crypto-custodians"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T19:28:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Congress is mulling a resolution aimed at rescinding guidance that proponents say drives U.S. banks away from holding digital assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto’s Electoral Impact: Over 20% Of Swing State Voters Weigh Digital Currency Policies Heavily]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742f466119</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/cryptos-electoral-impact-over-swing-state-voters/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T19:03:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the political temperature in the United States heats up ahead of upcoming elections, cryptocurrency is emerging as a significant topic among voters in key battleground states.
 
An extensive online survey spearheaded by the Digital Currency Group (DCG) has highlighted the growing importance of digital currency policies in the electoral dialogue, particularly in states known for their pivotal role in election outcomes.
 
 
Voter Sentiment On Crypto: A New Electoral Battleground
 
The influence of digital currency in shaping political landscapes is increasingly apparent, as evidenced by the recent survey conducted by The Harris Poll for DCG. From April 4-16, this poll involved 1,201 registered voters across Michigan, Ohio, Montana, Pennsylvania, Nevada, and Arizona.
 
Results indicate tha…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Game 'Fantasy Top' Pays $1.25M to Twitter Influencers It Turned Into NFT Cards]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229775</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229775/ethereum-game-fantasy-top-pays-1-25m-twitter-influencers-turned-nft-cards"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T19:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto influencers got a share of $1.25 million in ETH and potentially millions in Blast Gold for being tradable "heroes" in Fantasy Top.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MoMA’s Madeleine Pierpont: NFTs Are Already a Part of Art History]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742f420a01</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2024/05/07/momas-madeleine-pierpont-nfts-are-already-a-part-of-art-history/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T18:36:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Yes, there has been a hyper-financialization in the NFT space, but money is not a dirty word in art,” says the Consensus 2024 speaker.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Kuhn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former NFL Star Rob Gronkowski to Pay $1.9M to Settle Crypto Investor Suit]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742f4209f4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/05/07/former-nfl-star-rob-gronkowski-to-pay-19m-to-settle-crypto-investor-suit/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T18:36:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NBA's Victor Oladipo and racecar driver Landon Cassill also struck deals, and a group of Voyager investors said this was the "first tranche" of settlements with promoters of the former cryptocurrency lender.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano Ecosystem Set For Expansion: EMURGO And GSR Join Forces]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742f4edbfd</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/cardano-emurgo-gsr-join-forces/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T18:04:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EMURGO, the commercial arm of the Cardano blockchain, has formed a strategic alliance with GSR, a prominent global cryptocurrency trading firm. This partnership aims to bolster the infrastructure of the ecosystem by leveraging GSR’s expertise in market liquidity and financial services.
 
How The Partnership Will Boost Cardano
 
EMURGO, established in 2015, plays a critical role in driving the adoption and implementation of the Cardano blockchain. The collaboration with GSR is intended to address several key areas within the network.
 
First, GSR will bring its extensive experience in market-making to provide deeper liquidity for Cardano’s native token and other Cardano-based digital assets. This move is expected to reduce slippage and improve transaction efficiency on decentralized exchang…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Defeating Biden Would Be Good for Bitcoin: Standard Chartered]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229761</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229761/trump-defeating-biden-good-bitcoin-standard-chartered"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T18:01:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Analysts at British bank Standard Chartered today said that a second Donald Trump presidency could do Bitcoin good.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Australia Eyes Unreported Crypto Transactions: Taxman Targets 1.2 Million Accounts]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742f481249</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/australian-eyes-unreported-crypto-transactions-taxman-targets-12-million-accounts/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T17:56:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Australian Taxation Office (ATO) has requested  
personal data and transaction details from crypto exchanges for up to 1.2  
million accounts to crack down on potential tax evaders, Reuters reported. This  
move marks a significant escalation in the ATO's efforts to ensure compliance  
in the rapidly expanding digital currency market.
Oversight of Crypto Tax Compliance
The ATO's notice, issued last month, aims to identify  
individuals who may have failed to report their crypto transactions. It focuses  
on instances where crypto assets were exchanged or utilized for payments  
without proper tax declarations.
The ATO has acknowledged the complexities of the  
crypto industry, attributing non-compliance to a lack of awareness regarding  
tax obligations. Additionally, the potential for ano…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Mixers Targeted in U.S. House Democrats' Effort to 'Clamp Down' on Money Laundering]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742f49c255</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/05/07/crypto-mixers-targeted-in-us-house-democrats-effort-to-clamp-down-on-money-laundering/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T17:46:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several Democrats on the House Financial Services Committee have a bill coming this week to target money laundering through cryptocurrency mixing services, said Rep. Sean Casten (D-Ill.), one of its backers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Fan Jack Dorsey Takes Kendrick Lamar’s Side in Drake Beef]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229729</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229729/bitcoin-fan-jack-dorsey-kendrick-lamar-drake"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T17:42:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Who’s winning the Kendrick and Drake lyrical war? Dorsey says it’s no contest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cartier Family Member Indicted for Using USDT to Launder Hundreds of Millions in Drug Trafficking Money]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742f4ad0cc</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/cartier-family-member-indicted-for-using-usdt-to-launder-hundreds-of-millions-in-drug-trafficking-money/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T17:39:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maximilien De Hoop Cartier, a descendant of the family famous for their French luxury goods Cartier, has been indicted for his participation in a network that allegedly used several shell companies to launder drug trafficking money proceeds using USDT. Cartier and five Colombian individuals allegedly conspired to directly launder $14.5 million and used these shell […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Visa’s ‘Organic’ Stablecoin Report Misses]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742f352de3</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2024/05/07/what-visas-organic-stablecoin-report-misses/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T17:25:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new metric co-developed by the payments giant says only 10% of stablecoin transactions in April were  “real” or “organic.” But the methodology appears to leave out some key use cases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Kuhn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Government’s Hypocritical Case Against Tornado Cash]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742f3690ca</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2024/05/07/the-us-governments-hypocritical-case-against-tornado-cash/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T17:16:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You would think the government would be against an online privacy service facilitating money laundering. But it actually created one of the best, says attorney Alexandra Damsker.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexandra Damsker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. DOJ Identifies and Charges LockBit Ransomware Gang Leader with Fraud, Extortion]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742f3690a8</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/05/07/us-doj-identifies-and-charges-lockbit-ransomware-gang-leader-with-fraud-extortion/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T17:16:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. authorities have identified Russian national Dmitry Khoroshev as the mastermind behind the notorious LockBit ransomware gang, and are offering a $10 million reward for information that leads to his arrest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cheyenne Ligon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gary Gensler Says It’s Our Fault the SEC Appears So Focused on Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229736</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229736/gary-gensler-our-fault-sec-focused-crypto"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T17:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s an “outsized ratio of journalist questions and crypto journalists to market cap,” SEC Chair Gary Gensler claims.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Is Not The Time To Sell Chainlink: Industry Veteran Predicts Price Will Reach New ATH]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742f30b7bc</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/chainlink-will-reach-new-ath/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T17:03:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Popular cryptocurrency analyst, Michael van de Poppe has predicted a major bullish breakout for Chainlink (LINK), urging investors to hold on to their cryptocurrencies despite market volatility. 
 
Analyst Cautions Against Premature Sell-Off
 
In an X (formerly Twitter) post on Monday, May 5, Poppe shared a LINK/BTC price chart, depicting historical price movements from 2018 to 2025. Based on the technical analysis of the cryptocurrency’s price action across previous market cycles, the crypto analyst noted that Chainlink was presently undergoing a retest at its low point. 
 
 
This suggests that the cryptocurrency is experiencing a phase of reassessment and potential stabilization, followed by a possible price rebound. Poppe has disclosed that initiating sell-offs during Chainlink’s curren…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Botanix Labs Secures $11.5 Million Funding to Develop Bitcoin-Native DeFi Ecosystem]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742f318ead</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/botanix-labs-secures-11-5-million-funding-to-develop-bitcoin-native-defi-ecosystem"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T16:58:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Botanix Labs, a Bitcoin development startup based in New York and founded at Harvard, has announced a significant funding of $11.5 million in a press release sent to Bitcoin Magazine.
This funding round, led by prominent investors including UTXO Management, Polychain Capital, Placeholder Capital, Valor Equity Partners, ABCDE, Andrew Kang, Dan Held, Dovey Wan, Eric Wall and others, will fuel the creation of the Spiderchain. Spiderchain claims to be the first Bitcoin-native Layer 2 primitive with full EVM equivalence, envisioned to support a global financial system built on Bitcoin. This funding follows a previous seed series round of $8.5 million in April.
“Our team at Botanix Labs is driven by the mission of building the infrastructure that supports aglobal financial system running on Bitc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nik Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Going Bankless: Bitcoin Offers The Ultimate Financial Freedom]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742f318e9c</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/sponsored/going-bankless-bitcoin-offers-the-ultimate-financial-freedom"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T16:58:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is often said that Bitcoin allows anyone to be their own bank. If you know anything about Bitcoin’s ethos and underlying tech, you’ve likely heard of this concept before. But do you know exactly how that works and why Bitcoin is more suitable as a store of value than your bank?
To get the full picture, it’s important to understand how banks work today, and how Bitcoin differs from the traditional financial system. 
The Problem With Banks
The first problem with banks is their custodial nature, and with that, the risk of rehypothecation inherent to fractional reserve banking. If banks were simply means of warehousing cash for their clients, using them would only imply counterparty risk. While not ideal, this would not necessarily be a problem if banks simply let customer funds sit there, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood CEO Decries 'Regulatory Onslaught' on Crypto, Vows to Fight SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229728</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229728/robinhood-ceo-decries-regulatory-onslaught-crypto-fight-sec"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T16:58:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Though Robinhood Crypto thought its "safety-first" approach was distinct, the SEC said that enforcement action is on its way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETFs Take In $217 Million for Second Consecutive Day of Net Gains]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229727</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229727/bitcoin-etfs-take-in-217-million-for-second-consecutive-day-of-net-gains"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T16:44:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every single fund saw another day in the green with net inflows yesterday—including Grayscale Bitcoin Trust.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Crypto Crackdown: Every Company That Is Being Investigated]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229723</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229723/sec-crypto-crackdown-every-company-wells-notice"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T15:14:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC is taking aim at crypto companies in the United States. Here's who has disclosed a Wells Notice or is reportedly under investigation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[University Speaker Takes Ayahuasca, Shills Bitcoin, Gets Booed]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229687</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229687/osu-commencement-speaker-bitcoin-ayahuasca"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T14:04:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ohio State University commencement speech included Bitcoin shilling and some cringe-worthy karaoke—all fueled by psychedelics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nintendo Switch 2 Preview: Everything You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197793</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197793/nintendo-switch-2-rumors-leaks-latest-news"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T13:31:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATED: It's official: Nintendo has announced a Switch "successor." Here's everything we've heard so far about the Switch 2.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Play Social Games, Earn Crypto Rewards: Solana Gaming App 'Cupcake' Launches]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229618</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229618/play-social-games-earn-crypto-rewards-solana-cupcake"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cupcake uses a TikTok-like feed of social games to help bring players deeper into the crypto world—and serves up Solana-based rewards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance CEO Demands Release of Employee Detained in Nigeria]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229630</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229630/binance-ceo-demands-release-of-employee-detained-in-nigeria"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T11:05:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance CEO Richard Teng alleged that Tigran Gambaryan is being held in "a dangerous prison in order to control Binance."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tom Brady Ridiculed for FTX and Crypto Investments in Netflix Roast]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229627</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229627/tom-brady-ridiculed-for-ftx-and-crypto-investments-in-netflix-roast"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T10:54:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Star NFL quarterback Tom Brady was ridiculed for his Bitcoin affinity and ties to bankrupt crypto exchange FTX during a live roast on Netflix.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple's AI Ambitions Emerge Ahead of iPad Event]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229615</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229615/apple-ai-strategy-siri-xcode-music"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T00:46:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Between Tuesday's iPad event and WWDC, AI is expected to play a part in nearly every corner of the Apple ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Ethereum Game ‘Fantasy Top’ Is Taking Over Crypto Twitter]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229595</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229595/why-ethereum-game-fantasy-top-taking-over-crypto-twitter"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T23:06:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fantasy Top is like fantasy football, but with crypto influencers. The Blast game is the hot new thing amid a cooling crypto market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Wallet Maker Exodus Jumping Up to New York Stock Exchange]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229589</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229589/bitcoin-wallet-exodus-nyse-exod-listing"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T22:36:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Exodus says it is the only U.S. company that will have its EXOD common stock tokenized on the blockchain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale's Ethereum Fund Discount Steadies as ETF Deadline Looms]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229584</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229584/grayscale-ethereum-ethe-fund-discount"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T21:50:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale hopes to convert its Ethereum Trust to a spot ETH ETF, and current investors see opportunity in the uncertainty.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Is Down, But These Analysts Still Think BTC Hits $150K This Year]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229582</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229582/bitcoin-150000-price-doubling-18-months-bernstein"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T21:32:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AllianceBernstein join Standard Chartered analysts in seeing the price of BTC more than doubling in the next 18 months.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Long-Term Bitcoin Investors Have Returned To HODLing: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229577</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229577/bitcoin-long-term-btc-holders-grow"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T20:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin whales eagerly bought the latest dip, and long-term investors are now patiently awaiting the next leg up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETFs Are Back? $378 Million In Gains Marks Best Day In Over a Month]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229553</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229553/bitcoin-spot-etf-inflows-across-the-board-gbtc-turns-green"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T19:30:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every fund flipped green on Friday, as more traditional investors hold on to their BTC-based shares.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana's Dogwifhat Pumps as Bonk, Dogecoin and Other Meme Coins Lose Ground]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229555</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229555/meme-coin-wif-bonk-doge-pepe"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T19:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WIF is the only meme coin in the top 100 posting gains amid a broader crypto dip. Other popular meme coins are struggling to maintain momentum.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mixers Pull Out of the US Amid Regulatory Heat]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229543</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229543/bitcoin-coin-mixers-shut-americans-out"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T18:48:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Privacy preserving crypto services are shutting down or shutting out American users as U.S. agencies turn up the pressure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Whale Moves $44 Million After a Decade—Here's How Much It Gained]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229534</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229534/bitcoin-whale-moves-44-million-after-decade-how-much-gained"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T17:09:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An unidentified Bitcoin whale just moved 687 BTC after it sat for more than a decade. Here's how much the value increased during that span.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Price Jumps Nearly 5% as Bitcoin, Ethereum Lag Behind]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229533</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229533/solana-price-jumps-bitcoin-ethereum-lag-behind"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T16:13:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana is the biggest gainer in the top 10 cryptocurrencies on an otherwise quiet Monday morning, as Bitcoin and Ethereum tick down.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[90% of Ethereum, Tron, Solana Stablecoin Transactions Are ‘Inorgranic Activity’, Visa Says]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229515</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229515/stablecoin-transactions-inorganic-bots-ethereum-tron-solana"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T16:02:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smart contracts, not humans, are driving nearly all stablecoin arbitrage, liquidity provision, and market making.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood Crypto Says SEC Has 'Weak' Case in Response to Wells Notice]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229516</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229516/robinhood-crypto-sec-wells-notice"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T13:31:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company said it's looking forward to showing "just how weak any case against Robinhood Crypto would be on both the facts and the law."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott,André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Sees Modest Gains as Network Processes Its 1 Billionth Transaction]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229504</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229504/bitcoin-sees-modest-gains-as-network-processes-its-1-billionth-transaction"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T12:05:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The world's oldest and largest cryptocurrency just celebrated a birthday of sorts: Its network has processed more than 1 billion transactions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Ordinals Size Record Broken Again—How Much Bigger Can They Get?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229421</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229421/bitcoin-block-size-record-broken-again-how-much-bigger"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T18:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The largest-ever Bitcoin file was just inscribed, as an Ordinals asset broke the two-month-old size record. Can it be broken again?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Crypto Games: Supercell's Investment, Saga Airdrop, 'Parallel' Adds Expansion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229459</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229459/this-week-crypto-games-supercell-investment-saga-airdrop-parallel-expansion"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T16:53:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Catch up on this week’s biggest crypto and NFT gaming news and find some weekend reads in our latest roundup.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week on Crypto Twitter: Ethereum, CZ, and Roger Ver in US Government Crosshairs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229391</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229391/this-week-on-crypto-twitter-ethereum-cz-roger-ver-government-wrath"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T16:19:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CZ got sentenced, Ver got arrested, and Ethereum has been secretly considered a regulated security since April 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biggest Video Games Releasing in May 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229400</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229400/biggest-video-games-releasing-may-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-05-04T15:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's a busy month of sequels as Senua's Saga: Hellblade II, Homeworld 3, and World of Goo 2 lead May 2024's video game releases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Frederiksen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Do A Little With Mike Demarais]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ajrh0oiK/we-do-a-little-with-mike-demarais</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ajrh0oiK/we-do-a-little-with-mike-demarais"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T15:11:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mike dropped knowledge bombs from years of building in the trenches alongside some deep cuts on the early Williamsburg crypto mafia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eth Rally Fails]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Gj7TMrbP/eth-rally-fails</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Gj7TMrbP/eth-rally-fails"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T12:45:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto falls, ETH/BTC rally again marks mini sell-off. Yen carry-trade implosion linked to worries. ETH gas fees hit 6-month lows. 3rd straight week of institutional outflows. Slowing BTC ETF flows are just a pause: Bernstein. BTC now on track for 5 red weeks in a row. BTC may have topped, could hit $35k: Brandt. ETFs may become big sellers: Bianco. Consensys list 4 reasons ETH isn’t a security. Rumours continue to grow of EigenLayer airdrop. Perp DEX volumes continue fall, GMX underperforms. Wallets begin to block US users after Samourai case. WLD in reported partnership talks with OpenAI. Large unlocks this week for SUI, PYTH & MEME.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Sasha Stiles’ Experiential, AI-Infused NFT Drop with Bang & Olufsen]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/6Vi2IgYj/inside-sasha-stiles-experiential-ai-infused-nft-drop-with-bang-olufsen</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/6Vi2IgYj/inside-sasha-stiles-experiential-ai-infused-nft-drop-with-bang-olufsen"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T22:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At a launch party for the collection in New York’s SoHo neighborhood, the artist broke down her latest art experiment, “Four Core Texts,” with Decrypt’s Sander Lutz.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interview: How 'Notcoin' Will Evolve After the NOT Token Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PprnGP14/interview-how-notcoin-will-evolve-after-the-not-token-launch</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PprnGP14/interview-how-notcoin-will-evolve-after-the-not-token-launch"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Open Builders founder Sasha Plotvinov speaks with Decrypt's Sander Lutz at Token 2049 Dubai about how he envisions Notcoin's expansion and evolution after the token drop—into something akin to the "Netflix of social, viral games."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Magic Runes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IGWg0R64/magic-runes</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IGWg0R64/magic-runes"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T13:59:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC stables at $66k, liquidations in narrow range. BTC funding again turns negative in bullish sign. ETFs net inflow after Grayscale moves to lower fees. BTC demand 5x vs supply post-halving: Bitfinex. SOL congestion issue now largely solved. Two SEC lawyers resign after ‘gross abuse of power’. Ripple fights to lower $2bn SEC fine. SAFE trades at $2.8bn FDV after OKX lists. MANEKI hits $150m on first day, China memes pump. Memecoins are ‘black hole you can’t ignore’. DeGods up 20%, may switch back to SOL. Magic Eden launches Runes platform ahead of time.  Louis Vuitton gifts Pharrell jacket to NFT holders. Melania Trump launches necklace with SOL NFTs. Hoodie Punk trades for $620K.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Luxury Watches, Designer Shoes Will Soon Trade Like NFTs: Arianee CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/CSNQG2md/luxury-watches-designer-shoes-will-soon-trade-like-nfts-arianee-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/CSNQG2md/luxury-watches-designer-shoes-will-soon-trade-like-nfts-arianee-ceo"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arianee CEO Pierre-Nicolas Hurstel sat down with Rug Radio founder Farokh and Decrypt’s Sander Lutz at NFT Paris to discuss everything from the future of on-chain luxury to the secret hack to finding the best restaurants in France.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notcoin's Co-Creator Explains the Game's Token Delay—And When to Expect NOT Now]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/7Zx33xo5/notcoins-co-creator-explains-the-games-token-delayand-when-to-expect-not-now</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/7Zx33xo5/notcoins-co-creator-explains-the-games-token-delayand-when-to-expect-not-now"/>
        <updated>2024-04-22T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Notcoin co-creator Sasha Plotvinov spoke with Decrypt's Sander Lutz at Token 2049 Dubai to discuss why the NOT token launch was pushed back from the original 4/20 target, when to expect the listing, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TON’s Justin Hyun Breaks Down The Importance of USDT Coming to Telegram]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ODQI6ACA/tons-justin-hyun-breaks-down-the-importance-of-usdt-coming-to-telegram</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ODQI6ACA/tons-justin-hyun-breaks-down-the-importance-of-usdt-coming-to-telegram"/>
        <updated>2024-04-19T10:14:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Token 2049 in Dubai, The Open Network’s director of investments sat down with Decrypt’s Sander Lutz to discuss what he sees as the game-changing integration of USDT onto TON, and his plans for getting Telegram’s 900 million users to start using crypto in the immediate future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Influencer Ansem Explains His Meme Coin Thesis and Why He’s Bullish on Bitcoin Runes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/u9DHFoK0/crypto-influencer-ansem-explains-his-meme-coin-thesis-and-why-hes-bullish-on-bitcoin-runes</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/u9DHFoK0/crypto-influencer-ansem-explains-his-meme-coin-thesis-and-why-hes-bullish-on-bitcoin-runes"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T21:56:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ansem, the crypto trader who's amassed a sizable following on the back of meme coin Dogwifhat (WIF) and other calls, chats with Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz at Token 2049 Dubai about his meme coin thesis, why he's bullish on Bitcoin Runes, and what he sees ahead for the crypto markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Sander Lutz Braves the Dubai Floods for a Crypto Conference]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/mtjVHGa3/decrypts-sander-lutz-braves-the-dubai-floods-for-a-crypto-conference</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/mtjVHGa3/decrypts-sander-lutz-braves-the-dubai-floods-for-a-crypto-conference"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T21:33:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz reports from Dubai amid a historic storm that flooded the famed city, trudging through the streets to complete his essential task: Attending the Token 2049 crypto conference.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gold Beats Its All Time High]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/6ULgUKVk/gold-beats-its-all-time-high</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/6ULgUKVk/gold-beats-its-all-time-high"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T09:53:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) maintains its trend of reaching higher lows amidst choppy market conditions. Exchange-traded funds (ETFs) witness another influx of $125 million. There's anticipation of Hong Kong approving ETFs for both Bitcoin and Ethereum (ETH) come Monday. Notable institutional investor BlackRock shows interest in Bitcoin. Recent filings reveal increased Bitcoin purchases by banks. A Bitcoin-friendly political party secures victory in the South Korean election. Analyst Kang predicts Bitcoin could surge to $80-100k by May. Meanwhile, Ethereum sees accumulation by stablecoin whales on the rise. A new Ethereum Improvement Proposal (EIP) aims to streamline signing requests. Solana (SOL) experiences a resurgence in activity, reaching yearly highs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NASA’s Next Deep Space Mission Won’t Use Artificial Intelligence]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/0WGP33Rp/nasas-next-deep-space-mission-wont-use-artificial-intelligence</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/0WGP33Rp/nasas-next-deep-space-mission-wont-use-artificial-intelligence"/>
        <updated>2024-04-13T18:42:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Thursday, Decrypt Media visited NASA's Jet Propulsion Laboratory in Pasadena, CA to meet with the Engineering team behind the Europa Clipper before its launch to Jupiter's Europa moon in October.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Do A Little with Weesh]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LnaOT9bF/we-do-a-little-with-weesh</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LnaOT9bF/we-do-a-little-with-weesh"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T07:46:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week’s episode, we did a little something different. We took the man who is usually behind the camera and put him in front of it. We sat down with our producer Weesh to dive into how in fell in love with art and became a collector, how he met Andy and fun childhood memories together, his biggest wins in crypto, and so much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside VanEck’s Crypto Takeover of the New York Stock Exchange]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9YAY4wGD/inside-vanecks-crypto-takeover-of-the-new-york-stock-exchange</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9YAY4wGD/inside-vanecks-crypto-takeover-of-the-new-york-stock-exchange"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T14:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worlds collide as Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz heads to the floor of the NYSE to witness a special closing bell ceremony hosted by VanEck in honor of Web3. Featuring Choose Rich Nick, VanEck Head of Web3 Matt Bartlett, and more!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>