<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-08-16T18:17:09.201Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-08-16T18:17:09.201Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$0.001 Shiba Inu Price In View Amid SHIB Exploding Ecosystem Activity As Shibarium Debut Beckons]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18841376/0001-Shiba-Inu-Price-In-View-Amid-SHIB-Exploding-Ecosystem-Activity-As-Shibarium-Debut-Beckons</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18841376/0001-Shiba-Inu-Price-In-View-Amid-SHIB-Exploding-Ecosystem-Activity-As-Shibarium-Debut-Beckons"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T18:10:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That said, the launch of Shibarium is expected to be a major milestone for the Shiba Inu ecosystem as it will...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fundstrat’s Tom Lee Sets Bitcoin (BTC) Price Target of $150,000 on ETF-Approval]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18841374/Fundstrats-Tom-Lee-Sets-Bitcoin-BTC-Price-Target-of-150000-on-ETF-Approval</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18841374/Fundstrats-Tom-Lee-Sets-Bitcoin-BTC-Price-Target-of-150000-on-ETF-Approval"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T18:05:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin bull Tom Lee of Fundstrat Global Advisors says that the crypto king could be about to launch nearly 420% from current prices if the right fundamentals line up. In a new CNBC interview, Lee says that crypto is dependent on monetary policy and benefits from cooling inflation given that...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BREAKING: Highly Anticipated FED Minutes Released, Here are the Details!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18841379/BREAKING-Highly-Anticipated-FED-Minutes-Released-Here-are-the-Details</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18841379/BREAKING-Highly-Anticipated-FED-Minutes-Released-Here-are-the-Details"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T18:05:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The minutes of the FED's meeting held on 25-26 July were announced. Here are the details in it. Continue Reading: BREAKING: Highly Anticipated FED Minutes Released, Here are the Details!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analyst Says Bitcoin to Drop to $12k Following Recent Decline]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18841378/Analyst-Says-Bitcoin-to-Drop-to-12k-Following-Recent-Decline</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18841378/Analyst-Says-Bitcoin-to-Drop-to-12k-Following-Recent-Decline"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T18:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In what many would call a seemingly impossible scenario, crypto analyst Michaël van de Poppe says the world’s largest cryptocurrency by value and market cap may be approaching some of its worst days. Amidst the ongoing market slowdown, the analyst says BTC could see a steep decline to $12,000...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BitGo Defies Crypto Turmoil: Secures $100M Funding for Custody Services]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7552342774</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/bitgo-defies-crypto-turmoil-secures-100m-funding-for-custody-services/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T18:01:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cryptocurrency custody company BitGo has defied the  
odds to raise a substantial $100 million in funding at a valuation of USD $1.75  
billion. The funding arrived at a time the cryptocurrency sector has been  
marked by uncertainty, regulatory debates, and market volatility.
Regulatory Safety
According to a report by  
Bloomberg, the company’s CEO, Mike Belshe, acknowledged the challenging market  
conditions but attributed BitGo’s success to its adherence to licensing and  
regulations, which has reportedly enabled the company to defy uncertain legal  
environment facing digital assets.
The Palo Alto-based  
company’s funding was secured exclusively from new investors. Although Belshe  
kept the details of the investors under wraps, he revealed that they hail from  
both the US and …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BitGo Raises $100 Million Series C Funding At $1.75 Billion Valuation]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7552342314</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/bitgo-raises-100-million-series-c-funding-at-1-billion-valuation"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T18:01:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BitGo, a leading Bitcoin and cryptocurrency custody firm, announced on Wednesday that it has successfully raised $100 million in its Series C financing round, bolstering its valuation to $1.75 billion. The funds will be allocated to amplify BitGo's secure and regulated custody, wallet, and infrastructure solutions on a global scale and to facilitate strategic acquisitions.



"Not only are we seeing growing demand for regulated custody solutions in the US, but we're also seeing the demand on a global scale," said BitGo CEO Mike Belshe. "We are very pleased to announce our $100M Series C for the purpose of meeting this growing need and to provide institutions, brands, coin foundations, and others with secure and seamless participation in the digital asset ecosystem."
Amid a dynamic market environment, BitGo has registered growth across the board since the beginning of the year. With a 60% surge in new client onboarding, a 20% increase in Asset Under Custody (AUC), a 200% upswing in fiat custody, and a 40-fold growth in staked assets. Notably, BitGo has distinguished itself as the entrusted custodian for the FTX creditors' funds under the leadership of John Ray III. Previously, the company was also selected as the distributor for the Mt. Gox creditors.
BitGo's recent funding success comes on the heels of the launch of its Go Network, empowering institutions to trade and settle both digital assets and fiat currencies round the clock from secure custody. With a robust presence as a premier regulated custodian in more than 50 countries, BitGo consistently handles an 20% of all on-chain Bitcoin transactions by value, according to the announcement.
Big name clients, such as Nike, have also chosen BitGo's secure and scalable wallet-as-a-service solution to navigate the intricate regulatory landscape.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nik Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Digital USD soars on Binance as overall stablecoin market sinks to two-year low]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18841352/First-Digital-USD-soars-on-Binance-as-overall-stablecoin-market-sinks-to-two-year-low</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18841352/First-Digital-USD-soars-on-Binance-as-overall-stablecoin-market-sinks-to-two-year-low"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T17:50:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The total market cap of stablecoins has been on a continuous decline for 17 months, now standing at $124 billion, its lowest level since August 2021, according to CCData. The data aggregator highlighted a broader impact of the decline in stablecoin’s monthly trading volume. Notably, July saw...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gary Gensler Delays Spot Bitcoin ETF Until 2024 | EP 804]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18840972/Gary-Gensler-Delays-Spot-Bitcoin-ETF-Until-2024-EP-804</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18840972/Gary-Gensler-Delays-Spot-Bitcoin-ETF-Until-2024-EP-804"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T17:45:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF decision delayed; Push back on crypto regulation - Squawk Box (CNBC)✓ SUBSCRIBE - https://bit.ly/3QbgqTQ✓ LEAVE A LIKE & COMMENT SPONSORS:► Swan: https://www.swan.com/simply► Bitcoin Evangelism: https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0B38CX41D/ref=cm_sw_r_api_i_Y1RXNK7NGACQ5M8BV2RN_0►...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vertex protocol founders consider cross-chain trading solutions]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18841341/Vertex-protocol-founders-consider-cross-chain-trading-solutions</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18841341/Vertex-protocol-founders-consider-cross-chain-trading-solutions"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T17:45:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The trick is to have all the liquidity and trading happening in one place, Tabatabai says]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sei, Blockchain Designed for Trading, Goes Live but 'Frustration' Mounts Over Airdrop]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18841342/Sei-Blockchain-Designed-for-Trading-Goes-Live-but-Frustration-Mounts-Over-Airdrop</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18841342/Sei-Blockchain-Designed-for-Trading-Goes-Live-but-Frustration-Mounts-Over-Airdrop"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T17:38:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The buzzy blockchain project's SEI token saw a flurry of trading as it debuted on several crypto exchanges Wednesday, but there was much confusion over the status of a promised token "airdrop" to early adopters of the network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitgo Secures $100 Million in Series C, Firm’s Valuation Climbs to $1.75 Billion]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75523712d4</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitgo-secures-100-million-in-series-c-firms-valuation-climbs-to-1-75-billion/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T17:38:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The digital asset trust firm Bitgo, headquartered in Palo Alto, California, has secured $100 million in a Series C funding round. While the company remains tight-lipped about the participants in this financial endeavor, this fresh infusion of capital catapults the firm’s post-valuation to $1.75 billion.
 
Bitgo Raises $100 Million From Undisclosed Investors
 
Bitgo has successfully bagged $100 million in a Series C funding round, with the investors’ names under wraps, as per a Bloomberg report. Bitgo’s top executive, Mike Belshe, acknowledged the challenging market landscape. Yet, he emphasized the company’s commitment to licensing and regulatory measures, noting, “Regulatory safety is top-of-mind for everyone,” in a conversation with Bloomberg’s Hannah Miller.
 
This update comes on the heels of Galaxy Digital scrapping its intentions to snap up Bitgo for a cool $1.2 billion in August 2022. Earlier, in June, Bitgo had its eyes on the beleaguered crypto custodian, Prime Trust, with acquisition plans. However, the deal fell through. Prime Trust soon found itself filing for Chapter 11 bankruptcy protection the following month.
 
 
Though the Prime Trust deal went south, Belshe indicated to Miller that a portion of this fresh capital would fuel future acquisitions. He alluded to two potential buyouts already in the pipeline, as cited by Miller. While Bitgo remains mum on this round’s backers, past investors have featured big names like Pantera Capital, Digital Currency Group, Redpoint, Goldman Sachs, and DRW Holdings.
 
What do you think about Bitgo’s latest capital raise for $100 million? Share your thoughts and opinions about this subject in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase rally stalls as shares dip more than 28% from July peak]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18841330/Coinbase-rally-stalls-as-shares-dip-more-than-28-from-July-peak</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18841330/Coinbase-rally-stalls-as-shares-dip-more-than-28-from-July-peak"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T17:35:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Coinbase summer rally has stalled. The stock has fallen by more than 28% since peaking in July at just over $110.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code vulnerability puts damper on RUNE’s wild run]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18841325/Code-vulnerability-puts-damper-on-RUNEs-wild-run</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18841325/Code-vulnerability-puts-damper-on-RUNEs-wild-run"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T17:30:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of DeFi’s oldest projects is among the best-performing on the week, but a security vulnerability has derailed the run]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Chair Gary Gensler Takes Aim at Artificial Intelligence]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18841312/SEC-Chair-Gary-Gensler-Takes-Aim-at-Artificial-Intelligence</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18841312/SEC-Chair-Gary-Gensler-Takes-Aim-at-Artificial-Intelligence"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T17:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gary Gensler, the man at the helm of the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), has revealed that artificial intelligence (AI) is on his radar. In a recent post on X (formerly Twitter), the notorious securities regulator stated that he would closely follow developments in the AI sector...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin calls X’s Community Notes an example of ‘crypto values’]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18841326/Vitalik-Buterin-calls-Xs-Community-Notes-an-example-of-crypto-values</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18841326/Vitalik-Buterin-calls-Xs-Community-Notes-an-example-of-crypto-values"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T17:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The ULTIMATE ALTCOIN Tier List for Crypto's Highest 2025 Returns]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18841320/The-ULTIMATE-ALTCOIN-Tier-List-for-Cryptos-Highest-2025-Returns</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18841320/The-ULTIMATE-ALTCOIN-Tier-List-for-Cryptos-Highest-2025-Returns"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T17:27:17.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Valkyrie just filed for an ETH futures ETF with the U.S. SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18841302/Valkyrie-just-filed-for-an-ETH-futures-ETF-with-the-US-SEC</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18841302/Valkyrie-just-filed-for-an-ETH-futures-ETF-with-the-US-SEC"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T17:21:05.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Cryptocurrency Partnership from Ledger!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18841299/New-Cryptocurrency-Partnership-from-Ledger</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18841299/New-Cryptocurrency-Partnership-from-Ledger"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T17:16:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ledger has partnered with payments giant PayPal. Users will be able to buy Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH), Bitcoin Cash (BCH), Litecoin (LTC). Continue Reading: New Cryptocurrency Partnership from Ledger!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto, please leave AI alone]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18841324/Crypto-please-leave-AI-alone</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18841324/Crypto-please-leave-AI-alone"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T17:14:49.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uzbekistan Okays New Private Bank For National Crypto Card Project]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755232c8cc</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/uzbekistan-okays-new-bank-for-crypto-card-project/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T17:08:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Republic of Uzbekistan has approved the participation of another private bank in its ongoing national crypto card project. 
 
According to a press release on August 15, 2023, the country’s digital asset regulatory body, the National Agency of Perspective Projects (NAPP) announced the registration of JSV “Ravnaq-bank” as a member of the Special Regulatory Sandbox Regime.
 
Uzbekistan Approves Second Participant Bank For Crypto Card Initiative
 
In accordance with regulations issued by Uzbekistan’s Ministry of Justice on December 30, 2022, the Special Regulatory Sandbox Regime functions as a specific framework that empowers certain entities in the Uzbekistan crypto space to offer special services. 
 
The Ravnaq-bank is now authorized under this regime to actively participate in the pilot…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Semilore Faleti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum price could dump one last time before ‘giga pump’]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18841270/Ethereum-price-could-dump-one-last-time-before-giga-pump</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18841270/Ethereum-price-could-dump-one-last-time-before-giga-pump"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T17:05:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto analysts are eager to understand what is next for the second most valuable cryptocurrency by market cap, Ethereum (ETH). … Continued]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FBI Seizes $1.7 Million in Crypto in Ongoing Crackdown]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18841269/FBI-Seizes-17-Million-in-Crypto-in-Ongoing-Crackdown</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18841269/FBI-Seizes-17-Million-in-Crypto-in-Ongoing-Crackdown"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T17:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FBI has seized nearly $2 million in crypto assets within three months as its fight against crypto-related crimes intensifies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Alts Bloody]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18841249/Crypto-Alts-Bloody</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18841249/Crypto-Alts-Bloody"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T17:01:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[🚀 Learn Technical Analysis with our FREE course! https://www.chartguys.com/trading-courses/7/technical-analysis?utm_source=youtube&utm_medium=social&utm_term=&utm_content=&utm_campaign=free-ta-courseOur goal is to review and discuss the most recent price action in the market in a manner that...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why BTC Futures ETFs Are Bad For Bitcoin’s Price]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18841297/Why-BTC-Futures-ETFs-Are-Bad-For-Bitcoins-Price</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18841297/Why-BTC-Futures-ETFs-Are-Bad-For-Bitcoins-Price"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T17:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[🔥 GET MY FREE NEWSLETTER 👉 https://cryptolark.co/WEALTHMASTERY💸 BYBIT $30,030 BONUS & FEE DISCOUNT 👉 https://cryptolark.co/BYBIT💡💡💡 ESSENTIAL CRYPTO KNOWLEDGE 💡💡💡🔥 GET MY FREE NEWSLETTER 👉 https://cryptolark.co/WEALTHMASTERY💎 BITCOIN INVESTING COURSE 👉 https://cryptolark.co/BTCCOURSE🔑 ALTCOIN...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PayPal to Stop Crypto Purchases in UK Until 2024]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75523e679d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/08/16/paypal-to-stop-crypto-purchases-in-uk-until-2024/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T16:41:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Payments giant PayPal will temporarily pause crypto purchases in the United Kingdom until early 2024, the company said Wednesday, citing new rules by the country’s financial regulator.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PayPal Confirms It Is 'Pausing' Crypto Purchases for UK Customers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152627</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152627/paypal-confirms-pausing-cypto-purchases-uk-customers"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T16:26:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[British customers won't be able to buy crypto on PayPal as it navigates regulatory hurdles, the company confirmed Wednesday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The End of the End of Crypto]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7552397824</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/08/16/the-end-of-the-end-of-crypto/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T16:19:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Market sentiment is improving. And even the New York Times is fair-minded.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Kuhn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Slips to $29K, but Fundstrat's Tom Lee Sees $150K on ETF Approval]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7552397817</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/08/16/bitcoin-slips-to-29k-but-fundstrats-tom-lee-sees-150k-on-etf-approval/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T16:19:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Altcoins are leading declines, with majors like DOGE, SOL and MATIC shedding 6-7% in the past 24 hours.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to SCENE: Where Tech Meets Fashion, Art, and Entertainment]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152587</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152587/welcome-scene-where-tech-meets-fashion-art-entertainment"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T16:19:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Emerging technologies are reshaping mass culture faster than ever. SCENE will investigate and profile those shifts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Magazine Donates Third ‘Historic Cover’ to Ordinals Institute]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75523a522b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/bitcoin-magazine-donates-third-historic-cover-to-ordinals-institute"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T16:13:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An iconic Ordinal is being donated to the team that kickstarted the upstart protocol. 
Announced today, Bitcoin Magazine is gifting one of its 23 ‘Historic Covers,’ unique one-of-one Ordinals representing our print magazine’s original run, to the Open Ordinals Institute, a new non-profit dedicated to fostering development of the open-source Ordinals protocol. 
Launching at the beginning of August, the OOI is a registered 501(c)3 non-profit organization that plans to accept donations, including those in Ordinals, on behalf of the development team. 
This means that, a short few months after its debut, ‘Historic Ordinal #3’ is officially off the market. 
 
         
         
         
         
    
“We are proud that this prized collectible can give back to the team that has helped kickstart a new era of building on the Bitcoin blockchain,” said Namcios, Bitcoin Magazine Editor and project lead of its Ordinals OTC desk, Rare BTC. 
To date, Bitcoin Magazine’s Historic Covers have seen over 4.3 BTC in total volume, with our ‘Historic Cover #1’ selling for 1.25 BTC, worth over $30,000 at the time of sale. 
Since its January launch, the Ordinals protocol has caused no shortage of discussion in the Bitcoin community for its much-debated design trade-offs, most notably its ability to enable any arbitrary data to be stored in a bitcoin block and secured by the Bitcoin blockchain. 
Already, over 20 million ordinals have been minted using the protocol, a feat detractors say is bloating the blockchain. 
“We’re honored to receive one of the Bitcoin Magazine Historic Covers, a tangible piece of Bitcoin history,” said Erin Redwing, President of the Open Ordinals Institute. “As one of the first and most notable collections launched on the Ordinals protocol, these will stand the test of time. And how fitting that it’s a cover of the first Bitcoin ape!”
Bitcoin Magazine ‘Historic Covers’ are now for sale on popular secondary Ordinals markets, including Gamma and MagicEden.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Tokens Could Face Increased Scrutiny Amid SEC Targeting Of Artificial Intelligence]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75523b1697</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ai-tokens-could-face-scrutiny-from-sec/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T16:08:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI tokens have caught the attention of the US Securities and Exchange Commission, as its chair, Gary Gensler, highlighted potential conflicts of interest within the realm of artificial intelligence. 
 
In a series of posts on the social network X, Gensler acknowledged the transformative power of AI while expressing caution about its misuse by “bad actors” to manipulate capital markets. 
 
The statements underscore the SEC’s commitment to ensuring impartiality in technology-related matters, focusing on outcomes rather than the tools themselves.
 
 
We @SECGov are technology neutral. We focus on the outcomes, rather than the tool itself. Securities laws, though, may be implicated depending upon how AI tech is used. Within our current authorities, we’re focused on protecting against both the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biggest Movers: DOGE, XRP Fall to Multi-Week Lows, as Bearish Sentiment Intensifies]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75523b313f</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/biggest-movers-doge-xrp-fall-to-multi-week-lows-as-bearish-sentiment-intensifies/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T16:08:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin dropped to a one-month low on Wednesday, as a red wave swept through cryptocurrency markets. Bearish sentiment remained high as the session progressed, with the global market cap falling by nearly 2% today. XRP also plunged in today’s session.
 
Dogecoin (DOGE)
 
Dogecoin (DOGE) fell for a fourth straight session, as bears continue to regain momentum, following last week’s gains.
 
After peaking at $0.07407 on Tuesday, DOGE/USD dropped to an intraday low of $0.06893 earlier in the day.
 
As a result of this fall in price, dogecoin slipped to its lowest level since July 19, when price was at a bottom of $0.0682.
 
 
The decline comes following a downward crossover of the moving averages, which is also known as a death cross.
 
This week’s bearish momentum intensified after DOGE moved below a support point at $0.0730.
 
Additionally, the relative strength index (RSI) also edged lower, dropping to a reading of 39.10, its lowest in four weeks.
 
 
XRP
 
XRP, formerly ripple, also remained in the red on Wednesday, dropping to a multi-week low in the process.
 
XRP/USD bottomed out at $0.5918 earlier in today’s session, which comes following Tuesday’s high at $0.6275.
 
Similar to dogecoin above, today’s drop in price saw XRP move to its lowest point since mid-July.
 
 
One of the catalysts for the sell-off was a breakout of a support point at the 40.00 mark on the RSI indicator.
 
The index is now tracking at 36.76, which is its weakest point since May, a point when the price was hovering around $0.4600.
 
Bulls will hope to reject further drops in price, however will first need to drop below an upcoming floor at the 32.00 zone.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
What is behind today’s decline in price? Let us know your thoughts in the comments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Canada, Spot Bitcoin ETFs Have Been Working for Years]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7552258dab</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2023/08/16/in-canada-spot-bitcoin-etfs-have-been-working-for-years/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T15:52:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gorast Tasevski and Haan Palcu-Chang of Purpose Investments share thoughts about bitcoin ETFs – and Canada.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gorast Tasevski, Haan Palcu-Chang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Crypto Investors Should Care About Tokenomics: Crypto Long & Short]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7552258d9b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/08/16/why-crypto-investors-should-care-about-tokenomics/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T15:52:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Perceptions of token issuance by projects have changed dramatically during the crypto winter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Todd Groth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Machine Economy and the Convergence of Web3, AI and Fintech]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7552239797</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/08/16/the-machine-economy-and-the-convergence-of-web3-ai-and-fintech/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T15:12:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fintech, Web3, and artificial intelligence are one economic whole, and our ability to grow each relies on their deep synthesis, says Lex Sokolin, founder of Web3 investment fund Generative Ventures.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lex Sokolin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Authorities Uncover Massive $83 Million Filecoin Pyramid Scheme]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75522c0ebb</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/83-million-filecoin-pyramid-scheme/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T15:08:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[China is known for its clampdown on crypto-related activities in the country, and a recent development involving a Filecoin pyramid scheme could see the authorities move to intensify their efforts against the industry. 
 
Filecoin Miners Involved In $83 Million Fraud
 
Lai Mouhang and four other executives of Space-Time Cloud Company, a Filecoin mining service provider, are currently standing trial at the People’s Court of Pingnan County for spearheading a pyramid scheme that led them to amass over $83 million in illicit proceeds from their activities. 
 
 
According to a local report, the company was formed in 2018 by defendants Lai Mouhang and Lai Moujun, who later recruited fellow defendants Hu and Liang in 2019. 2019 also happens to be the same year the company kickstarted its fraudule…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Custodian BitGo Hits $1.75B Valuation After Latest Funding]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152676</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152676/crypto-custodian-bitgo-hits-1-75b-valuation-after-latest-funding"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T14:56:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the newly-raised funds, BitGo aims to meet a new demand for regulated crypto custody solutions and new acquisitions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2023 Centralized Crypto Exchange Study Highlights Winds of Change Among Top 10 Platforms]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75522878e1</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/2023-centralized-crypto-exchange-study-highlights-winds-of-change-among-top-10-platforms/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T14:37:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a report by the crypto market aggregation web portal Coingecko, Binance retains its crown in the centralized cryptocurrency exchange arena, but not without facing fierce competition and challenges.
 
Binance Leads But Not Without Contenders, Says Coingecko’s Mid-Year Crypto Study
 
According to the Coingecko research report, Binance continues to dominate the centralized cryptocurrency exchange market with a 51.7% share, boasting a spot trading volume of $235.3 billion in June 2023. However, researchers noted a significant drop from its March peak of $559.8 billion, suggesting possible weaknesses.
 
The research spotlighted Upbit’s perseverance, holding firm as the second-largest exchange. Despite a dip to a 6% market share in May 2023, Upbit rebounded with an 8.1% share by June, backed …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ledger Adds PayPal as On-Ramp for Bitcoin, Ethereum Purchases]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152674</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152674/ledger-adds-paypal-on-ramp-bitcoin-ethereum-purchases"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T14:28:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ledger users can now buy crypto through the Ledger Live App using PayPal, with direct storage to their hardware wallet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Update: Peter Todd Proposes Expiration Dates For BTC Addresses]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75521473db</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-peter-todd-expiration-date-btc-addresses/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T14:08:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a forward-thinking post to the Bitcoin-Dev mailing list, renowned Bitcoin Core developer and founder of OpenTimestamps, Peter Todd, has advanced the Bitcoin Improvement Proposal 352 (BIP-352) for integrating user-defined expiration dates to silent payment addresses in a bid to address concerns related to compromised or lost wallets.
 
Todd’s idea stems from a fundamental issue surrounding wallets that eventually fall into disuse. He postulates, “Wallets don’t last forever. They are often compromised or lost. When this happens, the addresses generated from those wallets become a form of toxic data: funds sent to those addresses can be easily lost forever.”
 
 
 #Bitcoin Update: @peterktodd suggests adding user-set expiration dates to $BTC addresses for silent payments. pic.twitter.com/zI…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Technical Analysis: BTC, ETH Hit 1-Week Lows Ahead of FOMC Minutes]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755210b885</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-ethereum-technical-analysis-btc-eth-hit-1-week-lows-ahead-of-fomc-minutes/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T13:37:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin neared a breakout below $29,000 on Wednesday, ahead of the release of anticipated Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC) minutes. The minutes will show the United States Fed’s reasoning behind its last rate hike, whilst also giving guidance on its future decisions. Ethereum dropped to a one-week low.
 
Bitcoin
 
Bitcoin (BTC) extended recent declines on Wednesday, as traders began to anticipate the upcoming FOMC minutes report.
 
BTC/USD fell to an intraday low of $29,061.95 earlier in today’s session, which comes after a high of $29,439.12 the day prior.
 
This drop sent bitcoin to its lowest point since August 7, when the price fell to a bottom of $28,660.
 
 
Bitcoin chart by TradingView
 

 
 

 
Wednesday’s decline comes despite an upward crossover taking place between the 10-day (red) and 25-day (blue) moving averages.
 
The relative strength index (RSI) did provide a bearish signal however, slipping towards a floor of 42.00
 
As of writing, the index is tracking at 44.49, which is also a seven-day low.
 
 
Ethereum
 
Additionally, ethereum (ETH) edged lower for a second straight session, as the cryptocurrency moved towards a floor of its own.
 
Following a high at $1,842.95 on Tuesday, ETH/USD dropped to an intraday low of $1,816.33 earlier today.
 
Like with bitcoin above, this plunge saw the world’s second largest cryptocurrency record a one-week low.
 
 
Ethereum chart by TradingView
 

 
 
Whilst the RSI on BTC was heading towards a floor, ethereum’s price strength broke out of its own support.
 
The index moved below a support level at 41.00, and is now tracking at 40.83, with the next visible point of support at 39.00.
 
Should this target be reached, ETH will likely be trading around the $1,780 mark.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
Do you expect ethereum to fall below $1,800 this week? Leave your thoughts in the comments below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Greenwashing': Gitcoin, Shell Sponsorship Draws Fire From Crypto Pundits]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152662</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152662/greenwashing-gitcoin-shell-partnership-draws-fire-crypto-pundits"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T13:33:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the center of the Gitcoin partnership is greenwashing, a slick marketing scheme some say Shell is employing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Mover Americas: Coinbase Secures NFA Approval to Offer Crypto Futures]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75521309aa</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/08/16/first-mover-americas-coinbase-secures-nfa-approval-to-offer-crypto-futures/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T13:20:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest price moves in bitcoin (BTC) and crypto markets in context for August 16, 2023. First Mover is CoinDesk’s daily newsletter that contextualizes the latest actions in the crypto markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lyllah Ledesma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Custodian Ledger to Let Users Buy Bitcoin, Ether Through PayPal Account]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7552130994</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/08/16/crypto-custodian-ledger-to-let-users-buy-crypto-through-paypal-account/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T13:20:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hardware wallet maker Ledger has partnered with payments giant PayPal to allow users to buy crypto in its Ledger Live app through their PayPal accounts, the companies announced Wednesday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Meta Engineer’s Layer-1 Blockchain Linera Riases $6M in New Funding]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7552130985</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/08/16/ex-meta-engineers-layer-1-blockchain-linera-riases-6m-in-new-funding/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T13:20:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The layer-1 blockchain’s initial seed funding round was led by a16z crypto and has now raised $12 million in total.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lyllah Ledesma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Lands Regulatory Approval to Offer Crypto Futures Trading in US]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152657</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152657/coinbase-lands-regulatory-approval-to-offer-crypto-futures-in-us"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T11:30:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The exchange has secured approvals from the NFA and CFTC to start offering regulated crypto futures trading for its customers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trading Volumes for Newly Launched SEI Token Topped $1B in One Day]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152651</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152651/trading-volumes-newly-launched-sei-token-topped-1b-one-day"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T10:30:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trading volumes for the new SEI token nearly outpaced market heavyweights like Bitcoin, Ethereum, and XRP on top crypto exchanges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prosecutors Aim to Use Caroline Ellison’s Personal Notes as Evidence Against SBF]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152650</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152650/prosecutors-use-caroline-ellisons-personal-notes-evidence-against-sbf"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T10:18:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A list of “Things Sam is Freaking Out About” has been cited by the prosecutors, which they hope to include as evidence in the upcoming trial.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adidas and BAPE Team for Ultra-Limited Sneakers With Digital Twins]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152638</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152638/adidas-bape-team-ultra-limited-sneakers-digital-twins"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T23:19:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just 100 pairs of the Adidas Originals Triple-White Forum 84 BAPE Low will be auctioned via NFT passes, which can be redeemed for the kicks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephanie Hirschmiller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Silvergate CEO Departs With Benefits as Bank Shutdown Continues]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152635</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152635/silvergate-ceo-departs-with-benefits-as-bank-shutdown-continues"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T22:48:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CFO is shipping out at the end of September, leaving only the former chief risk officer at the helm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google and iCAD to Harness AI in Cancer Detection and Care]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152630</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152630/google-health-icad-ai-cancer-profound-detection"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T22:37:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence can drastically increase the efficiency of cancer screening methods, sparking a joint effort between iCAD and Google.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump Crypto Wallet Holds Over $5 Million, New Filings Show]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152628</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152628/donald-trump-crypto-wallet-holds-over-5-million-new-filings-show"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T21:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The former president’s holdings make him a ‘whale’ despite his past skepticism about cryptocurrencies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stellar Invests in MoneyGram in Bid to Be a ‘Digital-Forward’ FinTech Leader]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152598</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152598/stellar-invests-in-moneygram-in-bid-to-become-a-digital-forward-leader-in-fintech"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T20:44:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The two money movers have been working together for years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Art Blocks to Block Art: Snowfro Gets Physical With 'Heart + Craft']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152604</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152604/from-art-blocks-to-block-art-snowfro-gets-physical-with-heart-craft"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T20:32:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Erick Calderon's affordable Arbitrum NFT collab with Prohibition's Jordan Lyall has a personal edge—and a physical expression.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Republicans Blast SEC For 'Shady' Prometheum Broker Approval]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152602</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152602/republicans-blast-sec-for-shady-prometheum-broker-approval"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T20:14:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[House Republicans believe the SEC's approval of Prometheum may have been politically orchestrated.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Actors Union Agreement That Includes AI Rules Is ‘Not a Waiver,’ Director Says]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152600</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152600/actors-union-agreement-that-includes-ai-stipulations-is-not-a-waiver-director-clarifies"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T19:52:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SAG-AFTRA Executive Director Duncan Crabtree-Ireland explained how the current deal offer addresses the use of artificial intelligence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Degens Are Betting on Whether Trump Will Smile for His Mugshot in Georgia]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152589</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152589/degens-betting-trump-smile-mugshot-georgia"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T18:48:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former President Donald Trump and 18 allies were indicted on racketeering charges in Georgia. "We’ll have a mugshot ready for you," the local sheriff says.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaramucci's SkyBridge 'Strongly Disagrees' With Grayscale on Bitcoin ETF]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152572</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152572/skybridge-anthony-scaramucci-grayscale-bitcoin-spot-etf-sec-applications"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T17:47:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SkyBridge claims that Coinbase should be more than adequate as a surveillance-sharing partner.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mired in Controversy, A Film Gives HEX and Richard Heart the Hollywood Treatment]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152557</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152557/documentary-film-gives-hex-richard-heart-hollywood-treatment"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T17:21:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“The Highest of Stakes,” a new documentary, attempts to give voice to advocates and critics of the controversial HEX founder. But how much is really up for debate?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zepeto, Jump Crypto Joint Venture ZTX Raises $13M for Metaverse Platform on Arbitrum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152574</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152574/zepeto-jump-crypto-raise-13-million-ztx-metaverse-arbitrum"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T17:08:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[South Korea's leading metaverse platform Zepeto is betting big on NFTs with its ZTX joint venture with Jump Crypto, which led the seed round.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephanie Hirschmiller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Helium Mobile Debuts Crypto Wireless Network in Miami—For $5 a Month]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152533</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152533/helium-mobile-debuts-crypto-wireless-network-miami-5-month"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T16:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Powered by the Helium network, the hybrid mobile carrier takes its first public steps with a cheap unlimited plan and crypto token rewards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Star Atlas CEO on Developing an MMO Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/WQCaahmH/star-atlas-ceo-on-developing-an-mmo-game</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/WQCaahmH/star-atlas-ceo-on-developing-an-mmo-game"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T13:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Jason Nelson speaks with Star Atlas Founder and CEO Michael Wagner about the MMO game's approach to development, marketing, and blockchain integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fintech in the Front, DeFi in the Back—Crypto's Quiet Revolution Is Underway]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152383</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152383/fintech-front-defi-back-cryptos-quiet-revolution-is-underway"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T12:11:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mainstream audiences may never know that the promise of crypto has finally been realized.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former FTX Exec Declines Testimony, Cites Fifth Amendment Rights]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152527</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152527/former-ftx-exec-declines-testimony-cites-fifth-amendment-rights"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T11:14:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Co-CEO of FTX Digital Markets will invoke his constitutional right against self-incrimination, opting to remain silent throughout the trial.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Singapore Financial Regulator Issues Key Requirements for Stablecoin Issuers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152517</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152517/singapore-financial-regulator-issues-key-requirements-stablecoin-issuers"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T10:14:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoins issued outside of Singapore or pegged to other currencies will still be subject to the existing token regulatory regime.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meme Coin Base DEX RocketSwap Hit by $866K Exploit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152519</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152519/meme-coin-base-dex-rocketswap-hit-866k-exploit"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T09:52:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The RocketSwap hackers then bridged the stolen amount back to Ethereum and created a meme coin with the loot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jacobi Asset Management Launch Europe's First Bitcoin ETF]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148433</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148433/jacob-asset-management-launch-europe-first-bitcoin-etf"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T07:01:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Europe's inaugural Bitcoin exchange-traded fund went live today on Euronext Amsterdam, beating the U.S. to the punch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance US Seeks Protective Order Against 'Fishing Expedition' by SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152513</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152513/binance-protective-order-sec-fishing-expedition"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T06:29:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto exchange says SEC discovery requests go far beyond the scope agreed upon in the consent order.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt AI, Edited by Ryan Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Custodian Prime Trust Files for Bankruptcy]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152508</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152508/prime-trust-chapter-11-bankruptcy"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T06:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A former Bank of Nevada president will oversee the Chapter 11 process, which may include the sale of all remaining Prime Trust assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt AI, Edited by Ryan Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Achieving the Singularity is 'All About Progress': AI Executive]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152496</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152496/the-singularity-ai-general-artificial-intelligence"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T00:23:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The arrival of the pivotal moment for civilization may arrive ahead of schedule, says SingularityNET COO Janet Adams.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix Starts Streaming Video Games—Here's Why It's a Big Deal]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152490</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152490/netflix-now-streaming-video-games-heres-why-big-deal"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T23:11:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gaming is an enormous industry, and streaming giant Netflix could fuel even further growth by serving on-demand games via nearly any device.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Are 5 Games Building on Ethereum Scaler Immutable zkEVM]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152481</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152481/games-building-on-ethereum-scaler-immutable-zkevm"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T23:02:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Immutable zkEVM's testnet launched today. From strategy games to shooters, here are five of the biggest NFT games coming to the network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried Used $100 Million in Stolen Cash for Political Donations, DOJ Alleges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152483</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152483/sam-bankman-fried-stolen-customer-funds-political-donations-democrats-republicans"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T22:31:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Justice Department claims the disgraced crypto mogul used client funds to “influence cryptocurrency regulation.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FDIC Highlights 'Novel and Complex' Crypto Risks in Annual Review]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152484</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152484/fdic-cryptocurrency-novel-complex-risks"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T22:26:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was the first time the bank regulator dedicated a section to digital assets in its regular risk report.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Sleuth ZachXBT Avoids Lawsuit After Backing Off Claims Against NFT Trader]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152463</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152463/crypto-sleuth-zachxbt-avoids-lawsuit-after-backing-off-claims-against-nft-trader"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T19:26:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jeffrey "Machi Big Brother" Huang has withdrawn his defamation suit against ZachXBT, but only after the sleuth softened his published accusations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Institutional Investors Continue to Bet Big on XRP Following Ripple's Partial SEC Win]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152421</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152421/institutional-investors-continue-bet-big-xrp-following-ripple-partial-sec-win"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T18:50:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Major investors are still showing interest in XRP, pouring cash into it for the 16th week running per data from CoinShares.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Claude AI Developer Anthropic Raises $100M From South Korean Telco Giant SK]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152450</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152450/claude-ai-developer-anthropic-raises-100-million-from-south-korean-telecom-sk"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T18:12:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic’s war chest gets a bit bigger, as firms line up to bet on the OpenAI rival.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miner Hut 8 Shares Plummet 8% After Disappointing Q2 Revenue Figures]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152455</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152455/bitcoin-miner-hut-8-shares-down-58-percent-after-disappointing-quarter"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T17:43:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since last year, Hut 8 has been squeezed between operational issues and rising Bitcoin network difficulty.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aurory's Origin Story: How JRPGs Inspired the Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/O0S201TB/aurorys-origin-story-how-jrpgs-inspired-the-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/O0S201TB/aurorys-origin-story-how-jrpgs-inspired-the-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T16:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Jason Nelson talks to Aurory's Head of Marketing and Business Development Michael Natoli about the origins of the Aurory crypto games at the Solana PlayGG event.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FarmVille Creator Zynga Reveals First Ethereum NFT Game: Sugartown]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152425</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152425/farmville-creator-zynga-reveals-first-ethereum-nft-game-sugartown"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T16:48:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The casual and mobile publisher behind FarmVille and Words With Friends will launch the Ethereum-based Sugartown later this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Parallel TCG: Inside the Sci-Fi Card Game’s Closed Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/q8YVWJh4/parallel-tcg-inside-the-sci-fi-card-games-closed-beta</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/q8YVWJh4/parallel-tcg-inside-the-sci-fi-card-games-closed-beta"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T15:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin goes hands-on with Parallel’s closed beta on Windows PC to find out what sets it apart from other crypto card-battlers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 Games Need to Compete with All Games, Says Solana Foundation GM]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ud9wTd4s/web3-games-need-to-compete-with-all-games-says-solana-foundation-gm</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ud9wTd4s/web3-games-need-to-compete-with-all-games-says-solana-foundation-gm"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T19:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Foundation's General Manager of Games Johnny Lee tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about Solana's PlayGG conference and shares his take on crypto gaming and the "play-to-earn" concept.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Many Early Blockchain Games Were 'Cash Grabs,' Says Twitch Streamer Alliestrasza]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BA4yE45A/many-early-blockchain-games-were-cash-grabs-says-twitch-streamer-alliestrasza</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BA4yE45A/many-early-blockchain-games-were-cash-grabs-says-twitch-streamer-alliestrasza"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T16:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["I wrote them off," Twitch streamer Alliestrasza said of her initial thoughts on many early blockchain games. She tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how her perspective on Web3 games has evolved over time and now sees blockchain games getting significantly better.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['MetalCore' Game Preview: Hands-on With the 'Titanfall' Meets 'Destiny' NFT Mashup]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/tjK6i7lv/metalcore-game-preview-hands-on-with-the-titanfall-meets-destiny-nft-mashup</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/tjK6i7lv/metalcore-game-preview-hands-on-with-the-titanfall-meets-destiny-nft-mashup"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T19:46:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MetalCore is an upcoming mech shooter developed by Studio 369, and it's being developed on Ethereum scaling network Immutable zkEVM. Decrypt contributor Ryan Gladwin played through the prologue and tested out the recent Alpha 3 online experience to get a sense of the NFT-infused mashup of Titanfall and Destiny.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Give Projects a Chance,' Says Aurory's Michael Natoli on NFT Game Challenges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/nBNKKZdK/give-projects-a-chance-says-aurorys-michael-natoli-on-nft-game-challenges</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/nBNKKZdK/give-projects-a-chance-says-aurorys-michael-natoli-on-nft-game-challenges"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aurory is an NFT-driven game franchise that started life on Solana and is expanding to other chains. Decrypt's Jason Nelson spoke with Aurory Head of Marketing Michael Natoli at Solana's PlayGG event, where Natoli shared his thoughts on the challenges that blockchain games face in reaching players.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Is Only Network Ready for Gaming: Solana Foundation's Johnny Lee]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5OvV3ZXn/solana-is-only-network-ready-for-gaming-solana-foundations-johnny-lee</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5OvV3ZXn/solana-is-only-network-ready-for-gaming-solana-foundations-johnny-lee"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T17:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Foundation General Manager Johnny Lee tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how the Solana network will tackle the scaling problem that blockchain games pose for the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Com2uS Is Going "Full Speed" on Crypto Gaming: Kyu Lee]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pYMZRoYy/com2us-is-going-full-speed-on-crypto-gaming-kyu-lee</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pYMZRoYy/com2us-is-going-full-speed-on-crypto-gaming-kyu-lee"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kyu Lee is the President of game studio Com2uS USA. In an interview, he shares the studio's approach to Web3 and crypto gaming with Decrypt GG's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Discord Game with AI and Blockchain: 'Alchemy: Battle for Ankhos' Creative Lead Alex Finden]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mF18GHGo/building-a-discord-game-with-ai-and-blockchain-alchemy-battle-for-ankhos-creative-lead-alex-finden</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mF18GHGo/building-a-discord-game-with-ai-and-blockchain-alchemy-battle-for-ankhos-creative-lead-alex-finden"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T21:55:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Jason Nelson interviews Alchemy: Battle for Ankhos Creative Director Alex Finden at the Solana PlayGG event in San Diego, California.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Big Respect Between Ethereum and Cosmos Developer Communities': dYdX Foundation CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/XU5MbCGE/big-respect-between-ethereum-and-cosmos-developer-communities-dydx-foundation-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/XU5MbCGE/big-respect-between-ethereum-and-cosmos-developer-communities-dydx-foundation-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T13:24:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CEO of the dYdX Foundation Charles d'Haussy unpacks the decision behind moving one of the largest decentralized exchange protocol's over to its very own chain built on Cosmos. A key driver, he told Decrypt at this year's EthCC event, was that instead of launching on a rollup or another layer-1, launching a fully customized chain will allow dYdX to fine tune the network for its product's needs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Staking Solution Lido 'Had Perfect Product Market Fit' at Launch, Says DAO's Biz Dev Contributor]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/fUHhelhV/ethereum-staking-solution-lido-had-perfect-product-market-fit-at-launch-says-daos-biz-dev-contributor</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/fUHhelhV/ethereum-staking-solution-lido-had-perfect-product-market-fit-at-launch-says-daos-biz-dev-contributor"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T08:43:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marin Tvrdić, a business development contributor to the Lido DAO, sat down with Decrypt during this year's EthCC to break down how the liquid staking protocol has managed such a massive lead, how it plans to keep that lead, and the protocol's new dual-governance tokenomics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's Going to Stop All the DeFi Hacks? 'Standards,' Says OpenZepplin Security Architect]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/aYNuFdAi/whats-going-to-stop-all-the-defi-hacks-standards-says-openzepplin-security-architect</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/aYNuFdAi/whats-going-to-stop-all-the-defi-hacks-standards-says-openzepplin-security-architect"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T08:04:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenZeppelin's security solutions architect Michael Lewellen sat down with Decrypt to discuss how the industry can become a little safer for users at this year's EthCC Paris. The key? Introducing security standards across the industry so folks know what an audit actually means and where risks lie, be it bad faith actors or poor implementation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Ev.io' Game Review: Earn Solana While Blasting Enemies]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/2ZmkuhL2/evio-game-review-earn-solana-while-blasting-enemies</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/2ZmkuhL2/evio-game-review-earn-solana-while-blasting-enemies"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T22:21:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ev.io is a web-based first-person shooter that's free to play, but lets NFT holders earn in-game currency that can be redeemed for Solana (SOL). Decrypt contributor Ryan Gladwin shares his review of the fun throwback to Quake-style blasting, albeit with a modern crypto twist.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Moving Fast and Breaking Things Isn't the Web3 Ethos': MetaMask Product Lead]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/l1EbLgl3/moving-fast-and-breaking-things-isnt-the-web3-ethos-metamask-product-lead</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/l1EbLgl3/moving-fast-and-breaking-things-isnt-the-web3-ethos-metamask-product-lead"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T15:45:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Account abstraction this, smart wallets that. Discussions at EthCC Paris about improving user experience have pointed at industry leader MetaMask as an example of what not to do. But that may soon change, with a host of updates and optimizations coming to crypto's number one wallet, said its product lead Alex Jupiter. It still may take some time, though, before these changes take effect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling Smart Wallets on Starknet 'Was The Winning Combination', Says Argent Co-Founder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/gnBsxw4D/scaling-smart-wallets-on-starknet-was-the-winning-combination-says-argent-co-founder</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/gnBsxw4D/scaling-smart-wallets-on-starknet-was-the-winning-combination-says-argent-co-founder"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T07:35:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Argent co-founder Julien Niset told Decrypt at EthCC Paris that he wants to make crypto wallets disappear. Or at least how they're currently conceived. From clunky seed phrases to a stiff user experience, Argent hopes to make using crypto a little less intimidating and a whole lot more fun.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Mighty Action Heroes' Open Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/litL6kKs/inside-mighty-action-heroes-open-beta</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/litL6kKs/inside-mighty-action-heroes-open-beta"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T18:23:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mighty Action Heroes is the flagship blockchain title from Mighty Bear Games. But is the browser-based battle royale shooter worth checking out? Decrypt's Kate Irwin offers her thoughts and a first look at the upcoming game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>