<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-02-16T23:17:23.089Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-02-16T23:17:23.089Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bankman-Fried $250M Bond Is a ‘Joke,’ Claims Securities Lawyer]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75c3ca9d4d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/02/16/bankman-fried-250m-bond-a-joke-claims-securities-lawyer/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T23:08:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“MetaLawMan” James Murphy says that in 30 years of experience he has “never seen anything this lenient in a situation” where someone has lost millions of dollars of users’ money.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fran Velasquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Flash loan exploit appears to be behind Platypus USD stablecoin attack]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/17658932/Flash-loan-exploit-appears-to-be-behind-Platypus-USD-stablecoin-attack</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/17658932/Flash-loan-exploit-appears-to-be-behind-Platypus-USD-stablecoin-attack"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T23:08:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The stablecoin from PlatypusDefi, Platypus USD, suddenly dropped over 52%, and the on-chain evidence points to a flashloan exploit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Changpeng Zhao Makes Stablecoin Prediction Following SEC’s Binance USD (BUSD) Enforcement Action]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/17658933/Changpeng-Zhao-Makes-Stablecoin-Prediction-Following-SECs-Binance-USD-BUSD-Enforcement-Action</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/17658933/Changpeng-Zhao-Makes-Stablecoin-Prediction-Following-SECs-Binance-USD-BUSD-Enforcement-Action"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T23:05:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CEO of crypto exchange giant Binance says investors may turn to non-US dollar-pegged and algorithmic stablecoins amid regulatory pressure on Binance USD (BUSD). During a Twitter Spaces AMA on Feb. 14th, Changpeng Zhao explains why USD-pegged stablecoins are widely used. “Stablecoins are...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 5 Meme Coins To Keep An Eye On In The Next Bull Run]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75c3cb21fc</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/top-5-meme-coins-bull-run/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T23:04:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the last bull run, and even into this year, meme coins have shown themselves to be formidable contenders in the crypto market. The gains from these digital assets with seemingly no utility have created their own fair share of millionaires. Now, while these assets are riskier to invest in due to their much higher volatility, they still get a lot of attention from investors. So here are five meme coins to keep an eye on going into the next bull run.
 
Dogecoin (DOGE) 
Dogecoin (DOGE) is the OG meme coin. Without DOGE, the whole idea of meme coins would not exist, and neither would they be seeing as many gains as they have. Dogecoin caught the eye of billionaire and SpaceX CEO Elon Musk who said it was his favorite cryptocurrency.
 
Related Reading: Bestselling Finance Author Says Bitcoi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Best Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Analyst Advises Followers To ‘Erase Context, Trade Price’, Calls Bitcoin to $30,000–$35,000]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/17658934/Top-Analyst-Advises-Followers-To-Erase-Context-Trade-Price-Calls-Bitcoin-to-3000035000</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/17658934/Top-Analyst-Advises-Followers-To-Erase-Context-Trade-Price-Calls-Bitcoin-to-3000035000"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T23:01:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A widely followed analyst says recent regulatory concerns from the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) will only strengthen the crypto ecosystem. Crypto analyst Michaël van de Poppe tells his 648,200 Twitter followers that the SEC’s recent crackdowns represent a huge hit on crypto, but...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 5 Meme Coins To Keep An Eye On In The Next Bull Run]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/17658928/Top-5-Meme-Coins-To-Keep-An-Eye-On-In-The-Next-Bull-Run</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/17658928/Top-5-Meme-Coins-To-Keep-An-Eye-On-In-The-Next-Bull-Run"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T23:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the last bull run, and even into this year, meme coins have shown themselves to be formidable contenders in the crypto market. The gains from these digital assets with seemingly no utility have created their own fair share of millionaires. Now, while these assets are riskier to invest in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bankman-Fried $250M Bond Is a ‘Joke,’ Claims Securities Lawyer]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/17658887/Bankman-Fried-250M-Bond-Is-a-Joke-Claims-Securities-Lawyer</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/17658887/Bankman-Fried-250M-Bond-Is-a-Joke-Claims-Securities-Lawyer"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T22:51:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“MetaLawMan” James Murphy says that in 30 years of experience he has “never seen anything this lenient in a situation” where someone has lost millions of dollars of users’ money.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC To Sue Firm Behind Failed Terra Stablecoin, Terraform Labs]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75c3b5a673</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/sec-sue-terraform-labs/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T22:45:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nearly a year after the demise of Terra and it’s UST stablecoin, the SEC is in pursuit. It’s the latest in a suite of regulatory hammers that the Securities and Exchange Commission has been bringing to the pavement in crypto lately.
 
Terraform Labs once operated what was considered the dominant decentralized stablecoin UST – and was building a robust defi ecosystem before the cards collapsed in the first half of 2022. While Terraform Labs co-founder and CEO Do Kwon maintained his innocence on public platforms, crediting Terra’s downfall to that of a targeted attack on the network, the SEC will look to present a formidable challenge for Kwon and company to present their case – arguably for the first time yet.
 
The SEC’s Suit: What We Know 
A press release from the commission that hit the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taylor Scott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin price derivatives look a bit overheated, but data suggests bears are outnumbered]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/17658866/Bitcoin-price-derivatives-look-a-bit-overheated-but-data-suggests-bears-are-outnumbered</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/17658866/Bitcoin-price-derivatives-look-a-bit-overheated-but-data-suggests-bears-are-outnumbered"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T22:41:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bullish BTC traders are using excessive leverage, but bears’ reluctance to fight back could extend the current Bitcoin price rally.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TrueFi token clocks triple digit gain as Binance mints TUSD stablecoin]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/17658869/TrueFi-token-clocks-triple-digit-gain-as-Binance-mints-TUSD-stablecoin</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/17658869/TrueFi-token-clocks-triple-digit-gain-as-Binance-mints-TUSD-stablecoin"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T22:40:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TRU popped over 145% after Binance minted $50 million in TUSD.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Senator Calls for Comprehensive Crypto Regulation to Protect Consumers]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75c3b6ba67</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/us-senator-calls-for-comprehensive-crypto-regulation-to-protect-consumers/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T22:37:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The chairman of the U.S. Senate Committee on Banking, Housing, and Urban Affairs, Sherrod Brown, has called for a comprehensive regulatory framework for cryptocurrencies. “Recent crypto meltdowns have made clear that we need a comprehensive framework to regulate crypto products to protect consumers and our financial system,” said the senator.
 
US Lawmaker Wants Comprehensive Regulatory Framework for Crypto
 
U.S. Senator Sherrod Brown (D-OH), chairman of the Senate Committee on Banking, Housing, and Urban Affairs, talked about crypto regulation Tuesday in his opening statement at the congressional hearing titled “Crypto Crash: Why Financial Safeguards are Needed for Digital Assets.”
 
“The cryptocurrency industry has imploded,” the senator began, noting that the crypto market lost $1.46 t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC To Sue Firm Behind Failed Terra Stablecoin, Terraform Labs]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/17658831/SEC-To-Sue-Firm-Behind-Failed-Terra-Stablecoin-Terraform-Labs</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/17658831/SEC-To-Sue-Firm-Behind-Failed-Terra-Stablecoin-Terraform-Labs"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T22:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nearly a year after the demise of Terra and it’s UST stablecoin, the SEC is in pursuit. It’s the latest in a suite of regulatory hammers that the Securities and Exchange Commission has been bringing to the pavement in crypto lately. Terraform Labs once operated what was considered the dominant...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi platforms can comply with regulations without compromising privacy — Web3 exec]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/17658832/DeFi-platforms-can-comply-with-regulations-without-compromising-privacy-Web3-exec</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/17658832/DeFi-platforms-can-comply-with-regulations-without-compromising-privacy-Web3-exec"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T22:32:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zero knowledge proofs, DIDs, and more could help DeFi protocols maintain regulatory compliance without exposing their users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The IRS Are Looking at Your Crypto More Than Ever Before]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/17658865/The-IRS-Are-Looking-at-Your-Crypto-More-Than-Ever-Before</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/17658865/The-IRS-Are-Looking-at-Your-Crypto-More-Than-Ever-Before"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T22:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US Government has never paid more attention to your crypto taxes. Filing them is often more complicated than you think.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Devs Found Critical Bug Ahead Of Major Upgrade]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75c3b1e3cb</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-devs-found-bug-ahead-of-major-upgrade/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T22:15:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marius VanDerWijden, a core developer at Ethereum’s upcoming Shanghai-Capella upgrade, reported a bug found on testnet Zhejiang. VanDerWijden stated:
 

The last 4 and a half stressful hours of debugging culminated in this amazing bug fix. We got reports that geth nodes wouldn’t sync the Zhejiang devnet correctly. The issue was that if a block body was empty  (no tx, no withdrawals) we wouldn’t initialize it correctly
 
 
Ethereum Keeps Improving Ahead Of Its Network Upgrade
 
According to Ethereum’s core developer Tim Beiko, this bug can be “patched quickly.” He also said it’s an “easy” test for the developers. In addition, the developers will be adding a Hive test for this case.
 
The goal of the Zhejiang testnet is to stress test withdrawals and BLS, a digital signature scheme used to p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking: SEC sues Do Kwon and Terraform Labs for fraud]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/17658777/Breaking-SEC-sues-Do-Kwon-and-Terraform-Labs-for-fraud</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/17658777/Breaking-SEC-sues-Do-Kwon-and-Terraform-Labs-for-fraud"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T22:14:54.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CleanSpark Acquires 20,000 Bitcoin Miners For New Facilities]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75c3b2dbff</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/cleanspark-acquires-20000-bitcoin-miners"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T22:09:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new miners will contribute to CleanSpark’s ongoing expansion, just as the Bitcoin market ramps up.
CleanSpark Inc. has purchased 20,000 brand new Antminer S19j Pro+ units, the latest generation of Bitmain’s bitcoin mining machines, for $43.6 million. After coupons, the company will pay $32.3 million, according to the press release sent to Bitcoin Magazine.
This purchase is expected to expand the company's bitcoin production capacity by 37%, adding 2.44 exahashes per second (EH/s) once installed. CleanSpark plans to deploy the fleet of new machines at its wholly-owned bitcoin mining locations in the USA with 15,000 of them planned for its Washington, Georgia, facility. There may be changes to that allocation, depending on the state of development of the site and the pace of order fulfillment by the manufacturer, the release states.
Zach Bradford, CEO of CleanSpark, said, "Building and owning our mining campuses at multiple locations provides us with a level of agility and reliability that cannot be achieved otherwise. As machines are delivered to us, we will have rackspace waiting for them at one of our sites. This is the advantage of proprietary mining or the 'prop mining' model. We exercise tremendous control over our infrastructure and, therefore, our ability to be highly efficient in the way we allocate our resources."
CleanSpark's capital management strategy includes selling a major portion of its mined bitcoins to reinvest in growth, manifesting in the form of these expansions. The Pro+ is more power-efficient and 22% more productive than the popular Antminer S19j Pro model and will be shipped in batches, with deliveries starting as early as next month. All batches are expected to be delivered to the company's mining campuses by the end of May 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BtcCasey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Sues Terraform Labs, Do Kwon for Misleading Investors on TerraUSD Stablecoin: Bloomberg]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75c3b308dc</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/02/16/sec-set-to-sue-terraform-labs-do-kwon-for-misleading-investors-on-terrausd-stablecoin-bloomberg/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T22:08:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The collapse of TerraUSD last year led to wave of bankruptcies in the crypto industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nelson Wang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Devs Found Critical Bug Ahead Of Major Upgrade]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/17658750/Ethereum-Devs-Found-Critical-Bug-Ahead-Of-Major-Upgrade</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/17658750/Ethereum-Devs-Found-Critical-Bug-Ahead-Of-Major-Upgrade"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T22:07:06.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US SEC files fraud lawsuit against Terraform Labs and Do Kwon]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/17658748/US-SEC-files-fraud-lawsuit-against-Terraform-Labs-and-Do-Kwon</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/17658748/US-SEC-files-fraud-lawsuit-against-Terraform-Labs-and-Do-Kwon"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T22:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US SEC has charged Do Kwon and Terraform Labs for committing securities fraud The SEC has also pressed fraud charges in relation to Chai payments The United States Securities and Exchanges Commission (SEC) has made yet another move in the stablecoin market. This time around, the regulator is...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Binance Moved $400 Million To CZ Owned Trading Firm]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/17658756/How-Binance-Moved-400-Million-To-CZ-Owned-Trading-Firm</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/17658756/How-Binance-Moved-400-Million-To-CZ-Owned-Trading-Firm"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T22:03:47.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Platypus DeFi faces flash loan attack, according to CertiK]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/17658752/Platypus-DeFi-faces-flash-loan-attack-according-to-CertiK</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/17658752/Platypus-DeFi-faces-flash-loan-attack-according-to-CertiK"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T22:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The market maker is used to swap stable coins on the Avalanche blockchain; it has a total locked value of $46 million, according to DefiLlama.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC charges Terraform and Do Kwon post Terra collapse]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/17658757/SEC-charges-Terraform-and-Do-Kwon-post-Terra-collapse</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/17658757/SEC-charges-Terraform-and-Do-Kwon-post-Terra-collapse"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T22:01:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC charged Terraform Labs and its CEO on Thursday, following a string of crypto-related enforcement actions over the past few weeks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UNDER ATTACK Cardano ADA 🤯 | US Crypto Industry under MASSIVE ATTACK | Major Binance News!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/17658776/UNDER-ATTACK-Cardano-ADA-US-Crypto-Industry-under-MASSIVE-ATTACK-Major-Binance-News</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/17658776/UNDER-ATTACK-Cardano-ADA-US-Crypto-Industry-under-MASSIVE-ATTACK-Major-Binance-News"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T22:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano is under attack, Binance might be getting ready to pay a fine and settle with the DOJ, and Bitcoin had its highest single day candle in 6 months. The US Crypto industry is under attack, and Square Enix partners with Polygon. 🚀Find the most undervalued gems, up-to-date research, and NFT...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Private, Secure Texting Disrupts iMessage | Shane Mac]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/17658747/Private-Secure-Texting-Disrupts-iMessage-Shane-Mac</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/17658747/Private-Secure-Texting-Disrupts-iMessage-Shane-Mac"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T22:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin mining report: Feb. 16]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/17658725/Bitcoin-mining-report-Feb-16</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/17658725/Bitcoin-mining-report-Feb-16"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T21:58:49.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Sues Terraform Labs, Do Kwon for Misleading Investors on TerraUSD Stablecoin]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/17658751/SEC-Sues-Terraform-Labs-Do-Kwon-for-Misleading-Investors-on-TerraUSD-Stablecoin</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/17658751/SEC-Sues-Terraform-Labs-Do-Kwon-for-Misleading-Investors-on-TerraUSD-Stablecoin"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T21:57:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The collapse of TerraUSD last year led to wave of bankruptcies in the crypto industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USP Stablecoin Loses Dollar Peg as DeFi Protocol Platypus Suffers $8.5M Attack]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75c3bca049</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/02/16/usp-stablecoin-loses-dollar-peg-as-defi-protocol-platypus-suffers-85m-attack/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T21:56:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The flash loan attack caused Platypus Finance’s native stablecoin to fall to 48 cents from $1. The potential loss is $8.5 million, according to blockchain security firm CertiK.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Multi-Chain Future: Rarible Adds New Support For Tezos And Polygon NFTs]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75c3bcde3f</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/multi-chain-future-rarible-tezos-and-polygon-nfts/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T21:54:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sure, Ethereum is still the NFT market share leader, but there’s an ever-present ‘multi-chain future’ discussion among the NFT space. NFT marketplace leader OpenSea has exhibited open arms to this concept, adding support for chains like Polygon and Avalanche.
 
It doesn’t just stop and start with OpenSea, either: the once Solana-dedicated NFT marketplace Magic Eden has been branching out, including support for Polygon NFTs. While not cross-chain (at least, yet), Ethereum-dedicated no-fee platform Blur has launched it’s own Ethereum-based platform token, causing quite a stir this week.
 
And now Rarible, another major longtime NFT marketplace, is expanding to a more multi-chain future as well – announcing new tools of support for Tezos and Polygon NFTs this week.
 
Runnin’ With Rarible 
Rar…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taylor Scott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will 2023 See Continued Growth in Stablecoins?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75c3bceec5</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/coins/will-2023-see-continued-growth-in-stablecoins/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T21:54:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Stablecoins  
have emerged as an increasingly popular investment option in the cryptocurrency  
industry in recent years. These digital assets are intended to maintain a  
stable value, usually pegged to a fiat currency such as the US dollar, and have  
become an appealing alternative for investors looking to reduce volatility and  
risk in their portfolios. </p><p>In this  
article, we will look at the increasing popularity of stablecoin investments as  
well as their role in the cryptocurrency industry. </p><p>What  
are Stablecoins?</p><p>Stablecoins are  
a type of cryptocurrency that is intended to have a consistent value. They  
accomplish this by being linked to the value of a fiat currency, commodity, or  
cryptocurrency. </p><p>Tether (USDT),  
USD Coin (USDC), and Binance USD …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Finance Magnates Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bankman-Fried Remains Out on Bond, but Judge Warns ‘Revocation’ Proceedings Possible in Future]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75c3bf85eb</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/02/16/bankman-fried-remains-out-on-bond-but-judge-warns-revocation-proceedings-possible-in-future/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T21:36:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried remains out on bail, but the New York judge overseeing his criminal fraud case said that could change if the former FTX CEO continues to defy the bail conditions set by the court.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cheyenne Ligon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong Announces World’s First Crypto Green Bond]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75c3bfc543</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/hong-kong-announces-worlds-first-crypto-green-bond/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T21:34:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While the crypto industry is currently undergoing regulatory scrutiny from U.S. authorities, some regions, such as Hong Kong, have shown continued interest in the underlying potential of blockchain technology. 
 
Related Reading: Hong Kong to Limit Retail Investors’ Crypto Trading to Only ‘Highly Liquid’ Assets
 
Earlier today, the Hong Kong Special Administrative Region (HKSAR) Government of the People’s Republic of China announced the successful sale of the world’s first-ever tokenized green bond.
 
Hong Kong Becomes World’s First Tokenized Green Bond Issuer 
 
Hong Kong has been demonstrating interest in the potential of blockchain. According to the latest report, the Hong Kong government was able to sell approximately 800 million HK dollars worth roughly $102 million of tokenized green…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Starbucks Polygon NFTs Are Already Selling for Thousands]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=121552</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/121552/starbucks-polygon-nfts-already-selling-thousands"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T21:29:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Early Starbucks Odyssey users are already flipping the free NFT stamps for nearly $2,000 apiece ahead of the platform's public rollout.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uzbekistan Allows Foreign Firms to Deposit Funds From Crypto Trading, Restricts Other Operations]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75c3bb44bb</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/uzbekistan-allows-foreign-firms-to-deposit-funds-from-crypto-trading-restricts-other-operations/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T21:09:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Central Bank of Uzbekistan has permitted foreign-based businesses to open domestic bank accounts and deposit funds received from cryptocurrency trading. These companies will also be able to transfer the money abroad, but operations in the country will be restricted.
 
Uzbekistan Updates Rules for Operations With Proceeds From Crypto Exchange Transactions
 
The Central Bank of the Republic of Uzbekistan has adopted amendments to its regulations for foreign exchange transactions that concern non-resident legal entities, including those working with cryptocurrencies. In particular, they are now allowed to have accounts at local banks but the options to operate with funds coming from cryptocurrency trading are narrow.
 
According to the new rules, money transferred from foreign accounts of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lubomir Tassev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Compute North’s Reorganization Plan Approved By Bankruptcy Judge]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75c3a4342d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/02/16/compute-norths-reorganization-plan-approved-by-bankruptcy-judge/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T21:02:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The hosting firm, one of North America’s largest, settled $250 million in secured debt and settled with about 11 companies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliza Gkritsi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CFTC Charges California Firm and CEO With Fraud, Misappropriation of Digital Assets]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75c3a4341b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/02/16/cftc-charges-california-firm-and-ceo-with-fraud-misappropriation-of-digital-assets/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T21:02:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The commission alleges the defendants fraudulently solicited over $7 million worth of bitcoin and ether and misappropriated a portion of the funds in a Ponzi-like scheme.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nelson Wang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance US Moved $400M to Trading Firm Linked to CEO CZ: Reuters]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=121555</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/121555/binance-400m-silvergate-bank-trading-cz"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T20:49:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance moved huge sums of cash from U.S. partner to a trading firm linked to Binance CEO, bank records show.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[By The Numbers: How Have Inscriptions Affected Bitcoin Blocksize?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75c3a2ed72</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/the-numbers-inscriptions-affect-bitcoin-blocksize/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T20:10:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Inscriptions have increased the average size of the cryptocurrency’s blocks; here’s how this could impact the blockchain.
 
Impact Of Inscriptions On The Bitcoin Blocksize
 
Very recently, “Inscriptions” have emerged on the Bitcoin network, basically an application of the BTC blockchain similar to non-fungible tokens (NFTs), but not the same.
 
Unlike NFTs on other blockchains like Ethereum, these Inscriptions are directly inscribed on the Bitcoin blockchain (hence the name). Inscriptions can be data, images, audio, video, or even software.
 
Since they are directly stored as a transaction on the blockchain, they have been quickly inflating the size of the chain. This has made these assets a hotly debated topic around the community regarding their impact on the future of the crypto…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hououin Kyouma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Moved Funds From US Affiliate's Silvergate Bank Account in 2021: Reuters]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75c3ad4a8b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/02/16/binance-moved-funds-from-us-affiliates-silvergate-bank-account-in-2021-reuters/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T19:51:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto exchange]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blur Surpassed OpenSea in Daily NFT Trading Volume Wednesday, Nansen Shows]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75c3ad4a75</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/web3/2023/02/16/blur-surpassed-opensea-in-daily-nft-trading-volume-wednesday-nansen-shows/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T19:51:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NFT marketplace OpenSea’s dominance in the NFT ecosystem faces a growing challenge from Blur’s rapid ascent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sage D. Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wyoming Legislature Passes Bill Protecting Bitcoin Private Keys From Courts]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75c3a8e6de</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/legal/wyoming-legislature-bill-protecting-private-keys"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is now up to the governor of Wyoming to put the final stamp of approval on the landmark bill.
The U.S. state of Wyoming has passed a bill that protects its citizens from having to disclose their private keys, with a singular exception. Having now been approved by the state Senate and House of Representatives, it now simply needs to be signed by the Governor in order to take effect.
The bill states that, “No person shall be compelled to produce a private key or make a private key known to any other person in any civil, criminal, administrative, legislative or other proceeding in this state that relates to a digital asset, digital identity or other interest or right to which the private key provides access unless a public key is unavailable or unable to disclose the requisite information with respect to the digital asset, digital identity or other interest or right.” 
It does not specify that it would be only for Bitcoin keys, so it would also apply the same to private keys utilized as decentralized identities, or any other use cases. Wyoming has been the center of attention in regards to Bitcoin adoption in the U.S. for some time, partially because of Senator Cynthia Lummis’ ardent support of Bitcoin and push for regulation within the country. 
Christopher Allen, internet cryptography pioneer and executive director of Blockchain Commons who previously wrote for Bitcoin Magazine in regards to the importance of protecting private key sovereignty, described why Wyoming has been a groundbreaking state for this type of legislature.
 “[Wyoming] has a long tradition of ‘good fences make for good neighbors’... and as a small state it has a true ‘citizen’ legislature.… they resonate well with the concept of "Self-Sovereignty" in bitcoin and digital identity,” Allen told Bitcoin Magazine.
If approved by the governor, the bill would take effect on July 1, 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BtcCasey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Canada Close to Tightening Rules for Crypto Exchanges: Sources]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75c3a948b8</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/02/16/canada-close-to-tightening-rules-for-crypto-exchanges-sources/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T19:22:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Later this month, Canada’s umbrella markets regulator, the Canadian Securities Administrators (CSA), will tighten requirements for cryptocurrency exchanges operating in the country, according to two people who have been briefed on the plans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miner CleanSpark Buys 20,000 ASICs, Expands Capacity by 37%]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=121528</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/121528/bitcoin-miner-cleanspark-buys-20000-asics"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T18:53:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cleanspark's new rigs will bring its mining capacity to 2.8% of the entire Bitcoin network by the end of May.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NBA Top Shot Will Let Users Buy NFTs via Apple, Android Mobile Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=121542</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/121542/nba-top-shot-nfts-new-mobile-apps"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T18:30:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dapper Labs is pivoting to mobile—and working to help evolve Apple and Google’s approach towards NFTs and Web3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Says Client Assets Are 'Segregated and Secure' Following Proposed SEC Rule Change]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=121523</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/121523/coinbase-client-assets-segregated-secure-sec-rule-change"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T17:22:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase says it already provides the protections available to the clients of qualified custodians and supports the SEC’s proposal to require such protections.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will McCurdy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Words With Friends Creator Previews Wildcard NFT Game on Polygon]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=121509</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/121509/words-with-friends-creator-previews-wildcard-nft-game-polygon"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T17:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an exclusive interview, Paul Bettner tells Decrypt how Web3 tech makes the magic of his "ultimate video game spectator sport" possible.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Words with Friends' Creator Paul Bettner: Web3 Can Solve Twitch's Limitations]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IoXjnyLz/words-with-friends-creator-paul-bettner-web3-can-solve-twitchs-limitations</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IoXjnyLz/words-with-friends-creator-paul-bettner-web3-can-solve-twitchs-limitations"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T16:57:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paul Bettner tells Decrypt about the challenges he faced while developing his Web3 game "Wildcard."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Words with Friends' Creator Paul Bettner on Why He's Building His Next Game 'Wildcard' in Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/VyZ7d8zL/words-with-friends-creator-paul-bettner-on-why-hes-building-his-next-game-wildcard-in-web3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/VyZ7d8zL/words-with-friends-creator-paul-bettner-on-why-hes-building-his-next-game-wildcard-in-web3"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T16:57:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paul Bettner shares his perspective on Web3 gaming platforms and his vision to make games everywhere and anywhere players want them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Breaks Above $25,000 for the First Time in Eight Months]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=121527</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/121527/bitcoin-price-breaks-above-25000"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T16:47:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto traders are shrugging off regulators, it seems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Collab.Land Reveals Token Airdrop for Over 2 Million Users]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=121513</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/121513/collab-land-reveals-token-airdrop-for-over-2-million-users"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T16:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The token-gating tool used by over 43,000 DAO and NFT communities will distribute its new governance token to millions of eligible users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[G20 Financial Stability Board Report Flags DeFi 'Vulnerabilities']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=121495</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/121495/defi-may-repeat-amplify-vulnerabilities-traditional-finance-financial-stability-board"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T14:54:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The FSB's latest recommendations take aim at DeFi, suggesting that regulators include the niche in their monitoring frameworks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Norwegian Authorities Recoup $5.9M From Axie Infinity Ronin Hack]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=121501</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/121501/norwegian-authorities-recoup-5-9m-axie-infinity-ronin-hack"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T13:48:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Norwegian financial crimes agency Økokrim has tracked and seized a portion of the funds stolen in the Axie Infinity Ronin hack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Max Koopsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GQ Joins List of Legacy Media Outlets Boarding NFT Bandwagon]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=121492</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/121492/gq-joins-list-legacy-media-outlets-joining-nft-bandwagon"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T12:26:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Men’s magazine GQ is launching a new NFT collection, offering holders exclusive merchandise and access to its GQ3 community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will McCurdy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mango Markets Attacker Urges Court to Let Him Keep Hacked Funds]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=121487</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/121487/mango-markets-attacker-urges-court-let-him-keep-hacked-funds"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T11:37:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avraham Eisenberg's legal team has objected to a January lawsuit that would see him return $47 million to Mango Labs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FLOKI Continues Musk-Fueled Rally, Soaring 62% Overnight]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=121483</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/121483/floki-continues-musk-fueled-rally-soaring-overnight"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T11:07:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk tweeted a pic of his pet dog Floki yesterday and pumped the price of the eponymous cryptocurrency by nearly 70% overnight.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Expects to Pay Fines to Settle US Investigations: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=121478</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/121478/binance-expects-pay-fines-settle-us-investigations-report"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T10:48:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The world’s largest crypto exchange expects it will be able to settle ongoing regulatory investigations in the U.S.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘You Are the Art’: Chainspace NFT Portals Connect Bitcoin and Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=121452</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/121452/you-are-the-art-chainspace-nft-portals-connect-bitcoin-and-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T02:33:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like a Web3-native Snapchat filter or ASCII-based video feed, this experimental art project is minting NFT-based apps across chains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fortnite Esports Star Wins Bored Ape Yacht Club Challenge]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=121467</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/121467/fortnite-esports-mongraal-wins-bored-ape-yacht-club-dookey-dash-challenge"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T02:27:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The “Dookey Dash” Ethereum NFT racing game has been plagued by cheating claims.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blur Advises NFT Creators to Block OpenSea in Royalties Battle]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=121450</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/121450/blur-advises-nft-creators-to-block-opensea-in-royalties-battle"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T02:23:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Riding high on the success of its BLUR token airdrop, the marketplace announced a provocative policy change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Bankruptcy Judge Agrees Independent Examiner Would Mean More Risk]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=121461</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/121461/ftx-bankruptcy-judge-agrees-independent-examiner-risk-loss"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T02:16:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Every dollar spent in these cases on administrative expenses is $1 less to creditors,” said Judge John Dorsey.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hester Peirce Says SEC Crypto Custody Plan Involves 'Substantial Departure' From Status Quo]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=121458</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/121458/hester-peirce-says-sec-plan-involves-substantial-departure-from-status-quo"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T01:16:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC commissioner joins Crypto Twitter in picking apart her own agency’s latest crypto proposal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Crosses $24K as Ordinals Takes the Network by Storm]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=121443</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/121443/bitcoin-price-over-24000-ordinals-nft-inscriptions"/>
        <updated>2023-02-15T23:19:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New interest in Bitcoin has pushed the price to a six-month high.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ordinals Support Comes to Bitcoin-Based Web Wallet Xverse]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=121430</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/121430/ordinals-support-bitcoin-web-wallet-xverse"/>
        <updated>2023-02-15T21:25:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Hiro also prepping Bitcoin NFT support in its wallet, Ordinals' place in blockchain history seems secure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Bitcoin Is the Best Brand in Crypto': Why DeGods NFTs Are Now on Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=121420</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/121420/degods-bitcoin-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-02-15T21:12:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an interview with Decrypt, DeGods founders Frank and Kevin explain why 535 burned Solana NFTs were inscribed on Bitcoin—and what they plan to do with them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celsius Reaches Acquisition Agreement with NovaWulf]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=121421</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/121421/celsius-reaches-acquisition-agreement-with-novawulf"/>
        <updated>2023-02-15T20:39:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bankrupt crypto lender agreed to a buyout plan after vetting a handful other bids.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[El Salvador to Launch 'Bitcoin Embassy' in Texas]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=121416</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/121416/el-salvador-plans-bitcoin-embassy-in-texas"/>
        <updated>2023-02-15T19:51:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Central American nation opened a “Bitcoin office” in Switzerland last year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried Forced to Reveal Names of Bond Signers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=121411</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/121411/judge-orders-sam-bankman-fried-reveal-bond-signers"/>
        <updated>2023-02-15T19:20:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A judge has ordered that the names of SBF's co-signers be unsealed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenSea Halts Trading on Rihanna Music NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=121410</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/121410/opensea-halts-trading-rihanna-music-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-02-15T19:07:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NFT marketplace has taken issue with the collection launched by one of Rihanna’s producers, which offers holders a percentage of future song royalties.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Regulatory Crackdown Feels ‘Like a Crypto Carpet Bombing’: Blockchain Association CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=121399</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/121399/regulatory-crackdown-feels-crypto-carpet-bombing-blockchain-association-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-02-15T15:37:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CEO of the Blockchain Association criticized recent statements from both Congresswomen Elizabeth Warren and SEC Chair Gary Gensler.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will McCurdy,Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keanu Reeves: Criticism of Crypto 'Is Only Going to Make it Better']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=121359</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/121359/keanu-reeves-criticism-crypto-is-only-going-make-better"/>
        <updated>2023-02-15T15:13:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To dismiss crypto because of its volatility will strengthen it "in terms of how it's safeguarded," the star of "The Matrix" argued.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Funds Web3-Friendly Studio Superplastic in $20 Million Round]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=121321</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/121321/amazon-funds-web3-studio-superplastic-20-million-round"/>
        <updated>2023-02-15T15:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Superplastic has launched loads of wacky NFTs and characters, and now Amazon Studios get first dibs on them for TV shows or films.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lido Finance Kicks Off Yield Farming Event on Ethereum Scaler Optimism]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=121365</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/121365/lido-finance-kicks-off-yield-farming-event-on-ethereum-scaler-optimism"/>
        <updated>2023-02-15T14:56:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new 1 million OP token grant means Lido Finance users looking to earn some extra yield can do so by porting over to Optimism.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ECB Advises Banks Comply With Conservative Cap on Bitcoin Exposure]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=121377</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/121377/ecb-advises-banks-comply-conservative-cap-bitcoin-exposure"/>
        <updated>2023-02-15T14:03:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto assets like Bitcoin pose high risks and as such should be subject to limits on holdings, according to the ECB.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Final Fantasy Maker Square Enix to Launch NFT Game on Polygon]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=121324</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/121324/final-fantasy-maker-square-enix-to-launch-nft-game-on-polygon"/>
        <updated>2023-02-15T14:01:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Symbiogenesis, an original NFT-driven narrative game, will debut on the scaling network instead of on Ethereum’s mainnet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Napster Acquires Mint Songs to Advance Its Web3 Ambitions]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=121341</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/121341/napster-acquires-mint-songs-to-advance-its-web3-ambitions"/>
        <updated>2023-02-15T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The resurrected music brand is expanding its footprint to include digital collectibles.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano, Dogecoin Lead Recovery as Crypto Market Recoups $44B]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=121376</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/121376/cardano-dogecoin-lead-recovery-crypto-market"/>
        <updated>2023-02-15T13:16:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the wider market digests the latest CPI report, crypto markets have been energized by Cardano upgrades and Dogecoin memes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Max Koopsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Kansas Bill Could Cap Political Donations in Crypto at $100]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=121373</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/121373/new-kansas-bill-could-cap-political-donations-crypto-100"/>
        <updated>2023-02-15T12:25:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Political recipients that receive donations in crypto would be unable to spend these funds directly or hold them as assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will McCurdy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Insiders Served Subpoenas Over Fallen Crypto Exchange's Financial Dealings]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=121357</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/121357/ftx-insiders-served-subpoenas-fallen-crypto-exchange-financial-dealings"/>
        <updated>2023-02-15T10:48:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried, his father, and other insiders have been served subpoenas as part of the crypto exchange's bankruptcy proceedings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Dogecoin?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=5678</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/dogecoin-crypto-cryptocurrency-guide-how-to-buy-doge"/>
        <updated>2023-02-15T10:02:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin is a peer-to-peer cryptocurrency based on a popular Internet meme. The token started off as a joke, but it's become a serious proposition.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward,Stephen Graves,Wendy Clack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Over 100K Ordinals Minted on Bitcoin, Bringing Cheers and Network Congestion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=121343</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/121343/over-100k-ordinals-minted-on-bitcoin-bringing-celebrations-and-network-congestion"/>
        <updated>2023-02-15T06:56:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The newest crypto sensation has many flocking to the original blockchain bringing new projects and slow transactions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[As BUSD Dies, Tether’s USDT Soaks Up Another $1 Billion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=121327</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/121327/busd-usdt-tether-market-cap-1-billion"/>
        <updated>2023-02-15T01:42:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the fall of a top-three stablecoin, Tether is emerging as a clear winner.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoin Markets Pick Winners and Losers Ahead of SEC Paxos Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=121335</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/121335/stablecoin-markets-pick-winners-and-losers-ahead-of-sec-paxos-lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2023-02-15T01:24:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance USD's market cap has dropped to $15 billion, down 31% from its all-time high.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm Week in Review: SEC Targets Staking, a16z Doesn’t Get Its Way, NFTs Popping]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/8n9eV0em/gm-week-in-review-sec-targets-staking-a16z-doesnt-get-its-way-nfts-popping</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/8n9eV0em/gm-week-in-review-sec-targets-staking-a16z-doesnt-get-its-way-nfts-popping"/>
        <updated>2023-02-14T14:41:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In our February 11, 2023 week in review episode, Matthew Diemer, Stacy Elliott, and Stephen Graves talk about the latest developments in the FTX case, 3AC founders trying for a comeback, a16z losing on a big Uniswap vote despite holding 15 million UNI tokens, and NFTs roaring back with CryptoPunks, Bored Apes, and Ordinals NFTs selling hot. Watch and make sure to subscribe to the gm podcast on Apple or Spotify.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bill Murray Discusses NFT Project, First Members-Only Event]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/taYx1lPU/bill-murray-discusses-nft-project-first-members-only-event</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/taYx1lPU/bill-murray-discusses-nft-project-first-members-only-event"/>
        <updated>2023-02-03T20:18:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comedic legend Bill Murray sits down with Decrypt at his first exclusive party for NFT holders in Oceanside, California. He describes the project’s origins and why it didn’t feel “mercenary” for him to create an NFT-based membership club.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: Kristin Smith and the Crypto Crusade in Washington]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pGOBvJCf/gm-kristin-smith-and-the-crypto-crusade-in-washington</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pGOBvJCf/gm-kristin-smith-and-the-crypto-crusade-in-washington"/>
        <updated>2023-02-02T15:31:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kristin Smith is Executive Director of the Blockchain Association, which advocates for crypto policy in Washington D.C.—an exhausting effort that Sam Bankman-Fried was closely involved in, until he set it all on fire. Kristin tells Dan Roberts and Stacy Elliott how SBF and FTX set things back, but there are still positive signs from crypto friendly voices in Congress. Watch and make sure to subscribe to the gm podcast on Apple or Spotify.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: Week in Review: Tech Layoffs, Porsche NFTs, Ted Cruz]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DyY1w5XP/gm-week-in-review-tech-layoffs-porsche-nfts-ted-cruz</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DyY1w5XP/gm-week-in-review-tech-layoffs-porsche-nfts-ted-cruz"/>
        <updated>2023-01-28T19:38:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In our January 28, 2023 week in review episode, Dan Roberts, Matthew Diemer, and Kate Irwin talk about more layoffs in crypto and broader tech (including how Google botched its layoffs), the NFT market rebound and Porsche’s NFT drop (fail or surprise success?), Sam Bankman-Fried’s latest claims about FTX US and the surprising list of big companies on the FTX creditor list, and Ted Cruz’s weird effort to get DC vendors to accept Bitcoin. Watch and make sure to subscribe to the gm podcast on Apple or Spotify.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Web3 Is Disrupting Video Streaming: Myco, Theta Labs, and Actor David Bianchi]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Dvd0ep0Y/how-web3-is-disrupting-video-streaming-myco-theta-labs-and-actor-david-bianchi</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Dvd0ep0Y/how-web3-is-disrupting-video-streaming-myco-theta-labs-and-actor-david-bianchi"/>
        <updated>2023-01-27T13:16:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At an investor event in L.A. hosted by watch-to-earn video streaming platform Myco, Decrypt's Sander Lutz moderated a discussion about Film3 with Myco CCO Phil McKenzie, Theta Labs BD Head Andrea Berry, and actor and filmmaker David Bianchi, whose Web3 series "RZR" got funding through NFT drops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Web3 and NFTs Are Disrupting Film: Myco, Livepeer, Ava Labs, Bad Grrls Creative Club]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/hY2PHbfN/how-web3-and-nfts-are-disrupting-film-myco-livepeer-ava-labs-bad-grrls-creative-club</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/hY2PHbfN/how-web3-and-nfts-are-disrupting-film-myco-livepeer-ava-labs-bad-grrls-creative-club"/>
        <updated>2023-01-26T19:12:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At an investor event in New York hosted by the watch-to-earn video streaming platform Myco, Decrypt's Dan Roberts moderated a lively chat about Film3 with Phil McKenzie from Myco, Toni Thai Sterrett the founder of NFT member collective Bad Grrls Creative Club, Doug Petkanics the founder of decentralized video hosting platform Livepeer, and Daniel Killeen of Avalanche blockchain developer Ava Labs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Iron Man' Comic Artist Sean Chen on Marvel vs. Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JNudgCRf/iron-man-comic-artist-sean-chen-on-marvel-vs-web3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JNudgCRf/iron-man-comic-artist-sean-chen-on-marvel-vs-web3"/>
        <updated>2023-01-25T21:56:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marvel and DC Comics alum Sean Chen argues that while studios have made billions, comic artists aren't seeing even a fraction of that wealth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Marvel Artist Sean Chen on How Artificial Intelligence Will Shape Comics]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/8yvKCMey/marvel-artist-sean-chen-on-how-artificial-intelligence-will-shape-comics</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/8yvKCMey/marvel-artist-sean-chen-on-how-artificial-intelligence-will-shape-comics"/>
        <updated>2023-01-25T20:58:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Eventually there's still a human brain that needs to be involved," Chen said of AI being used to create comics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Actor David Bianchi Previews His Web3 TV Series 'RZR']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Y5LpgI64/actor-david-bianchi-previews-his-web3-tv-series-rzr</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Y5LpgI64/actor-david-bianchi-previews-his-web3-tv-series-rzr"/>
        <updated>2023-01-24T23:01:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Veteran actor David Bianchi spoke to Decrypt's Jason Nelson right before a public table read for Bianchi's upcoming drama series "RZR," to be distributed through Gala Films. The show is already greenlit and will be set in a dystopian future Los Angeles, with Ethereum and other digital assets as part of the plot. Bianchi also conducted two NFT drops to build engagement from fans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: Farokh and the Rug Radio Roadmap]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MBr4jEqP/gm-farokh-and-the-rug-radio-roadmap</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MBr4jEqP/gm-farokh-and-the-rug-radio-roadmap"/>
        <updated>2023-01-23T16:15:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Mr. NFT: @Farokh, who preaches daily to hundreds of thousands of NFT faithful, and is trying to building Rug Radio into a fully formed Web3 media company. Dan Roberts and Kate Irwin from the gm podcast talk to Farokh about Rug DAO and all things NFT culture. Watch and make sure to subscribe to the gm podcast on Apple or Spotify.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: Big Bold Predictions for Crypto in 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QKx0FpSV/gm-big-bold-predictions-for-crypto-in-2023</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QKx0FpSV/gm-big-bold-predictions-for-crypto-in-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-01-19T13:56:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Will Sam Bankman-Fried serve prison time? Who will be the next crypto company to go bankrupt, or the next founder to see their reputation dissolve? Will we get a new crypto law this year? Decrypt's Dan Roberts, Stacy Elliott, and Matthew Diemer of the gm podcast crew kicked off the new year by trading predictions for 2023. Watch and make sure to subscribe to the gm podcast on Apple or Spotify.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>