<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-10-23T19:12:06.619Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-10-23T19:12:06.619Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Models Show Promise in Predicting Central Bank Interest Rate Decisions]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18988678/AI-Models-Show-Promise-in-Predicting-Central-Bank-Interest-Rate-Decisions</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18988678/AI-Models-Show-Promise-in-Predicting-Central-Bank-Interest-Rate-Decisions"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T18:57:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers at Sheffield Hallam University have conducted a groundbreaking study demonstrating the potential of large language models, such as ChatGPT, in predicting interest rate decisions made by central banks. This study, conducted by Sheffield Business School researchers, focused on...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Court confirms Grayscale ruling, says SEC must re-review bid for spot bitcoin ETF]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18988685/US-Court-confirms-Grayscale-ruling-says-SEC-must-re-review-bid-for-spot-bitcoin-ETF</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18988685/US-Court-confirms-Grayscale-ruling-says-SEC-must-re-review-bid-for-spot-bitcoin-ETF"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T18:54:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A DC court issued a mandate, asserting its initial ruling that the SEC needs to reconsider a bid from Grayscale for a spot bitcoin ETF.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BREAKING: Grayscale Gets Court Approval to Proceed with Bitcoin Spot ETF Application]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18988705/BREAKING-Grayscale-Gets-Court-Approval-to-Proceed-with-Bitcoin-Spot-ETF-Application</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18988705/BREAKING-Grayscale-Gets-Court-Approval-to-Proceed-with-Bitcoin-Spot-ETF-Application"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T18:53:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to breaking information, in the Grayscale case, the court allowed the company to proceed with its Bitcoin Spot ETF application and send the application back to the SEC. The court provided instructions to the SEC on how to proceed with Grayscale's Bitcoin Spot ETF application. *This is...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto funds see fourth week of net inflows, with Solana taking largest altcoin share]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18988684/Crypto-funds-see-fourth-week-of-net-inflows-with-Solana-taking-largest-altcoin-share</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18988684/Crypto-funds-see-fourth-week-of-net-inflows-with-Solana-taking-largest-altcoin-share"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T18:51:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Digital asset investment products saw net inflows for the fourth consecutive week totaling $66 million, according to CoinShares.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin $30k: Uptober is Back on the Menu!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18988699/Bitcoin-30k-Uptober-is-Back-on-the-Menu</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18988699/Bitcoin-30k-Uptober-is-Back-on-the-Menu"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T18:51:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today NLW explores the recent price push about $30,000 and what it says about the state of the market.Today's Sponsor: KrakenKraken: See what crypto can be - https://kraken.com/TheBreakdownEnjoying this content?SUBSCRIBE to the Podcast: https://pod.link/1438693620Watch on YouTube:...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FinCEN Introduces New Rulemaking Proposal To Surveil Crypto Mixing Services, Citing Patriot Act]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18988667/FinCEN-Introduces-New-Rulemaking-Proposal-To-Surveil-Crypto-Mixing-Services-Citing-Patriot-Act</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18988667/FinCEN-Introduces-New-Rulemaking-Proposal-To-Surveil-Crypto-Mixing-Services-Citing-Patriot-Act"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T18:45:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Financial Crimes Enforcement Network (FinCEN) has released a new proposal for the US government to begin monitoring crypto mixers. FinCEN cites Section 311 of the USA PATRIOT Act to propose requirements for financial institutions and financial agencies to keep records and reports on...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stock Market Sees Mixed Pre-market Activity; Economic Concerns Addressed]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18988665/Stock-Market-Sees-Mixed-Pre-market-Activity-Economic-Concerns-Addressed</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18988665/Stock-Market-Sees-Mixed-Pre-market-Activity-Economic-Concerns-Addressed"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T18:43:26.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin Adjusts Token Strategy; Shifts Orb Rewards and Alters Market Maker Agreements]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a920a6d7</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/worldcoin-adjusts-token-strategy-shifts-orb-rewards-and-alters-market-maker-agreements/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T18:43:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin, which uses iris biometrics to create a unique human identity database, said Sunday it is changing the distribution of its circulating WLD token supply and its market maker loan agreements. The project, launched in July, will decrease the loan amounts to market makers and will start rewarding operators with WLD instead of USDC.
 
Worldcoin Updates Token Supply and Loan Agreements
 
WLD’s circulating supply is now close to 134 million tokens, an increase from the 100 million at its debut. In an update published on Sunday, the company said this jump is attributed to more than 800,000 new and current users who claimed about 34 million tokens through free grants. To boost liquidity, Worldcoin provided 100 million WLD in loans to five market makers, with those loans set to end on Octo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Bulls Make A Statement]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18988407/Crypto-Bulls-Make-A-Statement</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18988407/Crypto-Bulls-Make-A-Statement"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T18:42:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[🚀 Learn Technical Analysis with our FREE course! https://www.chartguys.com/trading-courses/7/technical-analysis?utm_source=youtube&utm_medium=social&utm_term=&utm_content=&utm_campaign=free-ta-courseOur goal is to review and discuss the most recent price action in the market in a manner that...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not Regulators’ Job to Tell Americans What They Can and Can’t Speculate On: SEC Commissioner Hester Peirce]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18988668/Not-Regulators-Job-to-Tell-Americans-What-They-Can-and-Cant-Speculate-On-SEC-Commissioner-Hester-Peirce</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18988668/Not-Regulators-Job-to-Tell-Americans-What-They-Can-and-Cant-Speculate-On-SEC-Commissioner-Hester-Peirce"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T18:41:27.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reddit moderators removed for suspicion of insider trading during Community Points shutdown]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18988664/Reddit-moderators-removed-for-suspicion-of-insider-trading-during-Community-Points-shutdown</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18988664/Reddit-moderators-removed-for-suspicion-of-insider-trading-during-Community-Points-shutdown"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T18:40:47.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOX Journalist Lambasts XRP Army in Escalating Online Feud]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18988643/FOX-Journalist-Lambasts-XRP-Army-in-Escalating-Online-Feud</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18988643/FOX-Journalist-Lambasts-XRP-Army-in-Escalating-Online-Feud"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T18:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SEC vs. Ripple legal battle offsets a hard-fought online rivalry between XRP Army and Charles Gasparino.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ricardo Salinas Explains How Bitcoin Is Leveling The Playing Field For Developing Nations]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a921f62b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/ricardo-salinas-explains-how-bitcoin-is-leveling-the-playing-field-for-developing-nations"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T18:33:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In recent years, Bitcoin has been making waves as a transformative force in the world of finance. Its decentralized nature and potential for economic disruption have caught the attention of many, including Mexican businessman Ricardo Salinas. Salinas, a prominent advocate for economic empowerment in developing nations, believes that Bitcoin has the power to level the playing field and create opportunities for those who have traditionally been excluded from the global financial system.
Understanding Bitcoin's Role in Economic Equality
The Concept of Bitcoin
At its core, Bitcoin is a borderless form of currency that transcends geographical limitations. It allows individuals to send and receive funds without the need for intermediaries, such as banks or payment processors. This feature has th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bukele Likely To Step Down As President To Seek A Second Term]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a921f618</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/el-salvador-bitcoin-news/bukele-likely-to-step-down-as-president-to-seek-a-second-term"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T18:33:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In recent weeks, the Salvadoran media has been abuzz with speculation that Bitcoin Country President Nayib Bukele will step down from his current role to pursue a second term in office. This move hinges on obtaining a special license from the Salvadoran Legislative Assembly, a process that requires three-quarters approval from the body. Previously, it was widely believed that Salvadoran presidents were limited to a single five-year term. However, a landmark Supreme Court ruling has opened the door to the possibility of a second term, provided the incumbent steps down at least six months before the next presidential term commences on June 1, 2024.
The Constitutional Framework
The Supreme Court's ruling introduced a nuanced framework for seeking a second presidential mandate in El Salvador. …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jaime García</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rich Dad, Poor Dad Author: 'Next Stop' for Bitcoin Price $130,000]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a921f608</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/markets/rich-dad-poor-dad-kiyosaki-next-stop-for-bitcoin-price-130000"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T18:33:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Renowned financial educator and author of the best-selling book "Rich Dad Poor Dad," Robert Kiyosaki, has once again made a bold prediction regarding the future of Bitcoin, suggesting that the cryptocurrency's price is on a trajectory to reach $130,000. 
Kiyosaki's pronouncement on X comes amid his growing concerns about inflation and a shifting global economic landscape.
In a recent tweet, Kiyosaki shared his insights on various assets, including Bitcoin, gold, and silver. He started by forecasting a bullish future for gold, stating, "Gold will soon break through $2,100 and then take off."
Kiyosaki's optimism about gold stems from the precious metal's historical role as a hedge against inflation and economic uncertainty. His forecast suggests a significant increase in the value of gold, which has been catching the attention of investors as a traditional store of value.
However, what grabbed the attention of the Bitcoin community and investors was Kiyosaki's next prediction. He asserted, "Bitcoin testing $30,000. Next stop Bitcoin $135,000." This statement underscores Kiyosaki's belief in the potential of Bitcoin to not only recover from recent price fluctuations but to surge to new all-time highs.
Despite periodic market volatility, Bitcoin has maintained its status as the leading digital asset and is seen by many as a store of value and a hedge against global economic instability.
As investors and financial experts continue to navigate the complex financial landscape, Kiyosaki's forecasts serve as a reminder of the growing interest in alternative assets like Bitcoin and precious metals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reed Macdonald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Argentina's Pro-Bitcoin Presidential Candidate Javier Milei Forces Run-Off Election]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a921f5fd</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/argentina-bitcoin-president-javier-milei-run-off-election"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T18:33:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a surprising twist in Argentina's presidential election, pro-Bitcoin candidate Javier Gerardo Milei has emerged as a formidable contender, forcing a run-off election against current Economy Minister Sergio Massa after the first round of voting.
Javier Milei, a libertarian economist who has vowed to shut down the nation's central bank and expressed support for Bitcoin, managed to secure 31.2% of the vote, a remarkable achievement for a candidate with limited prior political exposure. 
Milei's passionate advocacy for economic reform have resonated with a significant portion of the electorate. In August, Milei won the most votes in the country's primary election, a fact owed to the nation's ongoing economic crisis.
In past remarks, Milei has said he will address Argentina's chronic economic woes, a message struck a chord with disillusioned voters. Argentina's annual inflation rate was 124.4% in August, its highest level since 1991.
The upcoming run-off election, slated for November 19th, will see Milei face off against Sergio Massa, who secured 46.7% of the vote in the first round, but missed the majority threshold needed to claim victory outright. In order to win outright, either candidate would have needed to claim 40% of the vote, and to lead his political opponent by 10% of the vote, owing to election rules.
The outcome of the run-off could have a profound impact on Argentina's economic policies and its role in the global cryptocurrency landscape.
Investors and crypto enthusiasts worldwide are closely watching this electoral showdown, anticipating its potential implications on the adoption of Bitcoin, and whether the nation could follow El Salvador's landmark legal tender law, which in 2021 made the cryptocurrency a payment method across the country.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reed Macdonald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two Unnoticed Details Caught in BlackRock’s Bitcoin Spot ETF Application: Coming Sooner Than Expected?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18988633/Two-Unnoticed-Details-Caught-in-BlackRocks-Bitcoin-Spot-ETF-Application-Coming-Sooner-Than-Expected</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18988633/Two-Unnoticed-Details-Caught-in-BlackRocks-Bitcoin-Spot-ETF-Application-Coming-Sooner-Than-Expected"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T18:28:06.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[World Blockchain Summit in Dubai Set to Unite Global Web3 Innovators and Decision-Makers]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18988625/World-Blockchain-Summit-in-Dubai-Set-to-Unite-Global-Web3-Innovators-and-Decision-Makers</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18988625/World-Blockchain-Summit-in-Dubai-Set-to-Unite-Global-Web3-Innovators-and-Decision-Makers"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T18:25:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The World Blockchain Summit, scheduled to commence at the esteemed Address Dubai Marina, is poised to bring together more than 2,000 influential web3 decision-makers from across the globe. With a vision to highlight the region’s dedication to a web3-driven future, the event has garnered...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OKX wants to build a ‘generational brand’ like Fidelity, says CMO]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18988615/OKX-wants-to-build-a-generational-brand-like-Fidelity-says-CMO</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18988615/OKX-wants-to-build-a-generational-brand-like-Fidelity-says-CMO"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T18:22:05.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The first international crude oil trade in digital Yuan by PertolChina]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18988602/The-first-international-crude-oil-trade-in-digital-Yuan-by-PertolChina</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18988602/The-first-international-crude-oil-trade-in-digital-Yuan-by-PertolChina"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T18:19:37.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Next-Gen Gaming Brings an Exciting Universal Industry Shift]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18988603/Next-Gen-Gaming-Brings-an-Exciting-Universal-Industry-Shift</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18988603/Next-Gen-Gaming-Brings-an-Exciting-Universal-Industry-Shift"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T18:19:26.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong regulator reverses its stance on spot crypto investments]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18988604/Hong-Kong-regulator-reverses-its-stance-on-spot-crypto-investments</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18988604/Hong-Kong-regulator-reverses-its-stance-on-spot-crypto-investments"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T18:17:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong’s financial regulator has recently made an important adjustment to its guidance regarding the sale of spot products in the cryptocurrency market. This change allows intermediaries to offer services to a broader range of clients, extending beyond professional investors. The Securities...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple CEO Reveals They’re Not XRP Maximalists, What’s The Catch?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a92c9f7c</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ripple-ceo-not-xrp-maximalists/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T18:16:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple’s Chief Executive Officer, Brad Garlinghouse has recently revealed that they are not XRP maximalists while sharing valuable insights on the significant role that XRP plays in the company’s broader business strategy and its extensive cryptocurrency operations. 
 
Ripple CEO’s Emphasis On Ripple Being Centered Around XRP
 
In an interview on Thursday, with Metaco Talks’s host Adrien Treccani, Brad expressed his optimism about the company being solely centered around XRP. 
 
The CEO affirmed that the digital asset is highly efficient for several use cases, which include cross-border payments and remittances. But despite the company possessing a lot of XRP, they are definitely not maximalists of the cryptocurrency, noting that there is a place for several other digital assets such as Bi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pro-Bitcoin Candidate Javier Milei Loses First Round, What Now? | EP 851]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18987861/Pro-Bitcoin-Candidate-Javier-Milei-Loses-First-Round-What-Now-EP-851</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18987861/Pro-Bitcoin-Candidate-Javier-Milei-Loses-First-Round-What-Now-EP-851"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T18:14:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FinCEN proposes regulations that would allow them to force businesses to report transaction details on almost anything they want✓ SUBSCRIBE - https://bit.ly/3QbgqTQ✓ LEAVE A LIKE & COMMENT LIMITED MERCH DROP:► https://simplybitcoin.com/collections/allSPONSORS:► Foundation's Bitcoin Hardware...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[If You Think This Rally Is A Coincidence, YOU ARE WRONG]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18988621/If-You-Think-This-Rally-Is-A-Coincidence-YOU-ARE-WRONG</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18988621/If-You-Think-This-Rally-Is-A-Coincidence-YOU-ARE-WRONG"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T18:13:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It looks like it isn’t slowing down anytime soon! Bitcoin is up 15% this week and has hit $31k ,We can thank a decade of past Octobers for this rally - two out of the last 10 years have seen a major spike in value. Let's keep our fingers crossed for another strong month!✴︎Sign Up Here for the CT...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Rises Above $31K, With Options Positioning Suggesting Price Has Further to Run]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a92d5318</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/10/23/bitcoin-rises-above-31k-with-options-positioning-suggesting-price-has-further-to-run/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T18:12:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC)surged past $31,000 Monday for the first time since mid-July as cryptocurrency markets continued their October bull run.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All Spot-Bitcoin ETF Applications May be Approved Together, Crypto ETF Expert Predicts]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a92d53ed</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/10/23/all-spot-bitcoin-etf-applications-may-be-approved-together-crypto-etf-expert-predicts/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T18:12:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All applications to the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission for spot bitcoin exchange-traded-funds (ETFs) may be approved together, predicts crypto ETF expert Stuart Barton, who, along with his company, pulled off two regulatory firsts recently.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amitoj Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI-Generated Closing Statements in Legal Trial Spark Controversy]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18988605/AI-Generated-Closing-Statements-in-Legal-Trial-Spark-Controversy</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18988605/AI-Generated-Closing-Statements-in-Legal-Trial-Spark-Controversy"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T18:10:42.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Blasts Past $31,000 as Optimism for BTC Spot ETF Surges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202840</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202840/bitcoin-31000-spot-btc-etf-optimism"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T17:19:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The last time the asset was this high was back in July.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Shorts Take $86 Million Beating As BTC Marches Towards $31,000]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a915a99b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-shorts-86-million-beating-btc-marches-31000/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T17:17:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data shows the crypto shorts have observed a high amount of liquidations in the past day as BTC has seen a sharp rally towards $31,000.
 
Crypto Futures Market Has Seen High Liquidations In The Past Day
 
The past day has been volatile for the crypto market as Bitcoin and other assets have seen some sharp bullish momentum. As is usually the case, this volatility has resulted in some chaos on the futures side of the sector.
 
The below table shows how the liquidations have looked in the crypto futures market today:
 

 
 
As displayed above, the crypto futures market as a whole has seen liquidations of almost $120 million in the last 24 hours. Out of these, a little under $86 million of the liquidations were of short contracts.
 
Most of the volatility in this period has come from assets ar…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF Coming Soon? Delays Have SEC’s Hester Peirce ‘Mystified’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202826</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202826/bitcoin-etf-coming-soon-delays-have-secs-hester-peirce-mystified"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T16:56:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After Grayscale's court loss, Hester Peirce doesn't know what her agency is waiting for.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Effective Altruism to Terms of Service — Pivotal Points in Bankman-Fried’s Court Battle]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a913ce73</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/from-effective-altruism-to-terms-of-service-pivotal-points-in-bankman-frieds-court-battle/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T16:38:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lawyers for former FTX CEO Sam Bankman-Fried have given proposed jury instructions to the court in advance of jury deliberations and his verdict. These instructions clarify the defense’s legal positions and emphasize their client’s right to be presumed innocent until proven guilty.
 
Sam Bankman-Fried’s Lawyers Request Specific Jury Instructions Ahead of Trial
 
In their court submission, Bankman-Fried’s attorneys request the judge instruct jurors that convictions can only be based on defined statutory crimes, not on general immorality. The instructions provide an in-depth description of fraud and details about FTX’s terms of service.
 
“The terms of service constituted a contract between FTX and its customers, and you must consider what that contract said and didn’t say regarding the lega…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microstrategy’s Bitcoin Billions Back in Profit as ‘Digital Gold’ Nears $31K]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202813</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202813/microstrategys-bitcoin-in-the-green-digital-gold-rallies"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T16:37:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC is fast closing in on $31,000 per coin—which means the largest public owner of the asset is making a return on its investment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How US Treasury’s Proposed Controls Could Impact Crypto Mixers]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a91f9420</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/how-us-treasurys-proposed-controls-could-impact-crypto-mixers/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T16:16:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US Treasury Department’s Financial Crimes Enforcement Network (FinCEN) has escalated its crackdown on crypto mixers, labeling them as critical hubs for illicit financial activities. 
 
In a move to intensify oversight of digital currency transactions, the agency unveiled a Notice of Proposed Rule Making (NPRM) over the weekend, singling out crypto transaction mixing as a prime concern in the realm of money laundering.
 
Cryptocurrency mixers, also known as tumblers, are services that shuffle digital assets to obscure their origin, making them challenging to trace. This blending process often involves pooling funds from various sources and then redistributing them to different addresses, effectively severing the transaction trail. 
 
With the rapid proliferation of cryptocurrencies and …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining Stocks Rally as BTC Holds Above $30K Despite Looming Halving Concerns]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a91fb54f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/10/23/bitcoin-mining-stocks-rally-as-btc-holds-above-30k-despite-looming-halving-concerns/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T16:16:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bit Digital (BTBT), Hut 8 (HUT) and Marathon (MARA) are among mining stocks that are outperforming on Monday as bitcoin's price continue to hold above $30,000.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aoyon Ashraf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CipherBlade Founder Says Blockchain Sleuthing Firm 'Hijacked']]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a91fb541</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/10/23/cipherblade-founder-says-blockchain-sleuthing-firm-hijacked/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T16:16:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Members of the original CipherBlade entity – who no longer control its domain or social platforms – are suing the new ownership.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandali Handagama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Argentina’s Pro-Bitcoin Javier Milei Heads to Run-Off Election Against Sergio Massa]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a91fb532</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/10/23/argentinas-pro-bitcoin-javier-milei-heads-to-run-off-election-against-sergio-massa/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T16:16:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Javier Millei lost to Sergio Massa who took around 37% of the vote.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lyllah Ledesma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BTC Valued at $144M Sent to Coin Mixer From Defunct Darknet Market After Eight-Year Wait]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a904c413</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/10/23/btc-valued-at-144m-sent-to-coin-mixer-from-defunct-darknet-market-after-eight-year-wait/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T15:46:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An entity has moved 4,800 BTC ($144M) to a coin mixer from a wallet tied to defunct darknet marketplace Abraxas, which closed in 2015.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CySEC Prolongs FTX License Suspension until March 2024]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a9055fbc</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/cysec-prolongs-ftx-license-suspension-until-march-2024/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T15:43:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Cyprus Securities and Exchange Commission  
(CySEC) has extended the suspension of the authorization of FTX (EU) Ltd until  
March 31, 2024. This decision is in response to the market instability caused  
when FTX and several of its subsidiaries filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy in the  
United States.
In an official statement published by CySEC on its  
website, during the suspension period, FTX is permitted to execute all  
transactions initiated by its clients based on their instructions. This  
provision ensures that existing clients are not affected while FTX navigates  
its regulatory challenges.
CySEC said: "For as long as the suspension of  
the authorization is in force, as provided for in section 9 of DI87-05, FTX  
(EU) Ltd is not permitted to provide or carry out investment s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biggest Movers: DOGE, MATIC Rally to 2-Month Highs on Monday]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a9002afe</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/biggest-movers-doge-matic-rally-to-2-month-highs-on-monday/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T15:26:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin rose by over 10% to start the week, as sentiment in cryptocurrency markets remained mostly bullish. The global market cap for crypto is up by 2.34% at the time of writing, which comes as a red wave swept through global stock indices. Polygon was another notable gainer on Monday.
 
Dogecoin (DOGE)
 
Dogecoin was a notable gainer on Monday, as the meme coin rallied past a key resistance level during the session.
 
Following a low of $0.06068 on Sunday, DOGE/USD raced to an intraday peak at the $0.06525 mark.
 
This surge saw dogecoin break out of a ceiling at $0.0640, hitting its highest point since August 31 in the process.
 
 
One catalyst for the move was a breakout that occurred at the 65.00 level on the 14-day relative strength index (RSI).
 
Currently, the index is tracking at 65.94, with remaining bulls more than likely targeting the 70.00 level.
 
Earlier gains have somewhat slipped, with DOGE now trading at $0.06407.
 
 
Polygon (MATIC)
 
In addition to dogecoin, polygon (MATIC) also surged strongly on Monday, as the cryptocurrency reached a multi-month high
 
MATIC/USD jumped to a peak at $0.6315 to start the week, which comes a day after trading at a low of $0.56.
 
Monday’s high pushed polygon to its strongest point since August 16, when price reached a top at $0.638.
 
 
As a result of the rally, MATIC’s RSI rose to a three-month high at 68.79, but failed to break out of a ceiling at 69.00.
 
The index is now tracking at 66.60, despite the 10-day (red) moving average being on the cusp of crossing its 25-day (blue) counterpart.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
Do you expect polygon bulls to retreat in the coming days? Let us know your thoughts in the comments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The US Risks Its Position as a Stablecoin Leader]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a9015f2e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/10/23/the-us-risks-its-position-as-a-stablecoin-leader/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T15:19:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[USD stablecoin transactions are rising fast, but most of the growth is happening outside of the United States, says Jason Somensatto, Head of North America Policy at Chainalysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Somensatto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Lead Dev Reveals Major Update For Builders]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a901df03</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-update-builders/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T15:17:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Lead Developer Shytoshi Kusama has briefly highlighted plans for the LEASH token that would advance the SHIB ecosystem and cater to the needs of community members. 
 
Shiba Inu Update Unveiled
 
A SHIB X (formerly Twitter) account, Kuro Shibaarmy JPN recently released a statement made by Shiba Inu’s Lead Developer, Shytoshi Kusama on the Shibarium project building telegram account.  
 
When asked about the plans he had in store for the LEASH token, Kusama responded by stating a brief outline of his vision for the token and the community. He said that he was working towards creating a solid framework that would effectively provide transparency and insight regarding all the plans, products, and platforms actively using the LEASH token. 
 
From his statement, this update represents …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PetroChina Completes First International Crude Oil Trade in Digital Yuan: Report]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a90a9ed7</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/10/23/petrochina-completes-first-international-crude-oil-trade-in-digital-yuan-report/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T14:26:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PetroChina bought 1 million barrels of crude oil settled in e-CNY at the Shanghai Petroleum and Natural Gas Exchange.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is the Lightning Network? Bitcoin's Scalability Solution.]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=5684</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/bitcoin-lightning-network"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T14:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lightning Network is a scaling solution that attempts to address Bitcoin's slow transaction speeds and high transaction costs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Hussey,Tim Copeland,Daniel Phillips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Banking Crisis Destroyed Institutional Crypto Trading: Chainalysis]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202791</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202791/us-banking-crisis-destroyed-institutional-crypto-trading-chainalysis"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T13:10:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto activity saw a sharp drop following Silicon Valley Bank and crypto-friendly banks Signature and Silvergate shutting down.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Almost All Mining Stocks Have Outpaced Bitcoin This Year]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202776</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202776/almost-all-mining-stocks-have-outpaced-bitcoin-this-year"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T11:01:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most mining stocks, except two, have outperformed Bitcoin by more than double this year despite the ongoing bear market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 Security Firm Blockaid Lands $33 Million in Latest Funding]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202523</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202523/web3-security-firm-blockaid-lands-33-million-latest-funding"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T11:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By offering an enhanced level of security for Web3 wallets, Blockaid aims to make the space safer for average users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Sees Lion’s Share of Investment Amid Spot ETF Hype: CoinShares]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202775</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202775/bitcoin-sees-lions-share-investment-amid-spot-etf-hype-coinshares"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T10:19:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As hype around a spot Bitcoin ETF reaches a pitch, investors are looking for more exposure to the leading cryptocurrency, reports CoinShares.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chainlink Leads Crypto Market Rally, Soaring 8% Overnight]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202771</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202771/chainlink-leads-crypto-market-rally-soaring-overnight"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T09:50:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price of Chainlink’s LINK rose about $10, bringing the oracle token to a high not seen in the last 17 months.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robot Hands Can Match Humans' Dexterity With New AI Smarts, Claims Nvidia]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202659</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202659/nvidia-eureka-ai-agent-allegedly-makes-robot-hands-dextrous-human-ones"/>
        <updated>2023-10-22T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia is all-in when it comes to AI. Eureka helps robots learn intricate skills faster than an aspiring surgeon, and its new SteerLM wants to make human annotation in AI training a thing of the past.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[God Mode: 9 Can't-Miss 'Starfield' Quests With the Best Stories and Rewards]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202444</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202444/9-cant-miss-starfield-quests-best-stories-rewards"/>
        <updated>2023-10-22T14:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to make the most of your time in Bethesda's epic sci-fi odyssey? Here are the Starfield quests that you must seek out and complete.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Frederiksen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Huawei Unveils OceanStor A310—A Speedy Storage Solution for AI Model Trainers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202568</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202568/huawei-unveils-oceanstor-a310-speedy-storage-solution-ai-model-trainers"/>
        <updated>2023-10-22T12:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Huawei steps into the AI storage arena with its OceanStor A310, showcasing potential solutions to industry-wide data processing hurdles.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dr. Disrespect's 'Deadrop' Shooter Unveils Cars, Racing Battles at Vegas Event]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202701</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202701/dr-disrespect-deadrop-shooter-unveils-cars-racing-battles-vegas-event"/>
        <updated>2023-10-22T02:04:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Midnight Society showed off the latest Deadrop update, Snapshot VII, at a lavish Las Vegas event that showcased newly-added cars and modes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Midnight Society's Rob Bowling on Deadrop's New Cars and User-Generated Modes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/A0auyZzn/midnight-societys-rob-bowling-on-deadrops-new-cars-and-user-generated-modes</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/A0auyZzn/midnight-societys-rob-bowling-on-deadrops-new-cars-and-user-generated-modes"/>
        <updated>2023-10-22T01:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt reporter and GG producer Kate Irwin interviews Midnight Society Studio Head Rob Bowling about Deadrop's development and Snapshot VII.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NASA Prepares Deep Space Mission—Why AI Will Play Important Role]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202611</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202611/nasa-prepares-deep-space-mission-why-ai-play-important-role"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T15:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NASA's Nancy Grace Roman Telescope, launching May 2027, aims to unravel dark matter mysteries and honor Roman's legacy in astronomy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week on Crypto Twitter: Fake ETF News Pumps Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202616</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202616/this-week-crypto-twitter-fake-etf-news-pumps-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T12:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One mistaken tweet on Monday pumped the price of Bitcoin by 10% in 24 hours—but it's not the only buzz from a busy week on Crypto Twitter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Is Like a Grocery Store Selling Oranges and SEC Should Leave It Alone, Says Crypto Lobby Group]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202626</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202626/binance-grocery-store-oranges-sec-crypto-lobby-group"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T22:10:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In its fight against Binance, "the SEC is suing the equivalent of a grocery store selling oranges and other fruit," says US Chamber of Digital Commerce in an amicus brief.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitch Will Let Users Stream Across Platforms—But They Better Act Right]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202617</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202617/twitch-let-users-stream-across-platforms-they-better-act-right"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T22:04:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Popular video game streaming site Twitch introduces big changes at TwitchCon 2023 as rivals new and old start to pose serious competition.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google and BlackRock Considered Investing in FTX as It Crumbled]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202583</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202583/google-blackrock-considered-investing-ftx-before-bankruptcy"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T20:12:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The exchange wanted to tap big names for its C1 funding, but FTX buckled before it closed the round.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI and Bitcoin Mining Meet in New Texas Data Center]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202590</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202590/ai-and-bitcoin-mining-meet-in-new-texas-data-center"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T20:09:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite the expansion, APLD shares fell 5.3% on Friday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Raini: The Lords of Light Review—SBF, CZ, and Satoshi Battle in This Crypto Card Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202585</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202585/raini-lords-light-review-sbf-cz-satoshi-battle-crypto-card-game"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T19:36:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[REVIEW: Putting an NFT spin on the Hearthstone formula, Raini: The Lords of Light goes even further with crypto memes and compelling card mechanics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Game Review: 'Raini: The Lords of Light' Brands Itself With Memes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/32YyJHCJ/game-review-raini-the-lords-of-light-brands-itself-with-memes</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/32YyJHCJ/game-review-raini-the-lords-of-light-brands-itself-with-memes"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T19:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Raini: Lords of Light is an NFT-optional card game bursting with crypto memes. From SBF to CZ and Elon, this free-to-play game has some truly wild animations. Decrypt contributor Ryan S. Gladwin shares his honest thoughts on the game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s Going On With Crypto Behemoth Digital Currency Group?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202551</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202551/whats-going-on-with-crypto-behemoth-digital-currency-group"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T18:31:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most important companies in the space has been steeped in legal woes. Here’s how it got to this point.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Model Transparency Is Getting Worse, Researchers Warn]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202555</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202555/ai-model-transparency-getting-worse-stanford-researchers"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T17:58:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Foundation models promise a new era in AI, but Stanford University researchers have flagged that they're becoming less transparent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Solana Explodes 25%, Bitcoin Reclaims $30K on ETF Hopes and Ripple Wins]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202554</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202554/week-in-coins-solana-bitcoin-xrp-ripple"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T16:59:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, usually the market pace-setter, was far outpaced by Solana, Bitcoin Cash and XRP.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Habbo Game Plans to Keep Using NFTs Without Uttering Dirty Crypto 'Jargon']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202553</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202553/habbo-game-keep-using-nfts-without-uttering-dirty-crypto-jargon"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T16:47:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The classic social web game will change the way it conveys its NFT push, but it’s still moving forward with the blockchain initiative.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vitalik's Biggest Worries? Crypto Stagnating and AI Risks, Says Ethereum Co-Founder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202548</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202548/vitaliks-biggest-worries-crypto-stagnating-ai-risks-says-ethereum-co-founder"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T15:07:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The co-founder believes that Ethereum can provide a potential solution to address AI-related challenges, such as digital impersonation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nintendo Switch 2 Preview: Everything You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197793</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197793/nintendo-switch-2-rumors-leaks-latest-news"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T14:47:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATE: How powerful will the Switch 2 be? The latest leaks point to some serious capabilities. Here's everything we know so far.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angry Birds, 'The Voice', Warner Music Artists to Launch Avatar Skins via Ready Player Me]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202484</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202484/angry-birds-voice-warner-music-artists-launch-avatar-skins-ready-player-me"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T13:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Multiplatform avatar startup Ready Player Me is unleashing a brand barrage, with licensed skins from major entertainment partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Game Upland Raises $7 Million Ahead of Ethereum Token Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202498</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202498/crypto-game-upland-raises-7-million-ahead-ethereum-token-launch"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T12:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The EOS-based metaverse game Upland expands its Series A raise, with plans to bridge its Spark utility token to Ethereum as Sparklet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maker Annualized Revenue Soars Past $200M to New All-Time High]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202515</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202515/maker-annualized-revenue-soars-past-200m-to-new-all-time-high"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T11:30:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The stablecoin issuer’s revenue is up on high U.S. treasury yields and increased yields for DAI holders through Gnosis chain integration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Hits $30,000 Amid Spot ETF Amendments From BlackRock, Fidelity]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202507</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202507/bitcoin-spot-etf-amendments-blackrock-fidelity"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T10:54:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With industry talking heads more bullish than ever of an ETF approval, Bitcoin has jumped 5% overnight, briefly hitting $30,000.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Soars 12% Overnight as Crypto Market Recoups $43 Billion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202505</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202505/solana-soars-overnight-crypto-market-recoups-billion"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T09:55:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the crypto market rebounds, the price of Solana's native token SOL has seen its price hit a 3-month high above $26.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Did an AI Hallucination Help Convict Fugees Rapper Pras?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202461</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202461/did-ai-hallucination-help-convict-fugees-rapper-pras"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T00:15:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pras Michel's new counsel filed for a fresh trial, claiming the AI tool and his previous legal team were ineffective in the Fugees star's conspiracy case.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoins on Bitcoin? Lightning Labs Aims to 'Bitcoinize the Dollar']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202474</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202474/stablecoins-bitcoin-lightning-labs-aims-bitcoinize-dollar"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T22:28:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lightning Labs launches Taproot Assets, enabling stablecoins and other assets to be tokenized on top of Bitcoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Dismisses Lawsuit Against Ripple Execs in 'Stunning Capitulation']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202471</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202471/sec-dismisses-lawsuit-against-ripple-execs-stunning-capitulation"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T21:51:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brad Garlinghouse and Chris Larsen are no longer facing charges from the U.S. regulator, which is still pursuing Ripple over securities violations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Human vs. AI-Generated Music: Indistinguishable, or Uncanny Valley?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202442</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/human-vs-ai-generated-music-indistinguishable-or-uncanny-valley"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T20:19:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some studies suggest that many listeners are already unable to tell the difference between music made by computers and music composed by humans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Reiff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Seeks to Label Crypto Mixers as National Security Threats Amid Money Laundering Concerns]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202428</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202428/us-seeks-label-crypto-mixers-national-security-threat"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T19:58:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The move comes amid an escalating narrative in D.C. that crypto was disproportionately responsible for triggering the escalating crisis in Israel and Palestine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SBF Asked Former FTX Lawyer to Find 'Legal Justifications' for Missing Customer Funds]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202417</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202417/sbf-asked-former-ftx-lawyer-for-legal-justifications-for-missing-funds"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T19:56:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Can Sun structured billions of dollars in personal loans to FTX insiders, but said he had "no idea that customer funds were being misused."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is a Bitcoin ETF, and Why Does Everyone from Blackrock to Grayscale Want One?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=12006</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-bitcoin-etf-explained-guide-learn-easy"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T19:54:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Bitcoin ETF creates a simple, legally compliant way to trade the price of Bitcoin, accessible on markets that investors are already familiar with.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Stevens,Ki Chong Tran,Daniel Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Art Blocks Marfa Weekend Recap]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/QaTBP6eO/art-blocks-marfa-weekend-recap</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/QaTBP6eO/art-blocks-marfa-weekend-recap"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T19:19:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Relive the Art Blocks Marfa Weekend 2023 event with this highlights video, produced by Vincent Roazzi Jr. for Decrypt Studios in partnership with Art Blocks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Phantom Galaxies: A Look Inside the Mech Shooter NFT Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QI1uDwQv/phantom-galaxies-a-look-inside-the-mech-shooter-nft-game</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QI1uDwQv/phantom-galaxies-a-look-inside-the-mech-shooter-nft-game"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T21:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animoca Brands and game studio Blowfish are developing Phantom Galaxies, an upcoming sci-fi mech shooter game inspired by mech battlers like Transformers. Decrypt's Kate Irwin asks Blowfish Studios Cofounder and Managing Director Ben Lee about what it's like to play the game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Clip: DeepMedia's DeepID Deepfake Detection Tool at Work]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/m4Vy4vhC/clip-deepmedias-deepid-deepfake-detection-tool-at-work</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/m4Vy4vhC/clip-deepmedias-deepid-deepfake-detection-tool-at-work"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T16:48:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A clip showcasing how DeepMedia's DeepID deepfake detection tool works. Courtesy: DeepMedia]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentraland AI World Fair Trailer]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/3tUb56Fv/decentraland-ai-world-fair-trailer</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/3tUb56Fv/decentraland-ai-world-fair-trailer"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A trailer for the AI World Fair event in metaverse game Decentraland, taking place from October 25-27. Courtesy: Decentraland.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BackTheBunny - Money, Conspiracy, Milady]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BRoKZzer/backthebunny-money-conspiracy-milady</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BRoKZzer/backthebunny-money-conspiracy-milady"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T19:48:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our host Reza Jafery sits down with BackTheBunny to dive deep into money, the fight against crypto that we're witnessing in real-time, and milady culture. 

Our Host: https://twitter.com/rezajafery
Our Guest: https://twitter.com/BackTheBunny

Our Sponsors
https://decrypt.co/1000x]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['A Grand Experiment': Shrapnel Studio Head Don Norbury Talks Game Economics]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Z2OMMsC5/a-grand-experiment-shrapnel-studio-head-don-norbury-talks-game-economics</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Z2OMMsC5/a-grand-experiment-shrapnel-studio-head-don-norbury-talks-game-economics"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T17:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How much of Shrapnel's in-game items are tradeable NFTs? Don Norbury, Studio Head at Shrapnel and CTO at game studio NEON, tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about Shrapnel's approach to game economics, including different game pricing models and how NFT game economies create different challenges for developers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trezor Safe 3 and Trezor Keep Metal Unboxing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/IjqnO9pR/trezor-safe-3-and-trezor-keep-metal-unboxing</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/IjqnO9pR/trezor-safe-3-and-trezor-keep-metal-unboxing"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T14:45:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trezor has launched the Safe 3, a hardware wallet aimed at "new entrants to crypto," alongside the new Keep Metal recovery seed storage device. We take a first look at what comes in the box.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why AI Arena is Building on Arbitrum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Gl80TQOm/why-ai-arena-is-building-on-arbitrum</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Gl80TQOm/why-ai-arena-is-building-on-arbitrum"/>
        <updated>2023-10-12T14:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI Arena CEO Brandon Da Silva and COO Wei Xie discuss the challenges that come with building on Ethereum, ETH sidechains, and layer-two blockchains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pet3rPan_ on venture DAOs and blockchain games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DawNLI3O/pet3rpan-on-venture-daos-and-blockchain-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DawNLI3O/pet3rpan-on-venture-daos-and-blockchain-games"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T18:24:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the 4th episode of this time will be different.

Our guest for today's episode is Pet3rpan_ from Metacartel, 1kx, HydraVentures, and more!

https://twitter.com/pet3rpan_

This Time Will Be Different is sponsored by 1000x
https://decrypt.co/1000x]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Shrapnel's Marketplace, New Map, and 'AI Director' Feature]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/F5RQCmvH/inside-shrapnels-marketplace-new-map-and-ai-director-feature</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/F5RQCmvH/inside-shrapnels-marketplace-new-map-and-ai-director-feature"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T16:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin chats with Shrapnel's Head of Studio Don Norbury to get the latest updates on how the NFT-powered first-person sci-fi extraction shooter's development is progressing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Art of the Times': Art Blocks Founder Erick Calderon on the State of Generative Art]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zSjfRrl5/art-of-the-times-art-blocks-founder-erick-calderon-on-the-state-of-generative-art</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zSjfRrl5/art-of-the-times-art-blocks-founder-erick-calderon-on-the-state-of-generative-art"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T18:10:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Art Blocks founder and CEO Erick Calderon sat down with Sander Lutz, lead culture reporter at Decrypt's SCENE, at Art Blocks Marfa Weekend 2023. They discuss the evolution of the company and the generative art world, along with what draws art enthusiasts to be an active part of the community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt Learn: Digital Ownership Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/6udZCotB/decrypt-learn-digital-ownership-explained</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/6udZCotB/decrypt-learn-digital-ownership-explained"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T10:57:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most powerful aspects of blockchain technology is its ability to provide us genuine ownership of our digital assets. This is called digital ownership. In this video, we’ll deep dive into digital ownership, why it matters, and how web3 makes owning digital assets like our social networks, music libraries, personal data, and beyond possible. Author: Clarissa Watson, Senior Writer at Consensys.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Martin Shkreli on E/ACC and SBF in Prison]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QONaWXKZ/martin-shkreli-on-e-acc-and-sbf-in-prison</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QONaWXKZ/martin-shkreli-on-e-acc-and-sbf-in-prison"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T22:03:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reza Jafery and Martin Shkreli sit down for a casual conversation about the growing movement that is E/ACC, what songs they could recite at gunpoint, and whether or not SBF will thrive or just survive during his time in prison.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Can AI Do in Gaming?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JKuqCMao/what-can-ai-do-in-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JKuqCMao/what-can-ai-do-in-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T17:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI Arena CEO Brandon Da Silva and COO Wei Xie discuss how artificial intelligence can shape the video game experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['There Are No Real Standards': Ready Player Me CEO Timmu Tõke on Building for an Open Gaming Ecosystem]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TH3KEAI0/there-are-no-real-standards-ready-player-me-ceo-timmu-tke-on-building-for-an-open-gaming-ecosystem</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TH3KEAI0/there-are-no-real-standards-ready-player-me-ceo-timmu-tke-on-building-for-an-open-gaming-ecosystem"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T17:29:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Timmu Tõke, co-founder and CEO of Ready Player Me, joins Decrypt contributor Ryan Gladwin to discuss the startup's approach to powering avatars that are interoperable across games and metaverse platforms—and what's needed to convince the industry to adopt standards and open up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain Is 'Only Way' Forward for Gaming, Says Shrapnel Studio Head]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/fhoy7Z8f/blockchain-is-only-way-forward-for-gaming-says-shrapnel-studio-head</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/fhoy7Z8f/blockchain-is-only-way-forward-for-gaming-says-shrapnel-studio-head"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T21:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shrapnel Studio Head Don Norbury tells Kate Irwin the reasons why the upcoming first-person shooter game will offer a wide range of NFTs. He also reveals team-based gameplay plans and shares how game maps have already changed this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Social Media Sentiment Is Key to Crypto Price Discovery]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/981TBppa/social-media-sentiment-is-key-to-crypto-price-discovery</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/981TBppa/social-media-sentiment-is-key-to-crypto-price-discovery"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T23:47:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sacha Ghebali, Director of Strategy and Business Development at The TIE, says social media sentiment remains a key factor in price movements for major cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin and Ethereum. However, he notes that sentiment has turned more negative lately amid regulatory uncertainty. Ghebali believes events like the Ripple lawsuit ruling significantly impacted sentiment and prices. André Beganski interviewed him at Messari Mainnet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[500Altcoins discusses DeFi Summer and the Dubai Crypto Scene - This Time Will Be Different - Episode 2]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cI7p8AK3/500altcoins-discusses-defi-summer-and-the-dubai-crypto-scene-this-time-will-be-different-episode-2</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cI7p8AK3/500altcoins-discusses-defi-summer-and-the-dubai-crypto-scene-this-time-will-be-different-episode-2"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our host Reza Jafery is joined by Gareth Fenney aka 500Altcoins. They discuss the glory days of DeFi Summer and whether or not its a smart move for builders in the crypto space to relocate to Dubai.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>