<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-07-15T03:01:09.502Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-07-15T03:01:09.502Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Allowing Coinbase to go public was not a 'blessing' of the business: SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18775579/Allowing-Coinbase-to-go-public-was-not-a-blessing-of-the-business-SEC</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18775579/Allowing-Coinbase-to-go-public-was-not-a-blessing-of-the-business-SEC"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T02:43:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC argued that just because it approves an S-1 filing from a company, does not mean the firm is not operating, or will not operate in “violation of the law.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin ($DOGE) Co-Founder Reacts to $XRP Ruling, Suggests It Could Impact Other Crypto Assets]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18775561/Dogecoin-DOGE-Co-Founder-Reacts-to-XRP-Ruling-Suggests-It-Could-Impact-Other-Crypto-Assets</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18775561/Dogecoin-DOGE-Co-Founder-Reacts-to-XRP-Ruling-Suggests-It-Could-Impact-Other-Crypto-Assets"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T02:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Popular cryptocurrency enthusiast Billy Markus, well-known in the cryptosphere for being the co-founder of the meme-inspired cryptocurrency Dogecoin ($DOGE)m has recently shard his analysis on the repercussions of the recent ruling on the Ripple vs. SEC case, saying that if $XRP isn’t a security...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Legal Expert Warns Victory May Be Short-Lived for Ripple and XRP — Says Judge ‘Got the Law Wrong’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756c179eb7</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/legal-expert-warns-victory-may-be-short-lived-for-ripple-and-xrp-says-judge-got-the-law-wrong/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T01:38:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A legal expert has warned that the district court ruling on XRP “rests on very shaky ground.” Expecting an appeal, he cautioned that Ripple’s victory “may be a short-lived victory,” claiming that the judge “got the law wrong.”
 
Lawyer on Ruling of SEC v Ripple Case
 
Lawyer Bryan Jacoutot shared his analysis of the ruling in the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) v. Ripple case on Twitter Thursday. Jacoutot is an attorney at Election Law Group and Taylor English Duma; his practice centers on general litigation and election law. He began:
 

I’ve reviewed the district court ruling on XRP and it rests on very shaky ground. Expect an appeal.
 
He explained that the court did rule that Ripple’s sale of XRP to institutional investors amounted to an unlawful security sale. Noting tha…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Key Levels To Watch As Stellar (XLM) Price Surges Over 50%]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756c1046e7</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/key-levels-to-watch-as-stellar-xlm-price-surges/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T01:28:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price of Stellar (XLM) has seen a significant surge in the last 24 hours, making it the second top gainer of the day after XRP. This rally could be attributed to Ripple Labs’ recent legal victory, which confirmed that XRP is not considered a security in the United States.
 
 
Jed McCaleb co-founded Stellar and Ripple, so their prices may sometimes exhibit similar trends. Over the past day, XLM has risen over 46%, with gains of around 50% on the weekly chart.
 
The technical outlook for the coin shows a strong bullish influence, with demand and accumulation seeing a significant increase.
 
However, it’s important to note that with any rally, there’s always the possibility of a price pullback. XLM must maintain a price above a certain mark to avoid the bears taking over. The increase in …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>anushsamal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Very Good News]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18775523/Very-Good-News</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18775523/Very-Good-News"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T01:07:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The former CEO of bankrupt crypto lender Celsius, Alex Mashinsky, has finally been arrested. DIRTY BUBBLE MEDIA: https://twitter.com/MikeBurgersburg Support: ► Patreon: https://patreon.com/coffeezillaFollow: ► Twitter: @coffeebreak_yt► Instagram: @coffeebreak_ytCredits:3D Artist: Ed Leszczynski...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Indie Films Killed Disney's Indy, and Other Bullish Bitcoin Trends, ep 314 The Breakup]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18774147/Indie-Films-Killed-Disneys-Indy-and-Other-Bullish-Bitcoin-Trends-ep-314-The-Breakup</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18774147/Indie-Films-Killed-Disneys-Indy-and-Other-Bullish-Bitcoin-Trends-ep-314-The-Breakup"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T01:04:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[- @stclairashley on Twitter payouts- @therealroseanne on Hollywood, actor's strike- @BasedMikeLee on Atlantic Resolve- @twobitidiot on XRP- @RobertKennedyJr poll]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Serious Global Financial Crisis Coming As Debt Levels Skyrocket, Warns Legendary Investor Jim Rogers]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18775528/Serious-Global-Financial-Crisis-Coming-As-Debt-Levels-Skyrocket-Warns-Legendary-Investor-Jim-Rogers</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18775528/Serious-Global-Financial-Crisis-Coming-As-Debt-Levels-Skyrocket-Warns-Legendary-Investor-Jim-Rogers"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T01:04:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The co-founder of Soros Fund Management, a $5.61 billion private investment firm, is painting a grim picture for the United States as the country continues to accumulate massive amounts of debt. In a recent interview with Sputnik International, legendary investor Jim Rogers says the US went from...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Key Levels To Watch As Stellar (XLM) Price Surges Over 50%]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18775522/Key-Levels-To-Watch-As-Stellar-XLM-Price-Surges-Over-50</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18775522/Key-Levels-To-Watch-As-Stellar-XLM-Price-Surges-Over-50"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T01:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price of Stellar (XLM) has seen a significant surge in the last 24 hours, making it the second top gainer of the day after XRP. This rally could be attributed to Ripple Labs’ recent legal victory, which confirmed that XRP is not considered a security in the United States. Related Reading:...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[If you bought $100 of XRP in 2014, today you’d have… #shorts]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18775537/If-you-bought-100-of-XRP-in-2014-today-youd-have-shorts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18775537/If-you-bought-100-of-XRP-in-2014-today-youd-have-shorts"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T01:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you bought $100 of XRP in 2014, today you’d have… With Ripple winning partially against the SEC on July 13th, XRP rallied over 80% in a single day to a high of 93 cents, but what if you bought back in 2014?Did you know that Bybit is giving out up to $81,000 in bonuses? Just click this link to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BNB Chain impresses in daily active users, but…]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18775500/BNB-Chain-impresses-in-daily-active-users-but</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18775500/BNB-Chain-impresses-in-daily-active-users-but"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T00:30:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BNB chain outshines rivals with soaring daily active users while token value skyrockets. Yet, as metrics diverge, questions arise about its overall impact.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Coin ($BNB) and Bitcoin Cash ($BCH) Could Surge Soon, Says Popular Crypto Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18775501/Binance-Coin-BNB-and-Bitcoin-Cash-BCH-Could-Surge-Soon-Says-Popular-Crypto-Analyst</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18775501/Binance-Coin-BNB-and-Bitcoin-Cash-BCH-Could-Surge-Soon-Says-Popular-Crypto-Analyst"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T00:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A popular cryptocurrency analyst has voiced his optimism for two popular altcoins, Binance Coin ($BNB) and Bitcoin Cash ($BCH), suggesting both could see their prices surge further in the near future. The pseudonymous analyst, known as Kaleo on the microblogging platform Twitter, has been...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Distress Prompts Fir Tree, a Hedge Fund, to Seek Profit From Turmoil]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756c1d473a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/07/14/crypto-distress-prompts-fir-tree-a-hedge-fund-to-seek-profit-from-turmoil/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T00:12:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Fir Tree is at its best when we identify opportunities that are mispriced, dislocated or complex. Rarely do we encounter situations that are all three, but that is precisely what we are seeing in digital assets right now,” Fir Tree said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Central Banks Warn Trillion-Dollar Debt Hammering US Dollar, Reveal Plans To Increase Chinese Yuan Holdings]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18775498/Central-Banks-Warn-Trillion-Dollar-Debt-Hammering-US-Dollar-Reveal-Plans-To-Increase-Chinese-Yuan-Holdings</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18775498/Central-Banks-Warn-Trillion-Dollar-Debt-Hammering-US-Dollar-Reveal-Plans-To-Increase-Chinese-Yuan-Holdings"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T00:04:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Central banks around the world no longer look at the US dollar with the same certainty they did just years ago, according to a new survey. Institutional asset manager Invesco surveyed 57 central banks and found they’re concerned America’s behavior on the geopolitical stage, plus its surging debt...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not Just XRP: Stellar (XLM) Rips by More Than 57% in One Day After Judge Issues Ruling in SEC’s Ripple Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18775493/Not-Just-XRP-Stellar-XLM-Rips-by-More-Than-57-in-One-Day-After-Judge-Issues-Ruling-in-SECs-Ripple-Lawsuit</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18775493/Not-Just-XRP-Stellar-XLM-Rips-by-More-Than-57-in-One-Day-After-Judge-Issues-Ruling-in-SECs-Ripple-Lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T00:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XRP isn’t the only crypto asset that’s soaring after a groundbreaking ruling was issued Thursday in the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission’s (SEC) lawsuit against Ripple. XRP challenger and payments blockchain Stellar (XLM) pumped by more than 57% on Thursday, going from trading around...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Won’t Comment on Appealing the Ripple Win]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18775490/SEC-Wont-Comment-on-Appealing-the-Ripple-Win</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18775490/SEC-Wont-Comment-on-Appealing-the-Ripple-Win"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T23:50:15.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlockFi CEO neglected warnings about FTX prior to collapse, court docs say]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18775488/BlockFi-CEO-neglected-warnings-about-FTX-prior-to-collapse-court-docs-say</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18775488/BlockFi-CEO-neglected-warnings-about-FTX-prior-to-collapse-court-docs-say"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T23:45:47.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bank of America Faces Scrutiny After Coinbase User Alleges the Bank Closed His Account Over Bitcoin Transactions]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756c1f9aa0</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bank-of-america-faces-scrutiny-after-coinbase-user-alleges-the-bank-closed-his-account-over-bitcoin-transactions/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T23:40:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bank of America has come under scrutiny after a Coinbase user claimed that the bank closed his account over Bitcoin transactions. Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong quickly addressed the issue, asking other users if they have encountered the same problem with Bank of America.
 
Coinbase’s CEO Raises Concerns Over Account Closures at Bank of America
 
Bank of America (BOFA) came under scrutiny on Wednesday when Muneeb Ali, co-founder of Stacks, a Bitcoin layer for smart contracts, revealed on Twitter that the bank unexpectedly closed his bank account, which he had been using for 15 years, without giving a reason. He strongly suspects that the closure was due to him using the bank account for bitcoin transactions through Coinbase. “This is a war on bitcoin & crypto,” he tweeted.
 
Coinbase CEO Bri…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arbitrum Could Be The Best Layer-2 Play In The Bull Market, Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756c187d23</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/arbitrum-could-be-the-best-layer-2-play/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T23:28:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arbitrum is one of the many Layer-2 rollups in the space helping to make transactions faster and cheaper on Ethereum. However, Arbitrum has managed to stand out from the rest, emerging as a leader in this sector.
 
Arbitrum Controls Majority Of Layer-2 TVL
 
Arbitrum, despite being younger than some of the Ethereum Layer-2 blockchains in the market, has been able to snag a significant portion of the market share for itself. According to data from DeFiLlama, the Layer-2 blockchain accounts for approximately 70% of in total value locked (TVL) across all Layer-2 blockchains.
 
 
Out of the over $4 billion locked across each of these networks, Arbitrum’s TVL is currently sitting at $2.794 billion. This puts it ahead of its predecessor Polygon, and fierce rival Optimism, both of which have TVL …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Best Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pierre Rochard: Not your Keys, Not your Bitcoin #bitcoin #crypto #shorts]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18775473/Pierre-Rochard-Not-your-Keys-Not-your-Bitcoin-bitcoin-crypto-shorts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18775473/Pierre-Rochard-Not-your-Keys-Not-your-Bitcoin-bitcoin-crypto-shorts"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T23:09:13.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Crypto to Buy Now 14 July – Lido DAO, Polygon, ApeCoin]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18775461/Best-Crypto-to-Buy-Now-14-July-Lido-DAO-Polygon-ApeCoin</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18775461/Best-Crypto-to-Buy-Now-14-July-Lido-DAO-Polygon-ApeCoin"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T23:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arbitrum Could Be The Best Layer-2 Play In The Bull Market, Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18775454/Arbitrum-Could-Be-The-Best-Layer-2-Play-In-The-Bull-Market-Heres-Why</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18775454/Arbitrum-Could-Be-The-Best-Layer-2-Play-In-The-Bull-Market-Heres-Why"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T23:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arbitrum is one of the many Layer-2 rollups in the space helping to make transactions faster and cheaper on Ethereum. However, Arbitrum has managed to stand out from the rest, emerging as a leader in this sector. Arbitrum Controls Majority Of Layer-2 TVL Arbitrum, despite being younger than some...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s time for the SEC to settle with Coinbase and Ripple]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18775455/Its-time-for-the-SEC-to-settle-with-Coinbase-and-Ripple</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18775455/Its-time-for-the-SEC-to-settle-with-Coinbase-and-Ripple"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T22:56:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Securities and Exchange Commission should recognize it’s time to settle its cases against Coinbase and Ripple Labs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC acknowledges Fidelity, VanEck, WisdomTree, and Invesco Spot Bitcoin ETF applications]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18775449/SEC-acknowledges-Fidelity-VanEck-WisdomTree-and-Invesco-Spot-Bitcoin-ETF-applications</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18775449/SEC-acknowledges-Fidelity-VanEck-WisdomTree-and-Invesco-Spot-Bitcoin-ETF-applications"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T22:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mysterious self-proclaimed Binance stakeholder “Eeon” seeks to intervene in SEC’s suit against the exchange]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18775446/Mysterious-self-proclaimed-Binance-stakeholder-Eeon-seeks-to-intervene-in-SECs-suit-against-the-exchange</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18775446/Mysterious-self-proclaimed-Binance-stakeholder-Eeon-seeks-to-intervene-in-SECs-suit-against-the-exchange"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T22:40:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Eeon,” an individual that claims to represent Binance customers, attempted to enter an ongoing securities case concerning the exchange company on July 14. Eeon and the affected customers wrote in a filing: “We are the proper parties to this matter as we have been identified by the Court in its...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA) Explodes Through Resistance in XRP-Fueled Rally]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18775438/Cardano-ADA-Explodes-Through-Resistance-in-XRP-Fueled-Rally</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18775438/Cardano-ADA-Explodes-Through-Resistance-in-XRP-Fueled-Rally"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T22:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple’s victory over the SEC has sparked a renewed wave of optimism, with Cardano registering an impressive 22% gain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Fired over 1,000 Employees in Recent Weeks: Report]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756c04d1bd</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/binance-fired-over-1000-employees-in-recent-weeksreport/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T22:31:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance reportedly sacked over 1,000 employees in recent weeks, further shrinking its previous 8,000-strong global workforce. The Wall  
Street Journal (WSJ) reported the mass retrenchment today (Friday), citing an  
insider source. 
Binance Cuts More Jobs Globally
Former  
employees told WSJ that more staff members across  
the exchange’s global markets were fired during this week, with customer-service workers mostly  
affected. In India alone, about 40 employees in this category were let go, the outlet said.
The  
downsizing comes as regulatory pressure continues to mount on the exchange,  
which recently endured an exodus of senior  
executives. Already, about 50 employees working for the exchange’s  
so-called independent US subsidiary have been booted out.
However,  
earlier this mon…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Solomon Oladipupo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple CEO Garlinghouse Takes On SEC, Calls Them A ‘Bully’ In Wake Of XRP Ruling]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756c0512cc</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ripple-ceo-takes-on-sec-calls-them-a-bully/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T22:28:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse has stated that the recent federal court ruling has confirmed that XRP is “not a security”. The ruling provides the digital payments company with greater flexibility to pursue various business opportunities across the globe.
 
Speaking on Bloomberg TV, Garlinghouse expressed relief that the company could now promote the various use cases for Ripple and its technology without the fear of regulatory action. 
 
Ripple CEO Calls Out SEC For Anti-Crypto Stance
 
The ruling signifies a win for the crypto industry over the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), which sued Ripple in late 2020. The SEC accused the firm, co-founder Chris Larsen, and Garlinghouse of misleading investors by selling more than $1 billion worth of tokens without registering them.
 
US D…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Goes All In on AI: Can It Compete With Google, ChatGPT and MidJourney?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148658</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148658/meta-all-in-ai-google-chagpt-midjourney"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T21:40:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meta’s CM3leon model and a reported commercial version of LLaMA could upend the generative AI industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Representative Ritchie Torres Calls for Investigation of SEC Over Prometheum’s License]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756c0119ab</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/us-representative-ritchie-torres-calls-for-investigation-of-sec-over-prometheums-license/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T21:39:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Rep. Ritchie Torres has called for an investigation into the special purpose broker-dealer (SPBD) license given by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to Prometheum, a cryptocurrency exchange platform. In two letters sent to U.S. Comptroller General Gene Dodaro and SEC Inspector General Deborah Jeffries, Torres calls for investigation of the “backroom deals” allegedly brokered between the SEC and Prometheum.
U.S. Rep. Ritchie Torres Requests Investigation Into Prometheum’s License
Ritchie Torres, a U.S. representative for New York, is requesting an official investigation on the licenses the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) gave to Prometheum, a digital assets trading platform that Torres states “does not trade digital assets.”
On July 13, Torres sent two let…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Slashes Staff But Says Reports of Thousands Being Cut Are 'Way Off']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148657</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148657/binance-slashes-staff-wont-say-how-much"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T21:28:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rumors swirled earlier in the year that the controversial digital asset behemoth would drastically reduce its headcount.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase to Pause Staking in California, New Jersey, South Carolina and Wisconsin]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756c0380f7</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/07/14/coinbase-to-pause-staking-in-california-new-jersey-south-carolina-and-wisconsin/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T21:13:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[tk]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nelson Wang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jay-Z’s Roc Nation and Puma Drop NFT-Enhanced Sneakers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148651</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148651/jay-z-roc-nation-puma-drop-nft-enhanced-sneakers"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T20:32:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Inspired by the 50th anniversary of hip-hop, each pair of Puma kicks comes tied to exclusive digital content, including new music.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ali Shutler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Massive Layoff: Over 1,000 Employees Fired]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756c0f9eb1</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/binance-massive-layoff-over-1000-employees-fired/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T20:29:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance, one of the world’s largest cryptocurrency exchanges, has laid off over 1,000 employees in recent weeks, according to a report by the Wall Street Journal. 
 
The ongoing exercise could reportedly result in Binance losing more than a third of its staff. The job cuts come amid increasing regulatory scrutiny of the cryptocurrency industry, and just weeks after the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) sued Binance and its CEO Changpeng Zhao.
 
As reported by Bitcoinist, last week several high-level executives also resigned from Binance, including its Chief Strategy Officer Patrick Hillmann. 
 
While Binance has said it will defend itself “vigorously” against the allegations made by U.S. regulators, the job cuts suggest that the exchange may be feeling the pressure from increas…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Could the Ripple Ruling Spell the End of Regulation by Enforcement?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756c0fd372</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/07/14/could-the-ripple-ruling-spell-the-end-of-regulation-by-enforcement/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T20:26:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A long-awaited district judge’s ruling that some XRP token sales were not investment contracts will likely eventually lead to a bipartisan regulatory framework that is more favorable to the pro-crypto crowd in Congress, writes John Rizzo.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John  Rizzo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aave DAO Votes to Launch GHO Stablecoin on Ethereum Mainnet]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148627</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148627/aave-dao-votes-to-launch-gho-stablecoin-on-ethereum-mainnet"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T20:15:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aave's GHO stablecoin has been in development for the last year, and its aim is to make markets more accessible and efficient for its users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Restricts Ethereum, Solana Staking in Four US States]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148648</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148648/coinbase-restricts-ethereum-solana-staking-in-four-us-states"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T20:13:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The announcement comes after 11 states alleged Coinbase was violating securities laws.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kim Dotcom Teases Bitcoin Cash 'Killer App’ as Bitcache Heads for Liquidation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148621</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148621/kim-dotcom-teases-bitcoin-cash-killer-app-as-bitcache-heads-for-liquidation"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T19:55:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kim Dotcom said on Twitter he would "love to see FileShop become a #BitcoinCash killer app."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi Lender MarginFi Fuels Growth With Loyalty Points, Spurring Talk of ‘Solana Renaissance’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756c0bdc4e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/07/14/defi-lender-marginfi-fuels-growth-with-loyalty-points-spurring-talk-of-solana-renaissance/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T19:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MarginFi has doubled its user base in two weeks after unveiling a loyalty points program that some believe will lead to a token airdrop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gucci's Iconic Fashion Is Reimagined in Christie's NFT Art Auction]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148628</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148628/guccis-iconic-fashion-reimagined-christies-nft-art-auction"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T19:44:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artists put a fresh spin on luxury fashion house Gucci's past, paired with other generative digital art pieces—some made with AI tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephanie Hirschmiller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celsius Founder Alex Mashinsky’s Bail Set at $40 Million, Travel Restricted Amid Fraud Charges]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756df527c9</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/celsius-founder-alex-mashinskys-bail-set-at-40-million-travel-restricted-amid-fraud-charges/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T19:32:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just before the now-defunct crypto lender Celsius was charged by three U.S. federal regulators — the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC), Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), and Federal Trade Commission (FTC) — its former CEO, Alexander Mashinsky, was arrested on fraud charges Thursday. A U.S. judge has set Mashinsky’s bail at $40 million and restricted him from traveling.
 
Fraud Charges Lead to $40 Million Bail Bond for Former Celsius CEO Mashinsky
 
Alexander Mashinsky, founder and former CEO of Celsius, was arrested and charged with fraud Thursday in New York. Mashinsky’s legal team said he vehemently denies the allegations and described the charges as unfounded. “[Mashinsky] vehemently denies the allegations brought today,” attorney Jonathan Ohring said in an email to Th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Crypto Prices Buckle After Altcoin Frenzy on XRP Ruling]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756df022f9</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/07/14/bitcoin-crypto-prices-buckle-after-altcoin-frenzy-on-xrp-ruling/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T19:02:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple's XRP was down 25% from its highest levels on Thursday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple's Legal Win Means It's Time for Crypto to Stand Up to the SEC]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756df1badd</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/07/14/ripples-legal-win-means-its-time-for-crypto-to-stand-up-to-the-sec/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T18:47:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company's partial victory in court is a watershed moment for the crypto regulatory fight, ConsenSys Director of Global Regulatory Matters Bill Hughes argues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Hughes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Ripple’s Partial XRP Win Means for Other Crypto Firms Fighting SEC]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756df1bad1</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/07/14/what-ripples-partial-xrp-win-means-for-other-crypto-firms-fighting-sec/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T18:47:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase and Binance have a new precedent to cite in court – if the decision survives potential appeal. That’s no sure thing, lawyers said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandali Handagama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is the Metaverse a 'Global Panopticon'?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756df1bac9</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/07/14/is-the-metaverse-a-global-panopticon/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T18:47:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an excerpt from her new book "Beyond Data," lawyer Elizabeth M. Renieris argues emerging extended-reality technologies erode individual and societal privacy rights.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Renieris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The End Of Money? BlackRock CEO Claims Crypto Will Surpass Traditional Currencies Worldwide]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756df3a57a</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/blackrock-crypto-surpass-traditional-currencies/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T18:29:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an interview with CNBC, BlackRock CEO Larry Fink discussed the potential of crypto as an international asset that can transcend the value of traditional currencies. Fink noted the recent depreciation of the US dollar and the appreciation of the digital asset industry over the past five years, pointing to the broad-based and worldwide interest in the asset class.
 
Crypto To Crush Cash?
 
According to Fink, Over the past five years, BlackRock has seen a significant increase in interest from investors regarding the role of crypto in their portfolios. Fink believes that crypto is an international asset that has the potential to transcend any other currency, as it is not tied to any particular country or government.
 
Fink also emphasized BlackRock’s commitment to ensuring the safety and pr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dr. Disrespect's Shooter 'Deadrop' Gets Bigger and Better]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148604</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148604/dr-disrespect-shooter-deadrop-expands-snapshot-vi-release"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T18:22:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PREVIEW: Movement still feels sluggish, but Deadrop's new Snapshot VI build shows progress elsewhere while expanding the experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dr. Disrespect's 'Deadrop': Early Access Gameplay From Snapshot VI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/8l21EHoa/dr-disrespects-deadrop-early-access-gameplay-from-snapshot-vi</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/8l21EHoa/dr-disrespects-deadrop-early-access-gameplay-from-snapshot-vi"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T18:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin playtests Dr. Disrespect and Midnight Society's first-person shooter Deadrop and shares the latest game updates, as well as her opinions on the game in development. Currently, Deadrop offers Polygon Founders Pass NFTs with no other crypto plans revealed just yet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple’s XRP Ruling a ‘Milestone Win’ for Crypto Industry, Says J.P. Morgan]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756dfd1f89</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/07/14/ripples-xrp-ruling-a-milestone-win-for-crypto-industry-says-jp-morgan/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T18:15:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A summary judgment partially in favor of payments network Ripple represents a milestone win for the crypto industry and provides legal clarity as to what does and doesn’t represent a security, J.P. Morgan wrote in a research note Friday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Trading Volume Surges 1351% as Major Crypto Exchanges Embrace the Token]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756dfd1f83</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/07/14/xrp-trading-volume-surges-1351-as-major-crypto-exchanges-embrace-the-token/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T18:15:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The spike in trading activity came after a partial win in a lawsuit against the SEC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock CEO Larry Fink: Crypto Will 'Transcend Any One Currency']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148612</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148612/blackrock-ceo-larry-fink-crypto-transcend-currency"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T17:34:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The boss of the world’s biggest asset manager today continued to sing Bitcoin’s praises.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Buy 'The Flash' as an NFT Just Weeks After Hitting Theaters]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148597</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148597/you-can-buy-flash-nft-just-weeks-after-hitting-theaters"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T16:19:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DC Comics superhero movie "The Flash" will be released via NFT on July 18, the very same day it hits traditional digital platforms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ali Shutler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Founder Sam Bankman-Fried Is Getting Lonely and Needs a Maid]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148578</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148578/sbf-friends-colleagues-household-help-approved-visitors"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T15:54:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The lawyers asked that "close friends and colleagues of Bankman-Fried’s parents and household help" be allowed to visit without security checks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Are CryptoPunks? The Ethereum NFT Sensation's Wild Ride]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=79859</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-are-cryptopunks-ethereum-nft-avatars"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T13:51:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some of the oldest ever NFTs are now some of the most desirable—and expensive—crypto collectibles. Here’s how they work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken, Crypto.com Join Coinbase in Relisting XRP After Court Ruling]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148562</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148562/kraken-crypto-com-join-coinbase-relisting-after-court-ruling"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T10:47:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Though the judge’s decision didn’t relate to secondary sales, exchanges are signaling greater confidence in trading XRP.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alys Key</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Court Sets Former Celsius CEO Alex Mashinsky’s Bail at $40M]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148554</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148554/court-sets-former-celsius-ceo-alex-mashinsky-bail-40m"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T10:19:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celsius’ boss Alex Mashinsky is set to be released on bail after agreeing to a $40 million personal recognizance bond.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multichain Shutters Operations After Chinese Police Take CEO’s Sister Into Custody]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148559</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148559/multichain-shutters-operations-chinese-police-take-ceo-sister-custody"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T10:01:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese police have detained Multichain's CEO and his sister, and impounded operational funds, forcing the team to shutter operations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Ripple Effect: Crypto Market Soars $73.5B After Judge's Ruling in XRP SEC Case]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148555</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148555/the-ripple-effect-crypto-market-soars-73-5b-after-judges-ruling-xrp-sec-case"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T09:46:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Positive gains spread across the board as Ripple’s partial win against the SEC uplifts the crypto market’s spirits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ruling on Ripple XRP Sales Sparks Optimism at Coinbase]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148541</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148541/ruling-on-ripple-xrp-sales-sparks-optimism-coinbase"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T07:28:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Judge Torres' partial ruling on the SEC vs. Ripple Labs case yesterday has added a new dimension to the agency's lawsuit against Coinbase.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Maximal Extractable Value (MEV)? What Blockchain Miners Need To Know]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148542</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-maximal-extractable-value-mev-what-blockchain-miners-need-to-know"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T02:22:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MEV hinges on the fact that miners and other participants in the validation process can reorder and manipulate transactions for their own personal gain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Reiff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unpacking the Federal Lawsuits Against Celsius Network and Its Ex-CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148522</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148522/unpacking-the-many-damning-federal-lawsuits-against-celsius"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T23:23:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Collapsed crypto lender Celsius Network and its ex-bosses have been sued by the DOJ, SEC, FTC, and the CTFC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['More and More' Game Publishers Will Embrace NFTs: Mythical Games CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/wBWogSkl/more-and-more-game-publishers-will-embrace-nfts-mythical-games-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/wBWogSkl/more-and-more-game-publishers-will-embrace-nfts-mythical-games-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T22:28:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the wake of EA Sports and Fortnite creator Epic Games embracing Nike's NFT platform, Mythical Games CEO John Linden tells Decrypt's Andrew Hayward how quickly he expects to see more major traditional game publishers enter the blockchain space and how quickly the industry will scale.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Actors Approve Strike as AI Fears Bring Hollywood to a Standstill]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148519</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148519/actors-approve-strike-ai-fears-bring-hollywood-standstill"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T21:27:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SAG-AFTRA will officially strike at midnight, joining striking writers with demands over AI, compensation, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase to Restart XRP Trading After Judge's Ruling in Ripple Case]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148517</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148517/coinbase-to-restart-xrp-trading-after-judges-ruling-in-ripple-case"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T20:03:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To be clear, Judge Analisa Torres has not issued a ruling on secondary sales of XRP "because that question is not properly before the Court."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Hits $2,000 for First Time Since May Following XRP Ruling]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148509</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148509/ethereum-hits-2000-for-first-time-since-may-following-xrp-ruling"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T18:56:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nearly everything’s green after a federal judge weighed in on whether XRP is a security, with Ethereum recapturing $2,000.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The US Dollar Is Under Threat, Says Circle CEO in Warning to Congress]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148498</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148498/the-us-dollar-is-under-threat-says-circle-ceo-in-warning-to-congress"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T18:38:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jeremy Allaire warns that US dollar dominance is waning as other nations outpace the US on financial innovation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is XRP? The Cryptocurrency Created by Ripple Founders]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=5709</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/ripple"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T18:31:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XRP is a type of cryptocurrency designed to help banks move money more quickly, and cheaply than existing methods. It is largely spearheaded by Ripple.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Hussey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Did XRP Restart Alt Season? Solana, Cardano, Polygon Up Double Digits]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148503</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148503/did-xrp-restart-alt-season-solana-cardano-polygon-up-double-digits"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T18:11:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most of the tokens previously deemed securities by the SEC are seeing large gains upon a federal court’s ruling in the XRP case.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Waging ‘Unlawful Harassment Campaign’ in Dogecoin Lawsuit, Says Attorney]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148480</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148480/elon-musk-waging-unlawful-harassment-campaign-in-dogecoin-lawsuit-says-attorney"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T17:26:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The billionaire's legal team is using a "bottomless war chest" to fund its dirty tactics, the Dogecoin investors' attorney claims.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CryptoPunk DJ Seedphrase Signs to WME, Plans to Release Music]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148476</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148476/cryptopunk-dj-seedphrase-signs-to-wme-plans-to-release-music"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T17:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Helmet-wearing musician Seedphrase, owner of the rarest CryptoPunks NFT, is also set to launch a new community project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ali Shutler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Are All the Federal Charges Celsius Founder Mashinsky Faces]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148450</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148450/feds-hit-former-celsius-ceo-alex-mashinsky-with-seven-criminal-charges"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T16:21:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The brains behind bankrupt crypto lender Celsius have been hit with a number of serious criminal charges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Judge Rules Ripple Sales of XRP Were Not Securities—Except to Institutions]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148460</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148460/judge-rules-ripple-xrp-securities-institutions"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T16:18:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Programmatic sales of XRP made by the company were not illegal, says the court. But Ripple isn't off the hook just yet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Surges 29% on Judge's Ruling in Ripple SEC Case]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148467</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148467/xrp-surges-29-on-judges-ruling-in-ripple-sec-case"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T16:12:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is XRP a security? Traders react positively to the latest development in the ongoing SEC case against Ripple over the cryptocurrency.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ConsenSys Mesh's TachyonX Fund Wants to Cut the Red Tape for Crypto Founders]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148311</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148311/consensys-mesh-tachyonx"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T15:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TachyonX will offer $150,000 in upfront funding to blockchain startups, along with mentorship from crypto industry heavyweights.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Now Pay Merchants on Telegram in Bitcoin—Here’s How it Works]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148441</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148441/telegram-now-lets-users-pay-merchants-bitcoin-heres-how-works"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T14:26:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new third-party chatbot powered by the TON blockchain allows instant Bitcoin, USDT, and TON payments via Telegram.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celsius CEO Alex Mashinsky Arrested—SEC, CFTC and FTC Sue for Fraud]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148431</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148431/sec-sues-bankrupt-crypto-lender-celsius-network-ceo-alex-mashinsky"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T13:24:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celsius and its former CEO have been charged with a host of fresh allegations from four different government agencies Thursday morning.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Safe Adds ERC-4337 Compatibility in Account Abstraction Push]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148430</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148430/safe-adds-smart-wallet-compatibility-account-abstraction-push"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T13:01:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ERC-4337 is named simply the "first starting stone" in a wider move towards account abstraction, by Safe co-founder Richard Meissner.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi Startup Ondo Expands Yield-Earning Stablecoin Alternative to Polygon]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148370</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148370/ondo-finance-tokenized-treasuries-stablecoin-alternative-ethereum-polygon"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first company to tokenize U.S. Treasuries wants to expand its market by moving beyond the Ethereum mainnet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Cites Supreme Court Student Loans Decision in SEC Legal Battle]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148428</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148428/coinbase-cites-supreme-court-student-loans-decision-in-sec-legal-battle"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T12:33:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The exchange argues that the SEC needed Congressional support before launching its sweeping crackdown on the crypto industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tron DAO To Kick Off Builder Tour In New York]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145205</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145205/tron-dao-to-kick-off-builder-tour-in-new-york"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T10:54:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Would-be Tron developers are invited to board the “blockchain bullet train” at a series of hackathons across the United States.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Public Good or Panopticon? Arkham’s ‘Dox-to-Earn’ Marketplace Cuts at Heart of Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148410</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148410/public-good-panopticon-arkhams-dox-earn-marketplace-cuts-heart-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T09:56:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arkham's new intelligence exchange polarized the community on its announcement, but is the idea really so alien to crypto's founding ethos?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gran Saga Unlimited Early Access: Inside the Anime MMORPG on Aptos]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JeFWMVwo/gran-saga-unlimited-early-access-inside-the-anime-mmorpg-on-aptos</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JeFWMVwo/gran-saga-unlimited-early-access-inside-the-anime-mmorpg-on-aptos"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T21:46:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin plays Gran Saga: Unlimited's second community playtest, reports her findings, and offer her opinion and insights on the upcoming game, which will offer optional Aptos NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[100 Thieves' Moe Says Blockchain Games Will 'Eventually' Be Accepted by Livestreamers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/xHhh62ID/100-thieves-moe-says-blockchain-games-will-eventually-be-accepted-by-livestreamers</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/xHhh62ID/100-thieves-moe-says-blockchain-games-will-eventually-be-accepted-by-livestreamers"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T16:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[100 Thieves content creator and gamer Moe also goes by "Yassuo" online after his favorite League of Legends character. Decrypt's Kate Irwin asks him about 100 Thieves' future crypto plans and whether Moe thinks creators like xQc and Pokimane might ever come around to blockchain games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Games of the Future Are Going to Be Different," Says Splinterlands Cofounder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/sQv6zcil/games-of-the-future-are-going-to-be-different-says-splinterlands-cofounder</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/sQv6zcil/games-of-the-future-are-going-to-be-different-says-splinterlands-cofounder"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T20:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Splinterlands Cofounder Matt Rosen tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about how the game has evolved over its five-year history and why he doesn't listen to the FUD around crypto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Champions Ascension: Like 'For Honor' with NFTs?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/gvM9ajww/inside-champions-ascension-like-for-honor-with-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/gvM9ajww/inside-champions-ascension-like-for-honor-with-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T22:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plai Labs Marketing Director Payton Kaleiwahea tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about player response to the combat game Champions Ascension in development, which offers arena combat, raid bosses, AI landscape features, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Activision VP Michael Lee: Gaming Is Crypto's 'Killer App']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/M9ulXrb3/ex-activision-vp-michael-lee-gaming-is-cryptos-killer-app</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/M9ulXrb3/ex-activision-vp-michael-lee-gaming-is-cryptos-killer-app"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Activision Vice President Michael Lee is now the SVP of Growth at Matter Labs. At the 3XP gaming conference, Lee sat down with Decrypt's Kate Irwin to discuss crypto gaming and give his predictions for the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Behind the Scenes with AMGI Studios and My Pet Hooligan]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/eQ71oapI/behind-the-scenes-with-amgi-studios-and-my-pet-hooligan</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/eQ71oapI/behind-the-scenes-with-amgi-studios-and-my-pet-hooligan"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T21:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin goes to Burbank, California for a behind-the-scenes tour of AMGI Studios, the developers of upcoming game My Pet Hooligan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Legend of Arcardia Chose Sui Over EVM Chains]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/H6JSRJIk/why-legend-of-arcardia-chose-sui-over-evm-chains</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/H6JSRJIk/why-legend-of-arcardia-chose-sui-over-evm-chains"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T21:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Legend of Arcadia Executive Producer Andy Lee tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the game and why they switched from EVM to new protocol Sui.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rumble Racing Star Game Preview: Is This Mario Kart With NFTs?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/lXVkuaeq/rumble-racing-star-game-preview-is-this-mario-kart-with-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/lXVkuaeq/rumble-racing-star-game-preview-is-this-mario-kart-with-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T16:47:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin shares a first look at Delabs' upcoming lawn mower racing game Rumble Racing Star, which offers a large cast of quirky characters pulled from the worlds of Bored Ape Yacht Club, Pudgy Penguins, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Laguna Games Turned Down 'Game of Thrones' for Crypto Unicorns]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/IqET3GYs/why-laguna-games-turned-down-game-of-thrones-for-crypto-unicorns</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/IqET3GYs/why-laguna-games-turned-down-game-of-thrones-for-crypto-unicorns"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T21:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin chats with Laguna Games about why the team chose to move away from an offer with WB Games to develop a Game of Thrones licensed title—and made Crypto Unicorns instead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mythical Games CEO John Linden on NFL Rivals Topping 1M Downloads]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/nDhvMd8r/mythical-games-ceo-john-linden-on-nfl-rivals-topping-1m-downloads</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/nDhvMd8r/mythical-games-ceo-john-linden-on-nfl-rivals-topping-1m-downloads"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T23:49:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mythical Games just raised a $37 million Series C1 round on the back of the early success of NFL Rivals, which has already topped a million downloads in two months. Mythical CEO John Linden joins Decrypt's Andrew Hayward to discuss the launch and impact of NFL Rivals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Ava Labs Is Approaching Gaming on Avalanche]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/M4TqVEkK/how-ava-labs-is-approaching-gaming-on-avalanche</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/M4TqVEkK/how-ava-labs-is-approaching-gaming-on-avalanche"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T22:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At 3XP, Ava Labs Head of Gaming Ed Chang sat down with Decrypt's Kate Irwin to discuss some of the biggest Avalanche-based games on the horizon and how the company is approaching and thinking about Web3 gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ogimi Founder David Gull on Why AI Should Be Your Meditation Coach]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DnNqBruk/ogimi-founder-david-gull-on-why-ai-should-be-your-meditation-coach</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DnNqBruk/ogimi-founder-david-gull-on-why-ai-should-be-your-meditation-coach"/>
        <updated>2023-06-25T18:45:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ogimi founder David Gull speaks with Decrypt's Jason Nelson about its AI-driven meditation guides and how the technology can enable a more unique, custom-tailored meditation experience for users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VaynerSports Gaming VP Discusses Web3 Content Creators, Decentralized Streaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/1MvGbnK5/vaynersports-gaming-vp-discusses-web3-content-creators-decentralized-streaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/1MvGbnK5/vaynersports-gaming-vp-discusses-web3-content-creators-decentralized-streaming"/>
        <updated>2023-06-24T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Darren Glover, VP of Gaming at talent management agency VaynerSports, sat down with Decrypt's Kate Irwin at the 3XP expo to discuss the challenges faced by Web3-centric content creators, the current state of the esports market, and how decentralized streaming platforms can challenge centralized leaders like Twitch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NYXL Co-Founder on the State of Esports and Crypto Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/xDHUNFLB/nyxl-co-founder-on-the-state-of-esports-and-crypto-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/xDHUNFLB/nyxl-co-founder-on-the-state-of-esports-and-crypto-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-06-23T22:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rohit Gupta, co-founder of esports team NYXL, chats with Decrypt's Kate Irwin at the 3XP expo to discuss challenges faced by the esports industry and opportunities and experiments in Web3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is GameBridge? Inside Shrapnel's Gaming Innovation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/xqVjzGLr/what-is-gamebridge-inside-shrapnels-gaming-innovation</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/xqVjzGLr/what-is-gamebridge-inside-shrapnels-gaming-innovation"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marc Mercuri, Head of Platform for Web3 shooter Shrapnel, speaks with Decrypt's Kate Irwin at the 3XP expo about GameBridge, a feature that simplifies blockchain item composability and interoperability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gods Unchained Executive Producer Discusses Epic Games Store Move]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/hjLymzUL/gods-unchained-executive-producer-discusses-epic-games-store-move</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/hjLymzUL/gods-unchained-executive-producer-discusses-epic-games-store-move"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daniel Paez, Executive Producer on Immutable X-based card-battler Gods Unchained, discusses the long-running NFT game's launch on the Epic Games Store and the opportunity it provides.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Play-to-Earn Is Not Dead. It Will Never Die' Says Words with Friends Creator Paul Bettner]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/znmOo9vp/play-to-earn-is-not-dead-it-will-never-die-says-words-with-friends-creator-paul-bettner</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/znmOo9vp/play-to-earn-is-not-dead-it-will-never-die-says-words-with-friends-creator-paul-bettner"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T14:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Words With Friends and Wildcard Creator Paul Bettner tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about his perspective on Axie Infinity and Web3 games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cross the Ages Game Review: A Tough But Rewarding Card Battler]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/2PfzFDVY/cross-the-ages-game-review-a-tough-but-rewarding-card-battler</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/2PfzFDVY/cross-the-ages-game-review-a-tough-but-rewarding-card-battler"/>
        <updated>2023-06-18T12:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cross the Ages is a digital collectible card game that challenges players to duel online opponents—and you can even mint your cards as tradable NFTs. It's complex and difficult to grasp at first, but this mobile-first game has some serious strategic upside. GG contributor Ryan Gladwin puts Cross the Ages through its paces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>