<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-04-14T15:15:05.832Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-04-14T15:15:05.832Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can Solana’s NFTs Boost SOL’s Price Prediction? Smart Investors are Backing Metacade As Tokens List on Exchanges]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18112818/Can-Solanas-NFTs-Boost-SOLs-Price-Prediction-Smart-Investors-are-Backing-Metacade-As-Tokens-List-on-Exchanges</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18112818/Can-Solanas-NFTs-Boost-SOLs-Price-Prediction-Smart-Investors-are-Backing-Metacade-As-Tokens-List-on-Exchanges"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T15:05:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While Ethereum is the primary home of NFT collections, Solana NFTs have steadily increased in popularity since 2021. However, recent developments in the ecosystem have led some to wonder how Solana price predictions have changed over the past few weeks. Meanwhile, rising star Metacade has...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK’s New Technology Department to Tackle Country’s Metaverse, Web3 Strategy]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7524464c7d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/04/14/uks-new-technology-department-to-tackle-countrys-metaverse-web3-strategy/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T15:05:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The department will explore economic growth, investment and business opportunities in these areas along with implications on regulation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camomile Shumba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC Protects the System, Not You]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18112816/The-SEC-Protects-the-System-Not-You</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18112816/The-SEC-Protects-the-System-Not-You"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T15:05:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC’s attack on Coinbase puts their malicious disregard for regulatory clarity and their clear intent to crush this industry on full display]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US-based drink retailer Boba Guys taps Solana for loyalty rewards program]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18112819/US-based-drink-retailer-Boba-Guys-taps-Solana-for-loyalty-rewards-program</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18112819/US-based-drink-retailer-Boba-Guys-taps-Solana-for-loyalty-rewards-program"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T15:04:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Boba Guys is a popular US tea retailer that operates in California and New York. Solana Foundation recently invested $100,000 into Boba Guys. Boba Guys has now tapped Solana for its loyalty rewards program. Solana has been chosen by popular US tea retailer Boba Guys for its loyalty rewards...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitrue Exchange Hacked, Resulting In $23 Million Worth of Crypto Stolen]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e752446b2f7</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitrue-hacked-23-million-worth-of-crypto-stolen/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T15:02:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Renowned cryptocurrency exchange Bitrue has fallen victim to a hack that has resulted in a loss of approximately $23 million worth of cryptocurrency. The manner in which the attack was executed was not explicitly stated by Bitrue. The exchange is investigating the situation at the moment.
 
Bitrue tweeted:
 

We have identified a brief exploit in one of our hot wallets on 07:18 (UTC), 14 April 2023. We were able to address this matter quickly and prevented the further exploit of funds.
 
According to the announcement made by Bitrue, all the withdrawals have been temporarily halted due to a “brief exploit” of their hot wallet. The exchange will conduct further security inspections and has planned to reestablish withdrawals by April 18, 2023.
 
 
Bitrue stated that the attackers were success…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>anushsamal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grant Haseley, Founder of Wagyu Games, on The Future of Web3 Gaming and Building Web3 Communities | Ep. 221]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18112828/Grant-Haseley-Founder-of-Wagyu-Games-on-The-Future-of-Web3-Gaming-and-Building-Web3-Communities-Ep-221</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18112828/Grant-Haseley-Founder-of-Wagyu-Games-on-The-Future-of-Web3-Gaming-and-Building-Web3-Communities-Ep-221"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an exclusive interview with cryptonews.com, Grant Haseley, Executive Director and Founder of Wagyu Games, talks about the future of web3 gaming, the future of 3 sports, and how to craft a web3 community. ... Read More: Grant Haseley, Founder of Wagyu Games, on The Future of Web3 Gaming and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Today in Crypto: Hackers Steal $23M from Bitrue, Canon USA to Launch NFT Marketplace, HashKey Launches Wealth Management Platform, Ripple Reveals Liquidity Hub]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18112825/Today-in-Crypto-Hackers-Steal-23M-from-Bitrue-Canon-USA-to-Launch-NFT-Marketplace-HashKey-Launches-Wealth-Management-Platform-Ripple-Reveals-Liquidity-Hub</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18112825/Today-in-Crypto-Hackers-Steal-23M-from-Bitrue-Canon-USA-to-Launch-NFT-Marketplace-HashKey-Launches-Wealth-Management-Platform-Ripple-Reveals-Liquidity-Hub"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________... Read More: Today in Crypto: Hackers Steal $23M from Bitrue, Canon USA to Launch NFT Marketplace, HashKey Launches Wealth Management...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MoneyGram Head of Fintech Strategy: Bad News Can't Stop the Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18112826/MoneyGram-Head-of-Fintech-Strategy-Bad-News-Cant-Stop-the-Blockchain</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18112826/MoneyGram-Head-of-Fintech-Strategy-Bad-News-Cant-Stop-the-Blockchain"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the world rapidly embraces digital transformation, blockchain technology and cryptocurrencies are gaining significant traction in the realm of global remittance, according to Luther Maday, Head of Fintech Strategy and Innovation at MoneyGram. However, the journey to mainstream adoption is...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Crypto: ChatGPT Crypto Limits, U.S. Mining Bans, BTC in El Salvador]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18112813/This-Week-in-Crypto-ChatGPT-Crypto-Limits-US-Mining-Bans-BTC-in-El-Salvador</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18112813/This-Week-in-Crypto-ChatGPT-Crypto-Limits-US-Mining-Bans-BTC-in-El-Salvador"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hoskinson: Cardano has a ‘beautiful plan’ for ZK-rollups]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18112778/Hoskinson-Cardano-has-a-beautiful-plan-for-ZK-rollups</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18112778/Hoskinson-Cardano-has-a-beautiful-plan-for-ZK-rollups"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T14:56:21.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK’s New Technology Department to Tackle Country’s Metaverse, Web3 Strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18112817/UKs-New-Technology-Department-to-Tackle-Countrys-Metaverse-Web3-Strategy</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18112817/UKs-New-Technology-Department-to-Tackle-Countrys-Metaverse-Web3-Strategy"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T14:55:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The department will explore economic growth, investment and business opportunities in these areas along with implications on regulation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Lido DAO (LDO) Price Reach a New All-Time High?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18112814/Will-Lido-DAO-LDO-Price-Reach-a-New-All-Time-High</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18112814/Will-Lido-DAO-LDO-Price-Reach-a-New-All-Time-High"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T14:47:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Lido DAO (LDO) price could accelerate its upward movement by a daily close above $3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance launches first NFT of the Brasileirão Assaí]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18112741/Binance-launches-first-NFT-of-the-Brasileirao-Assai</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18112741/Binance-launches-first-NFT-of-the-Brasileirao-Assai"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T14:35:14.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin [BTC] miners feel the heat with high sell pressure, can this ease their trouble]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18112738/Bitcoin-BTC-miners-feel-the-heat-with-high-sell-pressure-can-this-ease-their-trouble</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18112738/Bitcoin-BTC-miners-feel-the-heat-with-high-sell-pressure-can-this-ease-their-trouble"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T14:30:42.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pro-XRP Lawyer Warns of More Regulatory ‘Aggressiveness’ Against Crypto Industry if SEC Wins in Ripple Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18112753/Pro-XRP-Lawyer-Warns-of-More-Regulatory-Aggressiveness-Against-Crypto-Industry-if-SEC-Wins-in-Ripple-Lawsuit</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18112753/Pro-XRP-Lawyer-Warns-of-More-Regulatory-Aggressiveness-Against-Crypto-Industry-if-SEC-Wins-in-Ripple-Lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T14:30:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Attorney and XRP supporter John Deaton is warning of a harsher regulatory environment for the crypto industry if the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) emerges victorious in its lawsuit against Ripple. Deaton says in a new Real Vision Crypto interview that in the event that the court...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BNB Price Crosses $330 as Quarterly Token Burn Completes, Are More Gains Ahead?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18112739/BNB-Price-Crosses-330-as-Quarterly-Token-Burn-Completes-Are-More-Gains-Ahead</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18112739/BNB-Price-Crosses-330-as-Quarterly-Token-Burn-Completes-Are-More-Gains-Ahead"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BNB price is 20% up from the recent low on March 11. Can BNB shake off the media FUD from ongoing Regulatory squabbles to reach $350?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BitPay To Pay $1M to New York’s Financial Services Department]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18112714/BitPay-To-Pay-1M-to-New-Yorks-Financial-Services-Department</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18112714/BitPay-To-Pay-1M-to-New-Yorks-Financial-Services-Department"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T14:29:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An investigation found that BitPay’s cybersecurity and anti-money laundering programs were not in compliance with New York State’s Department of Financial Services regulations]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Geopolitics of CBDCs: Implications and Potential Power Shifts]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75244387e1</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/innovation/the-geopolitics-of-cbdcs-implications-and-potential-power-shifts/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T14:26:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The rise of  
central bank digital currencies (CBDCs) is soon becoming one of the most  
significant financial developments. CBDCs are blockchain-based digital  
representations of a country's fiat currency that are backed by the central  
bank. As more governments investigate the potential of CBDCs, the geopolitical  
consequences of this new technology become clearer.
The potential  
power shifts caused by CBDC implementation are enormous. In this article, we  
will look at the geopolitics of CBDCs, including potential ramifications and  
power transfers.
CBDCs and  
Their Potential Implications
CBDCs have the  
potential to transform the financial environment by providing a safe and  
efficient payment option. CBDCs can allow near-instant transactions, lower the  
risk of fraud, and pro…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Finance Magnates Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uniswap (UNI) Partners With China's MATIC Conflux (CFX), Here's the Deal]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18112722/Uniswap-UNI-Partners-With-Chinas-MATIC-Conflux-CFX-Heres-the-Deal</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18112722/Uniswap-UNI-Partners-With-Chinas-MATIC-Conflux-CFX-Heres-the-Deal"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T14:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Failure of Central Banking with Matthew Mezinskis]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18112725/The-Failure-of-Central-Banking-with-Matthew-Mezinskis</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18112725/The-Failure-of-Central-Banking-with-Matthew-Mezinskis"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T14:20:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SHOW NOTES:https://www.whatbitcoindid.com/podcast/the-failure-of-central-bankingMatthew Mežinskis is the creator of the Crypto Voices podcast and Porkopolis Economics website. In this interview, we discuss why free banking has always failed due to central bank interference, and how Bitcoin...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Magazine to Auction Historic Magazine Covers As 1 of 1 Inscriptions]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75244d20d9</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/bitcoin-magazine-announces-historic-nft-auction"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T14:14:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Historic 1/1 Ordinal inscriptions of the first 23 covers printed by Bitcoin’s oldest publication are up for grabs.
Bitcoin Magazine is launching its first-ever Ordinals collection, "Bitcoin Magazine Historic Covers." The collection features 1/1 inscriptions of the first 23 covers ever printed by Bitcoin Magazine, representing the publication's journey from its founding in 2012 to Bitcoin’s 10th anniversary in 2019.
The collection will be sold in a trust-minimized Dutch auction on the Gamma marketplace on Saturday, April 15. The launch will showcase cutting-edge auction technology in the Ordinals market that leverages partially-signed Bitcoin transactions (PSBT) to minimize trust in the auction process. Gamma will be releasing this technology with Bitcoin Magazine as a launch partner, providing buyers with a transparent and trust-minimized buying experience and ensuring the release of the inscription to the winning bid is automatic through the rules of the Bitcoin protocol.
Bitcoin Magazine Historic Covers collection offers a unique and limited-edition representation of Bitcoin Magazine's journey and captures the spirit of the Bitcoin community and the evolution of the Bitcoin landscape from the early days in 2012 until Bitcoin’s 10th anniversary in 2019. Each winner of a Historic Cover inscription will also receive a physical copy of the Bitcoin Magazine issue they purchased, further highlighting the unique history and scarcity of these publications.
David Bailey, CEO of Bitcoin Magazine, said, "We're experimenting at the edge of Bitcoin innovation and venturing into uncharted territory. Our Historic Covers collection is the start of Bitcoin Magazine's journey in the world of Ordinals. We're thrilled to offer our readers and the Bitcoin community a chance to own a piece of Bitcoin history."
The launch of the Ordinals collection by Bitcoin Magazine marks a new era in the world of Bitcoin, where fans and enthusiasts of the cryptocurrency can own a piece of history.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BtcCasey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoins Cannot Function as Money Because They Have No ‘Assured Value’ — Bank of England Governor]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75244d57e6</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/stablecoins-cannot-function-as-money-because-they-have-no-assured-value-bank-of-england-governor/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T14:13:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Andrew Bailey, the governor of the Bank of England, has asserted that stablecoins “will need to have the characteristics of, and be regulated as, inside money” before they function as money. Bailey also described crypto as a “highly speculative investment” with no intrinsic value. 
 
Stablecoins Purport to Be Money
 
According to the Bank of England (BOE) governor, Andrew Bailey, stablecoins can only function as money if they attain the characteristics of “inside money” and when they are regulated as such. Bailey also claimed the BOE had determined that stablecoins lack the “assured value” the public expects to see in digital money.
 
Bailey, who did not directly refer to the collapse of Terra’s stablecoin UST in 2022, suggested in his speech at the Institute of International Finance, that…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Popular Tea Shop Boba Guys Taps Solana for On-Chain Loyalty Rewards Program]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75244d73ee</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/web3/2023/04/14/tea-shop-boba-guys-taps-solana-for-on-chain-loyalty-rewards-program/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T14:12:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On top of building the chain’s loyalty infrastructure, the Solana Foundation recently invested $100,000 into Boba Guys.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cam Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. SEC Poised to Move Toward DeFi Oversight As It Reopens Proposed Regulations]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75244d73db</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/04/14/us-sec-poised-to-move-toward-defi-oversight-as-it-reopens-proposed-regulations/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T14:12:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission is considering reopening a rule proposal on how it oversees crypto platforms to more explicitly include decentralized finance (DeFi). Commissioners will vote on the language during an open meeting on Friday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De, Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance and Brazilian Football Federation launch free NFT aimed at wooing new customers]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18112712/Binance-and-Brazilian-Football-Federation-launch-free-NFT-aimed-at-wooing-new-customers</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18112712/Binance-and-Brazilian-Football-Federation-launch-free-NFT-aimed-at-wooing-new-customers"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T14:11:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance wants more Brazilian customers and has signed with the nation's football federation to help get them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP price jumps after Ripple’s business liquidity hub launch]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18112680/XRP-price-jumps-after-Ripples-business-liquidity-hub-launch</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18112680/XRP-price-jumps-after-Ripples-business-liquidity-hub-launch"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T14:05:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At press time, XRP was trading at $0.5281, up 3.53% in the last 24 hours. The XRP price has been soaring in correlation with Bitcoin’s (BTC) price. Ripple has today launched a business liquidity hub. Today’s launch of the business liquidity hub by Ripple Labs has added impetus to the already...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will NFTs Give Japan an Edge Over Economic Rivals?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18112740/Will-NFTs-Give-Japan-an-Edge-Over-Economic-Rivals</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18112740/Will-NFTs-Give-Japan-an-Edge-Over-Economic-Rivals"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T14:05:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Non-fungible tokens (NFTs) present a unique opportunity to revitalize depressed regions of a country. Herein, creating new jobs, injecting new money into the local economy, promoting tourism, and preserving cultural heritage. NFTs can significantly impact Japan's economic and cultural development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Firm HashKey Launches Wealth Management Program To Meet Demand]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75244e71a7</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/hashkey-launches-wealth-management-program/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T14:05:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Asian continent is witnessing a growing adoption of crypto assets. More crypto products and services are emerging to enhance users’ experience with digital assets. 
 
In a new development, a Hong Kong-based digital asset company HashKey Group has revealed a new wealth management service. HashKey Group aims to increase Asian users’ exposure to diverse digital assets.
 
HashKey Introduces A New Wealth Management Service
 
On April 14, 2023, HashKey announced its plans to introduce Wealth Program, a new wealth management service. This will mark the firm’s first investment and wealth platform with exposure to various virtual assets.
 
Related Reading: Coinbase Loses Key Executive As Vishal Gupta Resigns For New Crypto Project: Report
 
According to its statement, the new service platform a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miner Bitdeer Stock Slumps Nearly 30% at Trading Debut]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75244fb6d8</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/04/14/bitcoin-miner-bitdeer-stock-slumps-nearly-30-at-trading-debut/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T13:56:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Singapore firm is one of the largest bitcoin miners in the world with 16.2 EH/s of hashrate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliza Gkritsi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How CoinDesk Will Use Generative AI Tools]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7524493366</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/04/14/how-coindesk-will-use-generative-ai-tools/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T13:45:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI tools for generating content are changing the way we work – especially the media. Here are the rules of the road for CoinDesk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pete Pachal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Onramp Launches First Spot Bitcoin Trust With Multi-Party Custody]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e752449335d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/04/14/onramp-launches-first-spot-bitcoin-trust-with-multi-party-custody/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T13:45:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company, based in Austin, Texas, says the new offering is the first bitcoin trust that takes advantage of Bitcoin’s multi-signature capability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Frederick  Munawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Tweet Spurs 7% Aptos Price Surge]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7524344853</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/04/14/elon-musk-tweet-spurs-7-aptos-price-surge/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T13:23:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aptos (APT) surged by 7.4% on Friday after Twitter CEO Elon Musk tweeted “AI APT OTT!” before deleting it one hour later.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chia Network Submits Registration to U.S. SEC For Proposed IPO]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e752434484a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/04/14/chia-network-submits-registration-to-us-sec-for-proposed-ipo/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T13:23:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The size and price range for the offering has yet to be determined.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$198M in Ethereum Staked to Network in Last 24 Hours]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=136759</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/136759/224m-ethereum-staked-network-24-hours"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T13:21:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amid concerns over mass withdrawals, in the last 24 hours, roughly 94,800 Ethereum has been deposited to the network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly,Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Mover Americas: Ether Steals the Show, Alts Follow Suit]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e752436fbee</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/04/14/first-mover-americas-ether-steals-the-show-alts-follow-suit/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T13:03:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest price moves in bitcoin (BTC) and crypto markets in context for April 11, 2023. First Mover is CoinDesk’s daily newsletter that contextualizes the latest actions in the crypto markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lyllah Ledesma, Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Magazine Announces Auction For Historic Magazine Cover Inscriptions]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7524375bd7</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/bitcoin-magazine-announces-historic-nft-auction"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T13:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1/1 Ordinal inscriptions of the first 23 covers printed by Bitcoin’s oldest publication are up for grabs.
Bitcoin Magazine is launching its first-ever Ordinals collection, "Bitcoin Magazine Historic Covers." The collection features 1/1 inscriptions of the first 23 covers ever printed by Bitcoin Magazine, representing the publication's journey from its founding in 2012 to Bitcoin’s 10th anniversary in 2019. The collection will be sold in a trustless Dutch auction on the Gamma marketplace on Saturday, April 15.
The collection offers a unique and limited- edition representation of Bitcoin Magazine's journey and captures the spirit of the Bitcoin community and the evolution of the Bitcoin landscape. The PSBT-based Dutch auction on the Gamma marketplace will provide buyers with a transparent and trust-minimized buying experience, ensuring the release of the inscription to the winning bid is automatic through the rules of the Bitcoin protocol.
David Bailey, CEO of Bitcoin Magazine, said, "We're experimenting at the edge of Bitcoin innovation and venturing into uncharted territory. Our Historic Covers collection is the start of Bitcoin Magazine's journey in the world of Ordinals. We're thrilled to offer our readers and the Bitcoin community a chance to own a piece of Bitcoin history."
Each winner of a Historic Cover inscription will also receive a physical copy of the Bitcoin Magazine issue they purchased, further highlighting the unique history and scarcity of these publications.
The launch of the Ordinals collection by Bitcoin Magazine marks a new era in the world of Bitcoin, where fans and enthusiasts of the cryptocurrency can own a piece of history.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BtcCasey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shaq Can’t Be Subpoenaed Via Twitter Direct Message In FTX Class-Action Suit, Judge Rules]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7524307a2a</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/shaq-cant-be-subpoenaed-via-twitter/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T12:52:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A “Hack a Shaq” – a basketball strategy where a team intentionally fouls a poor free-throw shooter, often Shaquille O’Neal, to send them to the free-throw line – is being carried out by the former NBA superstar’s “opponents.”
 
Shaquille O’Neal has dodged a legal bullet as a Florida judge rejected a request to serve him electronically with a summons in a class-action lawsuit involving FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried and other celebrity spokespeople. 
 
Lawyers attempting to serve O’Neal since last fall had asked the judge if they could utilize his Twitter and Instagram direct messages to do so. However, the judge ruled against this method.
 
 
Lawsuit Over FTX Promotion Pay Continues As Shaq Remains Unserved
 
Shaq is the only defendant in a class-action lawsuit who has yet to be served by a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Technical Analysis: BTC Nears $31,000, as ETH Hits 11-Month High]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e752431d3f8</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-ethereum-technical-analysis-btc-nears-31000-as-eth-hits-11-month-high/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T12:42:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin moved towards the $31,000 mark on Friday, ahead of upcoming retail sales data from the United States. Sales are expected to remain flat, whilst overall consumer sentiment is forecasted to rise to 62.7, from a reading of 62.0. Ethereum extended recent gains, hitting an eleven-month high in the process.
 
Bitcoin
 
Bitcoin (BTC) was once again in the green on Friday, as traders pushed the price close to the $31,000 mark.
 
BTC/USD raced to a peak of $30,848.46 earlier in today’s session, a day after trading at a low of $30,160.59.
 
The move has resulted in bitcoin hitting its strongest point since June 7, when it hit a peak of $31,549.
 
 
Bitcoin chart by TradingView
 

 
 

 
Overall, this recent surge in momentum has sent the relative strength index (RSI) deep into overbought territory.
 
At the time of writing, the index is tracking at 72.18, which is marginally higher than a peak at 72.
 
Should the index move above a reading of 73.00, then it is very likely that BTC will be trading beyond $31,000.
 
 
Ethereum
 
Ethereum (ETH) continued to climb higher, following its recent Shapella update, with price surging above $2,100.
 
Following a low of $1,987.05 on Thursday, ETH/USD moved to a peak of $2,126.32 earlier in today’s session.
 
As a result of today’s surge in price, the world’s second largest cryptocurrency hit its highest level since last May.
 
 
Ethereum chart by TradingView
 

 
 

 
The latest rally took place as bulls broke out of a key resistance level of $2,030, with the RSI crossing a hurdle of its own at the 72.00 mark.
 
Like with BTC, ETH’s RSI is also overbought, with the index at a reading of 75.29 at the time of writing.
 
A higher ceiling at 80.00 now awaits current bulls in the market.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
Is there a chance ethereum can hit $3,000 in April? Leave your thoughts in the comments below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOJ Claims Google’s Search Engine 'Monopoly' Stifled AI Innovation: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=136755</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/136755/doj-claims-googles-search-engine-monopoly-stifled-ai-innovation-report"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T12:39:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Department of Justice thinks there's something illegal about Google's exclusivity deals now that it has a monopoly on the search market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[World's Most Influential Central Banks' Balance Sheets Look to Have Troughed]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75243c9c2a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/04/14/g4-central-bank-balance-sheets-look-to-have-troughed/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T12:23:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The directional change suggests an end to the quantitative tightening that roiled cryptocurrencies last year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HashKey Group to Debut Regulated Exchange in Second Quarter]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75243c9c1a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/04/14/hashkey-group-to-debut-regulated-exchange-in-second-quarter/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T12:23:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The exchange will be open to professional investors and the company is preparing to welcome retail users in "coming months."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lavender Au</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Boosts Business Payments With Launch Of Liquidity Hub]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75243f5eb7</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ripple-launch-of-liquidity-hun/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T12:03:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The firm behind XRP, Ripple Labs, has launched a business liquidity hub. The innovative solution allows business entities to access liquidity for digital assets from various crypto exchanges, market makers, and over-the-counter marketplaces worldwide.
 
According to Ripple, its liquidity hub will seamlessly bridge the gap between fiat systems and crypto. Ripple announced the launch on April 14 after the product’s pilot last year.
 
Ripple Liquidity Hub Will Integrate Diverse Solutions 
 
The new liquidity hub aims to integrate solutions to help businesses access and manage liquidity across platforms. With it, business corporations can optimize crypto liquidity and an extensive payout network to power payments, treasury operations, and other solutions.
 
 
The product utilizes advanced tech…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacker Robs Crypto Exchange Bitrue of $23M in Ethereum, SHIB, Other Assets]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=136751</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/136751/hacker-robs-bitrue-23m-ethereum-shib-assets"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T11:26:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Singapore-based crypto exchange Bitrue has been hit by a security breach, draining a hot wallet of $23 million in various assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Soars to 11-Month High Following Shanghai Upgrade]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=136748</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/136748/ethereum-soars-eleven-month-high-post-shanghai-upgrade"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T09:09:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Propelled by the latest Shanghai upgrade, the price of Ethereum has recaptured the $2,100 mark last seen in May 2022.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Goblintown Creator Trashes NFT Artwork, Disables Trading in Royalties Stand]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=126261</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/126261/goblintown-creator-trashes-nft-artwork-disables-trading-royalties-stand"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T00:22:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Goblintown NFTs went viral last year after holders rambled about piss. Now some of them are unhappy with the creator's surprise moves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Token Slides as Holder Hopes of Exchange Reopening Fade]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=126277</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/126277/ftx-token-slides-holder-hopes-exchange-reopening"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T23:09:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The token’s price doubled yesterday, yet its recent gains have now been partially pared back.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Marketplace OpenBazaar Is Coming Back]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=126270</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/126270/bitcoin-marketplace-openbazaar-coming-back"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T21:57:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The “decentralized Amazon” shut down in 2020 from a lack of funding—now it’s poised to make a come back.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alyssa Hertig</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastercard Drops Free Music Pass NFTs With Perks for Holders]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=126253</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/126253/mastercard-drops-free-music-pass-nfts-perks-holders"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T21:49:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Credit card giant Mastercard has started a Web3 artist accelerator, with free Polygon-based NFTs that provide benefits ahead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Leads Crypto Market Surge, Up 6% in 24 Hours]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=126251</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/126251/dogecoin-price-crypto-market-surge"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T19:47:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The original meme coin is today's best performing top 20 digital asset.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: Anthony Scaramucci Is More Bullish on Bitcoin Than Ever]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PqLOXL47/gm-anthony-scaramucci-is-more-bullish-on-bitcoin-than-ever</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PqLOXL47/gm-anthony-scaramucci-is-more-bullish-on-bitcoin-than-ever"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T18:58:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthony Scaramucci of hedge fund SkyBridge Capital got burned by Sam Bankman-Fried: he co-hosted SALT conferences with FTX and sold a 30% stake in SkyBridge to FTX Ventures. And yet "The Mooch" tells Dan Roberts and Stacy Elliott "I'm more bullish now than I have ever been" on crypto as an investment case. He discusses his frustration with SBF, how wrong he thinks politicians like Elizabeth Warren and Gary Gensler are about crypto and how to regulate it, what he sees happening next with adoption, and talks about Trump. Watch and make sure to subscribe to the gm podcast on Apple or Spotify.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[YouTuber Bitboy Ordered to Appear in Court to Face Lawyer’s Harassment Claims]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=126238</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/126238/bitboy-court-attorney-harassment-claims"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T17:35:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Armstrong said lawyer Adam Moskowitz and his firm “will be dealt with” in response.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Canon to Launch Ethereum Photo NFT Marketplace Cadabra]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125858</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125858/canon-cadabra-ethereum-nft-photo-marketplace"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T17:04:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The camera and digital imaging giant is pushing further into Web3 with a dedicated NFT photography platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Saga Review: The Web3 Smartphone Has Arrived]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=126218</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/126218/solana-saga-review-web3-smartphone-arrived"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T17:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana’s Android phone is here, delivering a premium flagship with baked-in Web3 functionality. Can it hook the masses?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Chaos-GPT: An AI Tool That Seeks to Destroy Humanity]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=126122</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/126122/meet-chaos-gpt-ai-tool-destroy-humanity"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T16:39:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chaos-GPT, an autonomous implementation of ChatGPT, has been unveiled, and its objectives are as terrifying as they are well-structured.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Asia Could Dominate 80% of Web3 Gaming: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=126147</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/126147/asia-could-dominate-80-of-web3-gaming-report"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T15:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to Web3, a new study suggests a free-to-play mobile game has incredible potential in the burgeoning Japanese market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uniswap Wallet Goes Live on iOS After Apple App Store Challenges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=126207</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/126207/uniswap-wallet-goes-live-ios-app-store-challenges"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Uniswap’s open-source mobile wallet app allows users to trade on Ethereum, Polygon, Arbitrum, and Optimism.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[eToro Announces Crypto, Stock Trading Integration With Twitter]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=126201</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/126201/etoro-announces-crypto-stock-trading-integration-twitter"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T11:07:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twitter has partnered with trading app eToro as the microblogging site's CEO pivots his company towards becoming an "everything app."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Surges 6% Following Successful Shanghai Upgrade]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=126198</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/126198/ethereum-jumps-successful-shanghai-upgrade"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T10:24:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following the successful execution of Ethereum's latest upgrade, the network's native asset ETH has soared overnight.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Older Version of DeFi Yield Aggregator Yearn Finance Exploited for $11.6M]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=126194</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/126194/older-versions-of-aave-yearn-finance-exploited-11-6m"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T09:39:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An attacker minted 1.2 quadrillion tokens by exploiting a Yearn vulnerability, selling them for $11.6 million in stablecoins.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pussy Riot Pitches Metaverse ‘Utopia’ With Virtual Social Network IMVU]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=126176</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/126176/pussy-riot-metaverse-pink-church-utopia-imvu"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T03:09:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The virtual church from Nadya Tolokonnikova and Metajuice will feature NFTs and special events, supporting LGBTQIA+ causes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shanghai Arrival Could Push Major Players to Disembark]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=126177</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/126177/ethereum-shanghai-staking-withdrawals-validator-exits"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T02:59:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After settling with the SEC, Kraken is among the firms in line to fully exit as a network validator.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Holds Steady Following Shanghai, Defying Expectations]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=126166</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/126166/ethereum-eth-shanghai-market-effect"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T00:22:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH's price was remarkably stable in the minutes following Ethereum's historic, successful Shanghai upgrade, which enabled withdrawals of staked ETH.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Perplexity AI: The Chatbot Stepping Up to Challenge ChatGPT]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=126127</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/126127/review-perplexity-ai-the-chatbot-stepping-up-to-challenge-chatgpt"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T23:24:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The free web and mobile chatbot offers many benefits, including links and sources for its answers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Shanghai Upgrade Goes Live, Unlocking $34 Billion in Staked ETH]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=126144</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/126144/ethereum-shanghai-upgrade-goes-staked-eth"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T22:39:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wednesday night’s long-awaited Shanghai upgrade marks a major milestone for the second-largest cryptocurrency by market cap.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Shanghai Could Change Institutional Appetite for Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=126117</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/126117/shanghai-ethereum-upgrade-institutional-investors-eth"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T22:29:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What does big money think of the latest Ethereum upgrade? Experts weigh in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Warren Buffett Blasts Bitcoin as 'Gambling Token' as BTC Surges 35% in 30 Days]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=126115</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/126115/warren-buffett-bitcoin-gambling-token"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T21:02:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The “Oracle of Omaha” made up his mind about crypto long ago, it seems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mr. Brainwash, 100 Influencers, and Web3 Walk Into a Museum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=126076</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/126076/mr-brainwash-100-influencers-web3-walk-into-museum"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T20:19:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At a Beverly Hills gala hosted by street artist Mr. Brainwash, social media influencers pondered the future—and the place for Web3 in it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LimeWire Launches Nostalgic Music Downloading Game With Crypto Rewards]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=126103</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/126103/limewire-launches-nostalgic-music-downloading-game-with-crypto-rewards"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T19:40:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the next month, the hunt is on for virtual music amidst dead-end viruses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Privacy Tool Aims to 'Confuse' Surveillance Companies]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=126075</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/126075/bitcoin-privacy-tool-confuse-surveillance-companies"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T17:53:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Analytics companies make a living tracking Bitcoin transactions. Developer Dan Gould wants to make their lives harder with PayJoins.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alyssa Hertig</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Sex Chatbots and the Dudes Who Love Them]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=126018</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/126018/ai-sex-chatbots-dudes-love-them"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T16:30:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new, uncensored open-source large language model is being used by the AI community to build X-rated chatbots, because of course it is.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More Than $300 Million in Ethereum Will Be Sold After Shanghai, Analysts Say]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=126057</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/126057/300-million-ethereum-sold-shanghai-staking"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T15:17:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain analysis from Glassnode estimates that roughly 170,000 ETH will be withdrawn and sold after the Shanghai upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly,Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bruce Lee Enters Web3, Starting With Open Edition NFT From Pplpleasr]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=126036</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/126036/bruce-lee-enters-web3-starting-open-edition-nft-pplpleasr"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T14:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The $15 NFT is billed as “your ticket to the House of Lee” and was created in collaboration with the Bruce Lee Estate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azuki NFT Creator Chiru Labs Reveals Collab With Line Friends]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=126031</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/126031/azuki-nft-creator-chiru-labs-reveals-collaboration-line-friends"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brown and other characters from the smash South Korean franchise will cross paths with Azuki’s Beanz NFT characters.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Edges Higher as Inflation Cools More Than Expected in March]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=126058</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/126058/bitcoin-edges-higher-as-inflation-cools-more-expected-march"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T13:10:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin rose slightly after fresh inflation data hinted at a possible path forward for future rate hikes from the Fed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miner Bitdeer Expected to Finally Go Public This Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=126055</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/126055/bitcoin-miner-bitdeer-expected-finally-go-public-this-friday"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T11:31:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After three previous delays, Bitcoin miner Bitdeer now expects to finally start trading on the Nasdaq on April 14.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alameda-linked Ren Protocol Transfers $13M in Bitcoin to FTX Debtors]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=126051</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/126051/alameda-linked-ren-protocol-transfers-13m-bitcoin-ftx-debtors"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T11:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ren community members say they were prepared for this event, having warned users to withdraw and redeem their remaining assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance US to Delist Justin Sun's Tron Token Next Week]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=126043</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/126043/binance-us-delist-justin-sun-tron-token-next-week"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T09:12:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Three weeks after the SEC accused Justin Sun of manipulating the price of TRX, Binance US said it will delist the asset.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[David Marcus's Lightspark Unveils Bitcoin Lightning Platform for Business]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=126009</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/126009/david-marcuss-lightspark-unveils-lightning-platform-for-businesses"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T21:47:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The former head of PayPal and co-creator of Diem announces a new open payment protocol.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alyssa Hertig</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More Bitcoin Than Ever Is Now ‘Dormant’—Here’s What That Means]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=126006</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/126006/more-bitcoin-than-ever-is-now-dormant-heres-what-that-means"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T21:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over 53% of coins ever minted haven’t budged for more than two years, new data shows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Is Losing Its Edge in Crypto, Says Andreessen Horowitz]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125988</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125988/usa-losing-edge-global-crypto-leadership-andreesen-horowitz-report"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T20:29:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The a16z investment firm warns that the rapid rise in regulatory actions are a threat to American innovation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-JP Morgan and Deutsche Bank Employee Charged With Crypto Fraud]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125983</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125983/jp-morgan-deutsche-bank-moodys-former-employee-crypto-fraud-charges"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T18:51:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Registered broker Rashawn Russell was arrested in New York yesterday for promising altcoin riches.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Chief Legal Officer: The Problem With SEC's Howey Test Isn't Its Age]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/woZFLgib/coinbase-chief-legal-officer-the-problem-with-secs-howey-test-isnt-its-age</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/woZFLgib/coinbase-chief-legal-officer-the-problem-with-secs-howey-test-isnt-its-age"/>
        <updated>2023-04-10T16:25:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Chief Legal Officer Paul Grewal discussed the "Howey Test," which the SEC uses as its yard stick for whether a crypto asset should be regulated as a security, and told Decrypt's Stacy Elliott and Dan Roberts the issue with it isn't that it's old (the case is from 1946) but how it's being applied to modern technology. Watch and make sure to subscribe to the gm podcast on Apple or Spotify.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized Pictures Plots Its Next Web3 Grant for Filmmakers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/WlVsgaOs/decentralized-pictures-plots-its-next-web3-grant-for-filmmakers</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/WlVsgaOs/decentralized-pictures-plots-its-next-web3-grant-for-filmmakers"/>
        <updated>2023-04-08T13:15:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leo Matchett from Web3 film funding platform Decentralized Pictures tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson at Outer Edge LA about DCP's just announced iPhone Filmmaking Initiative, which will support aspiring filmmakers who create a short film on their iPhones, and will be determined via DCP's crypto-native on-chain voting system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 YouTuber CryptoStache: Gaming Will Be the Catalyst That Takes NFTs Mainstream]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Exb7eWKj/web3-youtuber-cryptostache-gaming-will-be-the-catalyst-that-takes-nfts-mainstream</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Exb7eWKj/web3-youtuber-cryptostache-gaming-will-be-the-catalyst-that-takes-nfts-mainstream"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T02:51:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 gaming YouTuber CryptoStache talks to Decrypt's Jason Nelson at Outer Edge LA about why Web3 gaming will bring NFTs mainstream, the partnerships that prove it's already happening, how gamers will change their tune on NFTs, and how the terminology is likely to change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fordefi Aims to Dramatically Simplify the Institutional Crypto Wallet]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/LGxyFJP5/fordefi-aims-to-dramatically-simplify-the-institutional-crypto-wallet</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/LGxyFJP5/fordefi-aims-to-dramatically-simplify-the-institutional-crypto-wallet"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T02:39:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Steve H., VP of sales from Fordefi, which raised $18 million in funding last year, tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson at Outer Edge LA how Fordefi uses multi-party computation to make signing transactions on an institutional crypto wallet much simpler—no seed phrase needed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: Canadian Bitcoin Miner Hut 8 Is Heading West]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5AGD2ifd/gm-canadian-bitcoin-miner-hut-8-is-heading-west</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5AGD2ifd/gm-canadian-bitcoin-miner-hut-8-is-heading-west"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T21:40:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Toronto-based Bitcoin mining company Hut 8 recently announced a merger with U.S. Bitcoin Corp that will take it into Texas, Nebraska, and New York. Hut 8 CEO Jaime Leverton joined Dan Roberts and Stacy Elliott to talk expanding into the U.S., dealing with regulatory pushback post-FTX, why Texas is such a hotspot, and where she'd like to expand globally down the road (the climates may surprise you). Watch and make sure to subscribe to the gm podcast on Apple or Spotify.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: Kevin Owocki Wants to Regenerate DeFi]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/knbMLd17/gm-kevin-owocki-wants-to-regenerate-defi</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/knbMLd17/gm-kevin-owocki-wants-to-regenerate-defi"/>
        <updated>2023-04-01T14:23:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Move over, DeFi—ReFi is coming? Gitcoin founder Kevin Owocki has stepped away from DeFi grant-giving machine Gitcoin as it fully decentralizes and is now focused on regenerative finance (huh?) and ReFi incubator Supermodular. He aims to "regenerate the regenerators." He explained it all to Dan Roberts and Liam Kelly, and also talks DAO structure, crypto factions, NFT use cases, his book "Greenpilled," and much more. Watch and make sure to subscribe to the gm podcast on Apple or Spotify.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Aurory's Head of Production Left Ubisoft for Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PqJHF0N9/why-aurorys-head-of-production-left-ubisoft-for-web3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PqJHF0N9/why-aurorys-head-of-production-left-ubisoft-for-web3"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T21:24:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aurory executive producer and head of production Jonathan Campeau tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin at GDC about how the first-generation of Web3 games came out of DeFi and are now evolving.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['We Don't Really Do the Corporate Thing Very Well' Says Jason Brink on Gala Games Approach]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/EDzHoKrt/we-dont-really-do-the-corporate-thing-very-well-says-jason-brink-on-gala-games-approach</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/EDzHoKrt/we-dont-really-do-the-corporate-thing-very-well-says-jason-brink-on-gala-games-approach"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T21:14:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With roughly 50 video games in its pipeline, Gala Games is all-in on Web3. Gala's President of Blockchain Jason Brink told Decrypt's Kate Irwin at GDC about the studio's ethos and weighs in on the different approaches to Web3 gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: Coinbase's Top Lawyer Gets Real on SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mB7DMx7l/gm-coinbases-top-lawyer-gets-real-on-sec</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mB7DMx7l/gm-coinbases-top-lawyer-gets-real-on-sec"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T16:36:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paul Grewal is the Chief Legal Officer at Coinbase and a former U.S. magistrate judge in Northern California. He gave Dan Roberts and Stacy Elliott his candid takes on Sam Bankman-Fried and FTX, the SEC's crackdown on staking, the sanctioning of Tornado Cash, and more alpha on how Coinbase is approaching the current unfriendly US regulatory environment. Watch and make sure to subscribe to the gm podcast on Apple or Spotify.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Founder of Rotten Tomatoes Says Web3 Entertainment Isn’t Nearly Entertaining Enough Yet]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/ri2LLifZ/the-founder-of-rotten-tomatoes-says-web3-entertainment-isnt-nearly-entertaining-enough-yet</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/ri2LLifZ/the-founder-of-rotten-tomatoes-says-web3-entertainment-isnt-nearly-entertaining-enough-yet"/>
        <updated>2023-03-25T02:44:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rotten Tomatoes founder Patrick Lee, who has led companies at the intersection of technology and entertainment from Web1 to Web3, spoke to Decrypt's Sander Lutz at Outer Edge LA about the current state of decentralized gaming, film and television.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: How Gnosis Has Endured and Evolved]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Kxfs2Dmd/gm-how-gnosis-has-endured-and-evolved</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Kxfs2Dmd/gm-how-gnosis-has-endured-and-evolved"/>
        <updated>2023-03-24T20:58:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gnosis first launched in 2015 as a decentralized prediction market built on Ethereum. Now it's a DAO, a multi-sig wallet, a staking chain, and a vibrant community with its own GNO governance token. Co-founder and COO Friederike Ernst talked to Dan Roberts and Stacy Elliott about the careful evolution of Gnosis, decentralization impostors, account abstraction, DeFi UX failures, why Ethereum is the "Manhattan of crypto," and much more. Watch and make sure to subscribe to the gm podcast on Apple or Spotify.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Justin Aversano's Inspiration for Tarot-Themed NFT Photo Series 'Smoke and Mirrors']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/dkWNFMPb/justin-aversanos-inspiration-for-tarot-themed-nft-photo-series-smoke-and-mirrors</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/dkWNFMPb/justin-aversanos-inspiration-for-tarot-themed-nft-photo-series-smoke-and-mirrors"/>
        <updated>2023-03-24T20:03:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Justin Aversano, best known for his high-selling "Twin Flames" NFT photo series, joined Decrypt’s Andrew Hayward ahead of the upcoming L.A. exhibition for his new Ethereum NFT project "Smoke and Mirrors." He shared the wild inspiration behind the tarot-themed collection, and why—despite his growing profile—he opted not to exhibit at a major brand-name gallery.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Midnight Society’s Rob Bowling Talks Deadrop Launch and Working With Dr. Disrespect]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/yIc3fKH2/midnight-societys-rob-bowling-talks-deadrop-launch-and-working-with-dr-disrespect</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/yIc3fKH2/midnight-societys-rob-bowling-talks-deadrop-launch-and-working-with-dr-disrespect"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T21:28:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former "Call of Duty" developer Rob Bowling, now head of Midnight Society Studio, checked in with Decrypt's Kate Irwin at GDC and shared some behind-the-scenes statistics on how players are enjoying "Deadrop." The game saw 90,000 player hours over the weekend, with 97 minutes average play time per player, and their community size tripled in just a few days.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big Brands Get Serious About NFTs: Salesforce, VW, Panerai, Absolute Labs at NFT Paris]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/BHN8nxxH/big-brands-get-serious-about-nfts-salesforce-vw-panerai-absolute-labs-at-nft-paris</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/BHN8nxxH/big-brands-get-serious-about-nfts-salesforce-vw-panerai-absolute-labs-at-nft-paris"/>
        <updated>2023-03-16T14:57:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this panel from NFT Paris 2023 moderated by Decrypt's Dan Roberts, Web3 leads from some of the largest consumer and tech brands discuss their NFT strategies. Marc Mathieu of Salesforce, Tim Walther of VW Group, Eva Assayag of Panerai, and Samir Addamine of Absolute Labs joined the panel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFT Entertainment Revolution: Warner Bros, Orange Comet, CyberBrokers and NFT Now at NFT Paris]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/ZWr09Uou/nft-entertainment-revolution-warner-bros-orange-comet-cyberbrokers-and-nft-now-at-nft-paris</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/ZWr09Uou/nft-entertainment-revolution-warner-bros-orange-comet-cyberbrokers-and-nft-now-at-nft-paris"/>
        <updated>2023-03-16T14:49:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At NFT Paris 2023, Decrypt’s Stephen Graves moderated a discussion about NFTs and the entertainment industry with Warner Bros’ NFT head Josh Hackbarth, CyberBrokers founder Josie Bellini, NFT Now founder Matt Medved and Dave Broome, CEO of Orange Comet, which has produced NFTs for Anthony Hopkins and The Walking Dead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>