<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-06-17T14:16:24.357Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-06-17T14:16:24.357Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Shiba Inu (SHIB) Metric Explodes by 860%: Details]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19595238/This-Shiba-Inu-SHIB-Metric-Explodes-by-860-Details</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19595238/This-Shiba-Inu-SHIB-Metric-Explodes-by-860-Details"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T14:11:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Check out which Shibarium indicator skyrocketed on a daily scale.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zksync’s ZK Token Debuts With $932M Valuation, South Korean Market Shows Strong Interest]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7414d2ba6d</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/zksyncs-zk-token-debuts-with-932m-valuation-south-korean-market-shows-strong-interest/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T14:09:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zksync’s token, known as ZK, is currently trading at a value 19% below its initial price of $0.321 during early morning sessions. The new cryptocurrency’s market valuation stands at $932.14 million, with each ZK token trading at $0.2575. This positions ZK among the top 100 largest market capitalizations, ranking at 90th. Notable exchanges listing ZK […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[#FreeSamourai]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7414d2ced9</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/legal/freesamourai"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T14:08:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samourai Wallet
From the start, Samourai Wallet have been transparent about their services. They provided their code fully open sourced and explained every public service they ran. All of this was done in public for everyone to see as they, ironically enough, had nothing to hide.
As will be detailed below, they followed the law to the letter as was laid out in government legislation and guidelines. The key point was that Samourai Wallet's code allowed users to make transactions as they saw fit, without ever holding so much as a single sat of the user in their own possession.
Arrest & Seizure
Despite following the law, the IRS-CI and FBI have indicted the founders of Samourai Wallet, and charged them with "one count of conspiracy to commit money laundering" and "one count of conspiracy to o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Damm Kewl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Australia's Largest Stock Exchange Approves It's First Bitcoin ETF]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7414d2ced1</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/australias-largest-stock-exchange-approves-its-first-bitcoin-etf"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T14:08:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Australia's largest stock market, the Australian Securities Exchange (ASX), approved listing the first Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) on its platform on June 20. The issuer will be VanEck, and the instrument will be dubbed the VanEck Bitcoin ETF (VBTC).

BREAKING: 🇦🇺 Australia’s largest stock exchange, ASX has approved its first spot #Bitcoin ETF. pic.twitter.com/M4kApaqfhW
— Bitcoin Magazine (@BitcoinMagazine) June 17, 2024
  
  
  
The decision of the leading Australian stock exchange came after the success of Bitcoin ETFs in the United States, where 11 such instruments have been listed since January. Hong Kong also launched Bitcoin ETFs following the US.
Arian Neiron, CEO and Managing Director at VanEck Asia Pacific, said, "The demand for access to Bitcoin via a listed vehicle traded on ASX has been increasing, and many of our clients have told us that their clients are already positioned to have an allocation ready to invest."
Australia already had spot Bitcoin ETFs, and the first to debut in Australia was the Global X 21 Shares Bitcoin ETF (EBTC), which launched in April 2022. Most recently, the Monochrome Bitcoin ETF (IBTC) was approved and began trading on June 4 on Australia's second-largest stock exchange, the Cboe Australia exchange.
The arrival of a Bitcoin ETF on Australia's main exchange is a significant milestone. As the country's largest stock exchange, the ASX brings greater visibility, credibility, and access to Bitcoin exposure for both institutional and retail investors.
These approvals indicate a growing acceptance and interest in Bitcoin investment products within the Australian market and worldwide, and most countries will likely follow suit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vivek Sen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ZkSync token launches amid network load, RPC issues]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19595234/ZkSync-token-launches-amid-network-load-RPC-issues</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19595234/ZkSync-token-launches-amid-network-load-RPC-issues"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T14:08:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ZK token launch on multiple exchanges sees price fluctuations while zkSync manages network strain and scam threats.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum poised to 50% surge this year against Bitcoin — Fractal analysis]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19595193/Ethereum-poised-to-50-surge-this-year-against-Bitcoin-Fractal-analysis</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19595193/Ethereum-poised-to-50-surge-this-year-against-Bitcoin-Fractal-analysis"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T14:06:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ETH/BTC trading pair is forming a classic bullish reversal pattern similar to the one from 2019-2021, which led to 140% price gains for Ethereum.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Could Avert Debt Crisis, Says Ex-US House Speaker]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7414d33e93</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-could-avert-debt-crisis-ex-us-house-speaker/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T14:06:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a proposal laid out in the Wall Street Journal, former Speaker of the House Paul Ryan has advocated for a novel fiscal strategy that integrates cryptocurrency, specifically dollar-backed stablecoins, into the US economic framework to counteract the looming threat of a national debt crisis. Ryan, a prominent figure who led the House of Representatives until 2019, underscores the urgency of adopting stablecoins to prevent a catastrophic failure in the next debt auction, which he believes could undermine the global credibility of the United States and precipitate a major financial downturn.
 
Here’s How Crypto Can Save The US
 
Currently serving on the Policy Council for Paradigm, a venture capital firm focused on crypto innovations, Ryan brings a unique perspective that bridges traditiona…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Could Avert Debt Crisis, Says Ex-US House Speaker]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19595174/Crypto-Could-Avert-Debt-Crisis-Says-Ex-US-House-Speaker</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19595174/Crypto-Could-Avert-Debt-Crisis-Says-Ex-US-House-Speaker"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T14:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a proposal laid out in the Wall Street Journal, former Speaker of the House Paul Ryan has advocated for a novel fiscal strategy that integrates cryptocurrency, specifically dollar-backed stablecoins, into the US economic framework to counteract the looming threat of a national debt crisis....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC crypto watchdog resigns after nearly a decade]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19595144/SEC-crypto-watchdog-resigns-after-nearly-a-decade</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19595144/SEC-crypto-watchdog-resigns-after-nearly-a-decade"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T13:58:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Hirsch, the chief of the Crypto Assets and Cyber Unit for the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), announced hes leaving his role after almost nine years in a LinkedIn post. During that time I had the opportunity to work on more complex, challenging investigations and issues than I...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto chief bids SEC farewell after 9 years of service]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19595150/Crypto-chief-bids-SEC-farewell-after-9-years-of-service</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19595150/Crypto-chief-bids-SEC-farewell-after-9-years-of-service"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T13:58:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Hirsch has worked as an enforcement attorney for the SEC since 2015 and started his post as the chief of the crypto asset division in 2022.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SOLJU’s beverage-themed meme coin launches on Solana. Will it rally like Beercoin?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19595141/SOLJUs-beverage-themed-meme-coin-launches-on-Solana-Will-it-rally-like-Beercoin</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19595141/SOLJUs-beverage-themed-meme-coin-launches-on-Solana-Will-it-rally-like-Beercoin"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T13:57:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways Solju is introducing beverages to the meme coin ecosystem by blending South Korea’s popular Soju alcoholic beverage drink with Solana’s innovation. The presale is slated to commence in 24 hours, with a 100 million token supply. Meme coins have been among the leading...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Skyrockets With $1 Million Fund Flows as Ripple v. SEC Ruling Anticipated]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19595140/XRP-Skyrockets-With-1-Million-Fund-Flows-as-Ripple-v-SEC-Ruling-Anticipated</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19595140/XRP-Skyrockets-With-1-Million-Fund-Flows-as-Ripple-v-SEC-Ruling-Anticipated"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T13:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XRP defies market slump with $1 million inflows for second week as Ripple v. SEC verdict looms]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Runes racks up over 2500 BTC in fees under 2 months]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19595137/Bitcoin-Runes-racks-up-over-2500-BTC-in-fees-under-2-months</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19595137/Bitcoin-Runes-racks-up-over-2500-BTC-in-fees-under-2-months"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T13:52:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Runes-related transactions could extend a significant revenue boost for Bitcoin miners, after the 2024 halving.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SHIB Collapses in Key Metric Amid Price Slumping Below $0.00002]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19595090/SHIB-Collapses-in-Key-Metric-Amid-Price-Slumping-Below-000002</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19595090/SHIB-Collapses-in-Key-Metric-Amid-Price-Slumping-Below-000002"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T13:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of key Shiba Inu metrics has plummeted amid major price decline]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Bitcoin Faces A 'Critical Week Ahead']]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19595149/Why-Bitcoin-Faces-A-Critical-Week-Ahead</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19595149/Why-Bitcoin-Faces-A-Critical-Week-Ahead"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T13:39:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prominent crypto analyst Ted outlined why to key economic indicators and central bank actions could prompt significant price movements for Bitcoin (CRYPTO: BTC) in the upcoming week. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Legendary Crypto Analyst Predicts Exact Timing for Next Bitcoin Bull Run!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19595083/Legendary-Crypto-Analyst-Predicts-Exact-Timing-for-Next-Bitcoin-Bull-Run</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19595083/Legendary-Crypto-Analyst-Predicts-Exact-Timing-for-Next-Bitcoin-Bull-Run"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T13:38:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin is currently trading in a tight range between $67,000 and $65,500, showing unclear direction in the market. This lack of direction is due to unexpected economic data and the recent impact of Spot ETH ETFs approval taking away bitcoin from the limelight. Many in the crypto community...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. SEC's Crypto Enforcer David Hirsch Quits]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7414dfb5b2</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/06/17/us-secs-crypto-enforcer-david-hirsch-quits/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T13:37:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Hirsch, a senior member of the  U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission crypto oversight unit has left the organization, he posted on LinkedIn on Monday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amitoj Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Reason Micheal Saylor Bought Bitcoin #bitcoin #bitcoinnews #shorts]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19595077/The-Reason-Micheal-Saylor-Bought-Bitcoin-bitcoin-bitcoinnews-shorts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19595077/The-Reason-Micheal-Saylor-Bought-Bitcoin-bitcoin-bitcoinnews-shorts"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T13:35:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Micheal Saylor's thinking on why they ended up at bitcoinBrought to you by Bitcoinwell.com a bitcoin-only platform on a mission to enable independence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Metrics Signal Bitcoin Price Increase – But When Is Anyone’s Guess]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19595044/Metrics-Signal-Bitcoin-Price-Increase-But-When-Is-Anyones-Guess</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19595044/Metrics-Signal-Bitcoin-Price-Increase-But-When-Is-Anyones-Guess"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T13:30:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin has been on a bumpy ride in recent days. The world’s most popular cryptocurrency has seen its price steadily decline, raising concerns about a prolonged bear market. However, beneath the surface, some analysts are detecting faint bullish whispers that could signal a potential reversal....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is DOP Crypto?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19595089/What-is-DOP-Crypto</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19595089/What-is-DOP-Crypto"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T13:30:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want more privacy on-chain? Check out DOP (Data Ownership Protocol). Using zero-knowledge proof, DOP lets you choose which crypto assets and transactions to keep private. Hide your salary and portfolio from prying eyes but allow selective access for banks or tax purposes. Neat, right? Mainnet...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TXSE ‘upstart’ stock exchange could become a crypto-friendly challenger]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19595070/TXSE-upstart-stock-exchange-could-become-a-crypto-friendly-challenger</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19595070/TXSE-upstart-stock-exchange-could-become-a-crypto-friendly-challenger"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While there are many challenges for a new stock exchange in the U.S., many observers are optimistic about what it could mean for the crypto industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Discover India’s First Crypto Exchange and Its Historic Beginnings!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19595047/Discover-Indias-First-Crypto-Exchange-and-Its-Historic-Beginnings</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19595047/Discover-Indias-First-Crypto-Exchange-and-Its-Historic-Beginnings"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[India’s cryptocurrency market has been experiencing remarkable growth, with millions of users building their crypto portfolios and enjoying the benefits of digital assets. The landscape is dotted with numerous exchanges, both Indian and offshore, offering diverse services to these investors....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[#FreeSamourai]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19595068/FreeSamourai</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19595068/FreeSamourai"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samourai Wallet's founders were arrested, indicted, and charged despite following the law. It seems the US government is starting another campaign against privacy, which we cannot allow to remain unopposed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Saylor: Bitcoin’s Dip is an Opportunity, Not a Setback]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19595134/Michael-Saylor-Bitcoins-Dip-is-an-Opportunity-Not-a-Setback</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19595134/Michael-Saylor-Bitcoins-Dip-is-an-Opportunity-Not-a-Setback"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy co-founder and Bitcoin advocate Michael Saylor addressed the recent dip in Bitcoin’s price, emphasizing the importance of a long-term perspective and viewing market fluctuations as potential opportunities. His comments underscore the need for long-term thinking in Bitcoin...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Technical Analysis: ETH Faces Mixed Signals Amid Short-Term Downtrend]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7414d95ed7</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ethereum-technical-analysis-eth-faces-mixed-signals-amid-short-term-downtrend/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T13:27:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On June 17, 2024, ethereum is priced at $3,521, fluctuating between $3,495 and $3,645 over the past 24 hours. Ethereum On the 1-hour chart, ethereum’s (ETH) recent high is $3,652, and the low is $3,484. The trend has been bearish following the peak on June 21, characterized by increased selling volume. A potential entry point […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking Bitcoin with Casey Rodarmor]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19595084/Breaking-Bitcoin-with-Casey-Rodarmor</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19595084/Breaking-Bitcoin-with-Casey-Rodarmor"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T13:27:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Casey Rodarmor is a bitcoin developer and the creator of the ordinals, inscriptions, and runes protocols. In this interview, we discuss ordinal theory & inscriptions, the purpose of runes and why these projects have received so much backlash.“Especially as Bitcoin gets more popular, people are...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Doodles Will Migrate Avatar Creation 'Stoodio' to Ethereum Layer-2 Base]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235662</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235662/doodles-wmigrate-avatar-creation-stoodio-ethereum-l2-base"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T13:01:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Exclusive: Ethereum NFT project Doodles is moving its Stoodio character customization platform from Flow to Coinbase's Base network. Here's why.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erika Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why John Gerrard Is Generating Hourly Ethereum NFT Art for a Full Year]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235549</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235549/why-john-gerrard-hourly-ethereum-nft-art-full-year"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T13:01:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Released by Feral File, “Crystalline Work” will generate pieces that offer an optimistic outlook on humanity’s potential to combat climate change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Warden Protocol’s Modular Blockchain is Designed for the ‘Apps of Tomorrow’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235151</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235151/warden-protocols-modular-blockchain-is-designed-for-the-apps-of-tomorrow"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The modular layer 1 blockchain is onboarding newcomers to its ecosystem with an Incentivized Testnet Leaderboard.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bybit Integrates Apple Pay to Enhance Cryptocurrency Purchases]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7414c746f9</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/bybit-integrates-apple-pay-to-enhance-cryptocurrency-purchases/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T12:49:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cryptocurrency exchange Bybit has integrated Apple  
Pay with its Bybit Card. This new feature promises a blend of security,  
convenience, and better pricing for users purchasing cryptocurrencies through the Bybit app or website.
Access to 20+ Fiat Currencies
According to the press release, this latest offering enables Bybit's users to access over  
20 fiat currencies to purchase digital assets with Apple Pay, reportedly with  
zero transaction fees until July 1, 2024, 10 AM UTC. This promotion aims to  
encourage users to easily buy cryptocurrencies with their preferred payment  
currency directly through Apple Pay.
Apple Pay offers a payment method that is  
authenticated by face ID, Touch ID, or a device passcode, along with a unique  
dynamic security code for each transaction. Cu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Technical Analysis: BTC Endures Persistent Downward Trend Amid High Volatility]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7414c77d42</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-technical-analysis-btc-endures-persistent-downward-trend-amid-high-volatility/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T12:47:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As of June 17, 2024, Bitcoin is trading at $65,805, with a 24-hour intraday range between $65,518 and $66,992. The cryptocurrency market is displaying notable volatility, as evidenced by significant trading volume and fluctuating price levels. Bitcoin Bitcoin’s 1-hour chart reveals a clear downward trend following a recent peak, with key resistance and support levels […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[zkSync Airdrop: Almost Half of ZK Tokens Claimed Amid Tech Issues and Sybil Backlash]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235701</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235701/zksync-airdrop-half-zk-tokens-claimed"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T12:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The zkSync and ZK Nation teams have seen 45% of tokens claimed already, despite tech issues and community complaints about eligibility.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Vs. Altcoins: Renowned Finance Author Reveals The Easiest Way To Become A Millionaire]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7414c1640d</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-altcoins-a-millionaire/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T12:35:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robert Kiyosaki, the author of the renowned book “Rich Dad Poor Dad,” recently revealed Bitcoin is the easiest way anyone can become a millionaire. The renowned finance author is known to be a huge advocate of digital assets and again made a case for them while making this revelation. 
 
The “Easiest Way” To Become A Millionaire
 
Kiyosaki mentioned in an X (formerly Twitter) post that Bitcoin is the easiest way to become a millionaire. He highlighted how making millions as an entrepreneur can be. The renowned finance author noted that one has to be “really smart, dedicated, and lucky” to become a millionaire while starting their own business. As such, Kiyosaki claims he saves BTC instead because the flagship crypto does the hard work for him, which is why he loves Bitcoin. 
 
 
Besides ad…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Mover Americas: Crypto Majors Subdued After Fed's Hawkish Stance]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7414c1afe6</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/06/17/first-mover-americas-crypto-majors-subdued-after-feds-hawkish-stance/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T12:33:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest price moves in bitcoin (BTC) and crypto markets in context for June 17, 2024. First Mover is CoinDesk’s daily newsletter that contextualizes the latest actions in the crypto markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Investment Products Saw Over $600M in Outflows Last Week: CoinShares]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7414cb95ed</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/06/17/bitcoin-investment-products-saw-over-600m-in-outflows-last-week-coinshares/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T11:27:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto markets have been laid low by a hawkish stance on interest rate cuts by the FOMC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethiopian Airlines Partners With Blockchain-Based Loyalty Rewards Firm Loyyal]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7414cba140</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ethiopian-airlines-partners-with-blockchain-based-loyalty-rewards-firm-loyyal/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T11:27:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethiopian Airlines Group has partnered with Loyyal to leverage the latter’s blockchain infrastructure for its customer loyalty program. The partnership, which is earmarked for Ethiopian Airlines’ Shebamiles members, enables them to earn rewards daily, driving further engagement and loyalty. Three-Way Partnership One of the leading African airlines, Ethiopian Airlines Group, has appointed blockchain-based loyalty rewards […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin And Crypto At The Forefront: Biden Administration To Attend Key Roundtable In Washington]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7414b713a7</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/biden-admin-set-to-talk-about-bitcoin-and-crypto/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T11:04:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Administration under US President Joe Biden and Congressman Ro Khanna is slated to attend a roundtable on Bitcoin and cryptocurrencies this July in Washington, D.C., which is a significant move signaling the growing relevance of digital assets regulation and innovation.
 
Leaders in the industry, advocates, and important policymakers will come together to discuss the future of digital assets in the US at this high-profile event. In a statement, the office of Khanna called the planned gathering the most significant meeting between policymakers and innovation leaders in blockchain to date.
 
Cryptocurrency Innovation To Be Kept Inside The US
 
According to leaked reports from Bitcoin Magazine, the goal of the proposed discussion, which will be chaired by Congressman Ro Khanna of the Unit…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Godspower Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S.-Listed Bitcoin Miners Reached Record Total Market Cap of $22.8B in June: JPMorgan]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7414b10f56</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/06/17/us-listed-bitcoin-miners-reached-record-total-market-cap-of-228b-in-june-jpmorgan/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T10:51:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mining stocks outperformed bitcoin in the first half of the month as investors reacted positively to news of Core Scientific’s AI deal with CoreWeave, the report said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Canny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Singapore’s National Goalkeeper, Hassan Sunny, Appointed as Chief Security Officer for HTX Global and TRON]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7414b1b389</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/singapores-national-goalkeeper-hassan-sunny-appointed-as-chief-security-officer-for-htx-global-and-tron/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T10:47:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Singapore’s national goalkeeper, Hassan Sunny, has been appointed as the Chief Security Officer and spokesperson for HTX Global and TRON. The announcement was first made by Justin Sun on social media. Drawing parallels between Sunny’s role on the football field and his new position, Sun expressed confidence that just as Sunny defends the goal line […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Australian Securities Exchange (ASX) Approved Listing Its First Bitcoin ETF]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7414bf8a2e</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/australian-securities-exchange-asx-approved-listing-its-first-bitcoin-etf/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T10:07:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vaneck, a global investment firm, has announced the launch of the Vaneck Bitcoin ETF (VBTC), the first Bitcoin exchange-traded-fund on the Australian Securities Exchange (ASX). Set to commence trading on June 20, 2024, the ETF is touted as the most cost-effective Bitcoin fund exposure in Australia. Arian Neiron, Vaneck’s CEO for the Asia-Pacific region, emphasized […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden Officials Will Attend Bitcoin Roundtable in DC: Leaked Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235690</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235690/biden-officials-bitcoin-roundtable-dc"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T09:56:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The roundtable is being spearheaded by Rep. Ro Khanna (D-CA), a pro-crypto politician who supported the FIT21 bill.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarang Khaitan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These Central Banks Buy Bitcoin, Others Will Soon Follow, Claims Expert]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7414a4604b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/central-banks-buy-bitcoin-others-will-soon-follow/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T09:34:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a space on X that included influential voices from the industry—Bitcoin Magazine CEO David Bailey, alongside analysts Dylan LeClair and Matthew Pines—claims were made that are stirring intense discussions within financial and crypto circles. Bailey, who is serving as one of Trump’s closed Bitcoin advisors, boldly asserted that multiple central banks globally are actively acquiring Bitcoin.
 
Central Banks Are Buying Bitcoin
 
“David Bailey just claimed — without any evidence in Dylan LeClair ‘s space with Matthew Pines that central banks are buying Bitcoin,” stated Joe Carlasare, a partner at Amundsen Davis LLC. In a follow-up post on X, Bailey specifically pointed to lesser-known global players like Bhutan and Venezuela, as well as Iran, as early adopters in the central banking space.
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notcoin Loses 11% After the NOT Airdrop Claim Ends]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235669</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235669/notcoin-loses-11-after-the-not-airdrop-claim-ends"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T09:29:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Notcoin team said it's sharing details this week on how gold and platinum level stakers can earn extra rewards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Financial Stability Board to Extend Its Work on Stablecoin Risks in Emerging and Developing Economies]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7414a0c9e4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/06/17/financial-stability-board-to-extend-its-work-on-stablecoin-risks-in-emerging-and-developing-economies/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T09:03:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Financial Stability Board (FSB) said it will undertake further work to consider the challenges associated with risks of global stablecoin arrangements in emerging and developing economies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amitoj Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Counters Ripple’s $10M Penalty Proposal as It Defies “Purposes of Civil Penalty”]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7414ae9c95</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/sec-counters-ripples-10m-penalty-proposal-as-it-defies-purposes-of-civil-penalty/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T08:21:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has countered the proposal of Ripple Labs to lower the penalty against it to $10 million, saying “it would not satisfy the purposes of the civil penalty statutes.”
Ripple’s Attempt to Lower the Penalty
The SEC’s counter came on Friday, only a day after Ripple cited the recent settlement of the regulator with Terraform Labs and its former CEO, Do Kwon, to reduce a previously proposed civil penalty of $876.3 million to $10 million.
Ripple’s lawyers argued that the penalty proposed against the blockchain company by the regulator was “unreasonable” when compared to the civil penalty sought against Terraform Labs.
“As Ripple’s opposition explained, in comparable (and even more egregious) cases, the SEC has agreed to civil penalties ranging from 0.6% …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arnab Shome</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Japanese Regulator Issues Warning to Unregistered Crypto Platform Lbank Exchange]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7414af6b72</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/japanese-regulator-issues-warning-to-unregistered-crypto-platform-lbank-exchange/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T08:14:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Financial Services Agency (FSA) of Japan issued a warning to Lbank Exchange, an overseas cryptocurrency platform, for operating without registration. Lbank, which ranks 56th in trading volume according to Coingecko, has been offering services to Japanese residents despite reportedly having an unknown address and representative. This action follows similar warnings issued by the FSA […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Crypto Games: More Telegram Games Launching TON Tokens, Parallel Hits Epic Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235481</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235481/this-week-crypto-games-telegram-ton-tokens-parallel-epic"/>
        <updated>2024-06-16T16:38:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Catch up on this week’s biggest crypto and NFT gaming news and find some weekend reads in our latest roundup.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Everyone Deserves to Play': Why Xbox Head Phil Spencer's 'Doom' Comments Struck a Nerve]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235611</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235611/everyone-deserves-play-why-xbox-doom-comments-struck-nerve"/>
        <updated>2024-06-16T14:24:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Microsoft shifts away from console exclusivity, Xbox head Phil Spencer's comments on Doom: The Dark Ages aren't sitting well with some gamers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Frederiksen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Wall Street Is Greedy’: Tether Co-Founder Predicts Next ETFs After Bitcoin, Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235512</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235512/wall-street-greedy-tether-william-quigley-next-etfs-after-bitcoin-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2024-06-16T13:31:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While Wall Street interest has boosted the overall crypto market, William Quigley said it also brings risks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week on Crypto Twitter: Iggy Azalea and Andrew Tate Duel in Meme Coin Battle]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235520</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235520/this-week-on-crypto-twitter-iggy-azalea-andrew-tate-meme-coins"/>
        <updated>2024-06-16T12:31:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cameos abounded this week as a Mad Libs assortment of celebs appeared to embrace crypto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Notcoin’ Airdrop Claim Ending as Telegram Crypto Gaming Hype Builds]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235594</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235594/notcoin-airdrop-claim-ending-telegram-crypto-gaming-hype"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T15:34:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s one day left for Notcoin players to claim their NOT tokens as Hamster Kombat and other Telegram games gain serious traction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Would You Pay $40K in Solana for a Date With a Playboy Playmate?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235264</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235264/would-you-pay-40k-solana-date-playboy-playmate"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T13:01:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Only1 is a crypto-fueled OnlyFans alternative on Solana—and already, people are shelling out big bucks to get closer to creators.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erika Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week In Coins: Bitcoin Slumps, TON Surges as Gaming Tokens Burn]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235568</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235568/this-week-in-coins-bitcoin-ton-gaming-tokens"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T11:31:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto saw few winners this week, with the exception of Toncoin and some Bitcoin-bullish stocks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram Game 'Hamster Kombat' Claims Explosive Growth, Topping 150 Million Players]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235547</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235547/telegram-game-hamster-kombat-150-million-players"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T21:39:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That’s a 50% surge from just a week ago for the red-hot Telegram game ahead of the TON token. Toncoin hit an all-time high too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop Shares Edge Down Ahead of Critical Shareholder Meeting]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235538</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235538/gamestop-shares-edge-down-ahead-of-critical-shareholder-meeting"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T21:10:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price of GameStop shares were little changed Friday as Roaring Kitty's social media accounts were silent ahead of Monday's meeting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Will Hit $200,000 in 2025, MicroStrategy Will Outperform: Bernstein]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235527</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235527/bitcoin-price-200000-in-2025-microstrategy-outperform-bernstein"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T20:50:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The global investment firm Bernstein estimated Bitcoin will hit $200,000 by 2025, revising its price target from $150,000 in March.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pope Francis Calls for Global Ban on AI Weapons]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235521</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235521/pope-francis-g7-ai-weapon-ban"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T20:37:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“No machine should ever choose to take the life of a human being,” the Pontiff said at the G7 Summit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gemini to Pay Another $50 Million in Latest Settlement Over Earn Program]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235505</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235505/gemini-50-million-earn-settlement-new-york"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T19:27:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New York Attorney General Letitia James says the recovered funds “will make defrauded investors whole.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Kawailani Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Layer-2 Network Stacks Halted for 9 Hours—What Happened?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235507</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235507/bitcoin-layer-2-network-stacks-halted-9-hours"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T19:05:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stacks stopped producing blocks for about nine hours early Friday, causing a price plunge in the Bitcoin layer-2's token as well. Here's why.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[94% of Central Banks Considering Wholesale CBDCs, Says BIS]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235501</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235501/94-of-central-banks-considering-wholesale-cbdcs-says-bis"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T18:45:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to the report, central banks are more likely to issue wholesale CBDC than retail CBDC in the next six years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarang Khaitan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 138 - MORE CELEB COINS!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/KzCZzgqx/fomo-hour-138-more-celeb-coins</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/KzCZzgqx/fomo-hour-138-more-celeb-coins"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T18:05:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Altcoins bleed out heavy, BTC dominance rises towards 60%. Miners continue to be large BTC sellers, whales accumulate. ETF inflows slow, hedge fund allocations point to basis trades. ETH ETFs approvals see little movement, coming 'in the summer’. Stocks continue to hit ATHs as CPI & PPI both come in soft. TON performs best in L1s, active wallets eclipse ETH. Andrew Tate joins celebrity memecoin meta, DADDY hits $350m. SOL DEX volumes eclipse ETH in memecoin frenzy. Curve founder defaults on CRV debt as DeFi coins tumble. Terraform Labs & Do Kwon to pay $4.5bn fine to SEC. BAMK hits $350m in Runes as it issues BTC stablecoin. Gaming tokens face huge sell-off, PRIME changes tokenomics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Calculated Betrayal’: Snowden Slams OpenAI Over NSA Ties]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235490</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235490/calculated-betrayal-snowden-slams-openai-nsa-ties"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T17:38:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI's recent appointment of a former NSA director has sparked immediate backlash from whistleblower Edward Snowden and others.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Plunges as Over $150 Million in Longs Get Rekt]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235488</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235488/bitcoin-price-plunges-150-million-longs-get-rekt"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T16:53:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price of Bitcoin is falling, nearing a one-month low as more than $100 million worth of crypto long positions were liquidated in an hour.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward,Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy Can't Get Enough Bitcoin, Boosting Latest Raise to $700 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235476</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235476/microstrategy-bitcoin-boosts-latest-raise-700-million"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T15:51:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Saylor's firm just boosted its latest convertible notes raise to buy up even more Bitcoin. It already holds $14.3 billion worth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Hamster Kombat’ Daily Combo Guide: How to Earn 5 Million Free Coins in the Telegram Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233516</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/hamster-kombat-daily-combo-guide-earn-5-million-free-coins"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T15:33:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram game Hamster Kombat offers a huge daily bonus of in-game coins ahead of the airdrop. Here’s how to claim it each day.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop Stock Dips After Roaring Kitty Nearly Doubles Stake]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235470</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235470/gamestop-stock-dips-roaring-kitty-nearly-doubles-stake"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T15:16:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price of GME has been choppy early Friday as influencer investor Roaring Kitty ups position ahead of GameStop's board meeting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Greg Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nigeria Drops Tax Charges Against Binance Execs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235442</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235442/nigeria-drops-tax-charges-against-binance-execs"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T13:56:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two Binance execs have been dropped from tax evasion charges by a Nigerian agency but they still face a money laundering case.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Week in Polkadot: Moonbeam Launches $13 Million Funding Initiative]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235215</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235215/the-week-in-polkadot-moonbeam-launches-13-million-funding-initiative"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T13:01:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of Polkadot’s largest parachains is investing big in its ecosystem,  while the Polkadot community pours money into liquidity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will McCurdy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop Solana Meme Coin GME and Iggy Azalea's MOTHER See Big Weekly Losses]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235431</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235431/gamestop-solana-meme-coin-gme-and-iggy-azaleas-mother-see-big-weekly-losses"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T11:03:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MOTHER—a meme coin launched by rapper Iggy Azalea—has plummeted by 38% in the past 7 days.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarang Khaitan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notcoin Posts 10% Gain as TON Daily Active Wallets Match Ethereum Again]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235432</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235432/notcoin-posts-10-gain-as-ton-daily-active-wallets-match-ethereum-again"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T10:52:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram-based games are causing The Open Network to explode, with Notcoin leading the entire crypto market in the last 24 hours.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Cites Terra Settlement in Appeal to Cut Penalty From $2 Billion to $10 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235422</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235422/ripple-terraform-2-billion-to-10-million"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T09:45:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple arguing its penalty is too high, "even though there are no allegations of fraud in this case."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla Is Tops in ‘Real-World AI’, Elon Musk Declares]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235387</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235387/tesla-is-the-leader-in-real-world-ai-elon-musk-tell-shareholders"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T01:23:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With his massive pay package approved, the Tesla CEO touted the automaker's advancements in chip design and robotics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Backlash: Cara and ‘Not By AI’ Rage Against the Machine]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235334</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235334/anti-ai-cara-artists-platform-not-by-ai"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T23:10:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artists draw a line in the sand, declaring creative spaces free of artificial intelligence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SD3 Goes Head-to-Head With SDXL, MidJourney, and Ideogram—Which AI Image Maker Is Best?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235267</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235267/sd3-comparison-sdxl-midjourney-ideogram-best-ai-image-generator"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T22:31:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stability AI's latest release is a strong performer—just don't ask it to depict anyone lying in the grass.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paradigm Raises $850 Million to Invest in Early-Stage Crypto Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235323</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235323/paradigm-raises-850-million-invest-early-stage-crypto"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T22:01:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paradigm, the prominent crypto VC firm, has raised $850 million for its latest fund focused on nascent projects in various categories.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Greg Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roaring Kitty Now Owns $262 Million In GameStop Shares as Options Vanish]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235320</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/235320/roaring-kitty-gamestop-shares-options-gone"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T21:38:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Showing a change in his GameStop holdings, the value of Keith Gill's portfolio had decreased 55% from a week prior.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 137 - CRYPTO DIPS FURTHER]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mJ28rAx5/fomo-hour-137-crypto-dips-further</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mJ28rAx5/fomo-hour-137-crypto-dips-further"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T15:46:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto falls after slightly hawkish Fed speech. BTC whales buy $1.4bn in 24hrs. Miners continue to be large sellers of BTC. BTC ETFs see $100m inflows. MicroStrategy to raise $500m to buy BTC. Egorov CRV debt positions begin to liquidate  . Circle to support SOL for wallets. 4% of Turkey GDP used to buy stablecoins. QuantMatter say $11m stolen from OKX account. Biden to use Coinbase for crypto donations. Terraform Labs & Do Kwon set to pay $4.5bn fine. Franklin Templeton write report on SOL DePin. TON flips ETH for active addresses. Moonpay & Paypal integration goes live in EU & UK.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 136 - FIRST MOTHER, NOW DADDY?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LEzSMpGz/fomo-hour-136-first-mother-now-daddy</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LEzSMpGz/fomo-hour-136-first-mother-now-daddy"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T18:01:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETFs see another $200m outflows. Another $190m of liquidations in volatility. $1.2bn BTC leaves exchanges in a day. ETF flows largely driven by basis trades: Pal. ‘Perfect setup’ for longs into macro news today. ETH ETF approvals ‘expected this month’. Crypto in best place it has ever been: Circle CEO. China’s ICBC calls ETH ‘digital oil’. Trump wants ‘made in the USA’ BTC. Crypto hacks $19bn since 2011. Symbiotic restaking protocol sees $150m inflows. Polygon launches $720m grants program. ZKsync accused of insider allocations. CRV drop leaves $90m loans at risk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Has AI Already Changed Gaming Forever?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mZlR3He5/has-ai-already-changed-gaming-forever</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mZlR3He5/has-ai-already-changed-gaming-forever"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T19:51:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt’s Sander Lutz and Rug Radio creator Puke sat down with Simon Davis of Mighty Bear Games and VC Kyle Klemmer to discuss how AI has already remade the gaming industry—for better and for worse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 135 - BTC FALLS ON OUTFLOWS]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/bA3jJ5aA/fomo-hour-135-btc-falls-on-outflows</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/bA3jJ5aA/fomo-hour-135-btc-falls-on-outflows"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T19:03:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto falls as ETFs see first outflow in 19 days. Short positions grow on downwards move in BTC. BTC short-term realised price now at $64k. ETH ETF issuers still waiting for SEC response. UK ETNs continue to see tiny volume. SOL validators get kicked out for sandwich attacks. ZKsync airdrop happening next week. ZKsync to give 17.8% to the community. OP launches Fraud Proofs. Bitfarms plans poison pill to counter takeover bid. OKX sees outflows after security incidents. Bybit considers shutting China offices. COIN may get added to S&P500.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 134 - EU SNAP ELECTIONS LAND]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pZksMKIV/fomo-hour-134-eu-snap-elections-land</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pZksMKIV/fomo-hour-134-eu-snap-elections-land"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T15:46:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Volatility remains low, TL continues to be divisive. 2nd highest weekly close ever for BTC. Crypto funds saw $2bn inflows last week. Rumour that BlackRock will apply for SOL ETF. Base TVL hits $8bn, top of L2s for activity. zk Sync hint at TGE this week. PENDLE enters top 5 for DeFi TVL. Berachain v2 testnet goes live.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 133 - RUGGED BY HOGEN?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MSvAS9qX/fomo-hour-133-rugged-by-hogen</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MSvAS9qX/fomo-hour-133-rugged-by-hogen"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T17:26:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC still just below ATH after $218m ETF inflows. BTC OI hits record $37bn as long-short ratio rises. Amount of ETH on exchanges lowest since 2015. Franklin Templeton explores broader crypto fund. Mining stocks rise on takeover frenzy. Kraken considers $100m funding round. Binance reinstates crypto buys with Mastercard. Phantom & Jito partner for native staking.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 132 - CRYPTO STRENGTH IS GROWING]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/bQBFWC0w/fomo-hour-132-crypto-strength-is-growing</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/bQBFWC0w/fomo-hour-132-crypto-strength-is-growing"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T19:49:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto consolidates near ATH, $488m ETF inflow. BTC correlation to tech stocks highest since 2023. BTC options anticipate $74-80k move. ETH to $22k by 2030: VanEck. Robinhood to acquire Bitstamp.
Coinbase launches Smart Wallet. ByBit opens up explicitly to China users. Global liquidity breaks out to $94T. US President given new powers to block crypto. Cramer & Gensler continue to bash crypto. Gensler hints at prolonged ETH ETF process. Stand with Crypto PAC hits 1m advocates. Turkey denies plans to tax crypto. EigenLayer surpasses $20bn TVL. IONET to launch on Binance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webinar: Unleashing The Power Of Permissionless Markets With Vega Protocol]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OvA845JA/webinar-unleashing-the-power-of-permissionless-markets-with-vega-protocol</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OvA845JA/webinar-unleashing-the-power-of-permissionless-markets-with-vega-protocol"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T08:23:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join our expert panel for an insightful discussion on Vega Protocol's revolutionary approach to decentralized derivatives trading. Discover how Vega's permissionless markets enable anyone to create and trade futures and perpetuals on a fully decentralized network. Explore the potential of Vega's innovative features, such as the ability to add new assets, transfer network assets, and adjust network parameters—as well as the protocol's active markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 131 - BIG BITCOIN INFLOWS!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/a37DNT7n/fomo-hour-131-big-bitcoin-inflows</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/a37DNT7n/fomo-hour-131-big-bitcoin-inflows"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T17:06:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETFs see large $900M inflows, biggest in weeks. $800M of shorts would be liquidated above $72K. BTC to $100K if it breaks $73K in a week: Novogratz. BNB hits new ATH, breaks $100B market cap. FTX reaches $200M tax settlement with IRS. Most investors should hold BTC: Fidelity. Tether CEO criticises EU on stablecoin regulation. Japanese exchange raises $320M to recover funds. ETH ETFs could see $4B inflows in 5 months: K33. Paradigm propose MEV taxes. StarkWare plans ZK scaling for BTC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 130 - $DOG TARGETS 1B MC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ke2mFBwr/fomo-hour-130-dog-targets-1b-mc</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ke2mFBwr/fomo-hour-130-dog-targets-1b-mc"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T22:05:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Runes & Ordinals soar as DOG passes $900M. rekt Brands opens up its shares claim for NFT holders. BTC led NFT trading volume with $6.3M on the day. NodeMonkes +10% 0.289, Puppets +35% at 0.198. Runes up by DOG which soared 23% to $922M mc. BUS won the Blast Jackpot last night for a 3% win. Memecoin majors are mostly red this AM. Trader buys 10k SOL of GME. Base brings back Onchain Summer. Dapper settles massive lawsuit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 129 - ROARING RETURNS, AGAIN!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ABOejLBT/fomo-hour-129-roaring-returns-again</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ABOejLBT/fomo-hour-129-roaring-returns-again"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T21:42:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto bounces, BTC breaks 2-week downtrend. BTC low volatility points to trend continuation. BTC will top at $150k in September 2025: Brandt. $3bn ETH withdrawn from exchanges since ETF. ETH ETF inflows imply ‘base case’ price $5.3k. ETH ETF inflows won’t be like BTC: Fireblocks. BTC logo projected on ECB building. Ethena USDe hits $3bn market cap in 4 months. Maple launches DeFi institutional lending platform. OKX launches in the Netherlands. Matter Labs drops ZK ticker. Linea shuts down chain after hack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 128 - PUMP DOT FUN KEEPS PUMPING!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cziNL3TF/fomo-hour-128-pump-dot-fun-keeps-pumping</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cziNL3TF/fomo-hour-128-pump-dot-fun-keeps-pumping"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T21:41:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto nears break-out then falls on Trump verdict. 13 straight days of BTC ETF inflows, BTC whale accumulation ‘echoes 2020’. Crypto apps next year will onboard millions: Burniske. Elon denies talking crypto policy with Trump. RFK has bought 21 BTC during campaign. TON market cap falls after updating supply data. a16z donates $25m to crypto PAC. Vitalik sends 30ETH to Tornado devs. DBS Bank in Singapore custodies $650m ETH. Backlash grows over zkSync using ZK ticker. Implementing FIT21 a slow process: CFTC. Pierce recommends UK & US cross-border sandbox. Vitalik writes blog on block size wars. Hong Kong government expresses support for web3. Do Kwon & Terraform reach settlement with SEC. Large unlocks for a number of alts next month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 127 - CELEB COINS CRASH!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mGbE2GHV/fomo-hour-127-celeb-coins-crash</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mGbE2GHV/fomo-hour-127-celeb-coins-crash"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T20:28:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NYSE to launch BTC options. CME has ‘no plans’ to offer SOL futures. Stablecoin market cap rises to 2 year high. Inflation below 3.3% ‘means BTC ATH’. Crypto market cap heading to $200T: Yat Siu. Gemini recovers $2.2bn for Earn users. PayPal stablecoin will offer ‘confidential transfers’. Mastercard launches Crypto Credential pilot on BTC. Layer Zero launches on SOL. L2s are cultural extensions of ETH: Vitalik. FTX’s Salame says he will share story. SEI announces 27m SEI airdrop. ASI merger complete, to launch June 13th.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 126 - MEMECOIN MADNESS!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/eA3xqKLr/fomo-hour-126-memecoin-madness</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/eA3xqKLr/fomo-hour-126-memecoin-madness"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T21:30:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock ETF flips Grayscale in size. BTC ETFs see 11 straight days of inflows. ZKasino gives 72hours for ETH withdrawals. ENS to migrate to L2. ADA drops out of top 10 coins. Salame sentenced to 7.5 years in jail. Riot Platforms attempts takeover of Bitfarms. Ripple donates $25m to Fairshake PAC. Pump(.)fun launches live streaming. Iggy Azelea MOTHER coin leads celeb tokens. Beeple Everyday features many coins. Runes bounce, DOG hits $560m. PEPE active wallets double during rally. Cristiano Ronaldo launches 4th NFT. Friend Tech announces club wars.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum DN-404 Tokens Are a Sensation in Asia. Are They the West’s Next Big Trend?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/drcV3Zte/ethereum-dn-404-tokens-are-a-sensation-in-asia-are-they-the-wests-next-big-trend</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/drcV3Zte/ethereum-dn-404-tokens-are-a-sensation-in-asia-are-they-the-wests-next-big-trend"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T19:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz and Rug Radio creator Pukerainbow sat down for a conversation with some of the biggest adopters involved in Ethereum’s newest trend: dividing NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Buying Crypto Simplified with Mika]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/Z9rxTcnJ/buying-crypto-simplified-with-mika</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/Z9rxTcnJ/buying-crypto-simplified-with-mika"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T16:54:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the first part of our series turning crypto beginners into crypto pros, Rug Radio creator Mika guides you through the process of purchasing cryptocurrency using crypto exchange Kraken.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 125 - ETH NEARS 4K]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BrgFfEe8/fomo-hour-125-eth-nears-4k</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BrgFfEe8/fomo-hour-125-eth-nears-4k"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T17:40:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH leads rally on continued bullish ETF sentiment. Previous anti-crypto Trump comments highlighted. Wave of influencers and celebrities hacked, release coins. Phantom becomes no.1 finance app in the US. Argentina & El Salvador hold talks on BTC adoption. LINK to have large announcement on May 30th. PEPE, MOG, TURBO, TRUMP hit ATHs in ETH memes. MOG up 60%, mentioned in Beeple Everyday. Caitlyn Jenner hacker releases JENNER coin. Garga outlines future plans for BAYC. Friend Tech founder offers $200k to migrate off Base.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 124 - THE ETH ETF IS APPROVED!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5ELzjWt4/fomo-hour-124-the-eth-etf-is-approved</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5ELzjWt4/fomo-hour-124-the-eth-etf-is-approved"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T18:43:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH ETFs get approved 19b-4 forms. ETFs won’t trade until July or August: Galaxy. ETF means many coins not securities: Coinbase CLO. Coinbase relists XRP in US. SOL ETF coming: Scaramucci. US House passes vote to ban CBDC. Building a pro-crypto army in congress: Sen. Lummis. Polymarket backlash over if ETH ETF truly approved. Expect ETH ETFs to be 10-15% of BTC: Bloomberg. BTC ETFs see $1.75bn inflows over 9 days. BTC to $150k in 2024 is base case: Tom Lee. ETH co-founder moves $37m ETH to exchanges. Grayscale launches trusts for STX & NEAR. Coinbase loses against SEC on DOGE sweepstakes. ALGO ad attacks BTC, SOL, ETH. Phantom now no.2 finance App on Google Play.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 123 - ETHEREUM KEEPS GOING!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JE3lB00G/fomo-hour-123-ethereum-keeps-going</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JE3lB00G/fomo-hour-123-ethereum-keeps-going"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T15:43:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH soars, ETF S1 approvals expected in hours. US house greenlights FIT21 bill with broad support. Gensler says SEC already has rules for crypto. Hong Kong set to allow ETH staking for ETFs. ETH OI continues to soar. SOL mentioned as next ETF candidate on CNBC. SOL ETF will take years: Bloomberg. MetaMask plans BTC integration. Fed says only 7% of Americans own crypto. SBF heads to a new prison. Hong Kong orders WLD shutdown. TON added to Binance ahead of potential listing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>