<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-06-08T17:13:43.599Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-06-08T17:13:43.599Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US DOJ opposes bankrupt Bittrex’s plan to repay customers ahead of credited fines]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18533883/US-DOJ-opposes-bankrupt-Bittrexs-plan-to-repay-customers-ahead-of-credited-fines</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18533883/US-DOJ-opposes-bankrupt-Bittrexs-plan-to-repay-customers-ahead-of-credited-fines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T17:06:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bittrex owes $29 million on penalties for sanctions violations and may still face penalties in a case brought by the SEC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Are the Dangers of AI?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143861</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-are-the-dangers-of-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T17:04:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some experts believe the Singularity could occur within the next decade, although the implications for this event are broadly unknown and speculative.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Reiff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Are the Dangers of AI?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18533888/What-Are-the-Dangers-of-AI</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18533888/What-Are-the-Dangers-of-AI"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T17:04:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some experts believe the Singularity could occur within the next decade, although the implications for this event are broadly unknown and speculative.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC’s Gensler Rebuffs Crypto Complaints, Says Gave Ample Warning Heat Was Coming]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757a6f1f9e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/06/08/secs-gensler-rebuffs-crypto-complaints-says-gave-ample-warning-heat-was-coming/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T17:02:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Securities and Exchange Commissioner (SEC) Chair Gary Gensler argued there’s nothing special about the assets or exchanges in the crypto sector, and their backers can’t hide behind claims that their tokens provide utility.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cathie Wood Says ‘Uncertainty and Volatility’ Solidifies Belief That Bitcoin Will Reach $1 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18533881/Cathie-Wood-Says-Uncertainty-and-Volatility-Solidifies-Belief-That-Bitcoin-Will-Reach-1-Million</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18533881/Cathie-Wood-Says-Uncertainty-and-Volatility-Solidifies-Belief-That-Bitcoin-Will-Reach-1-Million"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T17:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ARK Invest CEO Cathie Wood has been one of the most vocal proponents of Bitcoin over the last few years. The CEO has given numerous predictions for the digital asset which she expects to reach as high as $1 million. And even though the cryptocurrency is currently trading just above $26,000 now,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gensler lays out paths for crypto compliance, criticizing Binance and Coinbase]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18533852/Gensler-lays-out-paths-for-crypto-compliance-criticizing-Binance-and-Coinbase</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18533852/Gensler-lays-out-paths-for-crypto-compliance-criticizing-Binance-and-Coinbase"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T16:55:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC chair also pushed back on public arguments about lack of guidance made by Coinbase.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fedi Hosting First Ever Pop-Up Federation At BTC Prague]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757a6826c8</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/industry-events/fedi-hosting-first-ever-pop-up-federation-at-btc-prague"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T16:55:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC Prague and Fedi are teaming up to launch the first-ever “Pop-Up Federation” on the OS, providing attendees of the BTC Prague conference with a unique opportunity to test Fedi Alpha, the builder-focused early release of the federated operating system. 
The Prague Pop-Up Federation will offer exclusive features to invitees, including the ability to broadcast messages on chat, use sats (satoshis) and access Sites sessions with event information. The event, only available during the conference, aims to turn it into a proving ground for Fedi Alpha, with attendees serving as test pilots.
Fedi co-founder and CEO, Obi Nwosu, expressed the importance of involving the Bitcoin community in shaping Fedi: "We’re building Fedi with you ... It’s about turning BTC Prague into a proving ground, and all of the attendees into the test pilots of Fedi Alpha."
Participants can download a limited version of Fedi Alpha to join the Prague Pop-Up Federation, enabling them to receive live updates from the conference, engage in secure chats and send/receive sats to fellow attendees. The project showcases Fedi's vision of a federated operating system that empowers individuals and communities to regain control over their money and data.
BTC Prague Organizer, Martin Kuchar, highlighted the project's ambition and expressed support for its success, stating, "The project is as ambitious as it is exciting, and we are rooting hard for its success."
Fedi encourages participants to approach the event as a test and provide feedback to help improve the platform. The pop-up serves as a testament to the collaborative spirit of the Bitcoin community and its commitment to building a decentralized future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BtcCasey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ZEBEDEE Announces Alpha For New Social Layer Powered By Nostr]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757a6826bb</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/zebedee-announces-alpha-for-new-social-layer-powered-by-nostr"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T16:55:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ZEBEDEE, a company known for its Lightning-powered ecosystem, has unveiled the alpha version of its latest app upgrade, Social. According to a press release shared with Bitcoin Magazine, this groundbreaking social layer introduces a new paradigm for social media, where engagement and content are transformed into monetary value. Creators on the platform will retain an impressive 99% of their earnings according to the release, providing what ZEBEDEE describes as a fair and value-driven experience. The ZBD app, powered by Nostr, a decentralized protocol with over 2 million users created at NBD, ZEBEDEE’s open-source arm, aims to empower individuals from diverse backgrounds to monetize their online identities.
ZEBEDEE noted that its app's new features have attracted partnerships with prominent…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BtcCasey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Can Save California’s Largest Pension Fund From Its Existential Problems]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757a6826b5</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/how-bitcoin-can-save-californias-440-billion-pension-fund"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T16:55:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is an opinion editorial by Dom Bei, the former Santa Monica Firefighters Union president.
Author’s note: Pension issues have been in and out of the media for decades. My own background and perspective on these issues come from over a decade of experience as an executive board member for my local firefighter’s union. Additionally, I sat on my municipality’s pension advisory board, where I learned the fundamentals of pension funds. This is a complex issue, but one worthy of our time and attention due to its significance in the global financial system and the lives of our workforce.
 
         
         
         
        Source 
    
What if I told you that the largest pension fund in the United States could be rescued by Bitcoin? Furthermore, what if it could happen in a way that maint…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dom Bei</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Where Does Crypto Stand Now?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18533854/Where-Does-Crypto-Stand-Now</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18533854/Where-Does-Crypto-Stand-Now"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T16:50:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[🚀 Learn Technical Analysis with our FREE course! https://www.chartguys.com/trading-courses/7/technical-analysis?utm_source=youtube&utm_medium=social&utm_term=&utm_content=&utm_campaign=free-ta-courseOur goal is to review and discuss the most recent price action in the market in a manner that...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tuberville bill would block Chinese ownership of US crypto companies]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18533832/Tuberville-bill-would-block-Chinese-ownership-of-US-crypto-companies</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18533832/Tuberville-bill-would-block-Chinese-ownership-of-US-crypto-companies"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T16:47:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bill could be slipped into the US Farm Bill up to be renewed in September 2023, Sen. Tommy Tuberville said]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mike Novogratz: Galaxy Digital 'Looking at How Fast We Can Move People Offshore']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143850</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143850/mike-novogratz-galaxy-digital-looking-at-how-fast-we-can-move-people-offshore"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T16:39:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A "legislative stalemate" in the U.S. has the crypto investment firm accelerating its plans to move offshore.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Justin Sun and Huobi play shell game with ownership]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18533815/Justin-Sun-and-Huobi-play-shell-game-with-ownership</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18533815/Justin-Sun-and-Huobi-play-shell-game-with-ownership"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T16:37:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Justin Sun no longer does business as a Chinese citizen but he has been establishing firms in Hong Kong with his St. Kitts and Nevis identity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Staked on Coinbase Sees Massive Redemptions, Over 27,000 Tokens Redeemed on June 6]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757a6ad822</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ethereum-staked-on-coinbase-sees-massive-redemptions-over-27000-tokens-redeemed-on-june-6/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T16:36:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recent statistics reveal that a significant amount of ethereum staked on Coinbase has been redeemed, with 27,280 tokens being redeemed on June 6. This development comes in the wake of the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) filing a lawsuit against Coinbase for not registering its staking-as-a-service program.
 
Redemptions Soar on Coinbase Amidst SEC Lawsuit Fallout
 
June 6, 2023, marked a pivotal moment for Coinbase as the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) filed a lawsuit against the San Francisco-based exchange. One of the SEC’s complaints alleges that Coinbase neglected to register its staking-as-a-service platform. In the aftermath of this legal action, Dune Analytics has recorded tens of thousands of redemptions for Coinbase’s CBETH, the exchange’s staked ether…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pro-Ripple Lawyer Highlights Monumental Day for Crypto Due to These Three Events]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18533842/Pro-Ripple-Lawyer-Highlights-Monumental-Day-for-Crypto-Due-to-These-Three-Events</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18533842/Pro-Ripple-Lawyer-Highlights-Monumental-Day-for-Crypto-Due-to-These-Three-Events"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T16:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Historic dates for crypto highlighted by pro-XRP lawyer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Chair Argues That It Is Possible for Crypto Platforms To Register Following Lawsuits Against Coinbase and Binance]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18533836/SEC-Chair-Argues-That-It-Is-Possible-for-Crypto-Platforms-To-Register-Following-Lawsuits-Against-Coinbase-and-Binance</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18533836/SEC-Chair-Argues-That-It-Is-Possible-for-Crypto-Platforms-To-Register-Following-Lawsuits-Against-Coinbase-and-Binance"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T16:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Securities and Exchange Commission Chair Gary Gensler laid into the crypto industry on Thursday, arguing that it is possible for exchanges to register with the agency, despite platforms’ assertions that they tried to do just that. ... Read More: SEC Chair Argues That It Is Possible for Crypto...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase isn’t changing a thing in the wake of the SEC’s lawsuit against it]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18533814/Coinbase-isnt-changing-a-thing-in-the-wake-of-the-SECs-lawsuit-against-it</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18533814/Coinbase-isnt-changing-a-thing-in-the-wake-of-the-SECs-lawsuit-against-it"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T16:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Developers Cement Final Lineup of Changes in ‘Dencun’ Upgrade]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757a6b8587</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/06/08/ethereum-developers-cement-final-lineup-of-changes-in-dencun-upgrade/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T16:31:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Proto-danksharding is at the heart of the package, with other improvements for storage on-chain, as well as minor code changes related to the Ethereum Virtual Machine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Margaux Nijkerk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Has the market lost its faith in stablecoins? Assessing…]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18533806/Has-the-market-lost-its-faith-in-stablecoins-Assessing</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18533806/Has-the-market-lost-its-faith-in-stablecoins-Assessing"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T16:30:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The stablecoin sector witnessed a decline in market capitalization, but signs of increased whale interest and potential recovery provide hope for its future stability and growth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Sandbox (SAND) Owner Animoca Brands to Focus on Non-US Customers]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18533816/The-Sandbox-SAND-Owner-Animoca-Brands-to-Focus-on-Non-US-Customers</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18533816/The-Sandbox-SAND-Owner-Animoca-Brands-to-Focus-on-Non-US-Customers"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC’s Gensler Rebuffs Crypto Complaints, Says Gave Ample Warning Heat Was Coming]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18533833/SECs-Gensler-Rebuffs-Crypto-Complaints-Says-Gave-Ample-Warning-Heat-Was-Coming</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18533833/SECs-Gensler-Rebuffs-Crypto-Complaints-Says-Gave-Ample-Warning-Heat-Was-Coming"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Securities and Exchange Commissioner (SEC) Chair Gary Gensler argued there’s nothing special about the assets or exchanges in the crypto sector, and their backers can’t hide behind claims that their tokens provide utility.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chancer introduces a unique betting platform for cryptocurrency enthusiasts]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18533773/Chancer-introduces-a-unique-betting-platform-for-cryptocurrency-enthusiasts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18533773/Chancer-introduces-a-unique-betting-platform-for-cryptocurrency-enthusiasts"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T16:27:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways Chancer is building a decentralised betting platform that allows users to create and bet on events of their choosing, The presale will commence next week and the team seeks to raise $15 million to fund its products. When you hear betting, the first thing that pops into your mind is...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Trading Volumes At 1-Month Highs, More Volatility Imminent?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757a54d996</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-ethereum-trading-volumes-1-highs-volatility/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T16:23:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data shows the trading volumes of large assets like Bitcoin and Ethereum have observed a surge toward one-month-highs.
 
Bitcoin, Ethereum, & Other Assets Have Registered An Increase In Volumes
 
According to data from the on-chain analytics firm Santiment, the trading volume has been up across the market since the price plunge. The “trading volume” here refers to an indicator that measures the daily total amount of a given cryptocurrency that’s being transacted on the blockchain right now.
 
When the value of this metric is high, it means a large number of tokens of the asset in question are being moved around on the network currently. Such a trend generally suggests that a high amount of traders are active in the market right now.
 
On the other hand, low values of the indicator…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hououin Kyouma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Make MILLIONS From Bitcoin BRC-20 Ordinals | How to BUY, STORE & TRADE!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18533770/Make-MILLIONS-From-Bitcoin-BRC-20-Ordinals-How-to-BUY-STORE-TRADE</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18533770/Make-MILLIONS-From-Bitcoin-BRC-20-Ordinals-How-to-BUY-STORE-TRADE"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T16:21:36.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Investors Remain Resilient Despite Blow on Coinbase, Binance: Data]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18533782/Bitcoin-Investors-Remain-Resilient-Despite-Blow-on-Coinbase-Binance-Data</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18533782/Bitcoin-Investors-Remain-Resilient-Despite-Blow-on-Coinbase-Binance-Data"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T16:20:47.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana is Going to Zero After SEC Lawsuit Deems SOL a Security and Investors are Moving to Ecoterra as the Platform Raises $4.9 Million – What Does it Do?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18533767/Solana-is-Going-to-Zero-After-SEC-Lawsuit-Deems-SOL-a-Security-and-Investors-are-Moving-to-Ecoterra-as-the-Platform-Raises-49-Million-What-Does-it-Do</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18533767/Solana-is-Going-to-Zero-After-SEC-Lawsuit-Deems-SOL-a-Security-and-Investors-are-Moving-to-Ecoterra-as-the-Platform-Raises-49-Million-What-Does-it-Do"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T16:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Regulators Uncover Binance's Billions of Dollars Transactions Through U.S. Banks]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18533847/Regulators-Uncover-Binances-Billions-of-Dollars-Transactions-Through-US-Banks</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18533847/Regulators-Uncover-Binances-Billions-of-Dollars-Transactions-Through-US-Banks"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T16:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Regulators Uncover Binance's Billions of Dollars Transactions Through U.S. Banks]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18533768/Regulators-Uncover-Binances-Billions-of-Dollars-Transactions-Through-US-Banks</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18533768/Regulators-Uncover-Binances-Billions-of-Dollars-Transactions-Through-US-Banks"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T16:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Trading Volumes At 1-Month Highs, More Volatility Imminent?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18533741/Bitcoin-Ethereum-Trading-Volumes-At-1-Month-Highs-More-Volatility-Imminent</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18533741/Bitcoin-Ethereum-Trading-Volumes-At-1-Month-Highs-More-Volatility-Imminent"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T16:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Circle Rolls Out Support for USDC Stablecoin on Arbitrum]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757a528841</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/06/08/circle-rolls-out-support-for-usdc-stablecoin-on-arbitrum/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T15:46:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several key applications will support Arbitrum-based USDC like Aave, Balancer, Camelot, Coinbase, Curve, GMX, Radiant, Trader Joe and Uniswap.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sage D. Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ConsenSys Faces Shareholder Vote Over Controversial Transfer of Company Assets]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757a5c0fd9</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/06/08/consensys-faces-shareholder-vote-over-controversial-transfer-of-company-assets/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T15:36:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ethereum developer is accused of squeezing former employees out of shares held in a previous incarnation of the company. The case, which could have wide-ranging consequences for ConsenSys, reaches its next stage today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashley Rindsberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When AI and Blockchain Merge, Expect the Mundane at First]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757a5c0fcd</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/06/08/when-ai-and-blockchain-merge-expect-the-mundane-at-first/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T15:36:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[dek tk]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Brody</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biggest Movers: ADA, SOL Plunge to 3-Month Lows on Thursday]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757a5db0e3</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/biggest-movers-ada-sol-plunge-to-3-month-lows-on-thursday/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T15:25:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano dropped to a three-month low on Thursday, as sentiment in cryptocurrency markets remained largely bearish. The move comes as traders continue to worry about what the recent Binance and Coinbase lawsuits could mean for the wider market. Solana also slipped to a multi-month low.
 
Cardano (ADA)
 
Cardano (ADA) plunged to a three-month low on Thursday, as traders remained nervous, following the recent U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) lawsuits.
 
After a high of $0.3376 on Wednesday, ADA/USD dropped to a bottom at $0.3196 earlier in today’s session.
 
The drop pushed the token to its lowest level since March 15, when price was at a bottom of $0.3166.
 
 
Looking at the chart, this decline came as the relative strength index (RSI) moved deep into oversold territory, falling to a low below 30.00.
 
The index has since rebounded, and is tracking at 34.21, which is marginally above a key level of resistance at the 33.00 mark.
 
Should this upward momentum continue, bulls will look to recapture the $0.3500 level.
 
 
Solana (SOL)
 
In addition to ADA, solana (SOL) sank to a multi-month low of its own during today’s session.
 
SOL/USD fell to an intraday low of $18.29 on Thursday, which comes less than a day after the price was above $20.00.
 
As a result of this latest decline, solana fell to its weakest point since March 13, when the price was under $18.00.
 
 
Overall, SOL is down by almost 9% in the last seven days, with the 10-day (red) moving average (MA) in free fall as a result.
 
Should the trend line maintain its current course, there will be a downward cross with the 25-day (blue) MA.
 
For bears who still remain despite the recent oversold status, the next target will likely be $16.00.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
Could solana fall to $16.00 this week? Let us know your thoughts in the comments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Shares Are 'Uninvestable' in the Near Term: Berenberg]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757a5dd2d5</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/06/08/coinbase-shares-are-uninvestable-in-the-near-term-berenberg/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T15:24:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The investment bank cut its price target on the stock to $39 from $55.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Canny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Judge Dismisses Lawsuit Against DeFi Startup, PoolTogether]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757a5e3352</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/us-dismissed-lawsuit-against-pooltogether-defi/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T15:22:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The decentralized finance (DeFi) community received good news yesterday after the 2-year-long lawsuit against the DeFi protocol PoolTogether finally came to an end. PoolTogether’s co-founder, Leighton Cusack, excitedly shared the update on Twitter, saying the court has dismissed the case.
 
US federal judge Frederic Block dismissed the lawsuit filed by Joseph Kent against the DeFi Startup in October 2022. 
 
Why Judge Dismissed Lawsuit Against DeFi Startup
 
The former head of tech for Senator Elizabeth Warren’s presidential campaign, Joseph Kent, filed a reformed class action lawsuit against PoolTogther Inc. The plaintiff sued the firm for severe damages after depositing $12 worth of stablecoins into the protocol. 
 
Related Reading: Anti-SEC And Gensler Meme Coins Skyrocket In Value – He…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kent Glory</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Gala Safe? Gala Games Head of Blockchain on GALA, Crypto, and SEC Regulatory Turmoil]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5bcrE8nL/is-gala-safe-gala-games-head-of-blockchain-on-gala-crypto-and-sec-regulatory-turmoil</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5bcrE8nL/is-gala-safe-gala-games-head-of-blockchain-on-gala-crypto-and-sec-regulatory-turmoil"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T15:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gala Games President of Blockchain shares his thoughts on the GALA token upgrade and the latest SEC turmoil with Decrypt's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[European Consumer Group Slams Twitter, Instagram for ‘Misleading' Crypto Ads]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757a583d70</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/european-consumer-group-slams-twitter-instagram-for-misleading-crypto-ads/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T15:09:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The European  
Consumer Organization (BEUC) has filed a complaint with the European Commission  
and consumer authorities against Instagram, YouTube, TikTok, and Twitter, for  
facilitating 'misleading' promotion of cryptocurrencies.
In a report dubbed  
'Hype or harm? The great social media crypto con', BEUC blamed the social  
media platforms for promoting cryptocurrencies using advertisements and  
influencers in what it termed 'unfair commercial practice' that exposes  
investors to potential losses.
Call to Tighten  
Crypto Regulations
The complaint  
follows lawsuits against top cryptocurrency exchanges, Coinbase  
and Binance, by the US financial regulators and the collapse  
of FTX in November last year. The loss suffered by investors from the  
collapse of the Bahamas-based deriva…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Artists Adopting NFTs Has Been ‘Really Market Dependent’, Says NFT Club Berlin’s Rebekka Revel]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/QKlIVlj3/artists-adopting-nfts-has-been-really-market-dependent-says-nft-club-berlins-rebekka-revel</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/QKlIVlj3/artists-adopting-nfts-has-been-really-market-dependent-says-nft-club-berlins-rebekka-revel"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T15:07:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Getting non-crypto artists to make the leap into Web3 comes in ebbs and flows according to the market’s bear and bull waves, says co-founder of NFT Club Berlin and Superteam Germany Rebekka Revel. But she’s hoping to change that by changing the narrative around digital collectibles, regardless of the market, one word at a time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big Brands Exploring Web3 to ‘Scale Up Their Superfan Base’: SuperDuper Co-founder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/he6UzJwz/big-brands-exploring-web3-to-scale-up-their-superfan-base-superduper-co-founder</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/he6UzJwz/big-brands-exploring-web3-to-scale-up-their-superfan-base-superduper-co-founder"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T14:49:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Co-founder and co-CEO of Web3 media brand SuperDuper Dom Smith says big brands are eager to enter the space—they just don’t know how. Still, they all maintain a thesis of turning their communities into “super fans” that generate value for users as well as a firm’s bottom line.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[eToro: 'We Remain a Supporter of Crypto' Amid Enforcement Blitz]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143819</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143819/etoro-we-remain-supporter-of-crypto-amid-sec-lawsuits"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T14:37:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The agency’s lawsuit against Binance and Coinbase has drawn the attention of other firms that offer stocks and crypto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another Mysterious Signed Message Appears Associated With the 2009 Bitcoin Block 1,018]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757a41d1df</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/another-mysterious-signed-message-appears-associated-with-the-2009-bitcoin-block-1018/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T14:05:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, the number of Ordinal inscriptions has exceeded 11 million, with one inscription in particular, numbered 11,035,214, standing out. The inscription bears a message that has been signed with the private key associated with block 1,018, and while the key is quite old, having been linked to the computer scientist Hal Finney, this isn’t the first time someone has used this specific private key from 2009 to sign a message.
 
Mysterious Messages Signed With Hal Finney’s Keys Puzzle Cryptocurrency Community
 
In November of 2022, a post on bitcointalk.org caught the attention of many in the cryptocurrency community. The user, who went by the name “Onesignature,” had published a message that was signed with a specific address created on January 19, 2009. This address, known as “1NChf,” h…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Providing Regulatory Clarity (Binance and Coinbase Edition)]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757a42755c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/06/08/providing-regulatory-clarity-binance-and-coinbase-edition/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T14:01:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC sued Binance and Coinbase this week, presenting the industry with both further analysis on why it thinks certain cryptocurrencies are securities and its biggest test to how cryptos may be regulated in the U.S. going forward.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are DAOs Doomed to ‘Decentralization Theater’?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757a427545</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/06/08/are-daos-doomed-to-decentralization-theater/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T14:01:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Consensus 2023 guests highlighted their concerns over 'decentralization theater' in DeFi projects, emphasizing the importance of genuine decentralization in the development of the Web3 ecosystem]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cam Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cut the Jargon, Keep Your Promises: How Crypto Can Fix Its Image Problem]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757a427538</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/06/08/cut-the-jargon-keep-your-promises-how-crypto-can-fix-its-image-problem/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T14:01:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Consensus 2023 attendees argued that improving crypto's image requires a clearer explanation of digital assets and a focus on tangible, user-centric products and services]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Baker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lens Protocol Raises $15 Million to Expand Decentralized Social Media]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143789</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143789/lens-protocol-raises-15-million-to-expand-decentralized-social-media"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Part of the Aave open-source decentralized lending network, Lens encourages users to own their online presence via alternatives to platforms like Twitter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK Authors' Union Issues Guidance to 'Protect' Writers’ Work From AI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143809</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143809/uk-authors-union-issues-guidance-to-protect-writers-work-from-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T13:46:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Society of Authors warned writers to be careful as “money today could simply speed up the absence of any work at all in the future.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aave-Developed Lens Protocol Raises $15M to Expand 'Social Layer' of Web3]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757a4ce576</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/06/08/aave-developed-lens-protocol-raises-15m-to-expand-social-layer-of-web3/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T13:45:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Uniswap CEO Hayden Adams, OpenSea co-founder Alex Atallah, entrepreneur Balaji Srinivasan and Polygon co-founder Sandeep Nailwal joined the round as angel investors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Moved Billions Through US Bank Accounts Controlled by CZ, Says SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143814</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143814/binance-moved-billions-through-us-bank-accounts-controlled-by-cz-sec"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T13:44:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The filing claims Binance entities commingled funds and funneled them to a Paxos affiliate through Merit Peak, which was controlled by Changpeng Zhao.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Banks Have Come to the Metaverse]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757a4ea903</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/web3/2023/06/08/banks-have-come-to-the-metaverse/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T13:34:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JPMorgan, HSBC and others have created metaverse-native banking experiences, hoping to entice a new generation of clients.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Akhlaghi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Earn Bitcoin for Using This Twitter Alternative]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143776</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143776/you-can-earn-bitcoin-for-using-social-media-zebedee-app"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T12:59:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Say goodbye to meaningless likes and embrace the opportunity to earn money for your online contributions," said Zebedee co-founder Andre Neves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alyssa Hertig</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New UK Crypto Investors Face ‘Cooling-Off Period’ Under FCA Rules]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143810</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143810/new-uk-crypto-investors-face-cooling-off-period-under-fca-rules"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T12:24:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new advertising rules will force first-time investors to wait 24 hours between requesting to purchase crypto and being able to buy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Vision Pro vs. Meta Quest Pro: What's the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143783</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143783/apple-vision-pro-vs-meta-quest-pro-whats-difference"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T12:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s the battle of Pro headsets from tech giants. How does Apple’s first effort compare to the market leader’s top-end device?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Chair Gensler Offered to Serve as Binance Advisor in 2019, Lawyers Claim]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143805</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143805/sec-chair-gensler-offered-to-serve-as-binance-advisor-in-2019-lawyers-claim"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T10:53:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Documents filed as part of the ongoing court case between the SEC and Binance allege that Gary Gensler and Changpeng Zhao have history.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How 1 Simple Question Kickstarted Performance Artist Foodmasku's Plunge Into NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/w86DMn3p/how-1-simple-question-kickstarted-performance-artist-foodmaskus-plunge-into-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/w86DMn3p/how-1-simple-question-kickstarted-performance-artist-foodmaskus-plunge-into-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T10:10:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As his food mask creations went viral on the Internet during the COVID lockdowns, reposted on TikTok and Instagram without his consent, he soon asked: "How do I protect my digital files?" Performance artist Foodmasku describes at this year's NFC Lisbon how that simple question spiraled into a minting collection after collection of his edible works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arianee CEO Pegs Wine and Spirits as Next 'Exciting' Industry to Make Web3 Leap]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Bo2NeG9Z/arianee-ceo-pegs-wine-and-spirits-as-next-exciting-industry-to-make-web3-leap</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Bo2NeG9Z/arianee-ceo-pegs-wine-and-spirits-as-next-exciting-industry-to-make-web3-leap"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T09:28:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CEO and co-founder of Arianee Pierre Nicolas Hurstel unpacks the wide spectrum of digital collectibles from 10,000 PFP collections to access passes for exclusive events. And with an unannounced big brand soon joining, Hurstel revealed at NFC Lisbon which kind of NFTs big brands are moving towards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cathie Wood's ARK Bought $22M Worth of Coinbase Shares After the Price Tanked]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143780</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143780/coinbases-stock-tanked-cathie-wood-bought-more-shares"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T00:28:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ARK Invest is the second largest COIN shareholder behind Vanguard Group.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s the Difference Between the Binance and Coinbase SEC Lawsuits?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143718</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143718/difference-between-binance-coinbase-sec-lawsuits"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T23:48:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC has gone after the two major crypto brands this week—but with very different allegations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Did Apple's Headset Reveal Revive the Web3 Metaverse—Or Kill It?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143752</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143752/did-apples-headset-reveal-revive-web3-metaverse"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T23:22:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple's Vision Pro could inject much-needed life into the sagging metaverse industry, but can the tech giant complement Web3's open ethos?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Radio Host Sues OpenAI for Libel After ChatGPT Accuses Him of Crime]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143764</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143764/openai-sued-for-libel-after-chatgpt-accuses-man-of-crime"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T23:14:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Georgia-based broadcaster claims defamation after ChatGPT allegedly said he embezzled funds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Big Ass No’: Hong Kong Trading Not a Sign China Is Warming Up to Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143739</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143739/big-ass-no-china-not-warming-up-to-crypto-following-hong-kongs-move"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T23:07:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong is trying to be a crypto hub again. This doesn’t mean China is following suit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC Has Not Labeled Any Proof-of-Work Asset as a Security—Why Is That?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143760</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143760/why-has-the-sec-not-labeled-any-proof-of-work-asset-as-a-security"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T22:51:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The agency has focused on Proof-of-Stake coins, leaving Bitcoin and other Proof-of-Work blockchains unfazed by the current regulatory push.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop Fires CEO Who Oversaw Retailer's NFT Push]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143757</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143757/gamestop-fires-ceo-who-oversaw-retailers-nft-push"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T22:31:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Months after signaling a retreat from crypto efforts, GameStop axes CEO Matt Furlong and promotes Ryan Cohen to executive chairman.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance.US Pulls Several Trading Pairs in Wake of SEC Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143741</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143741/binance-us-pulls-several-trading-pairs-in-wake-of-sec-lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T21:11:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cryptocurrency exchange will drop over 40 trading pairs from their platform, the majority against USDT.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why 'Words With Friends' Creator Paul Bettner is 'Allergic' to Pay-to-Win NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JkfOleb4/why-words-with-friends-creator-paul-bettner-is-allergic-to-pay-to-win-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JkfOleb4/why-words-with-friends-creator-paul-bettner-is-allergic-to-pay-to-win-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T20:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Words With Friends and Wildcard creator Paul Bettner tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about his perspective on what to do when NFTs become in-game characters and assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Puma Plots NFT Sneaker Drop With NBA's LaMelo Ball, Gutter Cat Gang]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143731</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143731/puma-plots-nft-sneaker-drop-nba-lamelo-ball-gutter-cat-gang"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T20:41:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sportswear brand Puma has partnered with NBA star LeMelo Ball to drop a limited edition pair of sneakers featuring Gutter Cat Gang branding.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Farren</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi Trading Surges as Centralized Exchanges Feel Regulators' Wrath]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143729</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143729/defi-trading-surges-as-centralized-exchanges-feel-regulators-wrath"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T20:06:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After back-to-back SEC enforcement actions against centralized exchanges, Uniswap has seen a 41% increase in trading volume.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitch Co-Founder Justin Kan: 18 Months is 'Several Decades' in Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rKVvsPFb/twitch-co-founder-justin-kan-18-months-is-several-decades-in-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rKVvsPFb/twitch-co-founder-justin-kan-18-months-is-several-decades-in-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fractal and Twitch co-founder Justin Kan gives Decrypt's Kate Irwin an update on all things Fractal and his perspective on blockchain technology in gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SAG Head: AI Is a ‘Game Changer’ With Both Threats and Opportunities]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143723</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143723/sag-head-ai-is-a-game-changer-presenting-both-threats-and-opportunities"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T19:18:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SAG-AFTRA members seek “informed consent and fair compensation” if AI is used to recreate an actor’s likeness.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will MiCA Jumpstart Crypto in EU? It's ‘Too Early To Tell’, Says Circle]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143717</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143717/unclear-whether-mica-will-jumpstart-crypto-in-eu-circle-europe-policy-head"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T18:43:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["It does give us that legal certainty that we needed, but it’s just really a part of the story," Kraken's EU policy head said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alys Key</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sandbox COO: 'We Do Not Agree' With SEC Labeling SAND Token a Security]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143707</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143707/sandbox-does-not-agree-sec-labeling-sand-token-security"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T18:26:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SAND was called out this week as the U.S. regulator targets Binance and Coinbase, but The Sandbox says it’s business as usual for now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Central Banks Should Not Dominate CBDCs, Says an Ex-Central Banker]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143702</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143702/central-banks-should-not-dominate-cbdc-says-ex-central-banker"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T17:45:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jón Helgi Egilsson, a former chairman of the Icelandic central bank, urged his former counterparts to "embrace competition" on CBDCs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alys Key</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do Kwon Claims to Have Backed Political Party in Montenegro: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143690</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143690/do-kwon-claims-to-have-backed-political-party-in-montenegro-report"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T16:04:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terra co-founder Do Kwon allegedly had financial relations with the leader of a political party in Montenegro.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Oasis Rocker Noel Gallagher Turns to NFTs to Top Foo Fighters in UK Chart Race]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143693</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143693/oasis-rocker-noel-gallagher-turns-nfts-top-foo-fighters-uk-chart-race"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T15:58:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s a fervent fight to top the album charts, and Noel Gallagher’s High Flying Birds is launching an NFT edition to try and eke out a win.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ali Shutler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IKEA Research Studio Uses AI to Create a Folding Sofa that Fits in an Envelope]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143677</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143677/ikea-research-studio-uses-ai-to-create-a-folding-sofa-that-fits-in-an-envelope"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T12:51:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re heading towards a future where getting sofas up and down flights of stairs is no longer a Sisyphean chore.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Court Gives SEC One Week to Respond to Coinbase’s Rulemaking Petition]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143673</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143673/us-court-gives-sec-one-week-to-respond-to-coinbases-rulemaking-petition"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T10:50:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Court of Appeals for the Third Circuit has given the SEC seven days to clarify its position on a rulemaking petition from Coinbase.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Louis Vuitton to Sell $41,000 NFTs to Top Customers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143654</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143654/louis-vuitton-to-sell-41000-nfts-to-top-customers"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T03:46:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Treasure Trunks” is the first in a series of projects to entice the luxury brand’s elite clientele with exclusive perks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Black Mirror' Creator Says ChatGPT Episode Script Was 'Shit']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143647</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143647/black-mirror-creator-says-chatgpt-episode-script-was-shit"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T00:31:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Emmy winning sci-fi creator found the AI tool only managed to write a subpar mashup of old episodes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Senators Question Meta CEO Mark Zuckerberg Over LLaMA AI Model “Leak”]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143638</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143638/senators-question-meta-ceo-mark-zuckerberg-over-llama-ai-model-leak"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T23:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lawmakers decry the release of Meta’s advanced and uncensored Large Language Model, and ask what the company is doing to minimize its damage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kevin O’Leary: Binance Will Be 'Starved of Oxygen' by SEC’s Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143631</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143631/kevin-oleary-binance-will-be-starved-of-oxygen-by-secs-lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T23:18:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The “Shark Tank” star says today’s top digital asset firms are likely destined to live on only in history books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tokens Bounce Back Across the Market After SEC Triggers Turmoil]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143633</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143633/tokens-bounce-back-across-the-market-after-sec-triggers-turmoil"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T22:39:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite legal actions against the two largest cryptocurrency exchanges, only two tokens are seeing red candles today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Seeks Emergency Order to Freeze Binance US Assets]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143621</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143621/sec-seeks-emergency-order-to-freeze-binance-us-assets"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T21:49:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If granted, the motion requests the repatriation of assets and the preservation of records.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meeting Giant Zoom Launches AI Meeting Summaries and Chat]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143620</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143620/meeting-giant-zoom-launches-ai-meeting-summaries-and-chat"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T21:41:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite a crowded marketplace, Zoom has huge market share and is emphasizing real-time results.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Looking to Sell Shares in Anthropic Amid AI Boom: Semafor]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143615</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143615/ftx-looking-to-sell-anthropic-shares-amid-ai-boom-semafor"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T21:18:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The collapsed exchange may be looking to sell its $500 million stake in a competitor to OpenAI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Plans to Fight SEC Lawsuit, Carry On With 'Business as Usual']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143612</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143612/coinbase-plans-to-fight-sec-lawsuit-carry-on-with-business-as-usual"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T20:47:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase legal chief Paul Grewal was in DC to speak at a hearing on the Digital Asset Market Structure Discussion Draft.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Are Possible Uses of ChatGPT?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143613</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-are-possible-uses-of-chatgpt-3"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T20:32:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A key distinction between ChatGPT and earlier chatbot models is that it was developed and trained using a process known as reinforcement learning from human feedback (RLHF).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Reiff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Hit With Pending Cease and Desist Orders From 11 States]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143603</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143603/coinbase-hit-with-pending-cease-and-desist-orders-from-11-states"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T20:10:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[California, Illinois, Maryland, and New Jersey were among the states warning Coinbase its staking product does not comply with securities rules.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ignoring Disruptive Blockchain Companies Is a 'Fundamental Mistake': Amplify ETFs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143591</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143591/ignoring-disruptive-blockchain-companies-fundamental-mistake-amplify-blok-etf"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T19:52:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As crypto markets see another dramatic turn of events, some digital asset managers are still betting on Bitcoin miners and other tech disruptors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Playing for Money in Web3 Games Not 'Durable,' Says Fractal's Justin Kan]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MQG3SaBM/playing-for-money-in-web3-games-not-durable-says-fractals-justin-kan</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MQG3SaBM/playing-for-money-in-web3-games-not-durable-says-fractals-justin-kan"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twitch and Fractal co-founder Justin Kan and Fractal co-founder Dan Borstelmann share their perspectives on Web3 gaming's changing landscape with Decrypt's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Cyber Cafe to Web3: How Everquest Dev Jeffrey Butler Got Into Game Development]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/hRlI4WXe/from-cyber-cafe-to-web3-how-everquest-dev-jeffrey-butler-got-into-game-development</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/hRlI4WXe/from-cyber-cafe-to-web3-how-everquest-dev-jeffrey-butler-got-into-game-development"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T14:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everquest developer turned Avalon Chief Product Officer Jeffrey Butler tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how he got into game development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Machines Arena Game Preview: Is This the Next Overwatch?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/tT0qWy4s/the-machines-arena-game-preview-is-this-the-next-overwatch</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/tT0qWy4s/the-machines-arena-game-preview-is-this-the-next-overwatch"/>
        <updated>2023-06-02T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt contributor Ryan S. Gladwin shares an inside look at The Machines Arena, an upcoming top-down 4v4 shooter from Directive Games that will offer NFTs minted on Ethereum sidechain network Ronin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You 'Have' to Be on Mobile: InfiniGods Cofounders on Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/l3KBurz4/you-have-to-be-on-mobile-infinigods-cofounders-on-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/l3KBurz4/you-have-to-be-on-mobile-infinigods-cofounders-on-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[InfiniGods developers Damon Gura and Owen O’Donoghue share their stance on why mobile gaming is essential to Web3 adoption and general success in the video games industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Chaos of 2022 'Didn't Damage Technology Underlying the Industry': X Ventures Co-Founder Matthias Reiser]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PDArXOkZ/crypto-chaos-of-2022-didnt-damage-technology-underlying-the-industry-x-ventures-co-founder-matthias-reiser</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PDArXOkZ/crypto-chaos-of-2022-didnt-damage-technology-underlying-the-industry-x-ventures-co-founder-matthias-reiser"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T13:13:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ahead of this month's Proof of Talk event in Paris on June 14 and June 15, X Ventures co-founder and the event's co-organizer Dr. Matthias Reiser said nothing's changed for those with a "long-term view" of the industry. Still, events like the collapse of Terra and FTX in 20222 have certainly damaged investors' trust in crypto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tron's Justin Sun Thinks Hong Kong Will Be a Big Fiat Onramp for Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/agBnfg7Z/trons-justin-sun-thinks-hong-kong-will-be-a-big-fiat-onramp-for-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/agBnfg7Z/trons-justin-sun-thinks-hong-kong-will-be-a-big-fiat-onramp-for-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T12:19:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Justin Sun, Tron founder and advisor to crypto exchange Huobi, talks to Decrypt's Liam Kelly and Stacy Elliott about the impact of Hong Kong allowing residents to trade crypto, complications of restricting access based on location, and how AI will change the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NVIDIA's AI Push Could Change Gaming Forever]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/79ArMuzj/nvidias-ai-push-could-change-gaming-forever</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/79ArMuzj/nvidias-ai-push-could-change-gaming-forever"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T14:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Computer tech firm NVIDIA profited off the crypto mining industry. Now, it's looking to artificial intelligence—and its stock price is soaring.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why InfiniGods Laughs at 'AAA' Web3 Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/WzdrzXOY/why-infinigods-laughs-at-aaa-web3-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/WzdrzXOY/why-infinigods-laughs-at-aaa-web3-games"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The InfiniGods founders share their approach to game development and offer a critique of games that call themselves "AAA."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Make it Fast, Make it Friendly: Jerome de Tychey Unpacks Key Themes at This Year's EthCC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yNyunUz4/make-it-fast-make-it-friendly-jerome-de-tychey-unpacks-key-themes-at-this-years-ethcc</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yNyunUz4/make-it-fast-make-it-friendly-jerome-de-tychey-unpacks-key-themes-at-this-years-ethcc"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T15:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After six years running, EthCC is back, this time in Paris from July 17 to July 20. Decrypt sat down with the brains behind one of Ethereum’s longest-running events Jerome de Tychey to get an inside look into what’s on the agenda this year, several unannounced guests, and the rollout of at least one “secret” DeFi project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unioverse Game Preview: Hands-on With the Cinematic Proving Grounds]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/t68sovuN/unioverse-game-preview-hands-on-with-the-cinematic-proving-grounds</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/t68sovuN/unioverse-game-preview-hands-on-with-the-cinematic-proving-grounds"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Unioverse is a multimedia sci-fi franchise with plans to facilitate user-generated content. Decrypt reporter and GG producer Kate Irwin checked out the Unioverse as Reyu, an alien character, and navigated the Proving Grounds with him. In the Proving Grounds, you'll fight an array of different drone-like flying robots (some have tentacles!!) as you navigate the puzzle-like dystopian environment. Alien meets Portal, anyone?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EverQuest Producer Jeffrey Butler on How Ready Player One Led Him to Web3 Project Avalon]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/fdmq9t7l/everquest-producer-jeffrey-butler-on-how-ready-player-one-led-him-to-web3-project-avalon</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/fdmq9t7l/everquest-producer-jeffrey-butler-on-how-ready-player-one-led-him-to-web3-project-avalon"/>
        <updated>2023-05-26T21:02:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jeffrey Butler started his game development career producing EverQuest. Now, he's Avalon's Chief Product Officer. Butler told Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how he wants to create a customizable world where users can create their own worlds and in-game content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Esports Orgs Should Become More Like Tech Companies: Community Gaming CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/t27ac1ik/esports-orgs-should-become-more-like-tech-companies-community-gaming-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/t27ac1ik/esports-orgs-should-become-more-like-tech-companies-community-gaming-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-05-26T16:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Community Gaming CEO and 3XP conference organizer Chris Gonsalves believes crypto and tech could rejuvenate and reinvent the esports industry. In an interview, he tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin why he thinks esports organizations should shake up their approach.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SNEAK PEEK: Inside Mirandus From Gala Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/RfqKM0Rm/sneak-peek-inside-mirandus-from-gala-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/RfqKM0Rm/sneak-peek-inside-mirandus-from-gala-games"/>
        <updated>2023-05-26T16:23:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GG's Kate Irwin takes us on a journey inside Mirandus, the upcoming MMORPG from Gala Games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>