<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-09-14T22:13:11.489Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-09-14T22:13:11.489Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMI Vantage Expands Crypto Reach With New Bitcoin Mining Facility in Sarawak]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7542fcbada</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/smi-vantage-expands-crypto-reach-with-new-bitcoin-mining-facility-in-sarawak/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T22:06:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Singapore-based investment management and software-as-a-service (SaaS) provider, SMI Vantage, plans to launch a bitcoin mining facility in the state of Sarawak in Borneo, Malaysia. The company has signed a rental agreement and anticipates operations to begin by the end of the third quarter.
 
SMI Vantage Charts New Territory With Sarawak Bitcoin Mining Venture
 
According to a report from The Edge Singapore, SMI Vantage, an investment and SaaS firm, has disclosed its intention to commence bitcoin mining operations in Sarawak. The firm is in the process of setting up two containers equipped with application-specific integrated circuit mining machines. Operations are projected to start by October 1, 2023, or the conclusion of the third quarter.
 
SMI’s recent agreement was advised by Sovereign Systemtechnik, a Singapore-based engineering and technology firm. The deal was inked in September 2022 and marks SMI’s third bitcoin mining venture. While SMI already has operations in Melaka, Malaysia, it also boasts a bitcoin mining facility in Bandar Seri Begawan, Brunei’s capital. Beyond SaaS and cryptocurrency mining, SMI has a keen interest in artificial intelligence (AI) and predictive analytics solutions.
 
 
While bitcoin mining is legal in Malaysia, using stolen electricity for crypto mining is highly discouraged. Reports indicate that from 2018, illegal crypto mining activities resulted in a loss of RM2.3 billion ($491,610) for Malaysia, with over 7,200 cases documented. SMI states that in Melaka, the company pays $0.07 to $0.08 per kilowatt-hour (kWh) and $0.05 to $0.06 per kWh in Bandar Seri Begawan.
 
What do you think about SMI expanding crypto mining operations to Sarawak? Share your thoughts and opinions about this subject in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Privacy remains sticking point in America’s ongoing CBDC debate]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904360/Privacy-remains-sticking-point-in-Americas-ongoing-CBDC-debate</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904360/Privacy-remains-sticking-point-in-Americas-ongoing-CBDC-debate"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T22:01:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A CBDC in the US could erode financial privacy and “upend the commercial banking system,” witnesses argued at a Thursday hearing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Inflation Come Back HOT? | Darius Dale]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904356/Will-Inflation-Come-Back-HOT-Darius-Dale</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904356/Will-Inflation-Come-Back-HOT-Darius-Dale"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T22:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Darius Dale is the Founder & CEO of 42Macro. In this conversation we talk about inflation, what is going on with headline CPI, core CPI, confusing data, sticky inflation, should the Fed move the inflation target to 3%? Pomp writes a daily letter to over 250,000+ investors about business,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Mt. Gox CEO Responds To FTX’s Sam Bankman-Fried Requesting For Freedom Before Trial]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904359/Former-Mt-Gox-CEO-Responds-To-FTXs-Sam-Bankman-Fried-Requesting-For-Freedom-Before-Trial</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904359/Former-Mt-Gox-CEO-Responds-To-FTXs-Sam-Bankman-Fried-Requesting-For-Freedom-Before-Trial"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T22:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The former CEO of the defunct Bitcoin exchange Mt. Gox, Mark Karpelès, has drawn an analogy between his case and that of FTX’s former CEO Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF) following the latter’s persistent request to be released in order to prepare his defense for his upcoming trial in October adequately....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friend.tech Records Two New Milestones Amidst Renewed Hype]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904344/Friendtech-Records-Two-New-Milestones-Amidst-Renewed-Hype</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904344/Friendtech-Records-Two-New-Milestones-Amidst-Renewed-Hype"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T22:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Friend.tech, a decentralized social network, has witnessed a sharp resurgence barely two weeks after critics pronounced the platform dead. The platform is enjoying renewed user interest, with its total value locked (TVL) surpassing $20 million a few days ago. Thanks to this growing momentum,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Will Send Bitcoin To $10,600,000?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904345/THIS-WILL-SEND-BITCOIN-TO-10600000</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904345/THIS-WILL-SEND-BITCOIN-TO-10600000"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T21:47:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dive into an in-depth analysis of British Hodl's bullish price prediction for Bitcoin. Discover why real estate might not be the gold standard for investments anymore and how Bitcoin could change the landscape of global finance. From ETF approvals to market movements, get ready for a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US lawmakers face-off over prospects for CBDC during Congressional hearing]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904339/US-lawmakers-face-off-over-prospects-for-CBDC-during-Congressional-hearing</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904339/US-lawmakers-face-off-over-prospects-for-CBDC-during-Congressional-hearing"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T21:44:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lawmakers weighed the pros and cons of issuing a central bank digital currency and faced a divide over privacy concerns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two more top executives depart Binance.US amid layoffs, SEC action: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904337/Two-more-top-executives-depart-BinanceUS-amid-layoffs-SEC-action-Report</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904337/Two-more-top-executives-depart-BinanceUS-amid-layoffs-SEC-action-Report"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T21:43:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Binance.US head of legal and the exchange’s chief risk officer have reportedly left the company while it faces an SEC suit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Co-Founder Predicts: Crypto’s Future In The US Will Be Embraced]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7542ff15dc</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-co-founder-regulators-will-embrace-crypto/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T21:43:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent interview with CNBC’s “Capital Connection,” Joseph Lubin, co-founder of Ethereum (ETH) and CEO of ConsenSys, expressed his confidence that US regulators will recognize the alignment between decentralized protocols, blockchain technology, and the underlying philosophies that founded the United States. 
 
As the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) engages in legal battles with various crypto firms, Lubin remains optimistic that “clear heads will prevail.”
 
 
Ethereum Co-Founder Calls For A Nuanced Regulatory Approach
 
Lubin drew parallels to past technological advancements, such as the internet, the web, and crypto, emphasizing the eventual acceptance and integration of these innovations into society. 
 
Lubin anticipates a similar trajectory for decentralized protocols…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Bitcoin’s market dominance signals good news for investors]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904318/How-Bitcoins-market-dominance-signals-good-news-for-investors</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904318/How-Bitcoins-market-dominance-signals-good-news-for-investors"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T21:30:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite price fluctuations, Bitcoin's market dominance has surged to 50%, overshadowing altcoins and reshaping the crypto landscape.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin-Only Exchange Swan Pledges to Launch New Custodian with BitGo]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904320/Bitcoin-Only-Exchange-Swan-Pledges-to-Launch-New-Custodian-with-BitGo</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904320/Bitcoin-Only-Exchange-Swan-Pledges-to-Launch-New-Custodian-with-BitGo"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T21:30:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Swan Bitcoin is offering new insight into how Bitcoin stored on its exchange will be held in custody in the future]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon 2.0 Implementation Begins: MATIC to be Upgraded to POL]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904310/Polygon-20-Implementation-Begins-MATIC-to-be-Upgraded-to-POL</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904310/Polygon-20-Implementation-Begins-MATIC-to-be-Upgraded-to-POL"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon Labs, the development team for the Polygon networks, has officially announced the commencement of the Polygon 2.0 implementation. In a recent tweet, the team proclaimed that Polygon 2.0 is commencing with the unveiling of three Polygon Improvement Proposals (PIPs). It also includes a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin clean energy usage reportedly exceeds 50% — Will Tesla start accepting BTC payments?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904295/Bitcoin-clean-energy-usage-reportedly-exceeds-50-Will-Tesla-start-accepting-BTC-payments</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904295/Bitcoin-clean-energy-usage-reportedly-exceeds-50-Will-Tesla-start-accepting-BTC-payments"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T21:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Bloomberg analyst reported the percentage of energy used for Bitcoin mining coming from renewable sources had exceeded 50% due in part to miners fleeing China’s ban.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Christie's Turns Keith Haring Digital Art Into NFC-Equipped Patch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156777</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156777/christies-turns-keith-haring-digital-art-nfc-equipped-patch"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T21:15:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MNTGE and the auction house transformed one of Keith Haring's works—currently on sale as an NFT—into a patch with its own proof of ownership.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephanie Hirschmiller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Christie's Turns Keith Haring Digital Art Into NFC-Equipped Patch]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904299/Christies-Turns-Keith-Haring-Digital-Art-Into-NFC-Equipped-Patch</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904299/Christies-Turns-Keith-Haring-Digital-Art-Into-NFC-Equipped-Patch"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T21:15:17.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sen. Brown pushes for ‘consistent, comprehensive’ crypto disclosures in letter]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904264/Sen-Brown-pushes-for-consistent-comprehensive-crypto-disclosures-in-letter</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904264/Sen-Brown-pushes-for-consistent-comprehensive-crypto-disclosures-in-letter"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T21:03:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sherrod Brown does not believe that there are clear enough crypto disclosures to protect Americans]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oil prices have surged 55% during Jerome Powell’s tenure as Fed Chair]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904268/Oil-prices-have-surged-55-during-Jerome-Powells-tenure-as-Fed-Chair</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904268/Oil-prices-have-surged-55-during-Jerome-Powells-tenure-as-Fed-Chair"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T21:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto market outflows reached $55B in August as liquidity dwindled — Bitfinex]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904266/Crypto-market-outflows-reached-55B-in-August-as-liquidity-dwindled-Bitfinex</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904266/Crypto-market-outflows-reached-55B-in-August-as-liquidity-dwindled-Bitfinex"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto’s liquidity crunch could allow event-based volatility to have a greater impact on prices, according to a recent analysis from Bitfinex.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Circle's USDC Expansion On NEAR Signals Resilient Multi-Blockchain Future]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904265/Circles-USDC-Expansion-On-NEAR-Signals-Resilient-Multi-Blockchain-Future</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904265/Circles-USDC-Expansion-On-NEAR-Signals-Resilient-Multi-Blockchain-Future"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T20:51:14.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Dilemma Of Distributing Tokens On XRP Ledger: Ripple CTO Chimes In]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7542e55af0</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/xrp-ledger-ripple-cto/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T20:43:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Xahau, a new smart contract sidechain, is set to launch, and as part of efforts to boost interoperability between the XRP Ledger and Xahau, the Chief Technology Officer of XRPL Labs, Richard AH, has proposed making an amendment to XRPL’s mainnet. 
 
A Reversed Burn2Mint Mechanism
 
In a tweet shared on his X (formerly Twitter) platform, Richard AH noted that XRP’s mainnet doesn’t support reversed Burn2Mint for issued currencies. According to him, if the protocol were to be amended, it would allow any form of wrapped XRP to be moved in both directions (from the XRP mainnet to the Xahau sidechain and back). 
 
 
Richard further noted that this amendment could also allow the wrapped XRP to be counter-party free if it was “made via a transactor on mainnet.” He stated this proposed move could h…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin’s Concerns Over Hong Kong’s Crypto Position Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904261/Vitalik-Buterins-Concerns-Over-Hong-Kongs-Crypto-Position-Explained</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904261/Vitalik-Buterins-Concerns-Over-Hong-Kongs-Crypto-Position-Explained"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T20:36:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum founder Vitalik Buterin expressed reservations about Hong Kong’s recent warming towards crypto. He voiced his concerns at the Web3 Transitions Summit in Singapore on Thursday. As Hong Kong boldly positions itself as a potential crypto hub by adopting a new regulatory framework,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ATOM price outlook after Cosmos Hub’s upgrade for liquid staking]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904210/ATOM-price-outlook-after-Cosmos-Hubs-upgrade-for-liquid-staking</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904210/ATOM-price-outlook-after-Cosmos-Hubs-upgrade-for-liquid-staking"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T20:35:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cosmos Hub’s Liquid Staking Module just went live, bringing new utility to ATOM. ATOM price has jumped 3% in the past 24 hours after seeing a slight increase on Wednesday. Cosmos Hub, the interchain service provider of the Cosmos Network and blockchain platform powered by the native token ATOM,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Remitano exchange allegedly hacked for $2.7M; $1.4M frozen by Tether]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904211/Remitano-exchange-allegedly-hacked-for-27M-14M-frozen-by-Tether</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904211/Remitano-exchange-allegedly-hacked-for-27M-14M-frozen-by-Tether"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T20:34:12.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance.US Sees More Key Departures: Chief Risk Officer and Legal Head Exit]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7542e6aa23</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/binanceus-sees-more-key-departures-chief-risk-officer-and-legal-head-exit/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T20:31:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The winds of change continue to sweep through Binance.US  
as the cryptocurrency exchange witnesses the departure of two more high-ranking  
executives. The Head of Legal, Krishna Juvvadi, and the Chief Risk Officer,  
Sidney Majalya, have decided to part ways with the exchange.
This latest shake-up  
comes in the wake of CEO Brian Shroder's recent exit and coincides with  
escalating regulatory scrutiny. Juvvadi, who joined the company in May of the  
previous year, and Majalya, who assumed his role in December 2021, have chosen  
to leave their positions, as reported by the Wall Street Journal, citing  
insider sources.
Regulatory Storms Cause Executive Exit
While the reasons behind  
these departures remain undisclosed, their timing is conspicuous. Brian  
Shroder, the CEO of the Americ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Australian Bank ANZ leveraging Chainlink’s CCIP for cross-chain operability]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904209/Australian-Bank-ANZ-leveraging-Chainlinks-CCIP-for-cross-chain-operability</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18904209/Australian-Bank-ANZ-leveraging-Chainlinks-CCIP-for-cross-chain-operability"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T20:30:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wednesday’s announcement signifies increasing harmony between the global financial system and the digital assets industry]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gods Unchained's Daniel Paez on the Future of NFT Gaming Interoperability]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/obt7FGYr/gods-unchaineds-daniel-paez-on-the-future-of-nft-gaming-interoperability</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/obt7FGYr/gods-unchaineds-daniel-paez-on-the-future-of-nft-gaming-interoperability"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T20:27:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daniel Paez, executive producer on NFT card-battling game Gods Unchained, speaks with Decrypt Culture Editor Andrew Hayward about what the future of NFT game interoperability will really look like—and what it won't.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Inanity of the SEC 'Stoner Cat' Action]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7542e76e0b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/09/14/the-inanity-of-the-sec-stoner-cat-action/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T20:24:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's as stupid as it sounds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Kuhn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LaLiga NFT Fantasy Soccer Games Coming to North America]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156757</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156757/laliga-nft-fantasy-soccer-games-coming-north-america"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T20:17:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spanish soccer league LaLiga has tapped gaming startup GameOn to develop fantasy games built around NFTs for the U.S. and Canada.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Cohen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paul Krugman: ‘The War on Inflation Is Pretty Much Won’ – Claims ‘Remarkable Disinflation’ Occurred]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7542e1a19e</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/paul-krugman-the-war-on-inflation-is-pretty-much-won-claims-remarkable-disinflation-occurred/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T20:05:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Wednesday, Nobel Prize-winning economist Paul Krugman provided a brief analysis of the current economic landscape in the United States. Krugman asserted that the nation has experienced “remarkable disinflation.” According to him, the available data paints a compelling picture, suggesting that the “war on inflation has been pretty much won — without a recession.” Krugman emphasized that inflation turned out “to be transitory,” contrary to initial apprehensions.
 
Krugman Declares Victory — ‘Inflation Turns Out to Have Been Transitory After All’
 
On Wednesday, the U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics (BLS) unveiled its eagerly anticipated Consumer Price Index (CPI) report, shedding light on the nation’s current inflation rate. The report revealed a notable surge in the CPI for all urban consu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple CEO Has Important Message For Crypto Community Regarding Regulation]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7542e3f084</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ripple-ceo-important-message-for-crypto-community/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T19:44:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the debate for implementing crypto regulation continues to surface, Brad Garlinghouse, CEO of Ripple, has recently shared his perspective. 
 
At a recent conference in Singapore, Garlinghouse highlighted the importance of crafting appropriate regulatory frameworks for the crypto industry.
 
The Necessity Of Proper Regulation
 
While appearing at Token 2049 in Singapore, Garlinghouse emphasized the inevitability of governmental involvement in crypto. Garlinghouse highlighted a prevailing sentiment among certain factions of the crypto community that vehemently opposes any form of regulation.
 
 
According to the Ripple CEO, this is a stance that, if perpetuated, may hinder the industry’s long-term growth. Garlinghouse stated: 
 

In my judgment, if we want this industry to thrive and fund…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Most Important U.S. Senator for Crypto’s Future Tells Regulators to Use Existing Powers]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7542ecacee</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/09/14/most-important-us-senator-for-cryptos-future-tells-regulators-to-use-existing-powers/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T19:38:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Sen. Sherrod Brown (D-Ohio), whose chairmanship of the Senate Banking Committee gives him power over crypto’s congressional destiny, issued a call to arms to regulators on Thursday, demanding that they use whatever authority they currently have over digital assets to improve market transparency and protect the investors putting their money into the sector.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bull Bitcoin Exchange Expands From Canada to Costa Rica]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156750</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156750/bull-bitcoin-exchange-expands-canada-costa-rica"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T19:29:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company announced that it will tap into Costa Rica's widely used payment infrastructure SINPE Movil for Bitcoin swaps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Princess Peach to Pikachu: 6 Biggest Reveals From Nintendo Direct]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156719</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156719/from-princess-peach-to-pikachu-6-biggest-reveals-from-nintendo-direct"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T18:58:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Nintendo Direct stream offered fans a look at loads of upcoming Switch games. Here's a look at the biggest announcements and trailers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance US Legal and Risk Heads Step Down Amid Exec Exodus]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156716</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156716/binance-us-legal-and-risk-heads-step-down-amid-exec-exodus"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T18:46:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest departures include legal head Krishna Juvvadi and Chief Risk Officer Sidney Majalya, according to a report from WSJ.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aliens in Mexico's Congress: Earth-Shattering Revelation or Another Hoax?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156710</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156710/aliens-mexico-congress-revelation-or-hoax"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T18:46:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's not the first time supposed alien mummies were rolled out into a legislative building in Latin America—and by the same "ufologist."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chainalysis Crypto Adoption Index Shares Insights: Here Are The Countries Leading The Charge]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7542eae914</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-adoption-countries/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T18:45:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New York-based blockchain data analytics firm Chainalysis shared insights on its crypto adoption index for 2023 on Tuesday, September 12, 2023, revealing the top countries leading the charge in terms of grassroots cryptocurrency adoption.
 
Leading Countries In Terms Of Grassroot Cryptocurrency Adoption
 
Following an excerpt released by the blockchain data analytics firm Chainalysis on September 12, 2023, based on a variety of parameters to determine grassroots cryptocurrency adoption, India, Nigeria, and Vietnam have secured the top three positions respectively to become the leading countries in grassroots cryptocurrency adoption in 2023.
 
 
According to the index, the lower-middle-income (LMI) countries were identified to be leading the way in grassroots crypto adoption over the past 1…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joy Division NFT Includes Previously Unheard Ian Curtis Audio]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156720</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156720/joy-division-nft-includes-previously-unheard-ian-curtis-audio"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T18:45:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joy Division drummer Stephen Morris and "Unknown Pleasures" artist Peter Saville created the upcoming audiovisual project from Pace Verso.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ali Shutler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Exchange Updates Marketing and Fees After Hong Kong Regulator Warning]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156730</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156730/crypto-exchange-updates-marketing-and-fees-after-hong-kong-regulator-warning"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T18:32:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong requires crypto firms to register with its securities regulator. According to SFC, JPEX never applied for a license.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Singapore’s Monetary Authority Issues 9-Year Ban on Three Arrows Capital Founders]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7542d5f112</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/singapores-monetary-authority-issues-9-year-ban-on-three-arrows-capital-founders/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T18:22:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS) has issued nine-year prohibition orders against Three Arrows Capital (3AC) founders Zhu Su and Kyle Davies, banning them from regulated financial activities in the country. The orders come after a MAS investigation that reportedly uncovered multiple violations of securities laws by the now-defunct crypto hedge fund and its directors.
 
MAS Slaps 9-Year Ban on Three Arrows Capital Founders Over Violations
 
The prohibition orders prevent Zhu and Davies from performing any regulated activity or taking part in managing or becoming a major shareholder of any Singapore capital market services firm. The notice disclosed that the bans took effect on September 13.
 
MAS first reprimanded 3AC in June for providing false information and exceeding assets unde…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Jumps as European Central Bank Signals End to Rate Hikes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156714</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156714/bitcoin-jumps-as-european-central-bank-signals-end-to-rate-hikes"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T18:18:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The central bank said Thursday its current interest rate level may reign in inflation if "maintained" for long enough.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Genesis’ Exit: Crypto Lender Shuts Down All Trading Operations]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7542d0e170</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/genesis-exit-crypto-lender-shuts-down-all-trading-operations/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T18:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a dramatic turn of events, Genesis, the now-bankrupt  
crypto lender, has brought its entire crypto trading venture to an abrupt halt.  
The decision to cease all trading operations, including its international spot  
and derivatives trading services, comes amid legal disputes involving FTX and  
Gemini.
Genesis Global Trading,  
a subsidiary of Genesis Global, recently announced plans to close its U.S.-focused spot crypto  
trading operations by the end of this month, a report by Coindesk indicated.  
GGT will cease its over-the-counter trading platform's operations on September  
18, 2023. 
While Genesis Global  
Trading is winding  
down its U.S. operations,  
GGC International Limited, another trading-focused entity affiliated with  
Genesis, will reportedly continue operating GGT's…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bright Horizons: Fideum Group Anchors Spot in Mastercard Lighthouse Elite Program]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7542d201d1</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bright-horizons-fideum-group-anchors-spot-in-mastercard-lighthouse-elite-program/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T17:52:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. Fideum Group, an ambitious financial aggregator renowned for its commitment to enhancing both retail and institutional client experiences, announced its notable inclusion in the prestigious Mastercard Lighthouse FINITIV 2023 Fall Program. As one of 15 selectees from the Nordic and Baltic regions, Fideum Group is poised to redefine the fintech industry alongside other innovators, startups, and early-stage scaleups.
 
A Legacy of Innovation and Dedication
 
Born from the strategic union of GenBlock and blockbank, Fideum Group, the London-based entity, has since its inception demonstrated an unwavering commitment to pushing the boundaries of fintech solutions. The merger signified not just the unification of two powerful entities but also their shared vision of a more integrate…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance.US Head of Legal and Chief Risk Officer Leaving the Crypto Exchange: WSJ]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7542d23a85</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/09/14/binanceus-head-of-legal-and-chief-risk-officer-leaving-the-crypto-exchange-wsj/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T17:50:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The departure comes just days after the crypto exchange lost its CEO Brian Shroder.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aoyon Ashraf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Metis Provides Support for Users Affected by PolyNetwork Exploit While Improving Cross-Chain Structure]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7542d2d90b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/metis-provides-support-for-users-affected-by-polynetwork-exploit-while-improving-cross-chain-structure/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T17:46:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Layer 2 scaling solution Metis has announced a plan to compensate users affected by last month’s PolyNetwork bridge hack.
 
The project will distribute 117,000 METIS tokens to impacted community members. At the same time, Metis is implementing an enhanced cross-chain architecture using LayerZero’s OFT model.
 
Recapping The PolyNetwork Exploit
 
On July 1st, a hacker exploited the PolyNetwork bridge to mint and drain liquidity pools of 8.8 million METIS tokens on Binance Smart Chain. Metis responded quickly by removing liquidity from PancakeSwap, Stargate, and other DEXes to limit the damage. This left the hacker only able to steal 117,000 METIS from users.
 
The exploit did not impact the total or circulating supply of METIS on Ethereum or Metis. However, BSC users were affected due to th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steven Hay</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amboss Launches Innovative New Tool to Boost Adoption of Bitcoin's Lightning Network]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7542d31048</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/amboss-launches-innovative-new-tool-to-boost-adoption-of-bitcoins-lightning-network"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T17:44:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amboss, a leading data analytics provider for the Bitcoin Lightning Network (LN), has unveiled a new subscription service called Hydro, designed to automate liquidity management for the LN, according to a press release sent to Bitcoin Magazine. This enables businesses to seamlessly receive payments through the Lightning Network without requiring expertise in LN operations or relinquishing custody of their funds.
Hydro attempts to simplify the Lightning Network's payment liquidity process by automating the sourcing of payment liquidity from decentralized sources directly to a business's LN node. As more businesses embrace the Lightning Network, the growing circular economy leads to increasingly cost-effective Lightning payments, with fees dropping from an initial 3.5% setup cost to as low a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nik Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[€1.3 Trillion Deutsche Bank To Offer Bitcoin and Crypto Custody For Institutions]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7542d3103b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/1-3-trillion-deutsche-bank-to-offer-bitcoin-and-crypto-custody-for-institutions"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T17:44:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to a report by Reuters, German banking giant Deutsche Bank has partnered with Swiss cryptocurrency firm Taurus to offer Bitcoin and crypto custody and other related services to its institutional clients.
"As the digital asset space is expected to encompass trillions of dollars of assets, it's bound to be seen as one of the priorities for investors and corporations alike," said Deutsche Bank's global head of securities services, Paul Maley. "Our focus is not just on cryptocurrencies, but supporting our clients in the overall digital assets ecosystem."
The announcement also comes at a time when regulatory clarity around the industry is improving. Governments and financial regulators worldwide have been working to establish clear guidelines for the use and trading of digital assets.
According to the report, Deutsche Bank is proceeding "cautiously and in line with the spirit and the letter of the regulations governing this asset class." Maley went on to further explain that "Our product design, and the nature of custody for clients, will make sure that there isn’t the risk of contaminating the bank’s other activities."
Bitcoin continues to gain momentum and recognition as a legitimate asset class, with the asset becoming a very attractive investment option for hedge funds, family offices, and other institutional investors. Deutsche Bank's decision to enter this market is seen as a strategic move to capture a share of this burgeoning market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nik Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried’s Father Attended Meetings on FTX Token Marketing and Tax Issues]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156704</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156704/sam-bankman-frieds-father-attended-meetings-on-ftx-token-marketing-and-tax-issues"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T17:37:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried’s father did more than appear in a commercial for FTX with comedian Larry David, per Bloomberg.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dueling CBDC Bills Heading for U.S. Digital Dollar Debate in Congressional Hearing]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7542dd9748</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/09/14/dueling-cbdc-bills-heading-for-us-digital-dollar-debate-in-congressional-hearing/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T17:26:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The idea of a digital dollar in the U.S. is so egregious to Republican lawmakers that it’s become a presidential campaign talking point and the subject of multiple bills to strangle it before it takes a first breath. But Rep. Stephen Lynch (D-Mass.) reintroduced a bill Thursday calling for the exact thing they’re trying to stop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miners’ Role In BTC’s Valuation Is Declining: Glassnode]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7542db5bac</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-miners-role-valuation-declining-glassnode/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T16:46:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data from Glassnode suggests the role of Bitcoin miners in the asset’s valuation has been going down over the years.
 
Bitcoin Miners’ Issuance Now Only Makes A Small Part Of Daily Realized Value
 
In a new report, the on-chain analytics firm Glassnode has studied the different components that contribute to Bitcoin’s “realized cap.” The realized cap is a capitalization model for the asset that assumes that the real value of any coin in circulation is the price at which it was last transacted on the blockchain.
 
This is different from the normal market cap, which simply takes every token’s value to be the same: the current spot price. Since the last transaction price of a coin is essentially its “buying price,” the realized cap serves as a measure of the aggregate value stored ins…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hououin Kyouma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The PrimeXBT mobile app puts powerful trading tools in the palm of your hand]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7542db5b9f</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/the-primexbt-mobile-app-puts-powerful-trading-tools-in-the-palm-of-your-hand/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T16:46:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The world of trading is faster and more competitive than ever before. With the right tools and technology, traders can react to breaking news and emerging opportunities in an instant. 
 
This is where the PrimeXBT mobile application shines. The PrimeXBT mobile app gives users access to an entire suite of advanced trading tools, competitive advantages, and more – all from the convenience of their smartphone.
 
Open and manage trades on the go
 
One of the key benefits of the PrimeXBT mobile app is the ability to react quickly to rapidly changing market conditions. As an active trader, you understand the importance of timing when entering or exiting positions. With the PrimeXBT mobile app, you can open and close trades instantly, without having to be in front of a computer. If you see a trad…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Genesis Has Ceased All Crypto Trading Services: Spokesperson]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7542c6b84e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/09/14/genesis-has-ceased-all-crypto-trading-services-spokesperson/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T16:25:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Company was hit hard by the collapses of Three Arrows Capital and FTX.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Baker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amboss Wants to Solve the Bitcoin Lightning Network Liquidity Problem]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156635</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156635/amboss-wants-to-solve-businesses-bitcoin-lightning-network-liquidity-problem"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T16:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Without liquidity, payments simply aren't possible,” Amboss CEO Jesse Shrader told Decrypt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alyssa Hertig</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deutsche Bank To Offer Crypto Custody With Swiss Fintech Taurus]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156670</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156670/deutsche-bank-to-offer-crypto-custody-with-swiss-fintech-taurus"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T12:03:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bank will establish digital asset custody and tokenization services, in a sign that "institutional interest is building," said Taurus.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3AC’s Su Zhu, Kyle Davies Slapped With 9-Year Finance Ban by Singapore Monetary Authority]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156666</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156666/3acs-zhu-su-kyle-davies-slapped-with-9-year-finance-ban-by-singapore-monetary-authority"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T11:34:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company hired a hedge fund manager without notifying authorities and then traded crypto with no risk framework in place.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase CEO: DeFi Projects Should Take Regulators to Court to ‘Establish Precedent’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156665</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156665/coinbase-ceo-defi-projects-should-take-regulators-to-court-to-establish-precedent"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T11:16:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brian Armstrong argued that the CFTC shouldn't be taking action against DeFi protocols, and that the courts would likely "uphold rule of law."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Like Star Wars Collectibles': SEC Commissioners Dissent on Stoner Cats Enforcement]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156659</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156659/like-star-wars-collectibles-sec-commissioners-dissent-on-stoner-cats-enforcement"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T10:27:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two SEC commissioners dissented on the regulator’s action against the Stoner Cats NFT series, likening them to 1970s Star Wars collectibles.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ralph Lauren, Burberry Alum Launches Digital Fashion Platform SYKY]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156644</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156644/ralph-lauren-burberry-alum-launches-digital-fashion-platform-syky"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T10:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The platform, which will offer both digital and physical fashion items, seeks to coax the traditional fashion industry onto the blockchain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diesel Debuts Digital Apparel for Meta Avatars With DressX]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156593</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156593/diesel-launches-digital-apparel-meta-avatars-dressx"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T08:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fashion brand Diesel joins the likes of Valentino and Balenciaga in dropping digital clothes on the Meta Avatars Store.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephanie Hirschmiller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Proposed California Legislation Would Protect Actors From AI Copycats]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156625</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156625/proposed-california-legislation-protect-actors-ai-copycats"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T01:42:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Assemblymember Ash Kalra's bill targets vague contracts that exploit an actor's digital likeness without clear consent or representation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No Bubble Here: Goldman Sachs Says AI Still in Early Stages]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156626</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156626/no-bubble-here-goldman-sachs-says-ai-still-in-early-stages"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T00:49:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Goldman Sachs foresees a promising future for AI investments, debunking bubble theories and projecting a bullish market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Game Developers Are 'Fucking Livid' Over Unity's New Fees]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156592</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156592/game-developers-fucking-livid-over-unity-new-fees"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T23:08:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The popular game engine's new fees have left some developers feeling stuck, although Unity is trying to explain its way out of the unrest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Up-and-Coming Generative Artists to Keep Your Eye On]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155352</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155352/community-spotlight-generative-artists-keep-your-eye-on"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T22:16:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The generative art world is thriving, and exciting new artists keep emerging all the time. Here are a few that you should know.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abigail Carlson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can't Beat the Real Thing? AI Is Making Coca-Cola Flavors Now]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156609</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156609/you-cant-beat-real-thing-ai-making-coca-cola-flavors-now"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T21:52:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t call it New Coke. Global beverage giant Coca-Cola offers a glimpse of the future with a new flavor co-created with AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It Wasn't PayPal—Paxos Fat Fingered $510,000 Bitcoin Transaction]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156571</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156571/it-wasnt-paypal-paxos-fat-fingered-510000-bitcoin-transaction"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T20:29:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paxos is now working with the lucky miner who received the fee to get its money back.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pedophile Rings Are Using AI to Create Child Pornography, UK Group Warns]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156558</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156558/pedophile-rings-are-using-ai-to-create-child-pornography-warns-iwf-uk-group"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T19:48:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The IWF says AI-generated child sexual abuse material is being spread on the dark web, complicating law enforcement efforts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Happens to Mila Kunis' Stoner Cats NFTs After SEC Settlement?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156555</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156555/what-happens-mila-kunis-stoner-cats-nfts-after-sec-settlement"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T19:44:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Questions remain as to the fate of the star-studded NFT animated series which was slapped with an SEC action Wednesday. Here's what we know.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Gets Court Approval to Sell Billions in Bitcoin, Ethereum and Solana]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156498</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156498/ftx-gets-approval-to-sell-bitcoin-ethereum-solana"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T18:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The collapsed exchange's new management now can sell billions of dollars in Solana, Bitcoin and other assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stoner Cats NFT Sales Surge After SEC Reveals Charges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156428</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156428/stoner-cats-nft-sales-surge-after-sec-reveals-charges"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T17:52:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enforcement action against the Mila Kunis-led cartoon series Stoner Cats has apparently led to a jump in NFT sales and prices alike.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mila Kunis' Stoner Cats NFT Project Sued by SEC, Settles for $1 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156245</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156245/mila-kunis-stoner-cats-nft-project-sued-by-sec-settles-for-1-million"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T14:54:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The creators of NFT-based cartoon series Stoner Cats will pay a civil fine and establish a fund to reimburse investors, as well.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward,Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Metamask]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156246</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156246/how-to-use-metamask"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T14:47:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MetaMask is a leading crypto wallet, and relies on browser integration and good design to serve as one of the main gateways to the world of Web3, decentralized finance (DeFi) and NFTs. Here's how it works, and how to get started with it. What Is MetaMask? MetaMask is a browser extension and mobile app that […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Euny Hong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Hold Ground Despite Rising Inflation in August]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156184</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156184/bitcoin-ethereum-hold-ground-despite-rising-inflation-in-august"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T12:52:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Inflation has fallen steadily since 9.1% last June, but it’s still above the Fed’s target of 2%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Judge Dismisses Sam Bankman-Fried's Pretrial Jail Release Request]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156183</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156183/judge-dismisses-sam-bankman-frieds-pretrial-jail-release-request"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T11:01:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Judge Lewis A. Kaplan explained that the FTX founder doesn’t have “a constitutional right to inspect every bit of discovery.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Exchange CoinEx Shuts Down Withdrawals Following Suspected Hack of $27M]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156173</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156173/crypto-exchange-coinex-shuts-down-withdrawals-following-suspected-hack-of-27m"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T10:30:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The exchange identified a number of suspicious wallets draining funds from the platform in "anomalous withdrawals."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alys Key</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TON Surges 13% after Telegram Integrates Blockchain’s Web3 Wallet]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156166</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156166/ton-surges-13-after-telegram-integrates-blockchains-web3-wallet"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T10:04:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The TON wallet is now accessible to the Telegram messaging app’s 800 million strong user base, prompting an overnight surge in the token’s price.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram Gets a Crypto Wallet—3 Years After SEC Pumped the Brakes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156109</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156109/telegram-gets-crypto-wallet-3-years-after-sec-pumped-brakes"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T06:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in 2020, Telegram announced an end to its participation in TON after the SEC filed suit. But now they're back together again.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Panerai to Include NFT 'Digital Passport' With All Luxury Watches]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156152</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156152/panerai-include-nft-digital-passport-all-luxury-watches"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T05:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Italian luxury brand Panerai will issue an NFT digital passport with its watches, providing a certificate of authenticity and other benefits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephanie Hirschmiller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance US CEO Brian Shroder Steps Down Amid Layoffs: Bloomberg]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156150</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156150/binance-us-ceo-brian-shroder-steps-down-amid-layoffs-bloomberg"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T02:52:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Norman Reed, Chief Legal Officer of Binance US, will take the helm after the abrupt executive departure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[White House Signs 8 More Companies to Safe AI Pledge]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156145</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156145/white-house-signs-8-more-companies-to-its-safe-ai-pledge"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T01:35:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NVIDIA, IBM, and Adobe are among the eight companies promising to focus on safety, security, and trust in advancing artificial intelligence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Mino Games is Using Artificial Intelligence]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/SrT1Afj7/how-mino-games-is-using-artificial-intelligence</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/SrT1Afj7/how-mino-games-is-using-artificial-intelligence"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T22:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mino Games CEO Sasha McKinnon tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about how the studio's upcoming game Dimensionals will use real-time AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INTERVIEW: How Will Aurory Use NFTs and Crypto?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qv3VwNmM/interview-how-will-aurory-use-nfts-and-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qv3VwNmM/interview-how-will-aurory-use-nfts-and-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T15:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Natoli, Aurory's Head of Marketing and Business Development, tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how the Aurory games will use NFTs and crypto and shares the studio's broader stance on the tech.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Cloud's James Tromans on the Intersection of AI and Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OeD4uoLj/google-clouds-james-tromans-on-the-intersection-of-ai-and-web3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OeD4uoLj/google-clouds-james-tromans-on-the-intersection-of-ai-and-web3"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google's Global Head of Google Cloud for Web3 James Tromans sat down with Decrypt's Jason Nelson to discuss how AI can help Web3 companies come to market faster and the real value of Web3 tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastering NFT Trading - Degen U]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/HQGt1Vrq/mastering-nft-trading-degen-u</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/HQGt1Vrq/mastering-nft-trading-degen-u"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T07:08:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Take Degen U's new course, Mastering NFT Trading, and earn an on-chain certificate. A top instructor will help you identify trends, seize the right moment to trade, weed out scams—and have fun while doing it!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Space Nation CEO on Working With 'Independence Day' Director Roland Emmerich]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LpznLhtx/space-nation-ceo-on-working-with-independence-day-director-roland-emmerich</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LpznLhtx/space-nation-ceo-on-working-with-independence-day-director-roland-emmerich"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T17:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jerome Wu, CEO of Space Nation, tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the upcoming Space Nation Online game in development and shares details on Space Nation Cofounder Roland Emmerich's role in the project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GAME REVIEW: Champions Arena from Gala Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qUE1RlDx/game-review-champions-arena-from-gala-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qUE1RlDx/game-review-champions-arena-from-gala-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Champions Arena is a turn-based fantasy RPG from Gala Games, where characters can become NFTs and crypto can be used to purchase gems, one of the game's synthetic currencies. Decrypt's Kate Irwin takes us inside the game for her thoughts on the fun, mobile-first title.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apex Legends Voice Actor Ben Prendergast on the Future of Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/X3RKdsaG/apex-legends-voice-actor-ben-prendergast-on-the-future-of-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/X3RKdsaG/apex-legends-voice-actor-ben-prendergast-on-the-future-of-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T18:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Voice actor Ben Prendergast, who's voiced characters in games like Apex Legends and God of War Ragnarok, shares his opinions on the tech space's history of "bubbles" and whether blockchain gaming has a future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Future of AI Stardom and Robotics With SingularityNET COO Janet Adams and Desdemona]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yVQaZI71/the-future-of-ai-stardom-and-robotics-with-singularitynet-coo-janet-adams-and-desdemona</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yVQaZI71/the-future-of-ai-stardom-and-robotics-with-singularitynet-coo-janet-adams-and-desdemona"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T16:45:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this interview, SingularityNET COO Janet Adams explains the intricate details that went into creating the Desdemona robot AI from Hanson Robotics and future plans for the AI Diva.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto a 'No-Brainer' for Video Games, Says Mino Games CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rdynom8C/crypto-a-no-brainer-for-video-games-says-mino-games-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rdynom8C/crypto-a-no-brainer-for-video-games-says-mino-games-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T18:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mino Games CEO Sasha MacKinnon, developer of the upcoming Dimensionals game, tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the studio's approach to digital collectibles.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Wagner's 'Controversial Take' on Crypto in Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tc2nKeqA/michael-wagners-controversial-take-on-crypto-in-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tc2nKeqA/michael-wagners-controversial-take-on-crypto-in-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T16:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Solana's PlayGG, Star Atlas CEO Michael Wagner shares his "controversial take" on crypto in games, shares the challenges of developing the upcoming scifi game, and how crypto's volatility has changed his perspective with Decrypt's Jason Nelson.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interview: Angelic CEO on Building the Sci-Fi RPG on Solana and Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/uCzW3K7P/interview-angelic-ceo-on-building-the-sci-fi-rpg-on-solana-and-ethereum</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/uCzW3K7P/interview-angelic-ceo-on-building-the-sci-fi-rpg-on-solana-and-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T15:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Angelic is a sci-fi roleplay game in development that will be free-to-play and offer optional, opt-in crypto features on Solana and Ethereum and a governance token. Metaverse Game Studios CEO and Founder Erkan Bayol tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how he sees AAA traditional games as Angelic's main competitors and shares his vision for the game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apex Legends Voice Actor on AI's Impact on Video Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IOIrmb0N/apex-legends-voice-actor-on-ais-impact-on-video-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IOIrmb0N/apex-legends-voice-actor-on-ais-impact-on-video-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T17:28:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ben Prendergast is an actor who has voiced characters like Apex Legends' Fuse, God of War Ragnarok's Tyr, and Patroclus in Hades. But as debates swirl around the use of artificial intelligence in entertainment in light of the SAG-AFTRA and WGA strikes, Prendergast gives Decrypt's Kate Irwin his honest take on the potential use of AI actors in games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>