<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-10-20T02:56:30.872Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-10-20T02:56:30.873Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP’s Legal Status Unshaken Amid SEC Appeal – Ripple Prepares Counterstrike]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74457185ec</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/xrps-legal-status-unshaken-amid-sec-appeal-ripple-prepares-counterstrike/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-20T02:39:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple’s legal chief has reaffirmed that the core ruling declaring XRP not a security remains intact despite the appeal by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). The regulator’s move challenges several other aspects of the July 2023 ruling regarding XRP. Ripple plans to file a cross-appeal, as both parties brace for a prolonged legal […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Schiff Predicts ‘Mother of All Gold Bull Markets’ — Early Signs of Massive Gold Surge]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74457d56e0</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/peter-schiff-predicts-mother-of-all-gold-bull-markets-early-signs-of-massive-gold-surge/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-20T01:40:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Economist and gold advocate Peter Schiff predicts the “mother of all gold bull markets” as gold prices surge to a record $2,720 per ounce. He attributes the rally to inflation fueled by central banks, warning that fiat currencies are losing value. Schiff suggests this is only the start and encourages investors to act before prices […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biggest Altcoin Gainers of the Third Week of October 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20051758/Biggest-Altcoin-Gainers-of-the-Third-Week-of-October-2024</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20051758/Biggest-Altcoin-Gainers-of-the-Third-Week-of-October-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-10-20T01:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several cryptocurrencies saw impressive gains this week, with some emerging as the biggest altcoin gainers. This performance outpaced the inconsistent movements seen during the second week. The biggest movers include Dogecoin (DOGE), Worldcoin (WLD), and Ethena (ENA). In this analysis,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Back On Top In Meme Coin Race – What’s Driving This Double-Digit Price Rally?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74457f988e</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-back-on-top-in-meme-coin-race-whats-driving-this-double-digit-price-rally/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-20T01:03:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin, the king of meme coins, is once again capturing the spotlight as it reclaims its throne among meme coins. According to price data from Coinmarketcap, Dogecoin is currently outperforming other meme coins in gains in both the 24-hour and seven day timeframes. 
 
 
Even more impressively, Dogecoin isn’t just outpacing its meme coin competitors. It’s also outperforming every other major cryptocurrency in the top 20 rankings by market capitalization.
 
As it stands, Dogecoin looks prime for a rally to $0.2, but what could be driving this rally?
 
What’s Behind The DOGE Double-Digit Price Rally?
 
At the time of writing, the Dogecoin price is posting double-digit gains across all major timeframes, with a notable 30% increase over the past seven days. A broader look at the cryptocurrenc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘We’re Heading to 6-Figure Bitcoin’ — What’s Driving This Bold Prediction]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74457929fc</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/were-heading-to-6-figure-bitcoin-whats-driving-this-bold-prediction/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-20T00:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin could reach six figures sooner than expected, driven by surging institutional flows into exchange-traded funds (ETFs), economic instability, and the U.S. presidential election, according to the chief investment officer of asset management firm Bitwise. The executive highlights factors like growing GOP support for cryptocurrencies and inflation concerns pushing investors toward BTC. With regulatory clarity […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana leaves Arbitrum, other L2 assets behind on THIS front]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20051536/Solana-leaves-Arbitrum-other-L2-assets-behind-on-THIS-front</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20051536/Solana-leaves-Arbitrum-other-L2-assets-behind-on-THIS-front"/>
        <updated>2024-10-20T00:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana's price surged, with strong social dominance driving its momentum this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Could Skyrocket by Over 600%, According to Top Crypto Trader – Here’s How]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20051522/Dogecoin-Could-Skyrocket-by-Over-600-According-to-Top-Crypto-Trader-Heres-How</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20051522/Dogecoin-Could-Skyrocket-by-Over-600-According-to-Top-Crypto-Trader-Heres-How"/>
        <updated>2024-10-20T00:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A top cryptocurrency analyst and trader believes Dogecoin (DOGE) could print a new all-time high this cycle. Pseudonymous analyst DonAlt tells his 591,700 followers on the social media platform X that the memecoin may surge more than 624% from its current value. “This is the chart for my thesis....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WIF Rally Faces Danger After 50% 30-Day Gain]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20051585/WIF-Rally-Faces-Danger-After-50-30-Day-Gain</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20051585/WIF-Rally-Faces-Danger-After-50-30-Day-Gain"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T23:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dogwifhat (WIF), the largest meme coin by market capitalization on Solana, registered notable recovery over the last 30 days. This rebound ensured that WIF’s price climbed by 50% and almost retested $3. Despite the impressive rally, technical analysis points to the possibility of a correction,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robert Kiyosaki Reveals His Secret to Surviving Inflation — Urges You to Do What He Did]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7445650685</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/robert-kiyosaki-reveals-his-secret-to-surviving-inflation-urges-you-to-do-what-he-did/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T23:36:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rich Dad Poor Dad author Robert Kiyosaki has shared his secret to surviving inflation, advising: “If you are wondering how you will survive and thrive in today’s high inflation environment … you may want to do what I did.” He warned of the dangers of relying on U.S. dollars and urged people to seek new […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin $233K forecast, SEC X account hacker arrested, and more: Hodler’s Digest, Oct. 13 – 19]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20051506/Bitcoin-233K-forecast-SEC-X-account-hacker-arrested-and-more-Hodlers-Digest-Oct-13-19</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20051506/Bitcoin-233K-forecast-SEC-X-account-hacker-arrested-and-more-Hodlers-Digest-Oct-13-19"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T23:18:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin is technically on track to hit $233,000, according to analytics data based on the RSI, FBI arrests SEC X hacker: Hodlers Digest]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joining this SHIB Killer Today is like Buying Shiba Inu in 2021 Before its 8,000% Rally, Says Analyst]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7445673acf</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/joining-this-shib-killer-today-is-like-buying-shiba-inu-in-2021-before-its-8000-rally-says-analyst/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T23:05:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Memecoins have a fascinating history in the crypto market, with assets like Shiba Inu (SHIB) turning small investments into millions, especially in 2021. Back then, few could predict SHIB’s extraordinary 8,000% rally, turning a meme coin into one of history’s most profitable altcoin investments.
 
Fast forward to today, a new contender is emerging that analysts believe could replicate that unprecedented growth. 
 
Dubbed the ‘SHIB killer,’ RCO Finance has turned the heads of many investors who believe in its utility propositions in the DeFi space. Could joining RCOF today offer the same explosive returns as Shiba Inu did just a few years ago?
 
Why is RCO Finance Considered as a ‘SHIB Killer’ 
Analysts are not using the term “SHIB Killer” lightly. SHIB achieved a high valuation through the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Reaches $0.1491 As RSI Flashes Overbought: Is A Correction Coming?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7445673aca</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-reaches-0-1491-as-rsi-flashes-overbought/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T23:05:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin‘s recent price surge to $0.1491 has pushed the Relative Strength Index (RSI) into overbought territory, signaling a potential shift in momentum. As the RSI climbs above 70%, it suggests that the token may be overvalued, raising the possibility of a price correction. As buying pressure slows, market participants are beginning to brace for a corrective move, making this a pivotal moment for DOGE’s price trajectory.
 
This article aims to analyze Dogecoin’s recent rise to $0.1491, with the RSI signaling overbought conditions. It will assess whether the rally has peaked and if a potential decline is imminent, providing insights into key technical indicators, market reactions, and the likelihood of a near-term price correction for DOGE.
 
RSI Hits Overbought Territory: What It Means Fo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Godspower Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Overvalued’ Toncoin holders are accumulating, but TON’s price will…]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20051432/Overvalued-Toncoin-holders-are-accumulating-but-TONs-price-will</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20051432/Overvalued-Toncoin-holders-are-accumulating-but-TONs-price-will"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T23:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain metrics gave a bearish outlook for Toncoin, and technical analysis agreed with this view.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$33.14 Billion At Risk If The Bitcoin Price Hits $72,462, Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20051418/3314-Billion-At-Risk-If-The-Bitcoin-Price-Hits-72462-Heres-Why</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20051418/3314-Billion-At-Risk-If-The-Bitcoin-Price-Hits-72462-Heres-Why"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T23:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto analyst Ash Crypto has alerted the crypto community that $33.14 billion is at risk if the Bitcoin price reaches $72,462. This relates to the short positions that could be liquidated if the flagship crypto hits that price target, a development that will be bullish for BTC.  Almost $33.14...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trial Postponed for Jailed Ex-US Federal Agent After Court No-Show]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74456137a4</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/trial-postponed-for-jailed-ex-us-federal-agent-after-court-no-show/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T22:37:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Nigerian court has adjourned the trial of Tigran Gambaryan, a jailed Binance executive, due to his illness. Gambaryan, a U.S. citizen and former federal agent, missed a scheduled court appearance. Nigerian High Court Judge Emeka Nwite postponed the trial to allow the Binance employee to receive medical treatment. Gambaryan’s Health Problems A Nigerian court […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[49.6% of global crypto millionaires owe their fortunes to Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20051400/496-of-global-crypto-millionaires-owe-their-fortunes-to-Bitcoin</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20051400/496-of-global-crypto-millionaires-owe-their-fortunes-to-Bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T22:32:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin millionaires have increased by over 111% from 2023 to 85400, accounting for 49.6 of % crypto millionaires in 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin’s 12% hike means traders should watch THESE levels now]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20051396/Worldcoins-12-hike-means-traders-should-watch-THESE-levels-now</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20051396/Worldcoins-12-hike-means-traders-should-watch-THESE-levels-now"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T22:30:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin is currently testing key resistance levels, but is that the direction WLD will take?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BRICS to Leverage Cryptocurrencies for Secure Investment Payments]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20051498/BRICS-to-Leverage-Cryptocurrencies-for-Secure-Investment-Payments</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20051498/BRICS-to-Leverage-Cryptocurrencies-for-Secure-Investment-Payments"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T22:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The BRICS bloc is taking major steps towards integrating digital assets to promote investments and economic development within its member states and across other emerging economies. This initiative builds on previous discussions about developing a blockchain-powered payment system for the group....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Flockerz Presale Review: Is the $FLOCK Coin Legit or a Scam?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20051394/Flockerz-Presale-Review-Is-the-FLOCK-Coin-Legit-or-a-Scam</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20051394/Flockerz-Presale-Review-Is-the-FLOCK-Coin-Legit-or-a-Scam"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T22:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We came to learn about the existence of Flockerz from its appearance on a "best crypto presales to invest in" list on one of the crypto news websites. On this type of list, we often find questionable projects, although occasionally there are some with genuine potential. The Flockerz crypto project d]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple CEO Praises the State of Cryptocurrency Regulation in Brazil]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e744563672a</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ripple-ceo-praises-the-state-of-cryptocurrency-regulation-in-brazil/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T22:07:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brad Garlinghouse, CEO of Ripple, a payments and cryptocurrency service provider, has praised the state of cryptocurrency regulation in Brazil, one of the largest crypto markets in Latam. In an interview with Valor Economico, Garlinghouse highlighted the central bank’s work to make Brazil an enticing destiny for crypto companies. “Brazil is one of the fastest-growing […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angel Drainer absorbs Inferno’s toolkit, becoming a larger threat to crypto wallets]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20051379/Angel-Drainer-absorbs-Infernos-toolkit-becoming-a-larger-threat-to-crypto-wallets</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20051379/Angel-Drainer-absorbs-Infernos-toolkit-becoming-a-larger-threat-to-crypto-wallets"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T22:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The team behind the infamous crypto wallet draining project Inferno has transferred control of its kit to rival draining as a service (DaaS) provider, Angel Drainer team. In an announcement shared on X by ScamSniffer, Inferno Drainer said it was time to quit. According to the Inferno developers,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Powell’s Legacy, the Ethics of ‘Doxing’, and Uptober or Rektober]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74456e1a7e</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/powells-legacy-the-ethics-of-doxing-and-uptober-or-rektober/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T21:29:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This editorial is from last week’s edition of the newsletter Week in Review. Subscribe to the newsletter to get this weekly editorial the second it’s finished. The newsletter also includes the biggest stories of the week with a comment on each story. Inflation, Memecoin drama, the SEC, and More The Fed’s easing cycle suggests Powell […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Sencil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk-backed pro-Trump PAC fumbles outreach, faces allegations]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20051284/Elon-Musk-backed-pro-Trump-PAC-fumbles-outreach-faces-allegations</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20051284/Elon-Musk-backed-pro-Trump-PAC-fumbles-outreach-faces-allegations"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T21:10:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The America PAC, heavily funded by Elon Musk to back Donald Trump’s re-election campaign, is struggling to meet voter outreach goals. The PAC is tasked with securing critical votes in swing states, and now faces allegations that canvassers have been lying about voter contacts, according to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Is Back To Shilling Dogecoin, Is A 36,000% Rally Possible Again?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74456fd020</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/elon-musk-shilling-dogecoin-36000/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T21:05:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The world’s richest man, Elon Musk, is back to support the foremost meme coin, Dogecoin (DOGE), although indirectly. This has raised the possibility of Dogecoin rallying 36,000%, just like it did in the 2021 bull run. 
 
Elon Musk Is Back To Shilling Dogecoin
 
Elon Musk is back to shilling Dogecoin, although this time in a political way. Musk proposed that the ‘Department of Government Efficiency’ be the name of the department that Donald Trump wants him to head if elected. This name led to the acronym ‘D.O.G.E’, which has brought about a correlation with Dogecoin’s ticker, DOGE. 
 
 
Considering Musk’s fondness for Dogecoin, this move has been considered deliberate and continues to provide a bullish outlook for the foremost meme coin as the US elections draw closer. It is worth mentionin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[- Bitcoin ETFs have had more than $20 BILLION of inflows since launching in January.

- Gold ETFs took 5 years to reach the same level of inflows when they launched.]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20051287/-Bitcoin-ETFs-have-had-more-than-20-BILLION-of-inflows-since-launching-in-January-Gold-ETFs-took-5-years-to-reach-the-same-level-of-inflows-when-they-launched</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20051287/-Bitcoin-ETFs-have-had-more-than-20-BILLION-of-inflows-since-launching-in-January-Gold-ETFs-took-5-years-to-reach-the-same-level-of-inflows-when-they-launched"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T21:01:20.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BONK Jumps 20% As ‘Dog Season’ Starts, Analyst Says]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20051234/BONK-Jumps-20-As-Dog-Season-Starts-Analyst-Says</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20051234/BONK-Jumps-20-As-Dog-Season-Starts-Analyst-Says"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T21:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As communities of the crypto space increase so does the amount of ludicrosity that comes with it, as meme coins are now starting to shine and seemingly trying to change the digital currency landscape. On the spotlight today is the meme coin BONK. If the meme coin breaks $0.000041 in October, it...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$77 Million Accumulation Could Shield XRP Price from Falling Below $0.50]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20051286/77-Million-Accumulation-Could-Shield-XRP-Price-from-Falling-Below-050</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20051286/77-Million-Accumulation-Could-Shield-XRP-Price-from-Falling-Below-050"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier this month, Ripple’s (XRP) price dropped by 18% within three days. Since October 3, however, the token has stabilized, trading between $0.52 and $0.55. While big market players are accumulating XRP, which could boost its value, it’s uncertain if this is enough to prevent the token from...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pump.Fun planning to launch a token in the future: X Spaces]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20051222/PumpFun-planning-to-launch-a-token-in-the-future-X-Spaces</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20051222/PumpFun-planning-to-launch-a-token-in-the-future-X-Spaces"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T20:41:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The pump.fun team said their goal is to create something "bigger than Binance" on a recent X space during which they teased a token launch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Rally Due To Trump’s Increased Election Odds, Blockchain Firm Claims]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e744569ec58</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-price-rally-due-to-trump-election-odds/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T20:36:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This year has been filled with numerous narratives for the cryptocurrency market, especially for the Bitcoin price. Ranging from the spot Bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs), the fourth halving event, to the United States presidential elections, the cryptocurrency industry and the Bitcoin market have been subject to various factors throughout 2024.
 
With the US elections barely a month away, there has been a lot of commentary on the outcome of the polls and how it could impact the market dynamics of the world’s largest cryptocurrency. Blockchain analytics firm IntoTheBlock is amongst the latest to join this discussion by making a connection between the Bitcoin price performance and the odds of former President Donald Trump.
 
How Trump’s Win Could Be A Victory For Crypto
 
In its latest …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Opeyemi Sule</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Bitcoin’s Fee Spike Is Raising Eyebrows as Prices Hold Steady Above $68K]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74456a83b7</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/why-bitcoins-fee-spike-is-raising-eyebrows-as-prices-hold-steady-above-68k/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T20:29:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While bitcoin’s price has remained above $68,000, onchain fees tagged along for the ride. Earlier this month, fees were below $1, but two days ago on Oct. 17, the average transfer fee hit a peak of $6.32. Today, onchain fees stand at around 22.9 satoshis per virtual byte (sat/vB), or roughly $3.61 per transaction. Bitcoin’s […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$400,000 Extracted From ATMs Across New York As Criminals Hit Banks in Sophisticated Scheme: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20051202/400000-Extracted-From-ATMs-Across-New-York-As-Criminals-Hit-Banks-in-Sophisticated-Scheme-Report</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20051202/400000-Extracted-From-ATMs-Across-New-York-As-Criminals-Hit-Banks-in-Sophisticated-Scheme-Report"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T20:21:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US Department of Justice says it’s apprehended six men accused of stealing over $400,000 from ATMs in New York. The men allegedly used a device to infect the New York ATMs with malware, forcing them to dispense all the cash they contain in a relatively short period of time in a scheme known as […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The #Bitcoin Breakout from the channel is confirmed and looks strong after these few daily closes above.

Weekly close coming up as well which is likely to end up here too.

We'll have a volatile few weeks ahead of us with the election. But besides that, the chart looks good.]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20051198/The-Bitcoin-Breakout-from-the-channel-is-confirmed-and-looks-strong-after-these-few-daily-closes-above-Weekly-close-coming-up-as-well-which-is-likely-to-end-up-here-too-Well-have-a-volatile-few-weeks-ahead-of-us-with-the-election-But-besides-that-the-chart</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20051198/The-Bitcoin-Breakout-from-the-channel-is-confirmed-and-looks-strong-after-these-few-daily-closes-above-Weekly-close-coming-up-as-well-which-is-likely-to-end-up-here-too-Well-have-a-volatile-few-weeks-ahead-of-us-with-the-election-But-besides-that-the-chart"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T20:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Judge Slaps Crypto Fraudster With Five-Year Prison Sentence Over $20,000,000 in Coinbase Spoofing Scheme]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20051161/US-Judge-Slaps-Crypto-Fraudster-With-Five-Year-Prison-Sentence-Over-20000000-in-Coinbase-Spoofing-Scheme</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20051161/US-Judge-Slaps-Crypto-Fraudster-With-Five-Year-Prison-Sentence-Over-20000000-in-Coinbase-Spoofing-Scheme"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T20:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A US judge sentenced a crypto fraudster to five years in prison over charges stemming from a $20 million scheme involving a fake Coinbase website. Chirag Tomar, an Indian national, facilitated a “spoofing” con that involved setting up a deceptive URL, CoinbasePro.Com, and creating a fraudulent...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring 7 Different Investment Strategies for Bitcoin: A Guide for Investors]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e744556a000</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/exploring-7-different-investment-strategies-for-bitcoin-a-guide-for-investors/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T19:38:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Investing in bitcoin (BTC) does not require buying a whole coin. Investors can buy fractions of a bitcoin, making it accessible to a wide range of budgets. This accessibility allows investors to explore a variety of strategies suited to their risk tolerance and goals. The following editorial explores seven distinct types of investment methods and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Liquidations Hint At Potential Volatility – Is BTC Bull Run At Risk?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7445511dc7</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-liquidations-hint-at-potential-volatility-is-btc-bull-run-at-risk/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T19:08:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin has reached local highs below $69,000 after weeks of steady bullish price action, igniting excitement and caution across the market. Investors are bracing for potential volatility, as this critical price zone has triggered sharp rejections five times in the past few months. 
 
While optimism is high for a surge beyond $70,000, uncertainty remains as traders watch for signs of a breakout or another pullback.
 
 
Key data from CryptoQuant reveals that liquidation levels on major exchanges are rising, signaling that a decisive move could be imminent. This increase in liquidations suggests that traders are positioning themselves for big swings in the coming week, either anticipating a continuation of Bitcoin’s uptrend or bracing for a rejection from this significant resistance level.
 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Villafuerte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Approves Spot Bitcoin ETF Options Trading On NYSE, Cboe – Details]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7445511dc6</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/sec-approves-spot-bitcoin-etf-options-nyse-cboe/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T19:08:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has granted a go-ahead to the New York Stock Exchange (NYSE) and Chicago Board Options Exchange (Cboe) to list options trading for several spot Bitcoin ETFs. This development comes amidst the massive inflows recorded by these Bitcoin ETFs in the past week. 
 
 
NYSE And Cboe Secure Accelerated Approval For Spot Bitcoin ETF Options Trading
 
According to filings by the SEC, NYSE and Cboe have obtained permission to list and trade options on multiple spot Bitcoin ETFs. 
 
Based on NYSE’s proposed rule change, the US securities regulator has allowed the exchange to provide options trading for Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC), Grayscale Bitcoin Mini Trust BTC (BTC), and Bitwise Bitcoin ETF (BITB). Meanwhile, Cboe has been greenlighted to list and t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Semilore Faleti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Is Today’s 'Captain Tsubasa: Rivals' Telegram Game Daily Combo]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=250928</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/captain-tsubasa-rivals-telegram-game-daily-combo"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T19:05:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anime soccer game Captain Tsubasa: Rivals gives out 5 million free daily balls ahead of the TON token airdrop. Here’s the combo for Saturday, October 19.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Sodastream CEO Offers $100K in Bitcoin for the Safe Return of Israeli Hostages]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7445529c81</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/former-sodastream-ceo-offers-100k-in-bitcoin-for-the-safe-return-of-israeli-hostages/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T18:51:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the midst of the ongoing conflict between Israel and Hamas, Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu recently made headlines by offering a form of immunity to Hamas fighters as part of his latest statements concerning the hostage crisis. Following Netanyahu’s statements, former Sodastream CEO Daniel Birnbaum upped the ante by pledging a $100,000 reward for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Moral Case for Bitcoin: Decentralized Currency as a Path to Freedom]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74455f3980</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/the-moral-case-for-bitcoin-decentralized-currency-as-a-path-to-freedom/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T17:58:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a world where state-backed currencies fund wars, inflate economies and deplete savings, digital alternatives like bitcoin offer a compelling ethical choice. By removing money from government control, bitcoin presents a route toward a freer and more just society. The Flaws of Fiat Currencies Government-issued fiat money, which lacks intrinsic value, is often manipulated through […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Is Today’s 'Tomarket' Telegram Game Daily Combo]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286780</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/here-is-todays-tomarket-telegram-game-daily-combo"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T16:20:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram game Tomarket is handing out free tomatoes and bonus items ahead of the airdrop. Here’s the combo for Saturday, October 19.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized Money Market Protocol Loses $4.3M in Social Engineering Attack]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7445413b9e</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/decentralized-money-market-protocol-loses-4-3m-in-social-engineering-attack/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T16:17:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tapioca DAO, has been the victim of a social engineering attack in which criminals exploited a vulnerability to compromise the ownership of the TAP token vesting contract. The breach led to the sale of 30 million vested tokens. A blockchain security firm detected suspicious activity involving Tapioca DAO. The attacker withdrew millions of TAP tokens, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock Seeks To Push BUIDL As Derivative Collateral In Crypto Market – Details]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74454d182c</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/blackrock-push-buidl-crypto-derivative-collateral/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T15:41:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The world’s largest asset manager, BlackRock, aims to expand its foray in the digital asset industry following the successful launch of spot Bitcoin and Ethereum ETFs in 2024. In a new venture, the American asset manager is attempting to push the adoption of its money-market token BUIDL as a collateral asset in the crypto derivative market. 
 
 
BlackRock’s BUIDL To Serve As Derivative Collateral: Report
 
According to a Friday report by Bloomberg, BlackRock has begun marketing BUIDL as collateral in the crypto derivative market. For context, BUIDL – which stands for BlackRock USD Institutional Digital Liquidity Fund – is a tokenized fund issued on the Ethereum blockchain offering institutional investors access to achieving US dollar yields.
 
Similar to stablecoins, BUIDL is pegged to a s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Semilore Faleti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kamala Harris Crypto Regulation Plans Spark Criticism—But Also Optimism]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287262</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287262/kamala-harris-crypto-regulation-criticism-optimism"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T13:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Kamala Harris campaign’s focus on Black male crypto investors sparks claims of pandering, but some still consider it a positive move.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Best Free Games to Play on Xbox Series X and S]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287076</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287076/best-free-games-xbox-series-x-s"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T11:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking for some great games to play on your Xbox Series X/S without paying a dime? Here are our favorite Xbox freebies right now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Frederiksen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Dookey Dash: Unclogged' Tips Guide: How to Dominate the Bored Ape Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287263</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/dookey-dash-unclogged-tips-guide-bored-ape-game"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T10:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bored Ape Yacht Club game Dookey Dash: Unclogged serves up an endless runner with real prizes. Here's how to rule the sewers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Stubbs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Is Today’s 'Major' Telegram Game Puzzle Durov Combo]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286896</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/here-is-todays-major-telegram-puzzle-durov-combo"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T01:15:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking to complete Major’s daily Pavel Durov puzzle on Telegram? Here’s the solution for Friday, October 18.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bluesky Signups Surge After Elon Musk's Twitter Says AI Can Be Trained on Tweets]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287241</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287241/bluesky-signups-surge-elon-musk-twitter-ai"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T20:31:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk's controversial moves at Twitter have sparked another user exodus, fueling explosive growth for decentralized rival Bluesky.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No, the SEC Isn't Backing Off Solana—Here's the Latest]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287253</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287253/sec-isnt-backing-off-solana-binance-latest"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T20:08:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New developments in the SEC’s lawsuit against Binance indicate the regulator is ratcheting up its case against SOL and other crypto tokens—not backing down, as some had hoped.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Huge week for BTC ETFs, Crypto now through Venmo, Memes Dominate Gainers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rLpBnnaQ/huge-week-for-btc-etfs-crypto-now-through-venmo-memes-dominate-gainers</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rLpBnnaQ/huge-week-for-btc-etfs-crypto-now-through-venmo-memes-dominate-gainers"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T19:24:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETFs see biggest inflow week since July. BlackRock ETF sees $1bn inflows in a week. Venmo can now be used to buy crypto on Moonpay. SEC’s XRP appeal doesn’t challenge security status. Worldcoin rebrands to World with new orb. EigenLayer X account compromised. FBI arrests hacker of SEC X account. SCB in Thailand adopts stablecoins for transfers. DBS in Singapore adopts ‘token services’. Trump family to get 75% of WLFL revenue. Scroll team accused of owning sybil addresses. STX Nakamoto upgrade to happen next week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Olympic Snowboarder Used Tether in Cocaine-Smuggling Murder Scheme, Feds Say]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287204</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287204/olympic-snowboarder-tether-cocaine-murders"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T19:20:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Canadian Olympic snowboarder and his gang used Tether (USDT) as part of its cocaine trafficking operation, U.S. authorities allege.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin 'Trump Trade' Returns as BlackRock's ETF Brings in Another $1 Billion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287209</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287209/bitcoin-trump-trade-blackrock-etf-billion"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T18:54:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF inflows have accelerated this week as the 2024 presidential election tightens in its final weeks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will 'Off the Grid' Take Crypto Games Mainstream?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287211</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287211/will-off-the-grid-take-crypto-games-mainstream"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T18:13:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche shooter Off the Grid has already made a huge splash in early access. We discuss the launch and potential impact on gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward,Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Let Him Come Home': Jailed Binance Exec’s Trial Postponed Due to Illness]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287207</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287207/jailed-binance-exec-trial-postponed-illness"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T17:42:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imprisoned Binance executive Tigran Gambaryan failed to attend a Nigerian court hearing due to his poor health, forcing a delay.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scammer Gets 5 Years in Prison After Swiping $20 Million via Fake Coinbase Websites]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287203</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287203/scammer-prison-fake-coinbase-websites"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T17:29:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chirag Tomar, an Indian national, drained the accounts of unsuspecting Coinbase customers in a scam built around impostor websites.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Is Booming—You Can Earn More by Playing These Free Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=205392</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/205392/bitcoin-booming-you-earn-more-playing-free-games"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T16:52:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATE: Bitcoin is making a move for $69,000 as "Uptober" takes root, and you can earn more BTC by playing these games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Radiant Capital’s $50M Breach Among ‘Most Sophisticated Hacks’ in DeFi History]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287162</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287162/radiant-capitals-50m-breach-among-most-sophisticated-hacks-in-defi-history"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T16:52:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The DeFi project claimed that hackers compromised the hardware wallets of its long-term developers and injected malware.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will McCurdy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[dGEN1 Mobile Device Launches for ‘Seamless’ Onchain Ethereum Transactions]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287120</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287120/dgen1-mobile-device-launches-for-seamless-onchain-ethereum-transactions"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T15:53:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Created by Freedom Factory, dGEN1 integrates Ethereum at the operating system level to streamline dapp interactions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy's Bitcoin Scheme Isn't an 'Infinite Money Glitch', Says Michael Saylor]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287163</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287163/microstrategy-bitcoin-scheme-isnt-infinite-money-glitch"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T15:18:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy founder Michael Saylor dismissed criticism over the firm's $16 billion Bitcoin haul, saying it's driving BTC scarcity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EigenLayer Twitter Account Hacked to Share Ethereum Airdrop Scam]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287159</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287159/eigenlayer-twitter-hack-airdrop-scam"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T14:37:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A hacker published a series of posts Friday from EigenLayer's Twitter account, urging users to click on an apparent phishing link.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Napolitano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Machine Learning AI Helped Detect $4 Billion Worth of Fraud in 2024, Says US Treasury]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287141</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287141/machine-learning-ai-us-treasury"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T12:54:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI models helped the department prevent $2.5 billion in fraud, while its check fraud detection systems facilitated the recovery of $1 billion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vismaya V</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Craig Wright Says Bitcoin Devs 'Misled the Public' in New $1 Billion Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287138</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287138/craig-wright-bitcoin-new-lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T12:29:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After the SegWit and Taproot upgrades, Craig Wright claims Bitcoin “fundamentally deviated” from Satoshi Nakamoto’s vision and misled investors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Could Hit Turbulence From US Bond Yields, Fed Policy: Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287119</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287119/bitcoin-could-hit-turbulence-from-us-bond-yields-fed-policy-analyst"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T11:49:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin has climbed 11% in the past week, but there could be some macroeconomic headwinds on the horizon, say analysts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Moons Again After Musk Drops Token Mention During Pennsylvania Town Hall]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287079</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287079/dogecoin-moons-again-musk-drops-token-mention-during-pennsylvania-town-hall"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T05:29:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Someone asked Musk if he would head up a new “Department of Government Efficiency.” Musk responded with a lighthearted grin, “Yeah, Doge.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vismaya V</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Files Last-Minute Appeal in Ripple Case—Why the XRP Army is Outraged]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287069</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287069/sec-files-last-minute-appeal-in-ripple-case-why-xrp-army-outraged"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T02:15:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While the SEC isn't contesting the ruling that XRP sales to retail investors aren't securities, it is instead focusing on other key aspects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Sinclair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin Rebrands as World, Launches New Eyeball Scanning Orb]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287051</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287051/worldcoin-rebrands-as-world-launches-new-retina-scanning-orb"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T23:30:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[World's redesigned Orb has 30% fewer parts and triple the production capacity of its predecessor, powered by NVIDIA’s Jetson.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Researchers Hacked AI Robots Into Breaking Traffic Laws—And Worse]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286994</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286994/how-researchers-hacked-ai-robots-into-breaking-traffic-laws-and-worse"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T23:14:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers showed vulnerabilities in AI-powered robots being exploited to perform dangerous tasks, including detonating bombs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Worldcoin Built an Ethereum Network Specifically for Humans]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286983</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286983/world-chain-launches-mainnet-world-coin"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T22:34:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[World, previously called Worldcoin, has debuted an Ethereum layer-2 chain with an aim to onboard real humans—not bots.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Napolitano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Bulls Have Reason to Worry If L2s Remain Dominant, Says VanEck Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286970</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286970/ethereum-price-target-plunge-vaneck-analyst"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T22:16:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum's "changing fundamentals" and growing embrace of layer-2 networks could massively impact ETH's future price, a VanEck analyst said Thursday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk-Themed ‘X Empire’ Ends Telegram Gameplay Ahead of Airdrop]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286977</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286977/x-empire-ends-telegram-gameplay-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T21:12:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tap-to-earn game X Empire is gearing up for next week’s X token launch and airdrop on The Open Network (TON).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PayPal's Venmo Can Now Be Used to Buy Bitcoin and Ethereum via MoonPay]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286969</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286969/paypal-venmo-buy-crypto-moonpay"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T20:52:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PayPal's Venmo can now be used by U.S. customers to top up and make crypto purchases on MoonPay, according to a Thursday announcement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETFs Race Past $20 Billion Milestone in Just 10 Months]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286948</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286948/bitcoin-etf-20-billion-milestone-inflows-blackrock"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T19:06:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Approved in January, Bitcoin exchange-traded funds have experienced trading activity like no other ETF product.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Galaxis Teams Up With TV Show ‘Killer Whales’ to ‘Empower Creators’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285090</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285090/galaxis-teams-up-with-tv-show-killer-whales-to-empower-creators"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T19:05:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The partnership will see Galaxis showcased throughout the reality show, as well as “actively supporting” the Web3 projects featured.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wrapped Bitcoin Wars Ramp Up as Kraken Reveals kBTC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286934</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286934/wrapped-bitcoin-wars-kraken-kbtc"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T17:58:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto exchange Kraken has unveiled a new wrapped Bitcoin product dubbed kBTC, joining a growing battle with Coinbase, 21.co, and BitGo.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Presidential Election Tops $2 Billion in Betting Volume on Polymarket]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286923</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286923/us-presidential-election-2-billion-volume-polymarket"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T17:46:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trump is currently leading the Polymarket betting pool on the winner of the U.S. election, which has topped $2 billion in total volume.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Napolitano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Majors Fall 1 to 2%, A New Tiger takes to the Charts, Van Eck teases Big Web3 Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/a6Tm7OGW/majors-fall-1-to-2-a-new-tiger-takes-to-the-charts-van-eck-teases-big-web3-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/a6Tm7OGW/majors-fall-1-to-2-a-new-tiger-takes-to-the-charts-van-eck-teases-big-web3-gaming"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T17:42:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lucky GOAT memecoin trader turned $5,000 into $1.5M during GOAT's run to $300M. A new memecoin based on Disney Park's new baby tiger "Bakso" was a top mover on Wednesday, running to $10M (now $6M). Crypto majors fall 1-2%, memes red across board. a16z calls 2024 crypto's biggest year yet in "State of Crypto" report. Vitalik publishes part 2 of blog outlining ETH's future. Van Eck teases big bet on Parallel and web3 gaming. Huge day for digital art with 4 marquee mints seeing success.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hamster Kombat Season 2 Teaser]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/qcvjjJxN/hamster-kombat-season-2-teaser</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/qcvjjJxN/hamster-kombat-season-2-teaser"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T12:03:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here's a first look at Season 2 of Telegram tap-to-earn game Hamster Kombat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BTC hits $68K, Trump odds Continue to Rise, GOAT nears $300M]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/c88qN8eB/btc-hits-68k-trump-odds-continue-to-rise-goat-nears-300m</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/c88qN8eB/btc-hits-68k-trump-odds-continue-to-rise-goat-nears-300m"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T18:31:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC hits $68k as ETF inflows continue to soar. Open Interest at CME hits ATH, funding still low. Tesla moves $750m BTC to new wallet. Canary applies for Litcoin ETF, LTC up 8%. Grayscale asks SEC to convert altcoin fund to ETF. Kraken integrates with EigenLayer for restaking. ‘Network state’ Praxis raises $525m for new city. Trump project raises only $11m so far. a16z founders donate $2.5m to Trump PAC. TikTok accused of being crypto exchange in UK. Gotbit CEO arrested in Portugal. Perplexity AI launches finance platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ETF Inflows Soar, Kamala Courts Crypto, TURBO Nears $1BN!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zn2lboMV/etf-inflows-soar-kamala-courts-crypto-turbo-nears-1bn</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zn2lboMV/etf-inflows-soar-kamala-courts-crypto-turbo-nears-1bn"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T18:22:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETFs see $800m inflows in 2-days, huge volume. ETF inflows may be linked to Trump odds: CoinShares. Bitcoin will rival housing market as asset class: Fink. Vitalik proposes drop to 1ETH to become validator. Kamala reveals pro-crypto policies. Kamala mocked for linking crypto to race. Hyperliquid announces HYPE token coming. PUFFER airdrop claim goes live. Tether considering lending to commodities trader. Man takes $500m lost Bitcoin case to court. Google removes crypto prices from search. SUI Foundation denies $400m insider selling. UAE approves $AED stablecoin. Bitget wallet now only behind Binance for downloads.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BTC hits 2-week High, China Stocks Rally again, GOAT hits $120M]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/0V0rYhMX/btc-hits-2-week-high-china-stocks-rally-again-goat-hits-120m</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/0V0rYhMX/btc-hits-2-week-high-china-stocks-rally-again-goat-hits-120m"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T14:09:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC hits 2-week high as China stocks rise. SUI breaks into the top 15 coins. $1.3bn ETH might be sold from PlusToken scam. S. Korea may approve BTC & ETH ETFs this month. Australia launches first ETH ETF. Samara to buy BTC with $33m bond. Altcoins to see $500m unlocks this week. Vitalik writes blog on the future of ETH. Grayscale reveals 35 altcoins considered for funds. Ethena proposes SOL for USDe collateral. Only one Binance launchpad coin up this year. AVAX summit begins this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Falls Ahead of CPI, Stripe Reinstates Crypto, Fed Charges Market-makers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/aYgFvZqj/crypto-falls-ahead-of-cpi-stripe-reinstates-crypto-fed-charges-market-makers</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/aYgFvZqj/crypto-falls-ahead-of-cpi-stripe-reinstates-crypto-fed-charges-market-makers"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T07:29:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Majors drop despite stocks hitting ATHs. Stripe reinstates crypto payments. Crypto settlements near $20bn in 2024. S. Korea to review ban on BTC ETFs. US charges market makers for market manipulation. FBI created their own coin to ensnare targets. Vitalik ‘outside pick’ for Nobel Prize. Trump family token to built on Aave stack. $16m OP tokens allocated to superchain users. Wisdomtree debuts debit card for on-chain fund. 47% of hedge funds have crypto exposure. Argentina overtakes Brazil for crypto inflows. Tucker interviews Ryan Salame over FTX.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Todd ‘revealed’ as Satoshi, Google may be Broken-up, Murad’s Wallets Doxxed]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pLw8b2d2/todd-revealed-as-satoshi-google-may-be-broken-up-murads-wallets-doxxed</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pLw8b2d2/todd-revealed-as-satoshi-google-may-be-broken-up-murads-wallets-doxxed"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T07:29:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC will be range bound until election: Bernstein. TAO & memecoins dominate mindshare. Peter Todd ‘revealed’ as Satoshi by HBO. US government able to sell $4.4bn Silk Road BTC. Ireland unable to access $378m seized BTC. SOL could do 5x if Trump wins: StanChart. Coinbase integrates Taproot addresses for BTC. Canary Capital applies for XRP ETF. S. Korea to regulate stablecoin transfers. CryptoCom files countersuit against SEC. Babylon fills cap with 22k BTC. Scroll airdrop coming Oct 22nd. USDC goes live on SUI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bounces from $59K, Tesla unveils Robotaxis, Memecoins Outperform]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cyJj6tWj/bitcoin-bounces-from-59k-tesla-unveils-robotaxis-memecoins-outperform</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cyJj6tWj/bitcoin-bounces-from-59k-tesla-unveils-robotaxis-memecoins-outperform"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T07:29:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC briefly dips under $59k, $160m liquidations. Mt Gox extends repayment plan by 1 year. Uniswap plans L2 for DeFi. SEC sues crypto trading firm Cumberland. Binomial sues SEC over futures trading. SEC’s Uyeda criticises agency’s policy. Justin Sun named prime minister of Liberland. MicroStrategy wants to become BTC bank. Binance pre-market trading goes live. Nearly 50% of US investors want crypto ETFs. Whale phished for $35m crypto. Ethena invests $46m in RWA funds. Trump’s crypto project aims to raise $300m.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentraland Desktop Client Preview]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qqzvDcTC/decentraland-desktop-client-preview</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qqzvDcTC/decentraland-desktop-client-preview"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T15:53:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum metaverse game Decentraland has shared an exclusive look at the visual and performance upgrades coming via its new desktop client.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Trader Murad Mahmudov talks about the Supercycle and how he chooses Meme Coins.]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Hj3nDp7G/crypto-trader-murad-mahmudov-talks-about-the-supercycle-and-how-he-chooses-meme-coins</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Hj3nDp7G/crypto-trader-murad-mahmudov-talks-about-the-supercycle-and-how-he-chooses-meme-coins"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T21:47:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Trader Murad Mahmudov talks about the Supercycle and how he chooses Meme Coins. Crypto stable, had sold off after China stocks fall. Crypto adopted faster than other tech: BlackRock. Crypto adoption to hit 8% of world population. CryptoCom recieves Wells notice from SEC. HBO documentary on Satoshi airs tonight. FTX bankruptcy plan approved by judge. Scroll airdrop may be imminent. Jupiter goes live on mobile iOS. Phantom rolls out support for Base. AAVE launches GHO on Base. Gensler may be replaced by Robinhood CLO. 87% of new token launches on SOL. National Bank of Bahrain creates BTC fund. BedRock DeFi allows BTC staking on ARB.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Memecoins take off, funding stays low, China stocks keep on rising!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/703mAYhV/memecoins-take-off-funding-stays-low-china-stocks-keep-on-rising</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/703mAYhV/memecoins-take-off-funding-stays-low-china-stocks-keep-on-rising"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T08:27:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR EP213. Memecoins take off, funding stays low, China stocks keep on rising!
Many altcoins & memecoins soar despite stable BTC. Funding rates continue to be low or negative. Crypto funds saw $147m of outflows last week. BTC remains best performing major assets this year. SUI breaks into the top 20 coins again. TAO leads top 100 away from memes, sifu shorts. $100m bridge to SOL over the last 7 days. Metaplanet buys $6.7m more BTC. ETH proposal aims to improve throughput 50%. EIGEN, OP, APT lead token unlocks this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Walrus Protocol Unlocks New Applications for Decentralized Data Storage]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kwEYLYWj/how-walrus-protocol-unlocks-new-applications-for-decentralized-data-storage</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kwEYLYWj/how-walrus-protocol-unlocks-new-applications-for-decentralized-data-storage"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T11:19:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mysten Labs Chief Scientist George Danezis joined Decrypt to talk about its new decentralized storage protocol Walrus, which promises to unlock new applications such as AI and social media, thanks to its novel Red Stuff data encoding algorithm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Coinbase Sees Crypto as a Bipartisan, 'Purple' Political Issue]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/YR2YmmwR/why-coinbase-sees-crypto-as-a-bipartisan-purple-political-issue</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/YR2YmmwR/why-coinbase-sees-crypto-as-a-bipartisan-purple-political-issue"/>
        <updated>2024-10-05T22:18:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase VP of Corporate and Business Development, Shan Aggarwal, joined Decrypt's Sander Lutz and Liz Napolitano at Messari Mainnet 2024 to discuss the exchange's efforts to grow mainstream crypto adoption—and how the changing political conversation around digital assets is rapidly playing a major role in that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Is Playing Offense—Not Just Defense—Against Crypto Crime, Says Head of Financial Investigations]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DiJ8D2Qc/binance-is-playing-offensenot-just-defenseagainst-crypto-crime-says-head-of-financial-investigations</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DiJ8D2Qc/binance-is-playing-offensenot-just-defenseagainst-crypto-crime-says-head-of-financial-investigations"/>
        <updated>2024-10-05T01:58:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nils Anderson Röed, the exchange’s global head of financial investigations, sat down with Decrypt’s Sander Lutz at Messari Mainnet 2024 to discuss how Binance is proactively dismantling criminal networks around the world, the strategy with which the crypto exchange is approaching sensitive conflicts in the Middle East, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 212 - SEEDPHRASE TALKS ART!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PJfaJNkZ/fomo-hour-212-seedphrase-talks-art</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PJfaJNkZ/fomo-hour-212-seedphrase-talks-art"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T19:29:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Payrolls Higher than expected, Bitcoin reacts hard. Crypto sank early in the week as Middle East tensions spooked markets. Powell signals two more rate cuts this year. SUI leads L1s again, nears YTD high despite large unlock. Majority of FTX repayments still months away. EIGEN becomes non-transferable, hits $6bn FDV. SEC to appeal Ripple securities law ruling. Visa launches tokenization platform for banks. SWIFT plans digital asset trial in 2025. ByBit launched trading of global stock indices. SPX, GIGA & FWOG hit ATHs, most memes fall. XCOPY to release 250 piece collection on Shape. HBO documentary claims to have identified Satoshi.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Altcoins bleed, ByBit launches stock index trading, POCHITA soars]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kYjAt3nt/altcoins-bleed-bybit-launches-stock-index-trading-pochita-soars</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kYjAt3nt/altcoins-bleed-bybit-launches-stock-index-trading-pochita-soars"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T21:11:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Altcoins sink, BTC dominance nears cycle high. BTC in ‘three blind mice’ downtrend. Tron revenue hits record $577m in Q3. ByBit to launch trading of major stock indices. Franklin Templeton launch fund on APT. SWIFT banks to trial digital assets in 2025. Aerodrome hits $1bn TVL on Base. Cronje calls out Aerodrome for copyright. ETH ICO wallet sells $47m. SEC files appeal against Ripple ruling. EIGEN falls 20% on staking rewards FUD. FTX to auction off WLD position. Half of US voters think crypto ‘important’. North Korea ‘infiltrating’ crypto industry. Snowden challenged over SOL centralisation view. Top SEC official on crypto set to depart.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DACOM Summit: Fastex CLO Vardan Khachatryan on Crypto Compliance]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LGGnxkb6/dacom-summit-fastex-clo-vardan-khachatryan-on-crypto-compliance</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LGGnxkb6/dacom-summit-fastex-clo-vardan-khachatryan-on-crypto-compliance"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T14:32:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fastex Chief Legal Officer Vardan Khachatryan joined Rug Radio creator Mlow at DACOM Summit to discuss how the crypto exchange is advancing compliance, and the regulatory challenges that lie ahead for the sector.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 210 - MIDDLE EAST TENSIONS RISE]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Bcj37IF2/fomo-hour-210-middle-east-tensions-rise</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Bcj37IF2/fomo-hour-210-middle-east-tensions-rise"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T17:14:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto drops as Middle East tensions flare. $500m liquidations in drop. BTC ETFs see largest outflows in a month. Fidelity ETH ETF sees 2nd highest outflow ever. SUI hits 6-month highs, bridge goes live on mainnet. Hashdex set to launch XRP ETF. Wormhole leads altcoin gains after Upbit lists. BTC miners hit record low profits in September Crypto hackers stole $750m in Q3. Telegram has been disclosing IPs since 2018.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Arbitrum is Simplifying Web3 for Web2 Adopters]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Mm9OGAoG/how-arbitrum-is-simplifying-web3-for-web2-adopters</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Mm9OGAoG/how-arbitrum-is-simplifying-web3-for-web2-adopters"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T14:19:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arbitrum's Head of Korea, John Park, joined Rug Radio creator Pukerainbow at ArbiVerse to talk about the Ethereum layer-2's strategy in Asia, hackathons, and bringing enterprise clients to its ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>