<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-05-29T21:13:00.753Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-05-29T21:13:00.753Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana: Crypto’s Next Apple? Co-Founder Shares Bold Vision For The Blockchain’s Future]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75001af922</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/solana-cryptos-next-apple-co-founder-shares-vision/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T20:58:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana is a layer-1 blockchain that has been making waves in the crypto industry since its launch in 2020. The co-founder, Raj Gokal, recently spoke to TechCrunch+ about the potential of Solana to become the “Apple of crypto.”
 
 
Solana Co-Founder Thinks Its Blockchain Could Rival Apple’s Success
 
According to Gokal, Apple’s success can be attributed to its relentless focus on user experience and performance. He believes Solana shares this same focus and is working to create a network that feels like the regular Internet but is an entirely new financial Internet. Gokal stated that creating a seamless user experience is key to the success of any platform, whether it is a smartphone or a blockchain network.
 
To achieve this, Solana is working on creating a fast, efficient, and scalable ne…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinEx launches BitHK trading platform for Hong Kong users]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18456313/CoinEx-launches-BitHK-trading-platform-for-Hong-Kong-users</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18456313/CoinEx-launches-BitHK-trading-platform-for-Hong-Kong-users"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T20:57:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BitHK will offer spot trading and looks to launch a P2P exchange for Hong Kong users. The exchange will submit an application for registration as a VASP with the Hong Kong Securities and Futures Commission (SFC) on 1 June. Another exchange, Huobi HK is also offering spot trading to Hong Kong...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano Transactions Spike 1.5M as SNEK Rallies to All-time High]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18456306/Cardano-Transactions-Spike-15M-as-SNEK-Rallies-to-All-time-High</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18456306/Cardano-Transactions-Spike-15M-as-SNEK-Rallies-to-All-time-High"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T20:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Memecoins are stirring quite the storm for Cardano as network transactions spike by 1.5 million.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Exchange BKEX Suspends Withdrawal to Aid Money Laundering Probe]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7500048c0e</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/crypto-exchange-bkex-suspends-withdrawal-to-aid-money-laundering-probe/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T20:40:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency  
exchange BKEX has frozen customer withdrawal on its platform to cooperate with  
police investigation into alleged money laundering by some of its  
users. The exchange on Monday said it decided to halt withdrawal in order to  
aid authorities in collecting evidence.
“The team  
will actively work with the relevant authorities to resolve the current issues  
faced to ensure that the rights of our users are protected to the greatest  
extent possible,” BKEX said in a statement on its blog. 

#BKEX Announcement on Suspension of Withdrawals- Details: https://t.co/gDh6Z3bg9apic.twitter.com/EMTEuU2DDO
— BKEX (@BKEXGlobal) May 29, 2023
The  
exchange assured that it will “do its best to restore the normal operation of  
the exchange.” BKEX through the platform offers crypto, derivatives and margin  
trading features to users.
According  
to CoinMarketCap, BKEX was founded in June 2018  
and boasts of  
over 8 million users from more than 100 countries in Asia, Europe and Latin  
America, among others. 
 
  
 
  
This article was written by Solomon Oladipupo at www.financemagnates.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Solomon Oladipupo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Laos government reportedly prioritizes blockchain technology for digital transformation]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18456304/Laos-government-reportedly-prioritizes-blockchain-technology-for-digital-transformation</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18456304/Laos-government-reportedly-prioritizes-blockchain-technology-for-digital-transformation"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T20:38:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Laotian Prime Minister Sonexay Siphandone chaired the inaugural Ministerial Conference on Blockchain 4.0 Digital Transformation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kava Token Price Pumped 41% in May, Analysts Predict This Little Known Crypto is Next to Rise – Find Out Why]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18456285/Kava-Token-Price-Pumped-41-in-May-Analysts-Predict-This-Little-Known-Crypto-is-Next-to-Rise-Find-Out-Why</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18456285/Kava-Token-Price-Pumped-41-in-May-Analysts-Predict-This-Little-Known-Crypto-is-Next-to-Rise-Find-Out-Why"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T20:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kava recorded a massive value-reclaiming trend in May amid the fluctuations in the crypto market.  According to data from CoinMarketCap, Kava pumped by over 41% over the past 30 days. Though several crypto assets recorded a southward price trend, Kava maintained a positive hold surging through...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Optimism’s upcoming token unlock pose a threat to OP?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18456282/Will-Optimisms-upcoming-token-unlock-pose-a-threat-to-OP</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18456282/Will-Optimisms-upcoming-token-unlock-pose-a-threat-to-OP"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T20:30:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The upcoming unlock of 3.6% of Optimism tokens may disrupt OP's growth, increasing selling pressure and price volatility. Protocol remains high, despite waning interest in its NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinEX Targets Hong Kong Users with New Crypto Trading Service]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7500057644</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/coinex-targets-hong-kong-users-with-new-crypto-trading-service/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T20:30:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency exchange CoinEX has launched a digital asset trading platform  
for its users in Hong Kong. Dubbed BitHK, the  
platform, which seeks to apply for a Virtual Asset Service Provider (VASP)  
license from the Securities and Futures Commission of Hong Kong (SFC) on June  
1, would offer spot trading and digital asset storage services in both  
the taditional Chinese and English languages. Additionally, BitHK aims to expand its  
current offerings.
''BitHK is constantly  
improving and plans to introduce P2P crypto trading on top of spot trading to  
support both HKD deposits and withdrawals,'' said Haipo Yang, CEO of CoinEX, in a statement. ''As  
an integral part of Hong Kong's financial services industry, BitHK has an  
obligation to uphold the city's image as an international…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana: Crypto’s Next Apple? Co-Founder Shares Bold Vision For The Blockchain’s Future]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18456283/Solana-Cryptos-Next-Apple-Co-Founder-Shares-Bold-Vision-For-The-Blockchains-Future</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18456283/Solana-Cryptos-Next-Apple-Co-Founder-Shares-Bold-Vision-For-The-Blockchains-Future"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T20:30:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana is a layer-1 blockchain that has been making waves in the crypto industry since its launch in 2020. The co-founder, Raj Gokal, recently spoke to TechCrunch+ about the potential of Solana to become the “Apple of crypto.” Related Reading: USDT Market Dominance Spikes While USDC Dips Amid...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Crypto to Buy Now 29 May –  CAKE, INJ, WMS, Ecoterra, Mask, ypredict, QNT]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18456286/Best-Crypto-to-Buy-Now-29-May-CAKE-INJ-WMS-Ecoterra-Mask-ypredict-QNT</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18456286/Best-Crypto-to-Buy-Now-29-May-CAKE-INJ-WMS-Ecoterra-Mask-ypredict-QNT"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T20:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrencies are experiencing a significant surge in popularity, with numerous new coins capturing the attention of investors. In this update, we will focus on one particular group of cryptocurrencies that show high growth potential.  Specifically, we will discuss CAKE, INJ, WMS, Ecoterra,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Currency Exchange Gemini Seeks to Have SEC Lawsuit Dismissed]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18456277/Currency-Exchange-Gemini-Seeks-to-Have-SEC-Lawsuit-Dismissed</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18456277/Currency-Exchange-Gemini-Seeks-to-Have-SEC-Lawsuit-Dismissed"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T20:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent update, the cryptocurrency exchange Gemini, run by the Winklevoss twins, filed a motion to dismiss the SEC’s securities violation lawsuit.  Gemini Trust Co filed the request in Manhattan federal court on May 26 in response to a January 12 lawsuit by the US Securities and Exchanges...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Major Bitcoin Whales Abandoning Crypto Exchanges]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18456272/Major-Bitcoin-Whales-Abandoning-Crypto-Exchanges</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18456272/Major-Bitcoin-Whales-Abandoning-Crypto-Exchanges"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T20:17:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a shift that could significantly impact the cryptocurrency market, major Bitcoin whales appear to be gradually retreating from crypto exchanges]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimism to Unlock Millions of OP Tokens: What It Means for You]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18456260/Optimism-to-Unlock-Millions-of-OP-Tokens-What-It-Means-for-You</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18456260/Optimism-to-Unlock-Millions-of-OP-Tokens-What-It-Means-for-You"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T20:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Optimism will unlock around 155 million OP tokens.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy is better than Coinbase for crypto exposure: Berenberg]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18456259/MicroStrategy-is-better-than-Coinbase-for-crypto-exposure-Berenberg</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18456259/MicroStrategy-is-better-than-Coinbase-for-crypto-exposure-Berenberg"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T20:01:39.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FBI Issues Warning to Americans, Says Fake Job Advertisements Force Victims to Commit Crypto Scams]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18456262/FBI-Issues-Warning-to-Americans-Says-Fake-Job-Advertisements-Force-Victims-to-Commit-Crypto-Scams</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18456262/FBI-Issues-Warning-to-Americans-Says-Fake-Job-Advertisements-Force-Victims-to-Commit-Crypto-Scams"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T20:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) is issuing a warning to Americans about fake job advertisements that harass applicants into committing crypto fraud. According to a new public service announcement from the FBI, false job advertisements linked to labor trafficking compounds in Southeast...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blocktrade raises €4.5M in its BTEX Token sale]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18456258/Blocktrade-raises-45M-in-its-BTEX-Token-sale</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18456258/Blocktrade-raises-45M-in-its-BTEX-Token-sale"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T20:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gamified asset marketplace Blocktrade says it has raised €4.5 million in an exclusive BTEX Token (BTEX) sale. The sale attracted 1,400 community members from 42 countries. Blocktrade will use the funds to grow its platform. Blocktrade, a gamified crypto asset and marketplace, has announced that...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Global Financial System vs Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18456257/The-Global-Financial-System-vs-Bitcoin</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18456257/The-Global-Financial-System-vs-Bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T20:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Taker Buy Sell Ratio At Highest Since Feb, What Does It Mean?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7500003d25</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-taker-buy-sell-ratio-highest-since-feb-mean/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T19:58:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data shows that the Bitcoin taker buy-sell ratio has been the highest since February. Here’s what this may mean for the market.
 
Bitcoin Taker Buy Sell Ratio Has Registered A Spike Recently
 
An analyst in a CryptoQuant post pointed out that the current taker buy-sell ratio values may suggest a bullish sentiment in the market. The “taker buy sell ratio” is an indicator that measures the ratio between the taker buy and the taker sell volumes in the Bitcoin market.
 
When the value of this metric is less than 1, it means the taker sell volume is currently greater than the taker buy volume, which implies that the selling pressure is higher in the market. Such a trend suggests that most investors currently share a bearish sentiment.
 
On the other hand, values of the ratio above this…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hououin Kyouma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Korean Court Jails Civil Servant Who Stole Public Funds to Buy Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18456248/South-Korean-Court-Jails-Civil-Servant-Who-Stole-Public-Funds-to-Buy-Crypto</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18456248/South-Korean-Court-Jails-Civil-Servant-Who-Stole-Public-Funds-to-Buy-Crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T19:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A South Korean court has handed a suspended jail term to a civil servant who stole thousands of USD worth of public funds to pay for crypto investments. Per Yonhap, the public official was handed a one-year suspended prison sentence, as well as two years of probation. The official was not named...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frog Cryptos Pump as Pepe Price Dumps - Kermit, Memetic PepeCoin, PepeDerp Up]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18456249/Frog-Cryptos-Pump-as-Pepe-Price-Dumps-Kermit-Memetic-PepeCoin-PepeDerp-Up</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18456249/Frog-Cryptos-Pump-as-Pepe-Price-Dumps-Kermit-Memetic-PepeCoin-PepeDerp-Up"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T19:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Looks Increasingly Ready To Breakout As BTC On-Chain Metrics Reach Boiling Point: Glassnode]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18456252/Bitcoin-Looks-Increasingly-Ready-To-Breakout-As-BTC-On-Chain-Metrics-Reach-Boiling-Point-Glassnode</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18456252/Bitcoin-Looks-Increasingly-Ready-To-Breakout-As-BTC-On-Chain-Metrics-Reach-Boiling-Point-Glassnode"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T19:55:31.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 Can Help Marginalized Communities Share Their Stories: Jordan Bayne]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142763</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142763/web3-can-help-marginalized-communities-share-their-stories-jordan-bayne"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T19:43:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The award-winning filmmaker says blockchain tech provides a powerful way for artists to connect with audiences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin transaction fee revenue soared this month thanks to Ordinals]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18456236/Bitcoin-transaction-fee-revenue-soared-this-month-thanks-to-Ordinals</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18456236/Bitcoin-transaction-fee-revenue-soared-this-month-thanks-to-Ordinals"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T19:36:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin transaction fee revenue skyrocketed in May thanks to the growth in bitcoin NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ETH Wallet Dormant Since 2015 Moves 8,000 ETH in Minutes]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18456232/ETH-Wallet-Dormant-Since-2015-Moves-8000-ETH-in-Minutes</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18456232/ETH-Wallet-Dormant-Since-2015-Moves-8000-ETH-in-Minutes"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T19:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Bitcoin Corp to Operate Restructured Mining Division of Celsius, Boosting Hashrate by 12.2 EH/s]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7500029b28</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/us-bitcoin-corp-to-operate-restructured-mining-division-of-celsius-boosting-hashrate-by-12-2-eh-s/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T19:32:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin mining company U.S. Bitcoin Corp (USBTC) has announced its intention to employ the mining assets of Celsius, the defunct crypto lender. The development follows the acquisition of application-specific integrated circuit (ASIC) machines from the bankrupt company by the Fahrenheit coalition, of which USBTC is a member. USBTC said it aims to revive the fleet of 121,800 Celsius machines and foresees a 12.2 exahash per second (EH/s) boost to its mining operations.
 
US Bitcoin Corp Assumes Control of Restructured Celsius Mining Unit
 
According to an announcement on May 25, 2023, U.S. Bitcoin Corp (USBTC) has plans to utilize the mining assets of the now-bankrupt crypto lender, Celsius. After multiple rounds of bidding for the restructured mining division of Celsius, USBTC submitted a wi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tron can easily overtake Ethereum, but for…]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18456226/Tron-can-easily-overtake-Ethereum-but-for</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18456226/Tron-can-easily-overtake-Ethereum-but-for"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T19:30:32.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PancakeSwap Launches Tower Defense Game—With CAKE Token Rewards]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142762</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142762/you-can-earn-cake-crypto-by-playing-pancake-protectors"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T19:23:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pancake Protectors enlists the CAKE token to lure new users to Web3 gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pro-XRP Lawyer Offers Key Solution To Ripple’s Legal Woes Against SEC]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75000dad6e</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/xrp-lawyer-offers-key-solution-ripples-legal-woes/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T18:59:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jeremy Hogan, a pro-XRP lawyer, has discussed the issue of secondary market sales and its potential impact on the Ripple vs. the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) lawsuit. 
 
The outcome of this case is crucial for XRP holders, as it will determine whether the asset is deemed inherently a security. If the issue of secondary market sales is not addressed, it could impact the relisting of XRP on exchanges like Coinbase.
 
The SEC lawsuit suggests that XRP is a security, like a share of stock. However, the SEC’s requests of the court in the lawsuit do not explicitly request anything that would confer this status on the asset. This leaves the issue of secondary market sales in question.
 
 
Disgorgement Order Could Force Ripple vs. SEC Case To Address Secondary Sales Issue
 
The SEC …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USDT Market Dominance Spikes While USDC Dips Amid Economic Uncertainty]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75000bb9f8</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/usdt-spikes-usdc-dips-amid-economic-uncertainty/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T18:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoins like Tether (USDT) and USD Coin (USDC) are usually steadier than other digital assets, especially those pegged to fiat currencies like the USD. 
 
These coins act as a hedge against extreme levels of market volatility. However, the latest data on USD-pegged stablecoin’s reactions to the current economic uncertainty displays unexpected outcomes.
 
 
However, these assets have seen a lot of action over the past few months. While many stablecoins are losing market share, the top stablecoin by market cap, Tether USDT, has climbed to an all-time high over the past year.  
 
Tether (USDT) Takes Over
 
According to data from Coingecko, Tether has gained market dominance in the past 12 months. The stablecoin currently holds a whopping 65.89% market dominance, far ahead of others in its…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Dambel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gemini and Genesis Fight Back Against SEC Lawsuit, Seek Dismissal of Allegations]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7501f6fe8d</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/gemini-and-genesis-fight-back-against-sec-lawsuit-seek-dismissal-of-allegations/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T17:31:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gemini Trust Company and Genesis Global Capital filed a court document on May 26, 2023, seeking the dismissal of a lawsuit brought by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). The regulatory body had accused the two crypto firms of offering unregistered securities.
 
Gemini and Genesis Refute SEC’s Claims of Unregistered Securities, File Motion to Dismiss
 
In January 2023, the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) filed a lawsuit against Gemini and Genesis for allegedly offering unregistered securities to American customers. The SEC complaint alleges that “through this unregistered offering, Genesis and Gemini raised billions of dollars’ worth of crypto assets from hundreds of thousands of investors.”
 
In a court document filed on May 26, 2023, lawyers representing Gemin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet the Crypto Rich Who Want to Live Forever: Inside Vitalik's Zuzalu]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142530</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142530/meet-crypto-rich-who-want-live-forever-inside-vitaliks-zuzalu"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T17:19:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zuzalu attendees tell Decrypt about the secretive two-month gathering of tech leaders in a Montenegrin seaside town, which ended last week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Undeads Metaverse Starts Building The New Endless Runner Mini-Game]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7501f132b9</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/undeads-metaverse-starts-building-the-new-endless-runner-mini-game/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T17:11:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. Hot on the heels of generating $1M in sales in sold-out first mint event, Undeads Metaverse is excited to announce the development of another zombie-filled game that will allow NFT holders to earn rewards on their Undead NFTs sooner than anticipated. The new game, “Undeads Runner,” was inspired by Yuga Labs’ Dookey Dash and is focused on continuing to build a strong, long-term and thriving Undead Metaverse community. 
 
The “Undeads Runner” game has gone into production and is being built in-house. The Undeads team has expanded to include a new production team dedicated to the game’s creation and will not affect the production of the current Undeads Metaverse game.
 
Undeads Metaverse team wanted to create this runner game to drive community engagement and provide fun and en…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hinman Emails Unveiling Inevitable, Affirms Deaton And Ripple CTO]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7501f25432</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/hinman-emails-unveiling-inevitable-ripple/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T17:01:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prominent pro-XRP attorney John Deaton and Ripple CTO, David Schwartz, have disclosed that unsealing William Hinman’s emails is inevitable, even if the SEC settles with Ripple.
 
The revelation came during a discussion initiated by a known figure within the XRP community and a crypto detective Mr. Huber.
 
Deaton and Schwartz both echoed the opinion that the authority to keep the emails confidential does not lie with Ripple. This is because Judge Analisa Torres had previously ruled that the emails and drafts from the former director of SEC’s Corporation Finance, Hinman, are judicial documents.
 
They stated that the public’s right to access these documents outweighs any potential settlement between Ripple and the SEC.
 
Ripple CTO And Attorney’s Opinion On Hinman Document
 
Notably, Judge …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Dambel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scientists Develop New Antibiotic To Kill Superbug Using AI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142739</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142739/scientists-develop-new-antibiotic-to-kill-superbug-using-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T16:07:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Machine learning enabled scientists to rapidly screen thousands of molecules to find a new antibacterial compound.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reddit Avatars NFT Collection Amasses 10 Million Holders In Less Than A Year]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7501f95686</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/reddit-nft-collection-10m-holders/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T16:03:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After nearly 11 months since its launch in July 2022, the social platform Reddit is on the verge of surpassing 10 million holders of its collectible avatars, known as “Reddit NFTs.”
 
This milestone represents another remarkable achievement for the NFT collection by Reddit, solidifying its position as one of the largest and most renowned NFT collections in the market.
 
With its widespread recognition and global appeal, Reddit’s NFT collection has garnered substantial acclaim within the NFT community and beyond.  Based on data from Dune Analytics, the current count of Reddit collectible avatar holders stands at approximately 9,909,465 million.
 
 
Among these holders, around 7.7 million are categorized as single collective avatar holders, indicating users who possess only one avatar and do…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>anushsamal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biggest Movers: BNB Hits 20-Day High, as LTC Extends Recent Gains]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7501e452f7</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/biggest-movers-bnb-hits-20-day-high-as-ltc-extends-recent-gains/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Litecoin rose for a sixth consecutive session to start the week, as bullish sentiment returned to cryptocurrency markets. As of writing, the global market cap is up by as much as 2.50%. BNB was also in the green, hitting a 20-day high on Monday.
 
Litecoin (LTC)
 
Litecoin (LTC) was a notable mover on Monday, as the token climbed for a sixth consecutive session.
 
LTC/USD raced to a peak of $92.16 earlier in the day, which comes less than 24 hours after trading at a low of $89.10.
 
This move has led to litecoin climbing to a key resistance level of $93.00, which was last hit on May 23.
 
 
From the chart, the recent rise seems to be a result of the relative strength index (RSI) breaking out of a ceiling at 51.00.
 
The index has since rallied further, hitting a resistance point at 57.00, which has resulted in earlier gains fading.
 
At the time of writing, LTC is trading at $91.38, with price strength at a reading of 56.05.
 
 
BNB
 
BNB, or binance coin, was also in the green to start the week, with prices moving to a multi-week high in the process.
 
Following a bottom at $307.53 on Sunday, BNB/USD rose to an intraday peak of $316.83 earlier today.
 
This surge saw BNB hit its highest level since May 9, when the token was trading above $320.00.
 
 
Overall, BNB is now trading 2% higher than at the same point last week, with today’s rally sending the RSI to its strongest reading since May 1.
 
In addition to this, the 10-day (red) moving average (MA) is also moving towards an upwards crossover with the 25-day (blue) MA.
 
Should this cross take place, there is a good chance that BNB will move towards a long-term ceiling at the $340.00 mark.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
What is the highest point BNB will hit before the month ends? Let us know your thoughts in the comments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Temasek Takes A Hit: FTX Investment Failure Triggers Pay Cuts For Singapore State Fund]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7501e0c527</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ftx-investment-failure-triggers-pay-cuts-state-fund/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T15:04:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Temasek Holdings, a prominent state investor in Singapore, has taken the decision to reduce the compensation of its investment team and senior management following the failed investment in the collapsed FTX cryptocurrency exchange. 
 
This move comes as Temasek aims to uphold collective accountability and address the repercussions of the investment setback. While an internal review found no misconduct by the investment team, the company acknowledges the need for action in the wake of the FTX investment failure.
 
A Costly Investment Misstep
 
Temasek’s plan to cut compensation comes after the state investor dismissed all of its $275 million exposure following the collapse of the FTX crypto exchange late last year. Despite investing $210 million in FTX International and $65 million in FTX U…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unioverse Game Preview: Hands-on With the Cinematic Proving Grounds]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/t68sovuN/unioverse-game-preview-hands-on-with-the-cinematic-proving-grounds</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/t68sovuN/unioverse-game-preview-hands-on-with-the-cinematic-proving-grounds"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Unioverse is a multimedia sci-fi franchise with plans to facilitate user-generated content. Decrypt reporter and GG producer Kate Irwin checked out the Unioverse as Reyu, an alien character, and navigated the Proving Grounds with him. In the Proving Grounds, you'll fight an array of different drone-like flying robots (some have tentacles!!) as you navigate the puzzle-like dystopian environment. Alien meets Portal, anyone?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Venezuelan Petro Blockchain Faces Operational Difficulties, Hundreds of Wallets Allegedly Blocked]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7501e3cb12</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/venezuelan-petro-blockchain-faces-operational-difficulties-hundreds-of-wallets-allegedly-blocked/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T14:39:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The blockchain of the petro, the Venezuelan official cryptocurrency asset, has been facing difficulties, halting on May 24, with block production restarting on May 27 only to stop again on May 28. Asonacrip, a local cryptocurrency association, also reported that hundreds of petro wallets were eliminated or blocked.
Venezuelan Petro Blockchain Halted
The blockchain of the petro, the official Venezuelan cryptocurrency, has allegedly been facing operational problems since last week. Asonacrip, a private association of crypto enthusiasts, issued a statement warning about the issue, stating that the Petro chain had stopped its block generation on May 24, affecting the functionality of the cryptocurrency asset.
In a joint statement with Cryptoland.vzla, a crypto education-focused group, Asonacri…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Square Enix to Ubisoft: The Biggest Publishers Building NFT Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142527</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142527/from-square-enix-to-ubisoft-the-biggest-publishers-building-nft-games"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T14:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The makers of Final Fantasy and Assassin's Creed, respectively, are leading the charge for traditional game publishers building in Web3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Shrimps Continue Aggressive Accumulation As Holdings Hit ATH]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7501e82ad5</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-shrimps-aggressive-accumulation-ath-supply/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T14:05:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data shows the Bitcoin shrimp supply has hit all-time high values as these small investors have continued to aggressively accumulate.
 
Bitcoin Shrimp Supply Has Hit A New All-Time High Value
 
According to data from the on-chain analytics firm Glassnode, the supply held by shrimps has gone up by 24,600 BTC in the past month alone. The “shrimps” here refer to Bitcoin holders that are currently carrying a wallet balance of less than 1 BTC.
 
As these investors are holding such low amounts, they are likely to be retail investors. This means that the “shrimp supply” (which is naturally the total amount of Bitcoin that the combined addresses of such holders are holding at the moment) can provide insight into the behavior of the retail investors.
 
When the shrimp supply trends are up,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hououin Kyouma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bybit Secures Preliminary Approval to Operate in Kazakhstan]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7501e87253</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/bybit-secures-preliminary-approval-to-operate-in-kazakhstan/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T14:03:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bybit, a cryptocurrency derivatives exchange, has been issued an 'in-principle' license by the regulators in Kazakhstan, according to a press release shared  
with Finance Magnates on Monday.
The license, issued by  
Astana Financial Services Authority (AFSA), allows Bybit to run a digital asset trading facility and to offer custody services at the Astana International Financial Centre  
(AIFC), which is a financial hub based in Astana. According to the press release, the  
approval subjects the exchange to pre-conditions that will lead to permanent  
authorization once the full license application process is complete.
''We are delighted to  
receive an in-principle approval from AFSA," Bybit CEO and Co-Founder Ben Zhou said, adding that ''we believe in the promising potential of the Commo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Memorial Day Reflections: Reinvigorating Critical Thought, Bitcoin Can Honor Service Members]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7501e92ef9</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/bitcoin-and-memorial-day"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T13:58:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is an opinion editorial by Mickey Koss, a West Point graduate with a degree in economics. He spent four years in the infantry before transitioning to the Finance Corps.

“That was before my time… Of course it’s true, everybody knows it’s true.”

The quote above is from the movie “The Sea Beast.” And although the film never mentions Bitcoin specifically, it might just be one of the best Bitcoin movies I’ve ever seen. 
 
         
         
         
        Source 
    
It is set in a fictional world gripped by perpetual war between a sea-faring economic power and a population of monsters who appear to attack ships out of nowhere. The hunters, the heroes of the story, patrol the seas in a near-constant state of combat, fighting to keep trade routes open and safe. In exchange, they are …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mickey Koss</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Technical Analysis: BTC Above $28,000 as Biden Announces Debt Ceiling Deal]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7501d4ac9a</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-ethereum-technical-analysis-btc-above-28000-as-biden-announces-debt-ceiling-deal/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T13:30:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin climbed above the $28,000 level on Monday, as U.S. President Joe Biden confirmed that a deal was agreed in principle. Biden labeled the agreement a “compromise,” with Republican Kevin McCarthy calling it “historic.” Ethereum was also higher on the news, hitting a three-week peak.
 
Bitcoin
 

 
Bitcoin (BTC) rose above the $28,000 to start the week, as crypto markets reacted to an apparent agreement to increase the U.S. debt ceiling.
 

 
Following a low of $27,125.53 on Sunday, BTC/USD raced to a peak of $28,432.04 earlier in today’s session.
 

 
As a result of today’s rally, bitcoin moved to its highest point since May 8, when price reached a high of $28,676.
 

 
Bitcoin chart by TradingView
 

 

 

 

 

 

 

 

 

 
Overall, it appears that the latest move took place once the relative strength index (RSI) broke out of a ceiling at 53.00.
 

 
Price strength has since climbed, and the index is currently tracking at 54.92, with the next point of resistance at 57.00.
 

 
Should this momentum continue to increase, there is a good chance that BTC will move above the $29,000 mark.
 

 

 
Ethereum
 

 
In addition to BTC, ethereum (ETH) also moved higher on Monday, climbing above the $1,900 level.
 

 
ETH/USD jumped to an intraday high of $1,926.42 earlier in the day, following a low of $1,839.13 the day prior.
 

 
This surge led to the world’s second largest cryptocurrency hitting a three-week high in the process.
 

 
Ethereum chart by TradingView
 

 

 

 

 

 

 

 

 

 
Looking at the chart, today’s surge came as the 10-day (red) moving average crossed over its 25-day (blue) counterpart.
 

 
If this trend continues, there is a strong chance that ethereum could move closer to $2,000 in the upcoming week.
 

 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 

 
Do you expect ETH to move above $2,000 this week? Leave your thoughts in the comments below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Chart Pattern Suggests Volatility Explosion Ahead]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7501d6c89e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/05/29/dogecoin-chart-pattern-suggests-volatility-explosion-ahead/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T13:14:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A technical analysis indicator called Bollinger bandwidth suggests dogecoin's unusual calm could soon end with a pronounced move in either direction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Eyes New Heights Amid Sentiment Boost Over US Debt Ceiling Deal]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7501d7eeb1</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-eyes-new-heights/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T13:06:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum is reaching new heights along with other cryptocurrencies, pulling the entire market in an upward swing. According to Coingecko, the market itself grew over a percent in the past 24 hours. The prime altcoin itself is up 5.5% since last week. 
 
This sudden swing in price can be attributed to recent on-chain and macro developments that emboldened the bulls in the broader financial market. 
 
 
Ethereum followed the stock market higher as US politicians broke their impasse over the federal government’s debt ceiling.
 
United States President Joe Biden and Republican Congressman Kevin McCarthy reached a tentative deal to suspend the $31.4 trillion debt of the US government. This came after a few months of tense back and forth deliberations between the Democrats and Republicans. 
 
US…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Debt Ceiling Deal Blocks 30% Bitcoin Mining Tax: Congressman]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142711</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142711/us-debt-ceiling-deal-blocks-30-bitcoin-mining-tax-congressman"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T11:01:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The proposed Digital Asset Mining Energy tax has reportedly been taken off the table, according to U.S. Congressman Warren Davidson.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bali Tells Tourists: Don’t Pay With Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142720</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142720/bali-tells-tourists-dont-pay-with-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T10:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Local authorities have warned that tourists who attempt to use crypto as a means of payment will be "dealt with firmly."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alys Key</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Touches $28,000 as U.S. Debt Ceiling Deal Heads to Congress]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142712</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142712/bitcoin-touches-28000-as-u-s-debt-ceiling-deal-heads-to-congress"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T10:14:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stock market indices rose to new yearly highs, while cryptocurrencies saw positive gains as risk-on sentiments returned.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Americans May Not Love Crypto, But These Top Brands Are Into It]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142698</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142698/americans-may-not-love-crypto-but-these-top-brands-are-into-it"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T04:28:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chick-Fil-A, Toyota, Pfizer and Samsung are among the Top 100 brands to explore the cryptocurrency space.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin and Ethereum Rise as U.S. Lawmakers Scramble to Dodge Historic Debt Default]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142689</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142689/bitcoin-ethereum-rise-avoid-debt-ceiling-default"/>
        <updated>2023-05-28T22:47:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The potential compromise comes as America’s “X-date” approaches quickly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 May Flip ‘Content Consumption on its Head,’ but Still Needs Traditional Media: MyCo Co-Founder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142687</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142687/web3-may-flip-content-consumption-on-its-head-but-still-needs-traditional-media-myco-co-founder"/>
        <updated>2023-05-28T20:57:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The streaming platform’s content lead said Web3 is still far from mainstream—and yields a unique opportunity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week on Crypto Twitter: Shaq Served with Two Crypto Lawsuits on Same Day]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142671</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142671/this-week-on-crypto-twitter-shaq-served-two-crypto-lawsuits-fake-ai-news"/>
        <updated>2023-05-28T19:44:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some viral fake news in the form of an AI-generated explosion at the Pentagon briefly tanked Bitcoin’s price on Monday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Earn Bitcoin by Playing Mobile Solitaire Games—Here's How Much]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142635</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142635/you-can-earn-bitcoin-by-playing-mobile-solitaire-games-heres-how-much"/>
        <updated>2023-05-27T22:10:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[REVIEW: These iPhone and Android solitaire games reward you with real Bitcoin. We picked the best of the bunch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Bitcoin and Ethereum See Fourth Flat Week as TRON and Tether Surge]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142627</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142627/this-week-in-coins-bitcoin-ethereum-fourth-flat-week-tron-tether-surge"/>
        <updated>2023-05-27T18:51:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Republican presidential hopeful Ron DeSantis touched on cryptocurrencies in his Twitter Space with Elon Musk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Social Tokens Finally Click? Stealcam Is Betting on It]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142543</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142543/will-social-tokens-finally-click-stealcam-friendtech"/>
        <updated>2023-05-27T13:22:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Steal to reveal" platform Stealcam is rebranding and shifting gears. Can Friend.tech finally crack the social token model for creators?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When DAOs Self-Execute—What Could Go Wrong?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142499</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142499/when-daos-self-execute-what-could-go-wrong"/>
        <updated>2023-05-27T12:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Self-executing DAO proposals are the pinnacle of autonomy for decentralized communities. Still, the feature comes with a lot of baggage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former EverQuest Lead: Games Must Be Co-Created With Players]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142554</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142554/former-everquest-lead-games-must-co-created-players"/>
        <updated>2023-05-26T22:14:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avalon's Jeffrey Butler says that the future of gaming, including the metaverse, will require players to co-create and be rewarded for it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not Just Nvidia: These Are the Other Big Winners in the AI Chip Biz]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142568</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142568/nvidia-big-winners-ai-chip-biz-tech-stocks"/>
        <updated>2023-05-26T21:44:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[COVID-19 was hell for tech stock and chip manufacturers. But AI has now flipped the script. Here are the companies benefiting the most so far.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JP Morgan Files Patent for ChatGPT Finance Clone, IndexGPT]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142577</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142577/jp-morgan-files-patent-for-chatgpt-finance-clone-indexgpt"/>
        <updated>2023-05-26T21:04:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bot would give financial advice on securities, investments, and monetary affairs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EverQuest Producer Jeffrey Butler on How Ready Player One Led Him to Web3 Project Avalon]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/fdmq9t7l/everquest-producer-jeffrey-butler-on-how-ready-player-one-led-him-to-web3-project-avalon</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/fdmq9t7l/everquest-producer-jeffrey-butler-on-how-ready-player-one-led-him-to-web3-project-avalon"/>
        <updated>2023-05-26T21:02:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jeffrey Butler started his game development career producing EverQuest. Now, he's Avalon's Chief Product Officer. Butler told Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how he wants to create a customizable world where users can create their own worlds and in-game content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There's Now a Dollar-Backed Stablecoin on Bitcoin Using Ordinals Protocol]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142548</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142548/usd-backed-stablecoin-on-bitcoin-using-ordinals-protocol"/>
        <updated>2023-05-26T20:16:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stably debuted Stably USD in 2019. It's got a $7 million market capitalization across 11 blockchains, according to its April attestation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grand Theft Auto 6 Crypto Rumors Are Swirling Again—Here’s What’s Going On]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142533</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142533/grand-theft-auto-6-crypto-rumors-swirling-again-heres-whats-going-on"/>
        <updated>2023-05-26T18:07:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rumors suggest that Rockstar Games' anticipated Grand Theft Auto 6 will feature cryptocurrency. Is there any truth to the claims?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Esports Orgs Should Become More Like Tech Companies: Community Gaming CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/t27ac1ik/esports-orgs-should-become-more-like-tech-companies-community-gaming-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/t27ac1ik/esports-orgs-should-become-more-like-tech-companies-community-gaming-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-05-26T16:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Community Gaming CEO and 3XP conference organizer Chris Gonsalves believes crypto and tech could rejuvenate and reinvent the esports industry. In an interview, he tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin why he thinks esports organizations should shake up their approach.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[European Securities Regulator Raises Concerns Over Crypto Products Ahead of MiCA Rollout]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142518</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142518/esma-raises-concerns-unregulated-crypto-products-mica-rollout"/>
        <updated>2023-05-26T13:44:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite the adoption of MiCA, ESMA said today firms must still label crypto offerings as unregulated until the framework is implemented.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Expects to Launch New Thai Crypto Exchange in Q4 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142511</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142511/binance-expectslaunch-new-thai-crypto-exchange-q4-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-05-26T13:21:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After landing a crypto operator's license in Thailand today, Binance Gulf is expected to open its doors at the end of this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum, Bitcoin Balances on Exchanges Edges Toward 5-Year Low]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142507</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142507/ethereum-bitcoin-balances-exchanges-edges-5-year-lows"/>
        <updated>2023-05-26T13:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The collapse of FTX, the rise in self-custody interest, and Ethereum’s latest upgrade appear to be fueling the latest exchange exodus.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Exchange Gemini Turns to Ireland for European Headquarters]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142500</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142500/crypto-exchange-gemini-turns-ireland-european-headquarters"/>
        <updated>2023-05-26T09:58:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amid increasing regulatory pressure in the U.S., the Winklevoss twins see the Emerald Isle as an “entry point” into the rest of Europe.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Hold Ground as $3.5 Billion in Options Expire]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142493</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142493/bitcoin-ethereum-hold-ground-3-5b-options-expiry-event"/>
        <updated>2023-05-26T09:17:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With billions in Bitcoin and Ethereum options expiring today, analysts expected the worst.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's the Environmental Impact of Generative AI Tools?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142483</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142483/whats-environmental-impact-generative-ai-tools"/>
        <updated>2023-05-26T02:36:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Will ChatGPT and other generative AI tools make an outsized impact on the planet? Maybe—but there's reason for optimism, too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ordinals Is Drawing Former Ethereum Devs to Build on Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142439</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142439/ordinals-draws-ethereum-devs-to-build-on-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-05-26T01:19:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The buzzy Bitcoin protocol is attracting talent from across the Web3 ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ubisoft's Rabbids Invade Reddit as Free NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142438</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142438/ubisoft-rabbids-invade-reddit-free-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T23:40:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reddit released a limited quantity of free Rabbids avatar NFTs and users are scooping them up, with multiple varieties already depleted.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mojo Melee Game Preview: Hands-on With the Casual Web3 Auto Battler]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LtI7u3W0/mojo-melee-game-preview-hands-on-with-the-casual-web3-auto-battler</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LtI7u3W0/mojo-melee-game-preview-hands-on-with-the-casual-web3-auto-battler"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T23:02:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mojo Melee is an auto battler game that offers Polygon NFTs. Decrypt contributor Ryan S. Gladwin playtested the game in beta and offers his thoughts on the gameplay experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No Virginia, Ron DeSantis's Campaign Didn't Alter His Video With AI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142455</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142455/no-virginia-ron-desantiss-campaign-didnt-alter-his-video-with-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T22:56:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[They used good old-fashioned digital editing tools instead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mojo Melee Puts a Casual Spin on Teamfight Tactics-Style Auto Battlers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142432</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142432/mojo-melee-puts-casual-spin-teamfight-tactics-style-auto-battlers"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T22:46:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PREVIEW: The NFT-infused Mojo Melee is simple in its beta state, but that makes it a good introduction to a complex genre.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Governments Need to 'Move Faster' on AI Rules, Says Microsoft President]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142430</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142430/governments-need-move-faster-ai-rules-says-microsoft-president"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T21:37:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft President Brad Smith is the latest tech leader to call for government AI regulation, but says companies have a role too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Panic Over $1.5 Billion DeFi Bridge Multichain Shifts to Fantom]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142421</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142421/panic-over-1-5-billion-defi-bridge-multichain-shifts-to-fantom"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T20:28:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Multichain has issued 35% of Fantom's assets, including 80% of its total stablecoin market cap, according to research firm Thanefield Capital.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Happens to Bitcoin and Ethereum If the US Defaults on Its Debt?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142413</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142413/bitcoin-ethereum-if-us-defaults-on-debt"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T19:57:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. has never defaulted before. Interestingly, Bitcoin and Ethereum have seen more losses than stocks after a warning from Janet Yellen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Passing Fad? Bitcoin Ordinals Inscriptions Just Hit a New Milestone]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142415</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142415/passing-fad-bitcoin-ordinals-inscriptions-hit-new-milestone"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T19:20:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The number of Bitcoin Ordinals—which includes NFTs and meme tokens—continues to surge, with supporters calling it a catalyst for adoption.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roman Coppola: ‘A New Tarantino or Kubrick’ Could Come From Web3 Film World]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142399</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142399/roman-coppola-new-tarantino-kubrick-could-come-web3-film-world"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T19:01:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coppola’s Web3 fund Decentralized Pictures aims to democratize the filmmaking process, fostering an inclusive platform for fresh talent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Lose Steam Amid Ledger Controversy and US Market Uncertainty]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142397</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142397/bitcoin-ethereum-lose-steam-gaming-tokens-rndr-sand-gain"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T17:23:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gaming tokens RNDR and SAND have seen impressive gains in the past day. Meanwhile, meme coin PEPE has lost 11% in the past week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Government Sanctions on Tornado Cash Don't Fit The Law: Coinbase Legal Officer]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142360</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142360/government-sanctions-tornado-cash-dont-fit-law-coinbase-chief-legal-officer"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T15:12:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase's Chief Legal Officer argues that the government's reasoning for sanctioning the Ethereum mixer is dangerously flawed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3XP Gaming Expo Showcases Upcoming Web3 Titles]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=142361</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/142361/3xp-gaming-expo-showcases-upcoming-web3-titles"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T13:01:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dozens of upcoming Web3 titles are joining gamers, developers and Twitch streamers at the upcoming gaming event.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How 3XP Plans to Reshape Crypto's Reputation Among Gamers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/dJRkJI2l/how-3xp-plans-to-reshape-cryptos-reputation-among-gamers</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/dJRkJI2l/how-3xp-plans-to-reshape-cryptos-reputation-among-gamers"/>
        <updated>2023-05-24T14:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Community Gaming CEO and 3XP organizer Chris Gonsalves tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the first 3XP video game conference, which aims to bring together fans of crypto-enabled video games, influencers, game developers, blockchain firms, and gamers under one roof in Pasadena, California from June 8-9, 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mark Otero Shares Why a16z Invested in Azra Games' Approach to Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/auPCxWfY/mark-otero-shares-why-a16z-invested-in-azra-games-approach-to-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/auPCxWfY/mark-otero-shares-why-a16z-invested-in-azra-games-approach-to-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-05-23T17:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is Azra Games' approach to NFTs in gaming? Azra Games CEO Mark Otero shares his vision and why he believes his approach was a key reason Azra received investment from venture capital firms like Andreessen Horowitz (a16z).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Funding Web3 Film Calladita With Traditional Systems 'Wasn't Working', Says Director Miguel Faus]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yJ4pf6MZ/funding-web3-film-calladita-with-traditional-systems-wasnt-working-says-director-miguel-faus</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yJ4pf6MZ/funding-web3-film-calladita-with-traditional-systems-wasnt-working-says-director-miguel-faus"/>
        <updated>2023-05-23T17:35:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spanish Film Director Miguel Faus talks with Decrypt about how he financed his movie “Calladita” with NFTs. In his view, Web3 and blockchain allow creators to get around some of the key difficulties present in the traditional movie industry, specifically finding funding.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Web3 Offers Something Hollywood Does Not': Film3 Pioneer, Filmmaker Jordan Bayne]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JBxcmUQf/web3-offers-something-hollywood-does-not-film3-pioneer-filmmaker-jordan-bayne</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JBxcmUQf/web3-offers-something-hollywood-does-not-film3-pioneer-filmmaker-jordan-bayne"/>
        <updated>2023-05-23T16:57:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Film3 pioneer, Metacannes and The Squad founder, Jordan Bayne discusses the advantages that crypto offers to filmmakers, notably owning their work's IP throughout the entire creation, production, and distribution processes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Film3 Offers 'a Whole Bunch of Independent Filmmakers' Hope, Says First Flights Co-founder Nick Sadler]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/NfeY8QGu/film3-offers-a-whole-bunch-of-independent-filmmakers-hope-says-first-flights-co-founder-nick-sadler</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/NfeY8QGu/film3-offers-a-whole-bunch-of-independent-filmmakers-hope-says-first-flights-co-founder-nick-sadler"/>
        <updated>2023-05-23T16:56:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[First Flights co-founder Nick Sadler sat down with Decrypt at this year's MetaCannes festival to discuss how Web3 can support independent filmmakers by leveraging its unique blockchain-powered crowdfunding platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Film3 Movement 'Doesn't Need Competitors, it Needs Collaborators': Bingeable CEO, Founder Stephen Murray]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/nv8Knuvw/the-film3-movement-doesnt-need-competitors-it-needs-collaborators-bingeable-ceo-founder-stephen-murray</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/nv8Knuvw/the-film3-movement-doesnt-need-competitors-it-needs-collaborators-bingeable-ceo-founder-stephen-murray"/>
        <updated>2023-05-23T16:52:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Founder and CEO of Bingeable Stephen Murray unpacks how creators and filmmakers can lower the barriers for audiences to connect with their work. "Within two clicks on hearing about the movie, you're watching it," he told Decrypt at this year's MetaCannes festival.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt Learn: Defining The Web3 Stack]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/33Mc05zz/decrypt-learn-defining-the-web3-stack</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/33Mc05zz/decrypt-learn-defining-the-web3-stack"/>
        <updated>2023-05-23T12:55:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this video, part of Infura’s Web3 Dev Series, you’ll learn how to define the web3 stack in order to build full stack decentralized applications. Author: Clarissa Watson, Senior Writer at ConsenSys.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Web3 Creates a Tighter Bond' Between Audiences, Creators: MyCo CCO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OthLPXDN/web3-creates-a-tighter-bond-between-audiences-creators-myco-cco</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OthLPXDN/web3-creates-a-tighter-bond-between-audiences-creators-myco-cco"/>
        <updated>2023-05-23T08:07:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MyCo’s streaming platform CCO Phil McKenzie talks with Decrypt about the Film3 movement and the Metacannes festival he helped to organize occurring alongside the Festival de Cannes. He explains how Web3 can help creators to find funding and create new ways to interact with the audience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Immutable's Chris Clay: Crypto Can Solve the 'Dreaded Rollback' in MMORPGs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Dg9am6Ro/immutables-chris-clay-crypto-can-solve-the-dreaded-rollback-in-mmorpgs</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Dg9am6Ro/immutables-chris-clay-crypto-can-solve-the-dreaded-rollback-in-mmorpgs"/>
        <updated>2023-05-22T15:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Immutable VP and Gods Unchained Game Director Chris Clay tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about how Immutable is actually immutable—and how that changes everything for both developers and players.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gary Vee Discusses the Rise and Impact of AI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/E2erJr3t/gary-vee-discusses-the-rise-and-impact-of-ai</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/E2erJr3t/gary-vee-discusses-the-rise-and-impact-of-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-05-20T16:46:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During VeeCon 2023, entrepreneur spoke with Decrypt's Andrew Hayward about the rise of AI tools, what excites him about the technology, and what kind of impact he thinks it will have on creators and business.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gary Vee Discusses VeeCon 2023's Broader Shift Beyond Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/FqIm7PfV/gary-vee-discusses-veecon-2023s-broader-shift-beyond-web3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/FqIm7PfV/gary-vee-discusses-veecon-2023s-broader-shift-beyond-web3"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T20:25:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VeeCon is back in 2023, moving from Minneapolis to Indianapolis, and creator and entrepreneur Gary Vaynerchuk joined Decrypt's Andrew Hayward to discuss his aim to make it the "coolest business conference in the world." And that means expanding the focus beyond NFTs and Web3 to include AI and other tech innovations, along with broader business and pop culture content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gary Vee on the NFT Market and Why 'NFTs Are Stuffed Animals']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Sij5GHus/gary-vee-on-the-nft-market-and-why-nfts-are-stuffed-animals</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Sij5GHus/gary-vee-on-the-nft-market-and-why-nfts-are-stuffed-animals"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T20:25:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gary Vaynerchuk called the NFT market decline back in 2021, but the owner of CryptoPunks and other valuable tokenized assets still believes that a sustainable market will eventually form. He joins Decrypt's Andrew Hayward amid VeeCon 2023 to discuss why he thinks the NFT space will be comparable to collectible sports cards, art, and even stuffed animals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Immutable's Chris Clay Learned in 23 Years of Game Development]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/lpOWjBfU/what-immutables-chris-clay-learned-in-23-years-of-game-development</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/lpOWjBfU/what-immutables-chris-clay-learned-in-23-years-of-game-development"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T20:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Immutable VP & Gods Unchained Game Director Chris Clay tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about what it's like to work in the game industry for decades and why he's not giving up on NFT games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Azra Games CEO Mark Otero is Not a Fan of "Play-to-Earn" Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/F08xddFc/why-azra-games-ceo-mark-otero-is-not-a-fan-of-play-to-earn-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/F08xddFc/why-azra-games-ceo-mark-otero-is-not-a-fan-of-play-to-earn-games"/>
        <updated>2023-05-18T16:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Each game is a miracle," says Azra Games CEO Mark Otero. In this clip, he shares his thoughts on "play-to-earn" games and gamer motivation with Decrypt's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Many Games Are Building On Solana? The Answer Might Surprise You]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/WV6HegEv/how-many-games-are-building-on-solana-the-answer-might-surprise-you</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/WV6HegEv/how-many-games-are-building-on-solana-the-answer-might-surprise-you"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T16:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Games General Manager Johnny Lee tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the current state of Solana's Web3 gaming ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Problems With Being an 'On-Chain Purist'  in Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/uOwArY6a/problems-with-being-an-on-chain-purist-in-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/uOwArY6a/problems-with-being-an-on-chain-purist-in-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T15:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[InfiniGods Cofounders Owen O'Donoghue and Damon Gura keep it real with Decrypt's Kate Irwin, sharing thoughts on game balancing and what to do when in-game assets become NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>