<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-08-02T12:29:32.204Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-08-02T12:29:32.204Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance U.S. Faced Potential Closure, CEO Weighed Options Amid Regulatory Turmoil]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755a6b3220</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-binance-us-faced-closure-ceo-weighed-options/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T12:23:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Per a recent report from The Information, the CEO of crypto exchange Binance, Changpeng “CZ” Zhao, considered closing its U.S. subsidiary. The possibility was reflected due to the increasing hostilities from regulators against Zhao and the trading venue in the country.  
 
 
A U.S. Company No More? Binance CEO Reviews Options
 
According to the report, Zhao thought about leaving the U.S. in early 2023 in a potential move to “protect” the international arm. However, Brian Shroder, current CEO of Binance.US, allegedly opposed the decision to safeguard the platform’s customers.
 
In the past two years, the crypto space saw the bankruptcy of major companies, including FTX, Celsius, and others. In that sense, crypto investors and the nascent industry’s reputation were negatively impacted; closi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reynaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Litecoin Halving Happening In 4 Hours: Buy Or Sell Signal?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755a6b3216</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/litecoin-halving-happening-in-4-hours/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T12:23:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Litecoin (LTC) halving is now here and the event is currently the most-watched among crypto investors. In addition to the anticipation of the cut in rate of supply, there are also speculations around the digital asset and what the current halving could mean for it.
 
Is It Time To Buy Or Sell LTC?
 
The question of whether buying or selling Litecoin (LTC) leading up to and following the halving event is a good idea remains on the minds of investors even with just a couple of hours to go. As such, taking a looking at the historical performance around this event could help to determine the best course of action.
 
 
The last Litecoin halving event actually saw the price of LTC rise leading up to the event. And like the halving before it, the price of LTC took a big hit not too long after…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Best Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Show Your Face to the Orb': Eyes-on With Sam Altman's Worldcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150961</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150961/show-your-face-to-the-orb-eyes-on-with-sam-altmans-worldcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T12:22:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In former East Berlin, Sam Altman’s Worldcoin is scanning irises for tokens—under the watchful eye of European privacy watchdogs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ApeCoin and BAYC Values Drop Following Otherside Metaverse Test]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18812422/ApeCoin-and-BAYC-Values-Drop-Following-Otherside-Metaverse-Test</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18812422/ApeCoin-and-BAYC-Values-Drop-Following-Otherside-Metaverse-Test"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T12:16:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data from CoinMarketCap, the leading cryptocurrency aggregation platform, shows that ApeCoin (APE) dropped to its lowest price this year on Tuesday, August 1, 2023. The price drop followed an exclusive event when 40 BAYC owners and superfans saw new areas of Yuga Labs’ virtual world and saw...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin finds no respite as Kenya suspends it over privacy concerns]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18812416/Worldcoin-finds-no-respite-as-Kenya-suspends-it-over-privacy-concerns</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18812416/Worldcoin-finds-no-respite-as-Kenya-suspends-it-over-privacy-concerns"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T12:15:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before Worldcoin officially launched, users from Kenya registered in droves. But a new government decision may affect the project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin Faces Another Hurdle as Kenya Suspends Eyeball Scans]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18812390/Worldcoin-Faces-Another-Hurdle-as-Kenya-Suspends-Eyeball-Scans</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18812390/Worldcoin-Faces-Another-Hurdle-as-Kenya-Suspends-Eyeball-Scans"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T12:08:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kenya has suspended Worldcoin's activities in the country citing data protection concerns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance U.S. Faced Potential Closure, CEO Weighed Options Amid Regulatory Turmoil]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18812376/Binance-US-Faced-Potential-Closure-CEO-Weighed-Options-Amid-Regulatory-Turmoil</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18812376/Binance-US-Faced-Potential-Closure-CEO-Weighed-Options-Amid-Regulatory-Turmoil"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T12:04:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Per a recent report from The Information, the CEO of crypto exchange Binance, Changpeng “CZ” Zhao, considered closing its U.S. subsidiary. The possibility was reflected due to the increasing hostilities from regulators against Zhao and the trading venue in the country. Related Reading: Ripple...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Analysts Optimistic Ahead of Q2 Earnings, but Warn About USDC Risks and Lower Trading Volumes]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18812417/Coinbase-Analysts-Optimistic-Ahead-of-Q2-Earnings-but-Warn-About-USDC-Risks-and-Lower-Trading-Volumes</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18812417/Coinbase-Analysts-Optimistic-Ahead-of-Q2-Earnings-but-Warn-About-USDC-Risks-and-Lower-Trading-Volumes"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoiners Must Appeal To America’s Increasingly-Independent Voters]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18812340/Bitcoiners-Must-Appeal-To-Americas-Increasingly-Independent-Voters</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18812340/Bitcoiners-Must-Appeal-To-Americas-Increasingly-Independent-Voters"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoiners Must Appeal To America’s Increasingly-Independent Voters]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755a564acb</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/bitcoin-needs-the-support-of-political-independents"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T11:59:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is an opinion editorial by Robert Hall, a content creator and small business owner.
The United States has two major political parties: the Democratic Party and the Republican Party. These parties are basically diametrically opposed to the other. As of late, both sides have drifted to the extreme edges of the political spectrum to a point where they can’t agree on a basic set of facts about America. Both parties essentially live in two different worlds and can hardly speak to one another. This is what political polarization looks like.
This polarization has resulted in serious problems for the country. For many of us, nothing ever seems to change from administration to administration. I wonder if anyone can anyone honestly say with a straight face that things haven’t ultimately stayed …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Hall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A New Bitcoin-Based Arcade Game Is Leaving a Mark on Gamers]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755a569775</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/08/02/a-new-bitcoin-based-arcade-game-is-leaving-a-mark-on-gamers/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T11:57:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A platform that went live last week looks to expand bitcoin usage by attracting players to win-to-earn games that run wholly on the Bitcoin blockchain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BALD Deployer Signals the Next Target, SushiSwap; Sushi Price Surges]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18812359/BALD-Deployer-Signals-the-Next-Target-SushiSwap-Sushi-Price-Surges</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18812359/BALD-Deployer-Signals-the-Next-Target-SushiSwap-Sushi-Price-Surges"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T11:54:15.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Litecoin Halving Happening In 4 Hours: Buy Or Sell Signal?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18812341/Litecoin-Halving-Happening-In-4-Hours-Buy-Or-Sell-Signal</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18812341/Litecoin-Halving-Happening-In-4-Hours-Buy-Or-Sell-Signal"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T11:52:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Litecoin (LTC) halving is now here and the event is currently the most-watched among crypto investors. In addition to the anticipation of the cut in rate of supply, there are also speculations around the digital asset and what the current halving could mean for it. Is It Time To Buy Or Sell...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A New Season of Reason Means Treason, ep 335 The Breakup @bitcoinmagazine]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18812375/A-New-Season-of-Reason-Means-Treason-ep-335-The-Breakup-bitcoinmagazine</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18812375/A-New-Season-of-Reason-Means-Treason-ep-335-The-Breakup-bitcoinmagazine"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T11:51:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[- @JonathanTurley on Trump indictment- @VivekGRamaswamy on the reason- @greg_price11 on the season- @RobertKennedyJr on the treason]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HODL LAW’s Legal Battle Over Ethereum’s Status Hits Procedural Roadblock]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18812339/HODL-LAWs-Legal-Battle-Over-Ethereums-Status-Hits-Procedural-Roadblock</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18812339/HODL-LAWs-Legal-Battle-Over-Ethereums-Status-Hits-Procedural-Roadblock"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T11:49:20.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Perfect Setup? Don’t Count on a Bitcoin Crash Back to $23,000, Says Glassnode Co-Founder – Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18812336/The-Perfect-Setup-Dont-Count-on-a-Bitcoin-Crash-Back-to-23000-Says-Glassnode-Co-Founder-Heres-Why</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18812336/The-Perfect-Setup-Dont-Count-on-a-Bitcoin-Crash-Back-to-23000-Says-Glassnode-Co-Founder-Heres-Why"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T11:45:46.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Obtains Dubai License to Provide Crypto Exchange Services]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755a51446f</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/binance-obtains-dubai-license-to-provide-crypto-exchange-services/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T11:36:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The world’s largest cryptocurrency exchange, Binance, has received a license to operate in Dubai as a regulated platform. The authorization will allow the crypto giant to offer exchange and other services for virtual assets to institutional and qualified retail investors. 
 
Dubai Virtual Assets Regulatory Authority Grants Binance MVP License
 
Crypto exchange Binance announced Monday that its Dubai subsidiary, Binance FZE, has been issued with an Operational Minimum Viable Product (MVP) license by Dubai’s Virtual Assets Regulatory Authority (VARA).
 
The license enables the platform to provide regulated services in and from Dubai such as exchange and broker-dealer services for crypto assets, initially limited to institutional and qualified retail investors, the company explained.
 
In a b…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lubomir Tassev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum outperforming Bitcoin as network growth hits 2-week high]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18812318/Ethereum-outperforming-Bitcoin-as-network-growth-hits-2-week-high</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18812318/Ethereum-outperforming-Bitcoin-as-network-growth-hits-2-week-high"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T11:35:53.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase to Explore Adding Bitcoin Lightning Network for Global Crypto Payments]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18812312/Coinbase-to-Explore-Adding-Bitcoin-Lightning-Network-for-Global-Crypto-Payments</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18812312/Coinbase-to-Explore-Adding-Bitcoin-Lightning-Network-for-Global-Crypto-Payments"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T11:33:07.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mixed signals: Binance denies reports of $90B in crypto trades in China]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18812310/Mixed-signals-Binance-denies-reports-of-90B-in-crypto-trades-in-China</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18812310/Mixed-signals-Binance-denies-reports-of-90B-in-crypto-trades-in-China"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T11:31:42.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong-based Cryptocurrency Company Is Also Registered In This European Country After Italy!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18812292/Hong-Kong-based-Cryptocurrency-Company-Is-Also-Registered-In-This-European-Country-After-Italy</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18812292/Hong-Kong-based-Cryptocurrency-Company-Is-Also-Registered-In-This-European-Country-After-Italy"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T11:31:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Custody Hex Trust has made a significant progress in its expansion plans in Europe by being registered in this country after Italy. Continue Reading: Hong Kong-based Cryptocurrency Company Is Also Registered In This European Country After Italy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin suspended in Kenya as Europe probes crypto project]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18812285/Worldcoin-suspended-in-Kenya-as-Europe-probes-crypto-project</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18812285/Worldcoin-suspended-in-Kenya-as-Europe-probes-crypto-project"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T11:30:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin has been eyed by watchdogs across Europe since launching last week... now, its key market Kenya has it in its cross hairs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum ETF Frenzy Sweeps SEC Following Bitcoin ETF Hype]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18812276/Ethereum-ETF-Frenzy-Sweeps-SEC-Following-Bitcoin-ETF-Hype</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18812276/Ethereum-ETF-Frenzy-Sweeps-SEC-Following-Bitcoin-ETF-Hype"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T11:30:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinspeaker Ethereum ETF Frenzy Sweeps SEC Following Bitcoin ETF Hype The rush to launch Ethereum spot ETFs has sparked interest in the crypto community. Ethereum ETF Frenzy Sweeps SEC Following Bitcoin ETF Hype]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Considers Integrating Bitcoin’s Lightning Network for Payments]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755a522f5c</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/coinbase-considers-integrating-bitcoins-lightning-network-for-payments/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T11:30:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase plans to integrate Bitcoin's Lightning Network to facilitate faster cryptocurrency payments. According to a comment by the exchange's CEO Brian Armstrong, Coinbase supports the efforts to facilitate payments on Bitcoin through the Lightning Network.
Armstrong was responding to a tweet by Jack Dorsey, the Co-Founder and former CEO of Twitter, who criticized the exchange for allegedly ignoring Bitcoin and Lightning Network. Lightning is a layer-2 payment platform on top of the Bitcoin network, intended to facilitate faster transactions.
"We are looking  
into how to best add Lightning. It is non-trivial, but I think it is worth  
doing," Armstrong said." I am all for payments taking off in  
Bitcoin." He added that the US-based cryptocurrency exchange had onboarded  
more users to B…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Curve breach: Fear of liquidation stirs further FUD]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18812308/Curve-breach-Fear-of-liquidation-stirs-further-FUD</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18812308/Curve-breach-Fear-of-liquidation-stirs-further-FUD"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T11:30:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Curve Finance is beginning to witness some improvements as Curve's founder avoids litigation. CRV's price has recovered, however the number of token holders continues to decline.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi and Fun Element Can Boost Gaming, says Billion-Dollar Crypto VC]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18812300/DeFi-and-Fun-Element-Can-Boost-Gaming-says-Billion-Dollar-Crypto-VC</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18812300/DeFi-and-Fun-Element-Can-Boost-Gaming-says-Billion-Dollar-Crypto-VC"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Billion-Dollar Crypto VC Suggest A Way to Boost GamingSince Framework Ventures announced at the beginning of 2017 that it has "earmarked" approximately $200 million for blockchain gaming, investment in cryptocurrency-enabled video games but there has been a slowdown. Moreover, according to the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Bard sets its Tezos price prediction for August]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18812245/Google-Bard-sets-its-Tezos-price-prediction-for-August</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18812245/Google-Bard-sets-its-Tezos-price-prediction-for-August"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T11:19:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tezos price has crawled back in the past few weeks even as the crypto fear and greed index remains in the neutral point. The XTZ coin was trading at $0.845, where it has been at in the past few days. This price is about 27% above the lowest level this year. Google Bard’s XTZ forecast […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Litecoin Halving Unlikely to Drive Immediate Price Gains, Past Data Show]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755a53af2c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/08/02/litecoin-halving-unlikely-to-drive-immediate-price-gains-past-data-show/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T11:18:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Litecoin's blockchain will cut the per-block reward to 6.25 LTC from 12.5 LTC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried's Lawyers Say Basis for Revoking Bail Is 'Extremely Thin']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150946</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150946/sam-bankman-frieds-lawyers-say-basis-revoking-bail-is-extremely-thin"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T10:26:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bankman-Fried's defense fights back against the DOJ’s recent motion, saying it's based on “innuendo” and “assumptions.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Sponsorships and Social Impact: How Brands are Making a Difference]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755a44f3fe</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/innovation/crypto-sponsorships-and-social-impact-how-brands-are-making-a-difference/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T10:09:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto  
sector has grown rapidly and attracted substantial attention from mainstream  
audiences. As the sector evolves, brands and businesses are seeing the  
potential of crypto sponsorships to have a significant societal impact. 
These  
sponsorships have the potential to generate positive change and support  
significant initiatives all across the world by leveraging the power of  
blockchain technology and digital assets. In this comprehensive analysis, we  
look at how businesses are leveraging the power of cryptocurrency sponsorships  
to make a difference in a variety of social issues.
The  
Increasing Popularity of Crypto Sponsorships
Crypto  
sponsorships have grown in popularity as cryptocurrencies and blockchain  
technology have grown in popularity. With cryptocurrency us…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FM Contributors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kenya Suspends Worldcoin Operations Amid Privacy Concerns]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150942</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150942/kenya-suspends-worldcoin-operations-privacy-concerns"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T09:41:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin faces further scrutiny over its iris-scanning project, despite over 2 million sign-ups worldwide.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple CLO Stuart Alderoty Explains Securities in ‘After Hours’ Parody Skit]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755a41291e</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ripple-clo-stuart-alderoty-explains-securities-in-after-hours-parody-skit/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T09:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stuart Alderoty, CLO of Ripple, prepared a skit explaining the definition of securities according to the company, supported by the recent ruling in the SEC v. Ripple case. The segment, titled “After Hours,” parodies U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Chair Gary Gensler’s “Office Hours” series of videos, where he briefly explains investment subjects.
Ripple CLO Stuart Alderoty Explains Securities, Investment Contracts, and Digital Currencies in Skit
Stuart Alderoty, CLO of Ripple, a cryptocurrency and financial services company, presented a parody skit titled “After Hours,” where he explained the definitions of securities and investment contracts. The segment was prepared as a parody of the “Office Hours” series of videos, where U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Chair…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Debunks 6 Misconceptions About The XRP Ruling]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755a42fee6</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ripple-debunks-6-misconceptions-about-xrp-ruling/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T09:23:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following the landmark court ruling in Securities & Exchange Commission (SEC) case, Ripple has cleared up some widespread misconceptions regarding the ruling. The company provided a detailed Q2 2023 XRP markets report today, where it underscored the verdict’s implications and presented key statistics about its XRP holdings.
 
On July 13, 2023, a significant milestone was achieved in the crypto industry as the court declared that XRP is not a security. Ripple stressed that the SEC’s previous efforts at “regulation by enforcement” have been shown to be “a strategy of intimidation and misinformation in furtherance of its own quest for political power.”
 
Ripple Clears The Misconceptions
 
1. The decision is not a split one
 
Contrary to some interpretations, Ripple emphasized that the ruling …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Defies China’s Crypto Ban, Records $90B Monthly Trading Volume: Report]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755a43a7b9</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/binance-defies-chinas-crypto-ban-records-90b-monthly-trading-volume-report/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T09:17:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance’s users in China traded more than USD $90 billion in a single  
month despite cryptocurrency trading being illegal in the country, the  
Wall Street Journal reported yesterday (Tuesday), citing the exchange's internal documents and  
former employees.
Crypto Futures Trading
According to the WSJ,  
most of Binance’s trading volumes in China, which accounted for 20% of its global volumes, came from spot and futures trading. According to the media publication,  
Binance had 5.6 million users in China as of May, out of which about 900,000  
were active.
Besides China, South Korea,  
Turkey, and Vietnam are the other biggest markets for Binance, the publication  
added. The WSJ also noted that about 100,000 Binance users in China are  
classified as politically exposed persons (PEPs) or…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Mulling Best Ways to Integrate Lightning Network for Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150938</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150938/coinbase-mulling-best-ways-integrate-lightning-network-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T09:05:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong has reiterated the crypto exchange’s intention to add support for Bitcoin’s Layer-2 scaling solution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aave Should Block Curve Token Borrowing, Risk Management Firm Proposes]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755a4e2688</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/08/02/aave-should-block-curve-token-borrowing-risk-management-firm-proposes/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T08:57:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An ongoing crisis situation stemming from a large curve token collateral can be prevented by pausing all borrowing activity, Gauntlet argued in a Wednesday protocol.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance’s Zhao Pushed to Shutter US Exchange Ahead of Lawsuits]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755a4e3b82</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/binances-zhao-pushed-to-shutter-us-exchange-ahead-of-lawsuits/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T08:56:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance's founder and CEO, Changpeng Zhao, has considered shuttering the US affiliate of the crypto exchange earlier this year to protect the broader global operations, according to a report by The Information. However, Zhao's decision was blocked by Brian Shroder, CEO of Binance.US.  

CZ Tried to Shutter Binance.US   

Though officially not confirmed, the board of directors of the US unit of Binance voted on the proposal to close the company. Though Zhao has no executive role in that US entity, he still sits on the board as the Chair. Binance refused to comment on the report.  

Binance, the largest global crypto exchange in terms of trading volume, launched its US exchange in September 2019 after securing registration from the Financial Crimes Enforcement Network (FinCEN). The purpose o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arnab Shome</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[East Meets West: Hong Kong's Hex Trust Secures French Crypto License]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755a4e3b79</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/east-meets-west-hong-kongs-hex-trust-secures-french-crypto-license/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T08:56:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While buzz  
grows around the Middle East and Hong Kong as emerging crypto hubs, do not  
overlook Europe. Specifically, France is making waves as a potential digital  
asset safe haven. Hex Trust just secured a license to offer digital asset custody  
and trading services.
From Hong Kong to Europe:  
Hex Trust Gets a License in France
The recent  
regulatory turmoil in the cryptocurrency industry has led many firms from the  
US and Europe to start relocating, among other places, to Hong Kong. This time,  
however, a firm from China's special administrative region decided to move to  
Europe, thereby expanding its previous scope of activity.
Hex  
Trading, a digital asset custodian, has just obtained a license from France's  
Autorité des Marchés Financiers (AMF) and Autorité de Contrôle …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Damian Chmiel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Race for Ether Futures ETFs Kicks Off With 6 Firms Filing SEC Applications]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755a493ca9</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/08/02/race-for-ether-futures-etfs-kicks-off-with-6-firms-filing-sec-applications/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T08:31:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As many as six entities have filed applications with the U.S. Securities and Exchange (SEC) for Ethereum Futures exchange-traded funds (ETFs) as of filing time on August 2, 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amitoj Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Voyager 30-Day Withdrawal Period Becomes Breeding Ground For Scammers – Report]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755a4a4417</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/voyager-scammers-exploit-withdrawal-period/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T08:22:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fraudulent actors targeted Voyager Digital patrons as they briefly gained the opportunity to withdraw portions of their funds from the insolvent cryptocurrency brokerage. Bloomberg’s report, referencing insights from Darren Azman, the company’s legal representative, disclosed that scammers seized this month-long window.
 
The scammers employed diverse tactics in a range of stratagems detailed by Bloomberg. Among these, a prevalent approach involved luring Voyager customers with promises of elevated returns via counterfeit websites. Tragically, these sites siphoned the unsuspecting customers’ wallets once connected. 
 
 
Azman further revealed that law enforcement agencies have been duly informed and are actively addressing the distressing situation.
 
Voyager Customers Withdraw Nearly Half…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kenyan Government Suspends Worldcoin Activity]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755a346986</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/08/02/kenyan-government-suspends-worldcoin-activity/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T08:03:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kenya is the first country to fully suspend Worldcoin operations. Data protection offices in Europe have started investigations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliza Gkritsi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Japan to Launch With 34 Listed Cryptocurrencies]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755a376f21</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/binance-japan-to-launch-with-34-listed-cryptocurrencies/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T07:36:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance, which is preparing to launch its new Japanese platform in August, will offer users the opportunity to trade 34 coins, local crypto media reported. Besides major cryptocurrencies such as bitcoin and ether, Binance’s own token will also be among the listed digital assets.
 
Binance to Restore Crypto Trading in Japan With More Coins Than Major Competitors
 

 
Binance Japan, a subsidiary of the world’s largest crypto exchange by daily trading volume, will launch with 34 listed tokens, according to the Japanese crypto news outlet Coinpost. On Aug. 1, the company shared details about the services it plans to provide later this month.
 

 
The initial offerings will include bitcoin (BTC), ether (ETH), and bitcoin cash (BCH), as well as XRP. Binance’s token Build and Build (BNB), formerl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lubomir Tassev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Custodian Hex Trust Expands European Foray With Registration in France]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755a325e24</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/08/02/crypto-custodian-hex-trust-expands-european-foray-with-registration-in-france/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T07:10:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The registration, which follows last year's approval in Italy, is "a significant milestone" for its European expansion plans, Hex Trust said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Looks to Add Bitcoin Lightning for Payments]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755a334242</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/08/02/coinbase-looks-to-add-bitcoin-lightning-for-payments/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T07:01:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The move is part of the exchange's broader plan to improve cryptocurrency-based payments globally.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Room-Temperature Superconductor Claim Sparks Excitement and Skepticism]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150927</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150927/room-temperature-superconductor-lk-99"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T00:38:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From supercomputer simulations to a kitchen recreation, the news has riled up the science community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ApeCoin Price Sinks to All-Time Low as Bored Ape NFTs Dip Again]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150902</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150902/apecoin-price-sinks-all-time-low-bored-ape-nfts-dip-again"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T23:39:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Days after Yuga Labs showcased fresh elements of its Otherside metaverse game, the Bored Ape-themed Ethereum token notched a new low.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Moneyball' Meets Crypto in 'The Boys of Summer' Experimental NFT Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150909</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150909/moneyball-meets-crypto-boys-summer-experimental-nft-game"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T22:47:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artist Mitchell F. Chan's Ethereum NFT game about statistical overload goes well beyond the baseball diamond.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Cohen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy Makes Profit, Reports $24 Million Bitcoin Impairment Charge in Q2]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150903</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150903/microstrategy-profit-impairment-charge-bitcoin-holdings"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T21:22:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company has returned to profitability after a modest rise in the price of Bitcoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Keep Finding New and Sophisticated Ways to Use AI for Crime]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150899</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150899/wormgpt-fraudgpt-ai-hackers-phishing-malware"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T20:02:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity firm SlashNext sounds the alarm as exploits get much more sophisticated.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop Is Killing Its NFT Wallet and Blames ‘Regulatory Uncertainty’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150898</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150898/gamestop-nft-wallet-canceled-killed"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T19:56:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The video game retailer's NFT push continues to crumble after it fired the CEO who oversaw its launch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Arrows Capital Co-Founder Kyle Davies Says He Doesn't Have to Answer to US Courts]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150890</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150890/three-arrows-capital-co-founder-kyle-davies-rejects-us-court-jurisdiction"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T19:15:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The co-founder of the collapsed firm said in documents that he became a permanent resident of Singapore years ago.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Bets Big on AI to Revive Facebook and Instagram]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150882</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150882/meta-ai-instagram-facebook-chatbot-personalities"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T18:57:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With new chatbots and image editing tools, the social giant is gunning to rise again like a phoenix—with AI as the wind beneath its wings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Ordinals Team Launches Nonprofit as Inscriptions Top 21 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150871</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150871/bitcoin-ordinals-team-launches-nonprofit-inscriptions-top-21-million"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T18:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The team behind Ordinals said its Bitcoin-based protocol's development will be supported by a nonprofit structure moving forward.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia AI Image Generator Fits on a Floppy Disk and Takes 4 Minutes to Train]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150861</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150861/nvidia-ai-image-generator-floppy-disk-4-minutes"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T17:44:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia's new Perfusion image generator takes 100KB of space and needs only 4 minutes of training.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Justin Sun, DCF God and Others Line Up to Buy Curve Finance Founder’s CRV Tokens]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150852</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150852/justin-sun-dcf-god-and-others-line-up-buy-curve-finance-founders-crv-tokens"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T14:27:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After selling CRV to a host of eager buyers, the Curve founder has repaid $9.2 million in Aave loans. But risks still abound.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Term Labs Launches Fixed-Rate Lending Protocol on Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150841</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150841/term-labs-launches-fixed-rate-lending-protocol-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T13:01:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Term Labs took inspiration from the U.S. Treasury to build a platform that matches borrowers with lenders according to their preferred rates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Genesis Digital Assets Expands Bitcoin Mining Activity in ‘Pro-Innovation’ South Carolina]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150837</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150837/genesis-digital-assets-expands-bitcoin-mining-activity-pro-innovation-south-carolina"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T13:01:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The mining firm is launching three locations in South Carolina, with its CEO citing the state’s “abundance of clean electricity” for the move.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Krantz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Worldcoin? Sam Altman's Eye-Scanning Global ID 'Orb' Project Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150832</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-worldcoin-the-app-and-token-that-protects-your-personhood"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T11:44:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin has introduced a concept called “proof of personhood" to keep AI bots out of its global financial network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Reiff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LeetSwap DEX Pauses Trading on Base Due to Potential Exploit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150826</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150826/leetswap-dex-pauses-trading-base-due-potential-exploit"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T10:58:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The decentralized exchange team pulls the circuit breaker to pause trading as their trading pools are potentially compromised.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Reboot Pitches New Offshore Exchange for Users]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150825</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150825/ftx-reboot-pitches-new-offshore-exchange-dotcom-users"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T10:48:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The FTX reboot is rolling out a new offshore entity, offering claimants the opportunity to hold equity securities, tokens, or other interests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IRS Says Staking Rewards Are Taxable Income in Latest Revenue Ruling]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150817</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150817/irs-says-staking-rewards-is-taxable-income-latest-revenue-ruling"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T10:20:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto investors who earn staking rewards are now required to report these earnings as part of their gross income for tax purposes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Industry Still Isn’t Close to Solving the Blockchain Trilemma: Offchain Labs Chief Strategy Officer]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150816</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150816/industry-still-isnt-close-solving-the-blockchain-trilemma-offchain-labs-chief-strategy-officer"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T08:52:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solving the famed trilemma “would be a huge breakthrough,” but it would also need to inspire developers, said the Offchain Labs’ exec.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly,Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain Sleuths Link BALD Liquidity Rug Pull to Sam Bankman-Fried]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150780</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150780/bald-token-liquidity-rug-pull-linked-to-sam-bankman-fried"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T01:01:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The disgraced FTX founder is fingered by some who believe he removed liquidity from the BALD meme coin—before putting some back.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Wall Street Interest in Bitcoin Scare Cypherpunks Away?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150762</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150762/wall-street-institutional-mainstream-interest"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T23:50:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As big banks develop an appetite for crypto, privacy-centric users are increasingly wary of newcomers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Judge Refuses to Dismiss SEC Lawsuit Against Terraform Labs Despite Ripple Ruling]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150770</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150770/judge-refuses-dismissal-sec-terraform-labs-lawsuit-despite-ripple-ruling"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T23:37:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ruling found that crypto "falls far short" of having the significance needed for Congress to review regulation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt AI, Edited by Ryan Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hasbro Flirts With AI as Dungeons &#038; Dragons Game Sites Push Back]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150765</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150765/dungeons-dragons-hasbro-ai-xplored-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T22:34:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hasbro taps Xplored to infuse AI into gameplay, adding real-time responses to player decisions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How an Ethereum Bot Used Uniswap to Save $5.4 Million From Curve Exploit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150713</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150713/how-ethereum-uniswap-save-5-4-million-curve-exploit"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T22:24:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The MEV bot’s white-hat operator returned the funds to Curve Finance, which may have otherwise been lost to malicious hackers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yuga Labs to Acquire Roar Studios for AI Expertise]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150757</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150757/yuga-labs-roar-studios-acquisition-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T21:48:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eric Reid, Roar Studios founder and CEO, will head Yuga Labs’ upcoming Otherside game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Barbie's Margot Robbie Says Bitcoin Is for 'Kens'—While Mattel Pushes NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150755</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150755/barbie-margot-robbie-bitcoin-ken-mattel-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T21:10:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The actress dunked on the cryptocurrency as a stereotypically male conversation topic in a recent interview promoting "Barbie."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Art Showdown: How Top Tools MidJourney, Stable Diffusion v1.5, and SDXL Stack Up]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150714</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150714/ai-art-comparison-midjourney-stable-diffusion-sdxl-dall-e"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T20:58:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A clash of titans in AI tech has accelerated a generative image creation arms race. Which tool takes top honors?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BALD Meme Coin on Coinbase Layer-2 Goes to Zero as Dev Pulls Liquidity]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150693</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150693/following-meme-coin-mania-on-coinbases-base-one-token-appears-to-be-a-rug"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T19:39:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The BALD token exploded with popularity yesterday, but its deployers have since run off with millions of dollars in liquidity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ron DeSantis Promises to End 'Biden's War on Bitcoin', Toss CBDC 'Into the Trash Can']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150711</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150711/ron-desantis-biden-war-on-bitcoin-crypto-trash-cbdc"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T19:31:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Florida governor is among a number of presidential candidates who have expressed support for the leading cryptocurrency.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Is Only Network Ready for Gaming: Solana Foundation's Johnny Lee]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5OvV3ZXn/solana-is-only-network-ready-for-gaming-solana-foundations-johnny-lee</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5OvV3ZXn/solana-is-only-network-ready-for-gaming-solana-foundations-johnny-lee"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T17:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Foundation General Manager Johnny Lee tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how the Solana network will tackle the scaling problem that blockchain games pose for the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi Contagion? Curve Finance Exploit Ripples Across Industry]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150679</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150679/defi-contagion-curve-finance-exploit-ripples-across-industry"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T17:09:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smart contracts built using older Vyper versions are vulnerable to hacks, according to the programming language’s developers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi,Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether Reports $850 Million Q2 Profit, $72 Billion Exposure to US Treasuries]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150678</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150678/tether-reports-850-million-q2-profit-72-billion-exposure-to-us-treasuries"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T16:49:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Altogether Tether has about $72.5 billion worth of U.S. Treasury Bills backing its USDT stablecoin, according to the report.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Charges Hex Founder Richard Heart With $1 Billion Unregistered Securities Offering]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150677</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150677/sec-charges-hex-founder-richard-heart-1b-unregistered-securities-offering"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T15:12:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hex founder Richard Heart and three entities have been charged today for allegedly conducting unregistered crypto asset securities offerings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly,Connor Sephton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robert F. Kennedy Jr: Bitcoin Energy Concerns Should Not Be Used as 'Smokescreen' to Limit Freedom]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150674</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150674/robert-f-kennedy-jr-bitcoin-energy-concerns-should-not-be-used-smokescreen-limit-freedom"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T14:31:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robert F. Kennedy Jr. says opponents shouldn't use Bitcoin's climate concerns as an excuse to block people's "freedom to transact."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase CEO Says SEC Wanted All Assets Except Bitcoin Delisted: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150670</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150670/coinbase-ceo-says-sec-wanted-all-assets-except-bitcoin-delisted-report"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T10:07:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The regulator reportedly wanted Coinbase to cease trading all cryptocurrencies except Bitcoin prior to its legal action against the exchange.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi Exchange Curve Finance Confirms Various Ethereum Pools Hacked]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150669</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150669/defi-exchange-curve-finance-confirms-various-ethereum-pools-hacked"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T09:44:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Curve Finance team has confirmed which pools were affected in the latest multi-million dollar exploit due to a Vyper vulnerability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Com2uS Is Going "Full Speed" on Crypto Gaming: Kyu Lee]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pYMZRoYy/com2us-is-going-full-speed-on-crypto-gaming-kyu-lee</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pYMZRoYy/com2us-is-going-full-speed-on-crypto-gaming-kyu-lee"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kyu Lee is the President of game studio Com2uS USA. In an interview, he shares the studio's approach to Web3 and crypto gaming with Decrypt GG's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Discord Game with AI and Blockchain: 'Alchemy: Battle for Ankhos' Creative Lead Alex Finden]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mF18GHGo/building-a-discord-game-with-ai-and-blockchain-alchemy-battle-for-ankhos-creative-lead-alex-finden</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mF18GHGo/building-a-discord-game-with-ai-and-blockchain-alchemy-battle-for-ankhos-creative-lead-alex-finden"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T21:55:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Jason Nelson interviews Alchemy: Battle for Ankhos Creative Director Alex Finden at the Solana PlayGG event in San Diego, California.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Big Respect Between Ethereum and Cosmos Developer Communities': dYdX Foundation CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/XU5MbCGE/big-respect-between-ethereum-and-cosmos-developer-communities-dydx-foundation-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/XU5MbCGE/big-respect-between-ethereum-and-cosmos-developer-communities-dydx-foundation-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T13:24:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CEO of the dYdX Foundation Charles d'Haussy unpacks the decision behind moving one of the largest decentralized exchange protocol's over to its very own chain built on Cosmos. A key driver, he told Decrypt at this year's EthCC event, was that instead of launching on a rollup or another layer-1, launching a fully customized chain will allow dYdX to fine tune the network for its product's needs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Staking Solution Lido 'Had Perfect Product Market Fit' at Launch, Says DAO's Biz Dev Contributor]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/fUHhelhV/ethereum-staking-solution-lido-had-perfect-product-market-fit-at-launch-says-daos-biz-dev-contributor</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/fUHhelhV/ethereum-staking-solution-lido-had-perfect-product-market-fit-at-launch-says-daos-biz-dev-contributor"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T08:43:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marin Tvrdić, a business development contributor to the Lido DAO, sat down with Decrypt during this year's EthCC to break down how the liquid staking protocol has managed such a massive lead, how it plans to keep that lead, and the protocol's new dual-governance tokenomics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's Going to Stop All the DeFi Hacks? 'Standards,' Says OpenZepplin Security Architect]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/aYNuFdAi/whats-going-to-stop-all-the-defi-hacks-standards-says-openzepplin-security-architect</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/aYNuFdAi/whats-going-to-stop-all-the-defi-hacks-standards-says-openzepplin-security-architect"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T08:04:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenZeppelin's security solutions architect Michael Lewellen sat down with Decrypt to discuss how the industry can become a little safer for users at this year's EthCC Paris. The key? Introducing security standards across the industry so folks know what an audit actually means and where risks lie, be it bad faith actors or poor implementation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Ev.io' Game Review: Earn Solana While Blasting Enemies]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/2ZmkuhL2/evio-game-review-earn-solana-while-blasting-enemies</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/2ZmkuhL2/evio-game-review-earn-solana-while-blasting-enemies"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T22:21:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ev.io is a web-based first-person shooter that's free to play, but lets NFT holders earn in-game currency that can be redeemed for Solana (SOL). Decrypt contributor Ryan Gladwin shares his review of the fun throwback to Quake-style blasting, albeit with a modern crypto twist.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Moving Fast and Breaking Things Isn't the Web3 Ethos': MetaMask Product Lead]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/l1EbLgl3/moving-fast-and-breaking-things-isnt-the-web3-ethos-metamask-product-lead</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/l1EbLgl3/moving-fast-and-breaking-things-isnt-the-web3-ethos-metamask-product-lead"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T15:45:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Account abstraction this, smart wallets that. Discussions at EthCC Paris about improving user experience have pointed at industry leader MetaMask as an example of what not to do. But that may soon change, with a host of updates and optimizations coming to crypto's number one wallet, said its product lead Alex Jupiter. It still may take some time, though, before these changes take effect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling Smart Wallets on Starknet 'Was The Winning Combination', Says Argent Co-Founder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/gnBsxw4D/scaling-smart-wallets-on-starknet-was-the-winning-combination-says-argent-co-founder</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/gnBsxw4D/scaling-smart-wallets-on-starknet-was-the-winning-combination-says-argent-co-founder"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T07:35:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Argent co-founder Julien Niset told Decrypt at EthCC Paris that he wants to make crypto wallets disappear. Or at least how they're currently conceived. From clunky seed phrases to a stiff user experience, Argent hopes to make using crypto a little less intimidating and a whole lot more fun.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Mighty Action Heroes' Open Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/litL6kKs/inside-mighty-action-heroes-open-beta</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/litL6kKs/inside-mighty-action-heroes-open-beta"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T18:23:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mighty Action Heroes is the flagship blockchain title from Mighty Bear Games. But is the browser-based battle royale shooter worth checking out? Decrypt's Kate Irwin offers her thoughts and a first look at the upcoming game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dr. Disrespect's 'Deadrop': Early Access Gameplay From Snapshot VI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/8l21EHoa/dr-disrespects-deadrop-early-access-gameplay-from-snapshot-vi</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/8l21EHoa/dr-disrespects-deadrop-early-access-gameplay-from-snapshot-vi"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T18:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin playtests Dr. Disrespect and Midnight Society's first-person shooter Deadrop and shares the latest game updates, as well as her opinions on the game in development. Currently, Deadrop offers Polygon Founders Pass NFTs with no other crypto plans revealed just yet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['More and More' Game Publishers Will Embrace NFTs: Mythical Games CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/wBWogSkl/more-and-more-game-publishers-will-embrace-nfts-mythical-games-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/wBWogSkl/more-and-more-game-publishers-will-embrace-nfts-mythical-games-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T22:28:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the wake of EA Sports and Fortnite creator Epic Games embracing Nike's NFT platform, Mythical Games CEO John Linden tells Decrypt's Andrew Hayward how quickly he expects to see more major traditional game publishers enter the blockchain space and how quickly the industry will scale.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gran Saga Unlimited Early Access: Inside the Anime MMORPG on Aptos]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JeFWMVwo/gran-saga-unlimited-early-access-inside-the-anime-mmorpg-on-aptos</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JeFWMVwo/gran-saga-unlimited-early-access-inside-the-anime-mmorpg-on-aptos"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T21:46:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin plays Gran Saga: Unlimited's second community playtest, reports her findings, and offers her opinion and insights on the upcoming game, which will offer optional Aptos NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[100 Thieves' Moe Says Blockchain Games Will 'Eventually' Be Accepted by Livestreamers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/xHhh62ID/100-thieves-moe-says-blockchain-games-will-eventually-be-accepted-by-livestreamers</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/xHhh62ID/100-thieves-moe-says-blockchain-games-will-eventually-be-accepted-by-livestreamers"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T16:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[100 Thieves content creator and gamer Moe also goes by "Yassuo" online after his favorite League of Legends character. Decrypt's Kate Irwin asks him about 100 Thieves' future crypto plans and whether Moe thinks creators like xQc and Pokimane might ever come around to blockchain games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Games of the Future Are Going to Be Different," Says Splinterlands Cofounder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/sQv6zcil/games-of-the-future-are-going-to-be-different-says-splinterlands-cofounder</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/sQv6zcil/games-of-the-future-are-going-to-be-different-says-splinterlands-cofounder"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T20:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Splinterlands Cofounder Matt Rosen tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about how the game has evolved over its five-year history and why he doesn't listen to the FUD around crypto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Champions Ascension: Like 'For Honor' with NFTs?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/gvM9ajww/inside-champions-ascension-like-for-honor-with-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/gvM9ajww/inside-champions-ascension-like-for-honor-with-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T22:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plai Labs Marketing Director Payton Kaleiwahea tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about player response to the combat game Champions Ascension in development, which offers arena combat, raid bosses, AI landscape features, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Activision VP Michael Lee: Gaming Is Crypto's 'Killer App']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/M9ulXrb3/ex-activision-vp-michael-lee-gaming-is-cryptos-killer-app</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/M9ulXrb3/ex-activision-vp-michael-lee-gaming-is-cryptos-killer-app"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Activision Vice President Michael Lee is now the SVP of Growth at Matter Labs. At the 3XP gaming conference, Lee sat down with Decrypt's Kate Irwin to discuss crypto gaming and give his predictions for the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>