<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-09-07T23:14:08.561Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-09-07T23:14:08.561Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CFTC Goes After Opyn, Other DeFi Operations in Enforcement Sweep]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18887762/CFTC-Goes-After-Opyn-Other-DeFi-Operations-in-Enforcement-Sweep</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18887762/CFTC-Goes-After-Opyn-Other-DeFi-Operations-in-Enforcement-Sweep"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T23:01:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) has charged three decentralized finance (DeFi) operations – Opyn, Inc., ZeroEx (0x), Inc. and Deridex, Inc. – with offering illegal derivatives trading, according to a Thursday statement from the agency.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-FTX Executive Ryan Salame Could Forfeit $1.5B as Part of Guilty Plea]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754e99bbac</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/09/07/ex-ftx-executive-ryan-salame-pleads-guilty-to-us-criminal-charges/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T22:54:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prosecutors say Sam Bankman-Fried used Salame as a “straw donor” to secretly funnel millions of dollars to Republican political candidates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Kessler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Digital Asset Regulation in Australia Faces Uncertainty as Senate Debates Key Bill]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18887750/Digital-Asset-Regulation-in-Australia-Faces-Uncertainty-as-Senate-Debates-Key-Bill</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18887750/Digital-Asset-Regulation-in-Australia-Faces-Uncertainty-as-Senate-Debates-Key-Bill"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T22:49:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Senator Andrew Bragg has issued a stark warning, stating that Australian investors could face exposure...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BITCOIN HOLDERS - WATCH THIS LEVEL | BNB Price Prediction]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18887747/BITCOIN-HOLDERS-WATCH-THIS-LEVEL-BNB-Price-Prediction</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18887747/BITCOIN-HOLDERS-WATCH-THIS-LEVEL-BNB-Price-Prediction"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T22:30:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this Altcoin Buzz Trading segment we conduct crypto price analysis on Bitcoin BTC, and altcoins: Binance Coin BNB and KAVA.Manage Your Crypto Portfolio with Regular Updates and Top Insights for only $15/ month.Sign up for Altcoin Buzz Alpha:Youtube:...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$XRP Ledger to Boost Transaction Throughput to 3,400 TPS with Upcoming Upgrades]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18887737/XRP-Ledger-to-Boost-Transaction-Throughput-to-3400-TPS-with-Upcoming-Upgrades</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18887737/XRP-Ledger-to-Boost-Transaction-Throughput-to-3400-TPS-with-Upcoming-Upgrades"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T22:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The transaction throughput of the $XRP Ledger is set to soon surge from around 1,500 transactions per second to an impressive 3,400 transactions per second (TPS), bolstered by upgrades that are soon set to be deployed. The transaction throughput’s upcoming increase was first spotted by Kevin...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JPMorgan Explores Game-Changing Blockchain Deposit Tokens For Swift Cross-Border Payments]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18887733/JPMorgan-Explores-Game-Changing-Blockchain-Deposit-Tokens-For-Swift-Cross-Border-Payments</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18887733/JPMorgan-Explores-Game-Changing-Blockchain-Deposit-Tokens-For-Swift-Cross-Border-Payments"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T22:20:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover how JPMorgan is pioneering blockchain-based deposit tokens to revolutionize international transactions. Regulatory approval stands as the final hurdle on the path to transforming banking efficiency. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korea's 'Lazarus' Hackers Stole $41 Million From Crypto Gambling Site, FBI Says]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754e856194</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/09/07/north-koreas-lazarus-hackers-stoke-41-million-from-crypto-gambling-site-fbi-says/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T22:19:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Lazarus Group has been targeting crypto companies for years now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[El Salvador Launches Pilot Project to Include Bitcoin Content in School Curriculums]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754e861165</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/el-salvador-launches-pilot-project-to-include-bitcoin-content-in-school-curriculums/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T22:12:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ministry of Education in El Salvador partnered with Mi Primer Bitcoin (MPB), a nonprofit educational organization, to make Bitcoin-related content part of the school curriculum in the country. The pilot program will train 150 teachers to impart Bitcoin education, bringing the program to 75 public schools.
El Salvador to Include Bitcoin Education in School Curriculum in 2024
Mi Primer Bitcoin (MPB), a nonprofit Salvadoran educational project, and the Ministry of Education of El Salvador have partnered to launch a pilot project to take Bitcoin courses to every school in the country by 2024. In a recent interview, John Dennehy, the founder of MPB, confirmed the involvement of the organization in this joint initiative.
The first part of the process began on September 7 with 150 teachers fr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Founder Explores Privacy Pool System In New Research]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754e865a2f</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-explores-privacy-pool-system/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T22:10:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As international regulations change, individuals are increasingly interested in preserving their privacy. One of the co-founders of Ethereum, Vitalik Buterin, and others released a research paper. The authors explored the intersection of blockchain technology and financial regulations through the lens of privacy pool systems. 
 
The paper introduces a fresh perspective by leveraging zero-knowledge proofs to tackle privacy challenges while simultaneously upholding regulatory standards. 
 
Buterin and his co-authors Jacob Illum, Matthias Nadler, Fabian Schar, and Ameen Soleimani seek to find a “middle ground” reconciling the need for privacy with regulatory compliance demands.
 
Research Raises Concern About Tornado Cash
 
The document starts by analyzing the well-known tool for enhancing pr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kent Glory</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OKX and Circle partner to add USDC features to OKX Wallet and DEX aggregator]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18887687/OKX-and-Circle-partner-to-add-USDC-features-to-OKX-Wallet-and-DEX-aggregator</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18887687/OKX-and-Circle-partner-to-add-USDC-features-to-OKX-Wallet-and-DEX-aggregator"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T22:09:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoin issuer Circle and crypto exchange OKX are partnering to bring USDC features to the OKX Wallet and OKX DEX aggregator.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samara Asset Donates $10,000 To Support Bitcoin Education For Women in Africa]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754e86874a</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/samara-donates-10000-to-support-bitcoin-education-for-women-in-africa"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T22:08:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a commendable move to advance financial literacy and inclusion, Samara Asset Group has donated $10,000 in bitcoin to Bitcoin DADA, per a press release sent to Bitcoin Magazine. 
This Kenya-based non-profit initiative is steadfastly working towards empowering African women through extensive financial education, emphasizing Bitcoin's power to bring about transformative change.
Bitcoin DADA, anchored in the belief that knowledge is empowerment, is convinced that arming African women with the understanding of Bitcoin can pave the way for their financial autonomy. This, in turn, empowers them to play a pivotal role in the burgeoning global digital economy.
The notable donation by Samara will significantly aid Bitcoin DADA in launching novel educational programs and initiatives, furthering its mission to uplift African women in the digital financial realm.
"Samara’s generous donation to Bitcoin DADA is a beacon of support for the empowerment of African women," Lorraine Marcel Atieno, the founder of Bitcoin DADA, remarked. "The contribution will fuel our mission to educate, uplift, and inspire women in Kenya and across the continent, fostering a brighter future for African females. We’re grateful for Samara being a pillar in this journey of empowerment."
Echoing these sentiments, Patrick Lowry, CEO of Samara, emphasized the organization’s core belief. He stated, "At Samara, we believe in a future where financial empowerment is accessible to everyone, irrespective of gender, race, or geographical location. Our donation to Bitcoin DADA is a testament to this vision. We’re not just investing in Bitcoin businesses, we are investing in a more inclusive and decentralized financial future for all."
The commendable efforts of Bitcoin DADA continue, and for those inspired to contribute to this noble cause, you can extend your support by donating to further Bitcoin education for women in Africa through their official donation link.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Surge In Crypto Cyber Threats: Binance's $1M Refund, Ethereum's $24M Loss, FBI's Stake.com Alert]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18887707/Surge-In-Crypto-Cyber-Threats-Binances-1M-Refund-Ethereums-24M-Loss-FBIs-Stakecom-Alert</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18887707/Surge-In-Crypto-Cyber-Threats-Binances-1M-Refund-Ethereums-24M-Loss-FBIs-Stakecom-Alert"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T22:08:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cryptocurrency world is under escalating cybersecurity threats, as evident from three significant incidents involving Binance (CRYPTO: BNB), Ethereum (CRYPTO: ETH) and a revealing read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fintech firm settles with SEC over crypto lending product]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18887681/Fintech-firm-settles-with-SEC-over-crypto-lending-product</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18887681/Fintech-firm-settles-with-SEC-over-crypto-lending-product"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T22:04:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linus Financial has agreed to stop offering its retail crypto lending product as part of the settlement]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon Founder Responds to Allegation That the Crypto Asset’s Backer Dumped Over $5,900,000 in MATIC on Binance]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18887686/Polygon-Founder-Responds-to-Allegation-That-the-Crypto-Assets-Backer-Dumped-Over-5900000-in-MATIC-on-Binance</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18887686/Polygon-Founder-Responds-to-Allegation-That-the-Crypto-Assets-Backer-Dumped-Over-5900000-in-MATIC-on-Binance"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T22:01:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The founder of the Ethereum (ETH) layer-2 scaling solution Polygon (MATIC) is responding to allegations that the Polygon Foundation deposited nearly $6 million worth of the digital asset on Binance. In a new thread on the social media platform X, Polyon founder Sandeep Nailwal says that previous...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Founder Explores Privacy Pool System In New Research]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18887680/Ethereum-Founder-Explores-Privacy-Pool-System-In-New-Research</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18887680/Ethereum-Founder-Explores-Privacy-Pool-System-In-New-Research"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T22:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As international regulations change, individuals are increasingly interested in preserving their privacy. One of the co-founders of Ethereum, Vitalik Buterin, and others released a research paper. The authors explored the intersection of blockchain technology and financial regulations through...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance To Refund Users $1 Million In USDT Following CyberConnect Incident]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18887664/Binance-To-Refund-Users-1-Million-In-USDT-Following-CyberConnect-Incident</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18887664/Binance-To-Refund-Users-1-Million-In-USDT-Following-CyberConnect-Incident"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T22:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CFTC commissioner calls for crypto regulatory pilot program]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18887661/CFTC-commissioner-calls-for-crypto-regulatory-pilot-program</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18887661/CFTC-commissioner-calls-for-crypto-regulatory-pilot-program"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T21:59:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Commissioner Caroline Pham called for the pilot program to kick off with a stakeholder roundtable and for the CFTC to propose and adopt rules on the risks retail investors face.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CFTC’s Pham says US needs to speed up crypto regulation]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18887660/CFTCs-Pham-says-US-needs-to-speed-up-crypto-regulation</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18887660/CFTCs-Pham-says-US-needs-to-speed-up-crypto-regulation"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T21:53:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The program should be time-limited and designed from a series of roundtable discussions between regulators and stakeholders, Caroline Pham suggested]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JPMorgan moves into deposit tokens for settlements: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18887656/JPMorgan-moves-into-deposit-tokens-for-settlements-Report</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18887656/JPMorgan-moves-into-deposit-tokens-for-settlements-Report"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T21:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JPMorgan is reportedly developing the infrastructure to run a new deposit token, allowing settlements between banks for corporate clients.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tokenization News Roundup: the 'Next Trillion']]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754e82122b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/09/07/tokenization-news-roundup-the-next-trillion/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T21:35:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A weekly digest of articles, reports and analyses about tokenized RWAs, the fast-growing financial instruments that merge traditional finance to the blockchain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Kuhn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Bitcoin Miners in Texas Are Making Millions Without Mining at All]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155460</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155460/how-bitcoin-miners-in-texas-are-making-millions-without-mining-at-all"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T21:34:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Miners “either mine BTC or curtail energy when prices are high to sell it back to the grid,” Compass Mining told Decrypt, giving them a better return than mining.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Pure’ DeFi has little chance for real-world use because of need for oracles: BIS]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18887635/Pure-DeFi-has-little-chance-for-real-world-use-because-of-need-for-oracles-BIS</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18887635/Pure-DeFi-has-little-chance-for-real-world-use-because-of-need-for-oracles-BIS"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T21:34:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to the BIS researchers, a centralized oracle based on trust is the only option for DeFi, and variations of that model do exist.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase is ramping up global efforts with ‘forward-looking regulators’]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18887633/Coinbase-is-ramping-up-global-efforts-with-forward-looking-regulators</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18887633/Coinbase-is-ramping-up-global-efforts-with-forward-looking-regulators"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T21:31:19.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chainlink whales are on the move – Is something brewing?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18887630/Chainlink-whales-are-on-the-move-Is-something-brewing</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18887630/Chainlink-whales-are-on-the-move-Is-something-brewing"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T21:30:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whales are accumulating LINK as overall market sentiment remains cautious. In just three days, these whales added an impressive $9.6 million worth of LINK tokens to their holdings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[London Fintech CEO Linked to Crypto Money Laundering for Brazilian Criminal]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18887618/London-Fintech-CEO-Linked-to-Crypto-Money-Laundering-for-Brazilian-Criminal</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18887618/London-Fintech-CEO-Linked-to-Crypto-Money-Laundering-for-Brazilian-Criminal"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Caio Marchesani, the owner of a financial technology company in London, allegedly helped drug traffickers launder hundreds of millions of euros through crypto exchange platforms. Marchesani’s fintech company is regulated by the Financial Conduct Authority and called Trans-Fast Remittance, a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Surges Suddenly: What’s the Latest Data?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18887619/Bitcoin-Surges-Suddenly-Whats-the-Latest-Data</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18887619/Bitcoin-Surges-Suddenly-Whats-the-Latest-Data"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T21:29:06.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JPMorgan exploring blockchain-based payment and settlement system: Bloomberg]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18887612/JPMorgan-exploring-blockchain-based-payment-and-settlement-system-Bloomberg</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18887612/JPMorgan-exploring-blockchain-based-payment-and-settlement-system-Bloomberg"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T21:21:35.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CFTC Takes Action against MTI: Imposes $1.7B Fine for Bitcoin-Related Forex Fraud]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754e8c2da8</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/cftc-takes-action-against-mti-imposes-17b-fine-for-bitcoin-related-forex-fraud/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T21:16:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a landmark ruling, the Commodities Futures Trading  
Commission (CFTC) has secured a staggering USD $1.7 billion in restitution from  
Mirror Trading International. The South African company was allegedly involved  
in a massive Forex fraud scheme. 
The legal matter  
involves a complaint filed by CFTC on June 30, 2022, which highlighted  
fraudulent activities, including deceiving retail investors through Forex  
transactions, violating registration requirements, and flaunting regulations  
governing commodity pool operators (CPOs).
CFTC Alleges  
"Multilevel Fraud Scheme"
According to CFTC, MTI's  
founder and CEO, Cornelius Johannes Steynberg, played a central role in  
orchestrating this elaborate scam. Steynberg, acting both individually and as  
MTI's controlling figure, solicited…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Co-Founder Slams SEC Chairman And US President For Hostile Crypto Regulations]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754e8d033d</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ripple-co-founder-slams-sec-chairman-us-president/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T21:09:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent interview with Bloomberg Television, Chris Larsen, the co-founder and executive chairman of Ripple Labs, expressed his views on the regulatory environment in the United States and its impact on the blockchain industry. 
 
Larsen claimed that San Francisco, once poised to be the “blockchain capital of the world,” lost its status due to hostile government policies and regulatory crackdowns.
 
Ripple Co-Founder Urges Proactive Crypto Regulation
 
According to Larsen, London, Singapore, and Dubai have emerged as bigger blockchain hubs because US federal government actions forced operations to relocate overseas.
 
 
While Ripple remains headquartered in San Francisco, Larsen believes the Biden administration’s decision to push the industry offshore has hindered the city’s growth. Sa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reject CBDCs, Embrace the Right to Transact]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754e8f2168</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/09/07/reject-cbdcs-embrace-the-right-to-transact/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T20:50:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The steady creep of payments digitization means governments will be able to increasingly intervene and potentially censor economic activity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zelinar XY</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Riot Showcases Demand Response Strategy: Bitcoin Mining’s Role in Strengthening Texas Energy Grid]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754e880df2</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/riot-showcases-demand-response-strategy-bitcoin-minings-role-in-strengthening-texas-energy-grid/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T20:42:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin mining aided the Electric Reliability Council of Texas, or ERCOT, when the bitcoin mining company Riot Platforms reduced its power usage amid a Texas summer heatwave. Riot said in its most recent production and operations update that it received $31.7 million in power and demand response credits for August. 
 
Bitcoin Mining’s Win-Win: Riot Cuts Power, Boosts Texas Energy Stability
 

 
Politicians skeptical of bitcoin, like the Massachusetts Democrat Elizabeth Warren, might want to familiarize themselves with demand response systems and how bitcoin mining can enhance the efficiency of energy grids. Simply put, demand response is a tactic used in electricity grids that encourages users to decrease or adjust their power use during peak times in response to time-based rates or other …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EA Sports UFC 5: Everything You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155400</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155400/ea-sports-ufc-5-everything-you-need-know"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T20:14:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you ready to rumble? EA Sports UFC 5 will be the first Mature-rated entry in the MMA fighting series, coming to PlayStation 5 and Xbox Series X/S.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former FTX Exec Ryan Salame Forfeits $1.5 Billion in Plea Deal]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155340</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155340/former-ftx-exec-ryan-salame-plead-guilty"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T20:04:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Salame, co-CEO of FTX Digital Markets, pleaded guilty to campaign finance violations and fraud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano Unveils Warp Transactions: A Game-Changer For ADA]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754e72b5d8</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/cardano-warp-transactions-game-changer-ada/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T19:10:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Strica, the software powerhouse behind Cardano-centric tools such as Cardanoscan.io, Typhon Wallet, and Flac Finance, has introduced Warp Transactions. This innovation promises to revolutionize the way ADA token transfers are conducted on the Cardano network.
 
The crux of the issue lies in Cardano’s inherent requirement for a minimum of approximately 1.14 ADA to accompany any token transfer. This mechanism, while designed to shield the network from potential threats and spam, has been a point of contention for users. The necessity to attach this minimum ADA when sending tokens has been seen as cumbersome. Warp Transactions, as integrated into the Typhon Wallet, offers a solution to this predicament.
 
Here’s How Warp Transactions Work On Cardano
 
“To understand the Warp Transactions it i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peach Bitcoin Celebrates One-Year Anniversary With Launch of Version 0.3]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754e72e289</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/peach-bitcoin-celebrates-one-year-anniversary-with-launch-of-version-0-3"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T19:08:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Peach Bitcoin has officially launched Peach 0.3, while coinciding with the one year anniversary of the company. This new version introduces new features, a comprehensive wallet that seamlessly integrates with the app, enabling users to manage their bitcoin holdings effortlessly. 
With this upgrade, users can send and receive bitcoin and fund a sell offer with just a few clicks. One standout feature of this wallet is its UTXO management accessibility, making coin control easier for everyone. It also integrates an address checker to verify if an address belongs to your wallet, ensuring added security. Peach emphasizes individual sovereignty and self-custody, and users retain full control of their private keys with a 12 seed word setup.
"Some people will join Peach because they align with our…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nik Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Former FTX Co-Chief Ryan Salame Contemplates Guilty Plea]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754e72fa6d</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/report-former-ftx-co-chief-ryan-salame-contemplates-guilty-plea/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T19:07:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to insiders who reached out to Bloomberg, there are intriguing developments surrounding Ryan Salame, the former co-chief executive of FTX Digital Markets. The buzz is that he is gearing up to admit guilt in response to criminal charges. This marks a significant shift from his earlier stance, which was revealed in mid-August when he appeared poised to invoke the Fifth Amendment, thereby rendering himself unavailable as a potential witness.
 
Ryan Salame’s Dramatic Turn: From Invoking the Fifth to Pondering Guilty Plea
 
The current narrative presents a contrasting perspective, hinting at the potential formation of a plea agreement concerning Ryan Salame, the former co-chief of FTX. Citing “people familiar with the case,” Bloomberg reports that Salame is poised to enter a guilty plea in connection with the FTX collapse.
 
Bloomberg’s Ava Benny-Morrison delivered this report on September 7, 2023, diverging from the accounts of the previous month. During that period, court documents from the prosecution’s case against ex-FTX CEO Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF) had indicated that Salame had expressed his intention to invoke the Fifth Amendment if subpoenaed, rendering him “unavailable as a witness.”
 
Should Salame indeed plead guilty, he will become the fourth individual to do so, joining Caroline Ellison, Gary Wang, and Nishad Singh. SBF, on the other hand, has pleaded not guilty to all the criminal charges against him and is presently incarcerated, awaiting trial at the Metropolitan Detention Center in Brooklyn. The trial is scheduled for October, and SBF’s legal team is actively seeking his release from custody to prepare for the upcoming proceedings.
 
What do you think about the insiders who say Salame plans to enter a guilty plea? Share your thoughts and opinions about this subject in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Basketball Title Rumble Kong League and Stance Launch In-Game and IRL HyperSocks]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154226</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154226/basketball-title-rumble-kong-league-and-stance-launch-in-game-and-irl-hypersocks"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T19:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The partnership will kick off with the launch of NFT HyperSocks by Stance, alongside IRL counterparts and an augmented reality filter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FBI Says North Korea’s Lazarus Group Was Behind $41 Million Stake Hack]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155360</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155360/fbi-says-north-koreas-lazarus-group-was-behind-41-million-stake-hack"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T18:58:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The hacker group is one of crypto’s most prolific, allegedly responsible for stealing $2 billion worth of assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Skyrim Creator's Starfield Tops One Million Concurrent Players on Launch Day]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155330</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155330/skyrim-creators-starfield-tops-million-concurrent-players-launch-day"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T18:32:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bethesda Game Studios' Starfield is making waves with a huge player turnout on day one and broadly positive reviews.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fraud Lawsuit Against Michael Egorov, the CEO of DeFi Giant Curve, Is Quashed in California]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754e7fcb93</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/09/07/fraud-lawsuit-against-michael-egorov-the-ceo-of-defi-giant-curve-is-quashed-in-california/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T18:30:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A judge ruled a California courtroom is the wrong venue since Egorov wasn’t living in the state when the alleged misdeeds took place.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CFTC Commissioner Pitches Pilot Program for U.S. Crypto Regulation]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754e79fd89</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/09/07/cftc-commissioner-pitches-pilot-program-for-us-crypto-regulation/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T18:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. watchdog for derivatives markets should create a limited pilot program for regulating cryptocurrencies, said Caroline Pham, one of the members of the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Bitcoin Transfer Fees Be Enough To Replace Block Subsidy In Future?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754e7a994e</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-transfer-fees-replace-block-subsidy-future/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T18:11:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bitcoin block rewards are becoming lesser and lesser with each halving. Will transaction fees eventually be able to fill up this void?
 
Bitcoin Transaction Fees Has Been Trending Up With Each Cycle
 
One of the most innovative features of the Bitcoin blockchain is that approximately every four years, the block subsidy (that miners receive for solving blocks on the network) is slashed in half. Such events are called the “halving.”
 
Halvings naturally mean that the miners’ revenues also take a heavy hit, primarily made up of the block rewards. Why does the concept of halving even exist? Well, consider the scenario if there was no halving.
 
The block rewards serve as the only way to mint new tokens so that they can be equated to the new production of the asset. Without halvings, miners…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hououin Kyouma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFL All Day Has Fumbled: NFT Sales Down 87% From a Year Ago]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155347</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155347/nfl-all-day-has-fumbled-nft-sales-down-87-from-a-year-ago"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T18:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dapper Labs may be hoping for a Hail Marry as NFL All Day’s sales flounder compared to its 2022 football preseason rally.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX’s Salame Set to Plead Guilty after Prolonged Negotiations with Prosecutors: Report]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754e64d85a</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/ftxs-salame-set-to-plead-guilty-after-prolonged-negotiations-with-prosecutors-report/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T17:55:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former FTX’s Executive Ryan Salame prepares to plead  
guilty to criminal charges to the cryptocurrency exchange’s collapse. This turn  
of events comes after extended negotiations with the prosecutors. The executive  
is scheduled to appear in a Manhattan federal court today (Thursday) for the  
guilty plea, according to the people familiar with the matter.
Salame served as  
Co-Chief Executive of FTX’s Bahamas subsidiary. His decision to plead guilty  
follows closely behind the impending trial of Sam Bankman-Fried, who faces  
allegations of orchestrating a multi-billion fraud scheme. Prosecutors contend  
that Bankman-Fried misappropriated FTX customer funds for personal  
expenditures, high-risk investments in Alameda Research, and political  
donations.
Salame Accused  
of Being SBF’…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Witnesses Second-Highest Daily Ordinal Inscription Count as Inscriptions Near 30 Million]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754e660c1f</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-witnesses-second-highest-daily-ordinal-inscription-count-as-inscriptions-near-30-million/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T17:46:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While Bitcoin-based nonfungible token (NFT) sales have declined, and the network has dropped to seventh out of 23 blockchains in sales this past month, Ordinal inscriptions continue unabated. The number of inscriptions linked to the Bitcoin blockchain is nearing 30 million. On September 3, a record 418,240 inscriptions were minted, marking the second-highest daily rate to date.
 
Bitcoin’s Ordinal Inscriptions Hit Second-Largest Daily Total
 

 
As of 10 a.m. Eastern Time on September 7, 2023, at block height 806,606, there are about 29.48 million Ordinal inscriptions tied to the Bitcoin blockchain. Bitcoin miners have to date received an estimated 1,976.62 BTC, valued at $50.85 million at current exchange rates, from Ordinal inscriptions. Daily inscriptions continue at a rapid pace, with …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FASB's Crypto Accounting Shakeup Could Lure More Corporate Investment, Michael Saylor and Others Argue]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754e600e3a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/09/07/fasbs-crypto-accounting-shakeup-could-lure-more-corporate-investment-michael-saylor-and-others-argue/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T17:32:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. accounting standards board yesterday unanimously voted in favor of "fair value" accounting for crypto assets held on corporate balance sheets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen  Alpher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[El Salvador Launches Education Program To Teach Bitcoin In Every School]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754e635433</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/el-salvador-bitcoin-news/el-salvador-launches-education-program-to-teach-bitcoin-in-every-school"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T17:10:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[El Salvador, the first nation to officially adopt Bitcoin as legal tender, is once again making headlines in the world of cryptocurrency. With the combined efforts of My First Bitcoin, Bitcoin Beach, and the Ministry of Education, the nation announced the inception of an ambitious pilot program today. This initiative aims to incorporate Bitcoin education in all schools across the country by 2024.
Initiated on the 2-year mark of the groundbreaking Bitcoin Law, this program is set to train 150 public school teachers about Bitcoin. After receiving their training, these educators will disperse across the nation, integrating Bitcoin knowledge into their respective curriculum and classrooms.
The key player, My First Bitcoin, is a non-profit and Bitcoin education-focused NGO rooted in El Salvador…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reed Macdonald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kenyan Official Calls Worldcoin a 'Gang of Criminals Who Are Coming to Harvest Data']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155283</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155283/kenyan-official-calls-worldcoin-gang-of-criminals-coming-to-harvest-data"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T16:01:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin CEO Alex Blania refuted the claim, saying "Worldcoin is designed to be privacy-preserving."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic Debuts Claude Pro to Rival ChatGPT's AI Chatbot]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155331</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155331/anthropic-debuts-claude-pro-rival-to-chatgpt-ai-chatbot"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T15:52:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new service competes against ChatGPT Plus and offers 5X more interactions, priority of computing power and access to early features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who is Vitalik Buterin, Ethereum Creator?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155291</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/who-is-vitalik-buterin-ethereum-creator"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T14:53:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Buterin’s interest in broadening Bitcoin’s scope led him to pursue a Turing-complete programming language to realize his vision. The young programmer created an initial white paper for this concept, which he called Ethereum, in 2013.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Reiff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MyLugano Crypto Payment App Adds Support for Internet Computer’s Multi-Chain Bitcoin ‘Twin’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155275</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155275/mylugano-crypto-payment-app-adds-support-for-internet-computers-multi-chain-bitcoin-twin"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Swiss city of Lugano will see more crypto adoption thanks to a partnership with the DFINITY Foundation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IMF, FSB Lay Out Roadmap To ‘Address Risks’ Posed by Crypto to Financial Stability]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155281</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155281/imf-fsb-lay-out-roadmap-to-address-the-risks-posed-by-crypto-to-financial-stability"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T13:45:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The international bodies warned of threats to monetary policy and financial stability if crypto adoption becomes widespread.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alys Key</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin Pushes for ‘Privacy Pools’ to Balance Anonymity With Regulatory Compliance]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155278</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155278/vitalik-buterin-pushes-for-privacy-pools-to-balance-anonymity-with-regulatory-compliance"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T13:18:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A research paper co-authored by the Ethereum co-founder explores a privacy-preserving blockchain protocol that complies with global regulations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Texas Paid Riot Platforms $31.7M to Slash Bitcoin Mining in August Heatwave]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155272</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155272/texas-paid-riot-platforms-31-7m-to-slash-bitcoin-mining-in-august-heatwave"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T11:43:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The mining company reduced its energy demand by 95% during the August heatwave, receiving credits for the energy it would have consumed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK’s Frontier AI Taskforce Appoints Advisors to ‘Start-Up Inside Government’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155268</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155268/uks-frontier-ai-taskforce-appoints-advisors-to-start-up-inside-government"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T10:34:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AI heavyweights joining the taskforce include a former OpenAI researcher, a Turing Award winner, and the Director of GCHQ.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alys Key</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Judge Refers Sam Bankman-Fried's Request for Pretrial Release to 3-Judge Panel]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155266</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155266/judge-refers-sam-bankman-frieds-request-for-pretrial-release-to-3-judge-panel"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T10:06:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With less than a month to go before the FTX founder’s trial, the judge has denied SBF’s request for "immediate release."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Louis Vuitton and Prada-Backed Aura Blockchain Consortium Names New CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155235</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155235/louis-vuitton-prada-backed-aura-blockchain-consortium-names-new-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T10:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aura Blockchain Consortium, which also counts Richemont and Mercedes-Benz among its members, is targeting a "new phase of growth."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephanie Hirschmiller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former OpenSea Manager Opts to Serve Prison Sentence While Appeal is Pending]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155261</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155261/former-opensea-manager-opts-to-serve-prison-sentence-while-appeal-is-pending"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T09:51:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nathaniel Chastain was previously sentenced to three months in prison for making tens of thousands of dollars through insider trades of NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Standards Board Approves Long-Sought Change in Crypto Accounting Rules]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155244</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155244/bitcoin-digital-assets-accounting-standards-gaap-fasb-sec"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T00:58:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new rules on how digital assets are reflected in business financial reporting will not include NFTs or wrapped tokens.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt AI, Edited by Ryan Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Genesis Hits Parent Company DCG With $600 Million Lawsuits]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155213</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155213/genesis-global-digital-currency-group-lawsuits-600-million-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T22:06:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The legal actions come a day after Genesis Global Trading said it would shutter its crypto spot trading operations in September.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reddit Kicks Off Football Season With NFTs of Every NFL Team]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155226</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155226/reddit-kicks-off-football-season-nfts-every-nfl-team"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T22:04:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Online discussion platform Reddit released a wave of collectible avatars Wednesday to commemorate the NFL's 32 teams as kickoff closes in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Despite the Hype, Crypto AI Tokens Have Been Languishing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155217</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155217/despite-the-hype-crypto-ai-tokens-have-been-languishing"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T20:09:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AI-inspired token category, including Fetch.ai and Worldcoin, has seen its market cap go from $170 million to $60 million in just a few months.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Open-Source ‘Falcon’ AI Language Model Overtakes Meta and Google]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155209</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155209/falcon-large-language-model-llm-ai-training-data-set"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T19:58:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meta's massive, 70-billion parameter LLaMA 2 has been outflanked by the newly released 180-billion parameter Falcon Large Language Model.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cathie Wood's Ark Invest, 21Shares Apply for First Spot Ethereum ETF]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155204</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155204/cathie-woods-ark-invest-21shares-apply-for-first-spot-ethereum-etf"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T19:12:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dubbed the ARK 21Shares Ethereum ETF, the application resembles those for spot Bitcoin ETFs that were recently delayed by the SEC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ice Cold: Feds Freeze Celsius Founder Alex Mashinsky's Assets]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155163</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155163/feds-freeze-former-celsius-ceo-alex-mashinskys-assets"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T18:37:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The alleged conman is facing a number of criminal and civil charges following the collapse of Celsius last year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Changes Policy to Allow NFT Game Ads—With Some Limits]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155185</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155185/google-changes-policy-allow-nft-game-ads-some-limits"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T18:14:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google's updated advertising policy permits NFT games, but titles that offer wagering or staking require a gambling certification.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visa Payments Will Rely on 'Multiple Blockchains', Says Head of Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155182</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155182/visa-payments-will-rely-on-multiple-blockchains-says-head-of-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T18:12:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cuy Sheffield’s post referenced skepticism attached to an early internet, when slow, chirping modems were the norm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Racing Legend Michael Andretti Bets on AI With $200 Million Zapata Merger]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155181</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155181/racing-legend-michael-andretti-bets-ai-200-million-zapata-merger"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T17:58:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IndyCar icon Michael Andretti's SPAC has agreed to merge with startup Zapata AI, which is already helping his racing teams on the track.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Cohen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Justin Bieber Producer Is Selling Royalties for the Song 'Company' as NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155164</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155164/justin-bieber-producer-selling-royalties-song-company-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T17:13:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to own a small share of streaming royalty rights for a Justin Bieber hit? AnotherBlock is set to serve them up via NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ali Shutler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Most Anticipated Crypto and NFT Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=15221</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/15221/most-anticipated-crypto-games"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T16:16:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATED: Lavish titles like Parallel and Deadrop are poised to redefine blockchain gaming. Here's what to watch for in 2023 and beyond.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward,Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Social Network Rep is Taking GalaChain Beyond Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152396</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152396/social-network-rep-is-taking-galachain-beyond-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T15:51:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rep’s novel location-based platform will integrate with Gala’s gaming, music and film platforms in innovative, social ways.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elspeth Taylor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Star Wars Outlaws: Everything You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155149</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155149/star-wars-outlaws-everything-you-need-to-know"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T15:03:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The sci-fi franchise takes its first step into open-world adventure with thief Kay Vess and her creature companion Nix in Star Wars Outlaws.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is the Bitcoin Fear and Greed Index?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155091</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-the-bitcoin-fear-and-greed-index"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T14:09:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Primarily, the Index is used to reveal the opportunity in the market. Traders can buy Bitcoin when fearful investors sell at a low price and later sell for a much higher price when the Index denotes greed, or high demand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melanie Kramer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TON Foundation Announces Registration as Swiss Non-Profit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155138</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155138/ton-foundation-announces-registration-as-swiss-non-profit"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T13:14:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The foundation that develops and manages the TON blockchain after it spun off from Telegram has found a new home in Switzerland.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aspen Launches With Tools to Help NFT Creators Reclaim Royalties]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155121</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155121/aspen-launches-tools-help-nft-creators-reclaim-royalties"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T13:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Monax Labs has debuted a tool suite that helps creators reclaim unpaid NFT royalty fees by restricting access to perks and utility.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lucy Harley-McKeown</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Marathon Digital's Bitcoin Production Drops 9% in August Due to Texas Heat]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155120</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155120/marathon-digitals-bitcoin-production-drops-9-in-august-due-to-texas-heat"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T12:41:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The mining firm blamed extreme weather conditions in the Lone Star State for the decrease in Bitcoin production in August.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global Crypto Wealth Study Reveals 6 Bitcoin Billionaires and 88,000 Crypto Millionaires]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155113</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155113/global-crypto-wealth-study-reveals-6-bitcoin-billionaires-and-88000-crypto-millionaires"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T12:31:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Henley & Partners' Crypto Adoption Index tracks the sector’s new elite and the growth and potential of the digital economy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Circle Joins Forces with Legend Trading to Broaden International Reach of USDC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155043</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155043/circle-legend-trading-usdc-stablecoin-latin-america-asia-pacific"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T12:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Legend Trading serves over 800 institutions, processes more than $1 billion a month, and aims to bring USDC to its clients.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried's Lawyers Question Former FTX Founder’s Ability to Prepare for Trial]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155101</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155101/sam-bankman-frieds-lawyers-question-former-ftx-founders-ability-to-prepare-for-trial"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T10:13:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried is currently confined at the Metropolitan Detention Center, preparing for a trial scheduled for early October.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Mino Games is Using Artificial Intelligence]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/SrT1Afj7/how-mino-games-is-using-artificial-intelligence</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/SrT1Afj7/how-mino-games-is-using-artificial-intelligence"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T22:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mino Games CEO Sasha McKinnon tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about how the studio's upcoming game Dimensionals will use real-time AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INTERVIEW: How Will Aurory Use NFTs and Crypto?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qv3VwNmM/interview-how-will-aurory-use-nfts-and-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qv3VwNmM/interview-how-will-aurory-use-nfts-and-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T15:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Natoli, Aurory's Head of Marketing and Business Development, tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how the Aurory games will use NFTs and crypto and shares the studio's broader stance on the tech.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Cloud's James Tromans on the Intersection of AI and Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OeD4uoLj/google-clouds-james-tromans-on-the-intersection-of-ai-and-web3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OeD4uoLj/google-clouds-james-tromans-on-the-intersection-of-ai-and-web3"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google's Global Head of Google Cloud for Web3 James Tromans sat down with Decrypt's Jason Nelson to discuss how AI can help Web3 companies come to market faster and the real value of Web3 tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastering NFT Trading - Degen U]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/HQGt1Vrq/mastering-nft-trading-degen-u</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/HQGt1Vrq/mastering-nft-trading-degen-u"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T07:08:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Take Degen U's new course, Mastering NFT Trading, and earn an on-chain certificate. A top instructor will help you identify trends, seize the right moment to trade, weed out scams—and have fun while doing it!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Space Nation CEO on Working With 'Independence Day' Director Roland Emmerich]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LpznLhtx/space-nation-ceo-on-working-with-independence-day-director-roland-emmerich</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LpznLhtx/space-nation-ceo-on-working-with-independence-day-director-roland-emmerich"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T17:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jerome Wu, CEO of Space Nation, tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the upcoming Space Nation Online game in development and shares details on Space Nation Cofounder Roland Emmerich's role in the project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GAME REVIEW: Champions Arena from Gala Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qUE1RlDx/game-review-champions-arena-from-gala-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qUE1RlDx/game-review-champions-arena-from-gala-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Champions Arena is a turn-based fantasy RPG from Gala Games, where characters can become NFTs and crypto can be used to purchase gems, one of the game's synthetic currencies. Decrypt's Kate Irwin takes us inside the game for her thoughts on the fun, mobile-first title.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apex Legends Voice Actor Ben Prendergast on the Future of Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/X3RKdsaG/apex-legends-voice-actor-ben-prendergast-on-the-future-of-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/X3RKdsaG/apex-legends-voice-actor-ben-prendergast-on-the-future-of-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T18:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Voice actor Ben Prendergast, who's voiced characters in games like Apex Legends and God of War Ragnarok, shares his opinions on the tech space's history of "bubbles" and whether blockchain gaming has a future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The future of AI Stardom and Robotics with SingularityNET COO Janet Adams and Desdemona]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yVQaZI71/the-future-of-ai-stardom-and-robotics-with-singularitynet-coo-janet-adams-and-desdemona</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yVQaZI71/the-future-of-ai-stardom-and-robotics-with-singularitynet-coo-janet-adams-and-desdemona"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T16:45:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this interview, SingularityNET COO Janet Adams explains the intricate details that went into creating the Desdemona robot AI from Hanson Robotics and future plans for the AI Diva.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto a 'No-Brainer' for Video Games, Says Mino Games CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rdynom8C/crypto-a-no-brainer-for-video-games-says-mino-games-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rdynom8C/crypto-a-no-brainer-for-video-games-says-mino-games-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T18:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mino Games CEO Sasha MacKinnon, developer of the upcoming Dimensionals game, tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the studio's approach to digital collectibles.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Wagner's 'Controversial Take' on Crypto in Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tc2nKeqA/michael-wagners-controversial-take-on-crypto-in-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tc2nKeqA/michael-wagners-controversial-take-on-crypto-in-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T16:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Solana's PlayGG, Star Atlas CEO Michael Wagner shares his "controversial take" on crypto in games, shares the challenges of developing the upcoming scifi game, and how crypto's volatility has changed his perspective with Decrypt's Jason Nelson.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interview: Angelic CEO on Building the Sci-Fi RPG on Solana and Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/uCzW3K7P/interview-angelic-ceo-on-building-the-sci-fi-rpg-on-solana-and-ethereum</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/uCzW3K7P/interview-angelic-ceo-on-building-the-sci-fi-rpg-on-solana-and-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T15:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Angelic is a sci-fi roleplay game in development that will be free-to-play and offer optional, opt-in crypto features on Solana and Ethereum and a governance token. Metaverse Game Studios CEO and Founder Erkan Bayol tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how he sees AAA traditional games as Angelic's main competitors and shares his vision for the game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apex Legends Voice Actor on AI's Impact on Video Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IOIrmb0N/apex-legends-voice-actor-on-ais-impact-on-video-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IOIrmb0N/apex-legends-voice-actor-on-ais-impact-on-video-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T17:28:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ben Prendergast is an actor who has voiced characters like Apex Legends' Fuse, God of War Ragnarok's Tyr, and Patroclus in Hades. But as debates swirl around the use of artificial intelligence in entertainment in light of the SAG-AFTRA and WGA strikes, Prendergast gives Decrypt's Kate Irwin his honest take on the potential use of AI actors in games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Star Atlas CEO on Developing an MMO Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/WQCaahmH/star-atlas-ceo-on-developing-an-mmo-game</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/WQCaahmH/star-atlas-ceo-on-developing-an-mmo-game"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T13:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Jason Nelson speaks with Star Atlas Founder and CEO Michael Wagner about the MMO game's approach to development, marketing, and blockchain integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aurory's Origin Story: How JRPGs Inspired the Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/O0S201TB/aurorys-origin-story-how-jrpgs-inspired-the-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/O0S201TB/aurorys-origin-story-how-jrpgs-inspired-the-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T16:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Jason Nelson talks to Aurory's Head of Marketing and Business Development Michael Natoli about the origins of the Aurory crypto games at the Solana PlayGG event.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Parallel TCG: Inside the Sci-Fi Card Game’s Closed Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/q8YVWJh4/parallel-tcg-inside-the-sci-fi-card-games-closed-beta</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/q8YVWJh4/parallel-tcg-inside-the-sci-fi-card-games-closed-beta"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T15:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin goes hands-on with Parallel’s closed beta on Windows PC to find out what sets it apart from other crypto card-battlers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 Games Need to Compete with All Games, Says Solana Foundation GM]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ud9wTd4s/web3-games-need-to-compete-with-all-games-says-solana-foundation-gm</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ud9wTd4s/web3-games-need-to-compete-with-all-games-says-solana-foundation-gm"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T19:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Foundation's General Manager of Games Johnny Lee tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about Solana's PlayGG conference and shares his take on crypto gaming and the "play-to-earn" concept.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>