<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-10-14T01:25:16.577Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-10-14T01:25:16.577Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple CEO Slams SEC for Ignoring XRP Ruling, Claims Agency Oversteps Legal Authority]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7441809fa3</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ripple-ceo-slams-sec-for-ignoring-xrp-ruling-claims-agency-oversteps-legal-authority/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T00:58:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple’s CEO has intensified criticism of the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), accusing the agency of ignoring a court ruling that XRP is not a security and overstepping its legal bounds. His remarks came after Bitnomial Exchange filed a lawsuit against the SEC, disputing the regulator’s authority over XRP futures. The case adds to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Shiba Inu (SHIB) Pattern Just Got Invalidated, Bitcoin (BTC) Secures Critical Price Level, Ethereum's (ETH) Massive Struggle at $2,400]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19999714/This-Shiba-Inu-SHIB-Pattern-Just-Got-Invalidated-Bitcoin-BTC-Secures-Critical-Price-Level-Ethereums-ETH-Massive-Struggle-at-2400</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19999714/This-Shiba-Inu-SHIB-Pattern-Just-Got-Invalidated-Bitcoin-BTC-Secures-Critical-Price-Level-Ethereums-ETH-Massive-Struggle-at-2400"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T00:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Market seeing partial recovery of momentum]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitwise CIO Matt Hougan Says He’s ‘Struck’ by Two Charts From One Solana (SOL) Rival]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19999697/Bitwise-CIO-Matt-Hougan-Says-Hes-Struck-by-Two-Charts-From-One-Solana-SOL-Rival</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19999697/Bitwise-CIO-Matt-Hougan-Says-Hes-Struck-by-Two-Charts-From-One-Solana-SOL-Rival"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T00:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitwise chief investment officer Matt Hougan is pointing out metrics for one Solana (SOL) competitor that he says are impressive. Hougan tells his followers on the social media platform X that out of all the charts he’s looked at recently, the on-chain metrics of Aptos (APT) are standing out the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microstrategy Stock MSTR Soars 1,620% — Outshining Bitcoin, S&P 500, and the Magnificent 7]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74418cc413</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/microstrategy-stock-mstr-soars-1620-outshining-bitcoin-sp-500-and-the-magnificent-7/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T23:55:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microstrategy’s stock, MSTR, has soared 1,620% since the company adopted a bitcoin-centered strategy, far outpacing bitcoin itself, the S&P 500, and tech giants such as Nvidia. The company’s bitcoin holdings now exceed 252,000 BTC. Microstrategy’s executive chairman, Michael Saylor, remains bullish about bitcoin’s price as his company plans to further boost its BTC investments. Microstrategy’s […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scroll Co-founder Defends Binance Partnership Amid User Dissatisfaction]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19999737/Scroll-Co-founder-Defends-Binance-Partnership-Amid-User-Dissatisfaction</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19999737/Scroll-Co-founder-Defends-Binance-Partnership-Amid-User-Dissatisfaction"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T23:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto community has significantly criticized the Ethereum Layer-2 network Scroll’s SCR governance token on Binance Launchpool. Scroll, a zkEVM rollup, currently ranks as the sixth-largest Ethereum Layer-2 network. Data from DeFillama shows that the total value locked (TVL) on it is $1.09...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[S15 E59: David Burkett on MWEB & Privacy]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19999711/S15-E59-David-Burkett-on-MWEB-Privacy</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19999711/S15-E59-David-Burkett-on-MWEB-Privacy"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T23:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MWEB (MimbleWimble Extension Block) is a way to add privacy & extra scalability on a parallel blockchain. First proposed by Andrew Poelstra in 2016, it was quickly forgotten in the Bitcoin world. But thanks to David Burkett, it's now live on Litecoin.Time stamps:Introduction to MWEB and David...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Franklin Templeton Introduces Tokenized Money Market Fund BENJI on Avalanche Network]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19999739/Franklin-Templeton-Introduces-Tokenized-Money-Market-Fund-BENJI-on-Avalanche-Network</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19999739/Franklin-Templeton-Introduces-Tokenized-Money-Market-Fund-BENJI-on-Avalanche-Network"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T23:31:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by   /u/Bullzilla123 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New South Korean Regulator ‘Could Speed Up Bitcoin ETF Verdict’]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19999682/New-South-Korean-Regulator-Could-Speed-Up-Bitcoin-ETF-Verdict</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19999682/New-South-Korean-Regulator-Could-Speed-Up-Bitcoin-ETF-Verdict"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T23:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new South Korean regulatory body is set to launch this month, with a ruling on Bitcoin ETF approval reportedly high on its agenda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Craig Wright Says Michael Saylor’s Plan For A Bitcoin Bank Is Betraying Bitcoin – But Why?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74418f8083</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/craig-wright-says-michael-saylors-plan-for-a-bitcoin-bank-is-betraying-bitcoin-but-why/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T23:14:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Saylor’s aggressive Bitcoin strategy over the past few years has largely paid off for him and MicroStrategy, making the company now one of the largest corporate holders of Bitcoin. In a recent interview, Saylor unveiled an ambitious plan to transform MicroStrategy into a leading Bitcoin bank, aiming to capitalize on the growing interest in digital currencies and enhance the company’s role in the crypto ecosystem. 
 
 
This plan does not sit well with some crypto participants like Craig Wright, a controversial figure who has controversially claimed to be the creator of Bitcoin.
 
In a recent post on social media platform X, Wright called out Michael Saylor, accusing him of defying Bitcoin’s true essence.
 
Craig Wright Says Saylor Is Betraying Bitcoin
 
According to Craig Wright, Bi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple whales accumulate as XRP struggles with key resistance]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19999644/Ripple-whales-accumulate-as-XRP-struggles-with-key-resistance</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19999644/Ripple-whales-accumulate-as-XRP-struggles-with-key-resistance"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T23:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple's XRP has been trading sideways, failing to break through critical resistance levels.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brazillian Central Bank Invites New Participants to CBDC Pilot Program]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7441890226</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/brazillian-central-bank-invites-new-participants-to-cbdc-pilot-program/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T22:54:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Brazilian Central Bank is opening the drex CBDC pilot to new entrants, aiming to test more advanced use cases and privacy solutions for the project’s second phase. Thirteen use cases have been confirmed, including carbon credits, agricultural bonds, and foreign trade platforms. Brazilian Central Banks Opens CBDC Pilot to New Consortiums Brazil is preparing […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Google Search Volume Falls To New 2024 Low — What’s Happening?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e744189b996</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-google-search-volume-falls-to-2024-low/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T22:45:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following a strong start to 2024, the Bitcoin price performance has been mostly disappointing all year, failing to capitalize on the strong momentum of the spot exchange-traded funds (ETFs). Despite its stop-start nature, BTC’s price action has been one of the most-talked topics in the crypto space this year.
 
However, the latest on-chain data shows the searches for the Bitcoin keyword on the Google search engine have crashed to a new yearly low, leaving investors wondering whether it’s bullish or bearish for the BTC price. Here’s how it might impact the price of the flagship cryptocurrency.
 
Is The Crash In Bitcoin Google Searches Bullish Or Bearish?
 
In a recent post on X, CryptoQuant CEO Ki Young revealed that the number of people searching for the Bitcoin keyword on Google has reach…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Opeyemi Sule</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin Offloads Over $2 Million in Meme Coins, Donates to Charity]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19999663/Vitalik-Buterin-Offloads-Over-2-Million-in-Meme-Coins-Donates-to-Charity</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19999663/Vitalik-Buterin-Offloads-Over-2-Million-in-Meme-Coins-Donates-to-Charity"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T22:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum co-founder Vitalik Buterin has once again offloaded a substantial portion of his meme coin holdings, amassing over $2 million from these transactions in the last day alone. Buterin is expected to direct the proceeds toward charitable causes, which is his consistent practice of handling...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Akash CEO Greg Osuri on DePIN’s appeal to mainstream users — and regulators]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19999576/Akash-CEO-Greg-Osuri-on-DePINs-appeal-to-mainstream-users-and-regulators</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19999576/Akash-CEO-Greg-Osuri-on-DePINs-appeal-to-mainstream-users-and-regulators"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T22:04:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Advocates of decentralized physical infrastructure networks, or DePIN, often claim that projects in the space, which generally aim to leverage blockchain technology in order to grant users control and ownership over physical infrastructure networks in the real world, from GPU chips to wireless...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Bitcoin' search volume drops to a yearly low, while 'memecoin' surges]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19999560/Bitcoin-search-volume-drops-to-a-yearly-low-while-memecoin-surges</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19999560/Bitcoin-search-volume-drops-to-a-yearly-low-while-memecoin-surges"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T21:52:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Memecoins experienced double-digit gains during September 2024, primarily driven by new token creation on the Solana and Tron networks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Post-FTX Collapse: 16 Settlements Finalized in Two Years Indicate Heightened Regulatory Focus]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19999528/Post-FTX-Collapse-16-Settlements-Finalized-in-Two-Years-Indicate-Heightened-Regulatory-Focus</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19999528/Post-FTX-Collapse-16-Settlements-Finalized-in-Two-Years-Indicate-Heightened-Regulatory-Focus"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T21:15:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fallout from FTX's collapse resulted in numerous lawsuits and settlements, as per CoinGecko.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Crypto Games: ‘Off the Grid’ Launches, ‘X Empire’ Airdrop Date, TikTok Gets Tap-to-Earn]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286058</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286058/this-week-crypto-games-off-the-grid-x-empire"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T21:08:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche game Off the Grid is making waves in early access, while X Empire is gearing up for its airdrop. Here are the week's biggest gaming stories.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Crypto Games: ‘Off the Grid’ Launches, ‘X Empire’ Airdrop Date, TikTok Gets Tap-to-Earn]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19999526/This-Week-in-Crypto-Games-Off-the-Grid-Launches-X-Empire-Airdrop-Date-TikTok-Gets-Tap-to-Earn</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19999526/This-Week-in-Crypto-Games-Off-the-Grid-Launches-X-Empire-Airdrop-Date-TikTok-Gets-Tap-to-Earn"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T21:08:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche game Off the Grid is making waves in early access, while X Empire is gearing up for its airdrop. Here are the week's biggest gaming stories.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling Bitcoin to 2050 w/ Shinobi, Marco  Argentieri, Simanta Gautam, Alex Bosworth]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19999524/Scaling-Bitcoin-to-2050-w-Shinobi-Marco-Argentieri-Simanta-Gautam-Alex-Bosworth</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19999524/Scaling-Bitcoin-to-2050-w-Shinobi-Marco-Argentieri-Simanta-Gautam-Alex-Bosworth"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T21:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us for an in-depth exploration of Bitcoin's scaling challenges and the innovative solutions being developed to address them. Industry leaders discuss the merits of various layer 2 technologies, including Lightning Network and rollups, and how they could shape the future of cryptocurrency...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Activity Spikes, but $3,000 Remains Out of Reach]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19999525/Ethereum-Activity-Spikes-but-3000-Remains-Out-of-Reach</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19999525/Ethereum-Activity-Spikes-but-3000-Remains-Out-of-Reach"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ethereum network has experienced a surge in activity over the past week, with a significant rise in daily active addresses and new accounts. However, despite this increase in network activity, ETH price has faced selling pressure, as traders continue to offload the altcoin, raising concerns...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Bitcoin Miners Are Tapping Into the AI Gold Rush – Part 2]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74417205e5</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/how-bitcoin-miners-are-tapping-into-the-ai-gold-rush-part-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T20:54:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The following guest post comes from Bitcoinminingstock.io, the one-stop hub for all things bitcoin mining stocks, educational tools, and industry insights. Originally published on Sept. 3, 2024, it was penned by Bitcoinminingstock.io author Cindy Feng. In the piece, Feng follows up on her first report on how bitcoin miners are branching out into high-performance computing […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Guest Author</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Serbia says joining BRICS is far better than joining the EU]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19999509/Serbia-says-joining-BRICS-is-far-better-than-joining-the-EU</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19999509/Serbia-says-joining-BRICS-is-far-better-than-joining-the-EU"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T20:40:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Serbia says it’s better off joining BRICS than the European Union. The country’s Deputy Prime Minister, Aleksandar Vulin, claims BRICS offers much more than the EU and demands nothing in return. Vulin made these remarks in an interview with National Defense magazine. He emphasized that Serbia...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP to be Adopted By Big Global Banks as Ripple Eyes Growing $16 Trillion Custody Market]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19999484/XRP-to-be-Adopted-By-Big-Global-Banks-as-Ripple-Eyes-Growing-16-Trillion-Custody-Market</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19999484/XRP-to-be-Adopted-By-Big-Global-Banks-as-Ripple-Eyes-Growing-16-Trillion-Custody-Market"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T20:11:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a significant move to bolster its position in the digital asset infrastructure space, Ripple has announced a major expansion of its custody services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[#Bitcoin The 200 Week Moving Average Heatmap is still in its "cool" territory.

What this shows is the distance price is trading from the Weekly 200MA.

The closer to the 200MA, the better it is to accumulate.

Price extending far away from the 200MA? Likely good to take profits.]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19999485/Bitcoin-The-200-Week-Moving-Average-Heatmap-is-still-in-its-cool-territory-What-this-shows-is-the-distance-price-is-trading-from-the-Weekly-200MA-The-closer-to-the-200MA-the-better-it-is-to-accumulate-Price-extending-far-away-from-the-200MA-Likely-good-to-</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19999485/Bitcoin-The-200-Week-Moving-Average-Heatmap-is-still-in-its-cool-territory-What-this-shows-is-the-distance-price-is-trading-from-the-Weekly-200MA-The-closer-to-the-200MA-the-better-it-is-to-accumulate-Price-extending-far-away-from-the-200MA-Likely-good-to-"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T20:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Analyst Predicts Incoming Parabolic Rally for Bitcoin, Says Wait Almost Over for BTC]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19999438/Crypto-Analyst-Predicts-Incoming-Parabolic-Rally-for-Bitcoin-Says-Wait-Almost-Over-for-BTC</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19999438/Crypto-Analyst-Predicts-Incoming-Parabolic-Rally-for-Bitcoin-Says-Wait-Almost-Over-for-BTC"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T20:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A closely followed crypto strategist and trader believes that steep rallies are now in sight for Bitcoin (BTC). Pseudonymous analyst Inmortal tells his 216,500 followers on the social media platform X that Bitcoin appears to be mirroring its 2023 price action. Back then, Bitcoin consolidated...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wall Street braces for earnings and retail sales reports – now what about crypto?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19999433/Wall-Street-braces-for-earnings-and-retail-sales-reports-now-what-about-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19999433/Wall-Street-braces-for-earnings-and-retail-sales-reports-now-what-about-crypto"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T19:54:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wall Street is getting ready for a big week as corporate earnings reports and retail sales data take center stage. Investors are hungry for more signs of the U.S. economy’s strength after recent gains in equity markets. The benchmark S&P 500 is set to post its fifth straight weekly gain, soaring...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Todd: HBO Documentary’s Satoshi Nakamoto Claim Endangers My Life]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74417ee74e</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/peter-todd-hbo-documentarys-satoshi-nakamoto-claim-endangers-my-life/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T19:52:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software developer Peter Todd has dismissed the HBO documentary identifying him as Satoshi Nakamoto, the creator of Bitcoin. Todd expressed concern that the documentary could endanger his life due to the significant amount of wealth associated with Satoshi Nakamoto. Two experts argue that newer crypto users are less interested in the creator’s identity and are […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency: How It Works, Pros, and Risks Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19999417/Cryptocurrency-How-It-Works-Pros-and-Risks-Explained</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19999417/Cryptocurrency-How-It-Works-Pros-and-Risks-Explained"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T19:41:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency offers high rewards but comes with risks like volatility and regulatory challenges, making it essential for investors to stay informed and cautious.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase’s Base Set To Overtake Arbitrum To Become The Biggest Ethereum L2 Network]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e744179d8f2</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/coinbases-base-set-to-overtake-arbitrum-to-become-the-biggest-ethereum-l2-network/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T19:17:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Base, the Ethereum layer-2 scaling solution from crypto exchange Coinbase, has witnessed a surge in activity in the past two months and is now gunning for the top spot in the Ethereum ecosystem. 
 
 
In an interesting development revealed by data from IntoTheBlock, the transaction volume on Base has increased massively within this timeframe, with it capturing about 40% to 60% of all volume to outpace Optimism and Arbitrum. Now, recent data in the past 24 hours show Base now seems to have made the leap to solidify its leading position in terms of total value locked (TVL).
 
Base Surges To Become Ethereum’s Biggest L2 Network
 
Base operates as a layer 2 network on Ethereum launched by Coinbase to offer a safe, low-cost, developer-friendly way to build on-chain. Since its inception, Base has…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Price At $0.1 And Dogecoin Price At $50? Stop Chasing Pipe Dreams And Buy This Token Set To Rally 5,233% In 10 Days]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e744179d8f0</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-price-at-0-1-and-dogecoin-price-at-50-stop-chasing-pipe-dreams-and-buy-this-token-set-to-rally-5233-in-10-days/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T19:17:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto analysts have continued to make ambitious price targets regarding how high the Shiba Inu price and the Dogecoin price can rise in the long term. However, several factors indicate the Shiba Inu price and Dogecoin price might eventually reach these price targets. Therefore, investors are better off focusing on the ETFSwap (ETFS) token, which is set to rally by 5,233% in 10 days. 
 
Analyst Says ETFSwap (ETFS) Token Will Rally 5,233% In 10 Days 
An analyst has predicted that the ETFSwap (ETFS) token will rally 5,233% in 10 days from its current price of $0.03846 in its ongoing presale. The analyst stated that this price rally will happen as soon as the token gets listed on exchanges. He further explained that the demand for the ETFS token will be massive as investors will be looking to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Shows Mixed Signals Amid Consolidation: Is a Reversal Coming Soon?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7441640bef</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-shows-mixed-signals-amid-consolidation-is-a-reversal-coming-soon/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T18:52:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) has experienced a steady decline in recent sessions, but technical indicators are sending mixed messages, hinting at a possible market shift on the horizon. Despite the bearish price trend, oscillators are providing a mix of neutral, buy, and sell signals, reflecting indecision among traders. Bitcoin On the 1-hour chart, bitcoin’s (BTC) downward trajectory […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: GOAT Meme Coin, Created by AI Bot, Gains Massive Value Over the Past Day]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74416f387e</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/report-goat-meme-coin-created-by-ai-bot-gains-massive-value-over-the-past-day/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T16:51:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A meme coin named GOAT, issued by an artificial intelligence (AI) bot known as “Truth Terminal,” has gained significant traction with a dramatic rise in value. According to a report published by chaincatcher.com, authored by Deep Tide Techflow, on Oct. 11, the meme coin achieved a 12,000% increase in the first 24 hours, bringing attention […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Professor Coin: How Do You Price Cryptocurrencies Like Bitcoin and Ethereum?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=250329</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/250329/professor-coin-how-price-cryptocurrencies"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T16:34:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Three recent academic papers explore how to price cryptocurrencies when—unlike companies—they don’t have balance sheets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Urquhart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Best Free Games to Play on Sony PS5]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286023</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286023/best-free-games-sony-ps5"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T16:17:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking for some great games to play on your PlayStation 5 without paying a dime? Here are our favorite PS5 freebies right now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Frederiksen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bored Ape Sells for $1.43M Amid 8.78% NFT Market Decline This Week]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e744155e9f5</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bored-ape-sells-for-1-43m-amid-8-78-nft-market-decline-this-week/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T15:50:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NFT sales experienced a dip this week, dropping 8.78% compared to the previous seven days. Total sales amounted to $77.46 million, with a sharp decrease in both buyers (down 64.47%) and sellers (down 66.40%). Bitcoin NFTs Surge 29.36% as Overall NFT Sales Dropped Over the past week, the digital collectible market struggled, bringing in $77.46 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Up to $1.3 Billion in Ethereum From PlusToken Ponzi Scheme Set to Hit Exchanges: Analysts]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285873</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285873/ethereum-seized-plustoken-ponzi-hit-market"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T15:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The looming sale of up to $1.3 billion in Ethereum seized from PlusToken could “dramatically increase selling pressure,” analysts said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk-Themed Telegram Game 'X Empire' Will End Season a Week Before Airdrop]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286019</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286019/telegram-x-empire-end-chill-phase-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T15:13:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are they for real this time? With the token launch and airdrop set for late October, Telegram game X Empire will cut off its gameplay soon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Are Today’s ‘X Empire’ Elon Musk Game Daily Combo, Riddle, and Rebus Solutions]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241078</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/todays-musk-empire-stock-exchange-daily-combo"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T14:45:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking for the X Empire daily combo and rebus solution for Sunday, October 13? Here are the latest boosts for the Telegram game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Is Today’s 'Captain Tsubasa: Rivals' Telegram Game Daily Combo]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=250928</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/captain-tsubasa-rivals-telegram-game-daily-combo"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T14:40:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anime soccer game Captain Tsubasa: Rivals gives out 5 million free daily balls ahead of the TON token airdrop. Here’s the combo for Sunday, October 13.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump Reveals Defi Project’s Token Launch—But Not Everyone’s Happy About It]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e744159ef11</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/donald-trump-reveals-defi-projects-token-launch-but-not-everyones-happy-about-it/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T13:49:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Saturday, former President Donald Trump announced that the World Liberty Financial (WLF) token sale will kick off on Tuesday, Oct. 15. In his post on X, Trump described it as a “chance to help shape the future of finance.” He also noted that an X Spaces discussion about the token launch will be aired […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Demand Growing At Fastest Pace Since April — Is BTC Price Next?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7441452ea8</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-demand-growing-at-fastest-pace-since-april/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T13:14:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to the latest on-chain data, demand for Bitcoin, the world’s largest cryptocurrency, has been picking up pace over the last few days. The question here is — can this growing pressure jumpstart the Bitcoin bull run?
 
Can The Latest Demand Spike Restart The Bull Run?
 
CryptoQuant’s head of research Julio Moreno took to the X platform to share an interesting on-chain observation about Bitcoin and investors’ appetite over the last few weeks. According to the on-chain expert, apparent demand for BTC is growing at its fastest monthly pace since April 22.
 
This on-chain revelation is based on the apparent demand metric, which measures the difference between the daily total Bitcoin block subsidy and the daily change in the amount of Bitcoin held for one year or longer. This metric ref…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Opeyemi Sule</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoin Liquidity Surges, JPMorgan Predicts Q4 Gains, and More — Week in Review]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74414d9207</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/stablecoin-liquidity-surges-jpmorgan-predicts-q4-gains-and-more-week-in-review/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T11:48:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In September 2024, stablecoin liquidity hit record highs. Meanwhile, JPMorgan analysts predicted further Bitcoin gains, citing October’s historical “Uptober” trend. The FBI made headlines by charging 18 individuals involved in crypto fraud after setting up a fake crypto operation. Economist Peter Schiff warned of impending financial ruin unless the U.S. allows its “phony economy” to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Sencil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Data Shows Slowing Bitcoin Volatility – Setting Up For The Next Rally?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74413146a8</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/new-data-shows-slowing-bitcoin-volatility-setting-up-for-the-next-rally/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T09:45:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin is currently holding above the $62,000 mark following a 5% surge from lower demand in the past few days. While the market grapples with uncertainty, recent data from Coinglass indicates that Bitcoin’s volatility has significantly decreased during this period of sideways trading. This reduction in volatility often serves as a precursor to major price movements, leading many investors to speculate that a significant shift in market dynamics could be on the horizon.
 
 
As traders analyze market trends, the prevailing sentiment is mixed, with some expressing optimism about a potential bullish rally, while others remain cautious due to the current volatility landscape.
 
With many eyes on Bitcoin’s next move, the question remains: will it break out to new highs, or will it face further…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Villafuerte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain Takes Root: USDA Approves Blockchain-Based Certification System]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74413146a7</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/blockchain-takes-root-usda-approves-blockchain-based-certification-system/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T09:45:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US cattle industry is going blockchain. Decentralized cow verification service, CattleProof’s “Verified,” has been approved, giving it the historic title as the United States Department of Agriculture’s very first blockchain-based Process Verified Program (PVP). CattleProof is a Wyoming company that uses the distributed ledger technology to store individual cow’s data. 
 
 
Blockchain For Livestock Verification
 
The electronic identification tags attached to each animal provide a combination of data, noting the animal’s condition, location, and many other attributes, which are then stored immutably on a blockchain. This change dramatically makes tracking easier with farm-to-fork traceability also enabling farmers to observe the health of the animals in real time for better care and mo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Serial Entrepreneur: Web3 Stagnant, Echoing 1980s AI]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7441315987</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/serial-entrepreneur-web3-stagnant-echoing-1980s-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T09:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to Bernie Bloom, overcoming the blockchain trilemma requires building storage solutions that scale to exabytes and integrate seamlessly with smart contracts. Bloom, a serial entrepreneur and co-founder of Xandeum Labs, argues that this is essential for the “wholeness” of smart contract blockchains. Storage: A Key to Resolving the Blockchain Trilemma In written responses shared […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kenya Launches Digital and AI Skills Center]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e744124b5a0</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/kenya-launches-digital-and-ai-skills-center/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T07:36:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kenya, in partnership with the United Nations Development Program (UNDP) and Microsoft, has established the Africa Centre of Competence for Digital and AI Skill. This center aims to equip public sector employees with digital and AI skills to improve service delivery across Africa. It aligns with Kenya’s National Digital Master Plan and focuses on topics […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Are Based Roll-Ups? A Beginner’s Guide]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7441219d0e</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/what-are-based-roll-ups-a-beginners-guide/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T06:36:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This piece is a guest post by Blocmates. Blocmates is an invaluable crypto news and educational resource that offers clarity in the often complicated and jargon-filled crypto space. In this article, author Gaz critiques Vitalik Buterin’s recent actions, while explaining the advancements in Ethereum scaling solutions like roll-ups, particularly focusing on “based roll-ups.” From Token […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Guest Author</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is ‘Off the Grid’? The Buzzy Battle Royale Shooter Built on Avalanche]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285941</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-off-the-grid-battle-royale-shooter-avalanche"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T20:10:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Off the Grid just launched on PS5, Xbox, and PC in early access, and it's already a hit with players—oh, and it's a blockchain game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Stubbs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accused $150M Crypto Fraudster Turns Fugitive After Disabling Ankle Monitor]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285882</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285882/accused-150m-crypto-fraudster-fugitive"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T15:57:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Horst Jicha is being treated as a fugitive after the accused crypto scammer's ankle monitor went dark and he skipped a pre-trial meeting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gotbit? Never Heard of It! Meme Coins Try to Distance Themselves]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285890</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285890/gotbit-charges-meme-coins-distance-themselves"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T22:39:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Numerous token projects now claim they have severed ties with market maker Gotbit after it was hit with market manipulation charges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Labs Co-Founder Donates $1 Million in XRP to Pro-Kamala Harris PAC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285904</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285904/ripple-cofounder-1-million-kamala-harris-election"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T22:23:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An FEC filing released this week shows that Chris Larsen donated more than 1,700,000 XRP to the Future Forward USA PAC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Napolitano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche Shooter 'Off the Grid' Becomes Top Free Title on Epic Games Store]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285896</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285896/avalanche-shooter-off-the-grid-becomes-top-free-title-on-epic-games-store"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T20:49:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following its early access release, the Avalanche-based battle royale shooter Off the Grid saw notable traction on the Epic Games Store.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Crypto Project World Liberty Financial Sets Token Sale Date]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285871</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285871/trump-world-liberty-financial-token-sale"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T20:40:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Donald Trump-backed DeFi project World Liberty Financial will launch its token sale for accredited investors next week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wall Street Is on a Bull Run—It’s Nothing Compared to Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285872</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285872/wall-street-bull-run-bitcoin-dominates"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T20:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The S&P 500 is up 60% over the last two years, but Bitcoin's price jump during the same span has crushed that mark.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prediction Markets Invite Insider Trading—And That’s a Good Thing, Experts Say]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285857</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285857/prediction-markets-insider-trading"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T19:36:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Platforms like Polymarket are attracting billions of dollars in bets, but appear to be doing little to prevent insider trading. Is that a flaw, or a feature?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When to Expect Season 2 of Telegram Crypto Game 'Hamster Kombat']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285855</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285855/hamster-kombat-telegram-season-2"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T19:01:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Players who withdrew their HMSTR tokens will have the option to deposit them into Hamster Kombat for benefits, the devs told Decrypt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy Aims to Be ‘Bitcoin Bank’ With Trillion-Dollar Valuation: Michael Saylor]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285838</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285838/microstrategy-bitcoin-bank-trillion-dollar"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T18:20:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With nearly $16 billion worth of Bitcoin in the bank, MicroStrategy's Michael Saylor shares big plans ahead for BTC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeLorean, Christopher Lloyd Reunite for Time Capsule Digital Collectibles]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285836</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285836/delorean-christopher-lloyd-reunite-for-time-capsule-digital-collectibles"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T18:15:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lloyd features in a new promo film for the digital collectibles, which unlock exclusive prizes including a new DeLorean EV.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk-Themed Telegram Game ‘X Empire’ Sets Airdrop Date]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285834</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285834/telegram-game-x-empire-airdrop-date"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T17:40:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The X token launch is less than two weeks away, and will follow X Empire’s brief “chill phase” season after the airdrop was delayed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Exec Ryan Salame Headed to Prison After Tucker Carlson Video Derails 'Dog Bite' Claim]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285811</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285811/ftx-ryan-salame-prison-tucker-carlson"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T16:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ryan Salame's latest request for a prison postponement wasn't granted, due in part to a Tucker Carlson video interview posted this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Christopher Lloyd Reunites With Delorean to Unveil the Time Capsule]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285684</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285684/christopher-lloyd-reunites-with-delorean-to-unveil-the-time-capsule"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T15:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DeLorean Labs will be giving away a brand new electric vehicle.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Press Releases</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Gets a Boost as Mt. Gox Postpones Repayments]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285812</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285812/bitcoin-mt-gox-postpones-repayments"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T15:29:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mt. Gox now has another full year to repay billions of dollars in Bitcoin to users of the hacked exchange. Here's why BTC is now rising.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward,Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Karate Combat Launches Layer-2 Network to License Game Model to Other Sports]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285706</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285706/karate-combat-layer2-license-game-model-up-token"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T14:16:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Karate Combat, a crypto-friendly fighting organization, is set to launch a layer-2 next year in a move to help other sports copy its betting app.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Has Been Stuck Trading Sideways After Halving—What's Different This Time?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285793</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285793/bitcoin-trading-sideways-whats-different"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T14:09:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some "components of this cycle, such as altcoin seasons or bull runs, might have different timelines than we’re used to seeing," an analyst said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Creditor Says Hedge Fund Owes Him for Claim It Bought at '42% Discount']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285785</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285785/ftx-creditor-sues-hedge-fund"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T12:10:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gierczyk sold his $1.59 million claim to the hedge fund last year at what he says was a 42% discount.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Exec Tigran Gambaryan Denied Bail Despite 'Meeting All the Requirements,' Says Family]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285782</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285782/binance-exec-tigran-gambaryan-denied-bail-despite-meeting-all-the-requirements-says-family"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T11:33:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gambaryan has "suffered countless health scares," the family spokesperson said in an emailed statement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla Reveals Autonomous Robotaxi and Robovan, Plans 2025 Self-Driving Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285760</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285760/the-future-should-look-like-the-future-elon-musk-says-at-robotaxi-reveal"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T06:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The late-night presentation showed off Tesla's new line of self-driving vehicles and updates to its Optimus robots.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From LinkedIn to LockedIn: Former FTX Exec Ryan Salame Shares Bizarre Prison Post]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285759</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285759/former-ftx-exec-ryan-salame-shares-bizarre-prison-post"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T05:45:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Salame, who once held a high-flying position at FTX, is now one of several executives to face consequences following the exchange's fall]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vismaya V</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Metaplanet Scoops Another $6.5 Million in Bitcoin, Doubling Down on Its October Spree]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285756</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285756/metaplanet-scoops-6-5-million-bitcoin-doubling-down-october-spree"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T05:08:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Metaplanet's latest purchase brings the company's total Bitcoin holdings to 748.502 BTC, reinforcing its long-term bet on the leading crypto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Holds Steady Despite SEC's Case Against Market Maker Cumberland DRW]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285754</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285754/bitcoin-price-holds-steady-despite-secs-case-against-market-maker-cumberland-drw"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T01:59:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Thursday, the SEC charged Cumberland DRW with various securities allegations, though bellwether Bitcoin has so far shrugged it off.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Sinclair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your Lifelike Zoom Clone May Soon be Taking Meetings For You. Here's How]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285732</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285732/your-lifelike-zoom-clone-may-soon-be-taking-meetings-for-you-heres-how"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T00:22:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Zoom prepares to launch lifelike AI clones in 2025, the company is banking on a rethink to workplace communication—for better or worse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who is Cumberland, the SEC's Latest Big Crypto Target?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285729</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285729/what-is-cumberland-sec-lawsuit-crypto"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T00:09:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC's latest target isn't exactly a household name. Yet, as a critical liquidity provider, Cumberland is one of crypto’s major players.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Napolitano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Justin Sun Is Now Prime Minister of Liberland—What Does That Even Mean?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285717</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285717/justin-sun-prime-minister-liberland"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T23:12:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Liberland is an imagined libertarian utopia on the Danube, where every system lives on-chain and the age of consent is 13.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto ETFs Still Hot, With Nearly 50% of U.S. Investors Planning to Buy: Charles Schwab]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285715</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285715/crypto-etfs-still-hot-nearly-50-u-s-investors-planning-buy"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T22:48:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Charles Schwab survey shows that there’s massive demand for new American Bitcoin and Ethereum exchange-traded funds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Labs Files Cross-Appeal as Battle With SEC Rages On]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285714</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285714/ripple-labs-cross-appeal-sec"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T22:23:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Labs moved to file a cross-appeal in its years-long legal battle with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission over XRP sales.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Falls Under $60,000 as $150 Million in Crypto Longs Get Rekt]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=284560</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/284560/bitcoin-falls-60000-150m-longs-rekt"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T21:55:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin dipped below the $60,000 mark Thursday after three weeks above that line. What's to blame for the latest cooldown?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Settles Charges With Trading Firm It Says Tricked Investors With AI 'Buzzwords']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285680</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285680/sec-trading-firm-tricked-investors-ai"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T20:40:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC has hit trading firm Rimar Capital with civil charges for allegedly lying to investors about its use of AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentraland Desktop Client Preview]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qqzvDcTC/decentraland-desktop-client-preview</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qqzvDcTC/decentraland-desktop-client-preview"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T15:53:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum metaverse game Decentraland has shared an exclusive look at the visual and performance upgrades coming via its new desktop client.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Trader Murad Mahmudov talks about the Supercycle and how he chooses Meme Coins.]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Hj3nDp7G/crypto-trader-murad-mahmudov-talks-about-the-supercycle-and-how-he-chooses-meme-coins</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Hj3nDp7G/crypto-trader-murad-mahmudov-talks-about-the-supercycle-and-how-he-chooses-meme-coins"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T21:47:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Trader Murad Mahmudov talks about the Supercycle and how he chooses Meme Coins. Crypto stable, had sold off after China stocks fall. Crypto adopted faster than other tech: BlackRock. Crypto adoption to hit 8% of world population. CryptoCom recieves Wells notice from SEC. HBO documentary on Satoshi airs tonight. FTX bankruptcy plan approved by judge. Scroll airdrop may be imminent. Jupiter goes live on mobile iOS. Phantom rolls out support for Base. AAVE launches GHO on Base. Gensler may be replaced by Robinhood CLO. 87% of new token launches on SOL. National Bank of Bahrain creates BTC fund. BedRock DeFi allows BTC staking on ARB.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Memecoins take off, funding stays low, China stocks keep on rising!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/703mAYhV/memecoins-take-off-funding-stays-low-china-stocks-keep-on-rising</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/703mAYhV/memecoins-take-off-funding-stays-low-china-stocks-keep-on-rising"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T08:27:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR EP213. Memecoins take off, funding stays low, China stocks keep on rising!
Many altcoins & memecoins soar despite stable BTC. Funding rates continue to be low or negative. Crypto funds saw $147m of outflows last week. BTC remains best performing major assets this year. SUI breaks into the top 20 coins again. TAO leads top 100 away from memes, sifu shorts. $100m bridge to SOL over the last 7 days. Metaplanet buys $6.7m more BTC. ETH proposal aims to improve throughput 50%. EIGEN, OP, APT lead token unlocks this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Walrus Protocol Unlocks New Applications for Decentralized Data Storage]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kwEYLYWj/how-walrus-protocol-unlocks-new-applications-for-decentralized-data-storage</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kwEYLYWj/how-walrus-protocol-unlocks-new-applications-for-decentralized-data-storage"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T11:19:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mysten Labs Chief Scientist George Danezis joined Decrypt to talk about its new decentralized storage protocol Walrus, which promises to unlock new applications such as AI and social media, thanks to its novel Red Stuff data encoding algorithm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Coinbase Sees Crypto as a Bipartisan, 'Purple' Political Issue]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/YR2YmmwR/why-coinbase-sees-crypto-as-a-bipartisan-purple-political-issue</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/YR2YmmwR/why-coinbase-sees-crypto-as-a-bipartisan-purple-political-issue"/>
        <updated>2024-10-05T22:18:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase VP of Corporate and Business Development, Shan Aggarwal, joined Decrypt's Sander Lutz and Liz Napolitano at Messari Mainnet 2024 to discuss the exchange's efforts to grow mainstream crypto adoption—and how the changing political conversation around digital assets is rapidly playing a major role in that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Is Playing Offense—Not Just Defense—Against Crypto Crime, Says Head of Financial Investigations]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DiJ8D2Qc/binance-is-playing-offensenot-just-defenseagainst-crypto-crime-says-head-of-financial-investigations</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DiJ8D2Qc/binance-is-playing-offensenot-just-defenseagainst-crypto-crime-says-head-of-financial-investigations"/>
        <updated>2024-10-05T01:58:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nils Anderson Röed, the exchange’s global head of financial investigations, sat down with Decrypt’s Sander Lutz at Messari Mainnet 2024 to discuss how Binance is proactively dismantling criminal networks around the world, the strategy with which the crypto exchange is approaching sensitive conflicts in the Middle East, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 212 - SEEDPHRASE TALKS ART!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PJfaJNkZ/fomo-hour-212-seedphrase-talks-art</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PJfaJNkZ/fomo-hour-212-seedphrase-talks-art"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T19:29:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Payrolls Higher than expected, Bitcoin reacts hard. Crypto sank early in the week as Middle East tensions spooked markets. Powell signals two more rate cuts this year. SUI leads L1s again, nears YTD high despite large unlock. Majority of FTX repayments still months away. EIGEN becomes non-transferable, hits $6bn FDV. SEC to appeal Ripple securities law ruling. Visa launches tokenization platform for banks. SWIFT plans digital asset trial in 2025. ByBit launched trading of global stock indices. SPX, GIGA & FWOG hit ATHs, most memes fall. XCOPY to release 250 piece collection on Shape. HBO documentary claims to have identified Satoshi.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Altcoins bleed, ByBit launches stock index trading, POCHITA soars]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kYjAt3nt/altcoins-bleed-bybit-launches-stock-index-trading-pochita-soars</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kYjAt3nt/altcoins-bleed-bybit-launches-stock-index-trading-pochita-soars"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T21:11:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Altcoins sink, BTC dominance nears cycle high. BTC in ‘three blind mice’ downtrend. Tron revenue hits record $577m in Q3. ByBit to launch trading of major stock indices. Franklin Templeton launch fund on APT. SWIFT banks to trial digital assets in 2025. Aerodrome hits $1bn TVL on Base. Cronje calls out Aerodrome for copyright. ETH ICO wallet sells $47m. SEC files appeal against Ripple ruling. EIGEN falls 20% on staking rewards FUD. FTX to auction off WLD position. Half of US voters think crypto ‘important’. North Korea ‘infiltrating’ crypto industry. Snowden challenged over SOL centralisation view. Top SEC official on crypto set to depart.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DACOM Summit: Fastex CLO Vardan Khachatryan on Crypto Compliance]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LGGnxkb6/dacom-summit-fastex-clo-vardan-khachatryan-on-crypto-compliance</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LGGnxkb6/dacom-summit-fastex-clo-vardan-khachatryan-on-crypto-compliance"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T14:32:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fastex Chief Legal Officer Vardan Khachatryan joined Rug Radio creator Mlow at DACOM Summit to discuss how the crypto exchange is advancing compliance, and the regulatory challenges that lie ahead for the sector.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 210 - MIDDLE EAST TENSIONS RISE]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Bcj37IF2/fomo-hour-210-middle-east-tensions-rise</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Bcj37IF2/fomo-hour-210-middle-east-tensions-rise"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T17:14:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto drops as Middle East tensions flare. $500m liquidations in drop. BTC ETFs see largest outflows in a month. Fidelity ETH ETF sees 2nd highest outflow ever. SUI hits 6-month highs, bridge goes live on mainnet. Hashdex set to launch XRP ETF. Wormhole leads altcoin gains after Upbit lists. BTC miners hit record low profits in September Crypto hackers stole $750m in Q3. Telegram has been disclosing IPs since 2018.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Arbitrum is Simplifying Web3 for Web2 Adopters]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Mm9OGAoG/how-arbitrum-is-simplifying-web3-for-web2-adopters</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Mm9OGAoG/how-arbitrum-is-simplifying-web3-for-web2-adopters"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T14:19:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arbitrum's Head of Korea, John Park, joined Rug Radio creator Pukerainbow at ArbiVerse to talk about the Ethereum layer-2's strategy in Asia, hackathons, and bringing enterprise clients to its ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rep. Tom Emmer Is Confident Crypto Laws Are Coming Soon—No Matter Who Wins the Election]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qWDybFgM/rep-tom-emmer-is-confident-crypto-laws-are-coming-soonno-matter-who-wins-the-election</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qWDybFgM/rep-tom-emmer-is-confident-crypto-laws-are-coming-soonno-matter-who-wins-the-election"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T20:37:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Republican Majority Whip Tom Emmer sat down with Decrypt’s Sander Lutz and Liz Napolitano to discuss the state of crypto legislation, Kamala Harris, Fairshake, and more at Messari Mainnet 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 209 - LET UPTOBER BEGIN!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DdOpex2X/fomo-hour-209-let-uptober-begin</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DdOpex2X/fomo-hour-209-let-uptober-begin"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T19:23:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETFs see inflows for 8 straight days. SUI enters top 20, $110m of unlocks today. SOL weekly DEX volume flips ETH. Firedancer sees very fast TPS on Testnet. ETH gas up 500% in 2 weeks. EIGEN opens at $7bn FDV. FTX creditors vote in favour of restructuring plan. Dell to sell another $1.2bn Dell stock. Metaplanet buys another 107 BTC.Grayscale opens decentralised AI fund to investors. Robinhood allows crypto transfer in EU. Pollak to head Coinbase Wallet & join exec team. Gemini to close in Canada. Japan considers lower cap gains tax on crypto. Ohio bill would make it legal to pay taxes in crypto. Trump project opens whitelist to non-US users. CZ pledges to invest in blockchain companies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance CEO Richard Teng Talks Progress on Exchange's Global Regulatory Goals]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DNhZEWGn/binance-ceo-richard-teng-talks-progress-on-exchanges-global-regulatory-goals</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DNhZEWGn/binance-ceo-richard-teng-talks-progress-on-exchanges-global-regulatory-goals"/>
        <updated>2024-09-28T22:11:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt Reporters Sander Lutz and Liz Napolitano spoke with Binance CEO Richard Teng about the crypto exchange's progress on establishing a global headquarters, improving its relationships with regulators, and expanding its global presence in the wake of founder Changpeng "CZ" Zhao's jailing in the U.S.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 207 - WELCOME BACK TO THE BULL!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/2OVTsv7N/fomo-hour-207-welcome-back-to-the-bull</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/2OVTsv7N/fomo-hour-207-welcome-back-to-the-bull"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T18:14:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kamala signals support for crypto. Top memecoins all soar, add $10bn in value in a week. MOODENG hits $180m, does 11x in a week. SUI & SEI continue to lead L1s for price & TVL growth. Revolut & Robinhood are considering stablecoin. Visa launches new tokenisation platform for banks. PayPal to allow business accounts to hold crypto Hamster kombat's HMSTER disappoints on launch. Biden admin may have forced Silvergate’s closure. Court rules crypto mining boxes ‘are securities’.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 206 - MEMES ARE PUMPING!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Uc5GOy50/fomo-hour-206-memes-are-pumping</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Uc5GOy50/fomo-hour-206-memes-are-pumping"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T15:50:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC nears $65k key resistance level. Kamala makes positive comments about crypto. PayPal allows businesses to hold crypto. Visa allows banks to test RWAs & smart contracts. Cuban wants to be head of SEC. Silvergate claims about ‘Chokepoint 2.0’ grow. Truflation hacked for $5m. Telegram Wallet blocked in UK & US. Court rules crypto mining boxes are securities. Infinex DeFi platform raises $65m. Ethena announces new stablecoin linked to BUIDL.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 205 - ALTCOINS CONTINUE TO RALLY!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mtR8OATG/fomo-hour-205-altcoins-continue-to-rally</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mtR8OATG/fomo-hour-205-altcoins-continue-to-rally"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T15:16:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SUI leads L1 gains as TVL crosses $1bn. Altcoin market cap close to breaking downtrend. SEI becomes top chain for 1 month TVL growth. ETH ETFs sees 3rd largest inflow ever. SEC delays ETH ETF options decision. SOL took most of ETH outflows over last 3 months. SOLETH continues to be trading at resistance. $8.1bn BTC options to expire this week. BTC heading to $500k-$1m in a year: PlanB. Stablecoin supply hits new ATH. Caroline Ellison sentenced to 2 years in jail. SBF & Diddy in the same jail. SEC settles against TUSD for not being collateralised. Gensler gets derided for crypto approach. Hester Pierce admits flaws in SEC crypto policy. Harris against regulation by litigation: Cuban. Golem claims ETH move to CEXs due to staking. Binance refutes data leak claims. Next Y combinator batch has ‘no crypto companies’. Celo overtakes Tron for stablecoin addresses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 204 - MOODENG MOO-NING!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/g2yV7DjU/fomo-hour-204-moodeng-moo-ning</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/g2yV7DjU/fomo-hour-204-moodeng-moo-ning"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T15:53:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC needs to top $65.2k to put in a higher high. ETH ETFs see biggest outflow since July. ETH outperformance could be start of ‘alt season’. BlackRock gets 12hr BTC withdrawal from Coinbase. cbBTC only wrapped BTC to not show reserves. Telegram to share user data upon legal requests. EIGEN non-transferability to be removed Sep 30th. TIA announces $100m funding round. TIA deal was OTC token sale ‘done months ago’. Polymarket considers token, trying $50m raise. Maybe we will pay off debt with crypto: Trump. Harris unlikely to give full crypto policy pre-election. 13m Binance users’ data may have been leaked. Caroline Ellison likely won’t serve time in jail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 203 - KAMALA GOES PRO-CRYPTO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZIgJfh06/fomo-hour-203-kamala-goes-pro-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZIgJfh06/fomo-hour-203-kamala-goes-pro-crypto"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T16:14:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto funds saw $321m inflows last week. Kamala commits to crypto & AI expansion. TAO leads gains in AI hype, does 2x in 2 weeks. SUI TVL breaks $900m. Average Q4 returns for BTC is 88%. BTC Google searches down 75% since 2021. BTC 161 days from halving, when it rallied in 2020. Crypto VCs raised $2.2bn this year, well below 2021.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 202 - SOL STARTS TO SEND IT]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kMr0ptrw/fomo-hour-202-sol-starts-to-send-it</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kMr0ptrw/fomo-hour-202-sol-starts-to-send-it"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T18:42:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SOL leads majors as Breakpoint begins. SOL launches Frankendancer on mainnet. Helio Pay allows Shopify items to sell on X. Franklin Templeton to launch fund on SOL. BTC short term holders fall at fastest rate in 12 years. MicroStrategy upsizes convertible note raise to $1bn. BingX loses $52m in hack. $243m crypto heist exposed by ZachXBT. Supreme Court of India hacked on X, shills scam. SocGen launches Euro stablecoin on SOL. Sky agrees to stop using WBTC. Germany shuts down 47 crypto exchanges. Stablecoin’s now 18th biggest holder of treasuries. Consensys lawsuit against SEC dismissed. Partisanship will stop Trump crypto plans: Hoskinson. Scaramucci working with Kamala on crypto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>