<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-05-19T15:14:48.810Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-05-19T15:14:48.810Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Where the SEC’s Proposed Custody Rule Comes Up Short for Crypto]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750ff819eb</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2023/05/18/where-the-secs-proposed-custody-rule-comes-up-short-for-crypto/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T15:09:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Financial advisors looking for clarity on crypto and digital assets from the SEC’s proposed changes to Custody Rule 206(4)-2 won’t get everything they want.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Kolesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple CTO confirms its CBDC Platform’s ability to use XRP token]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18382746/Ripple-CTO-confirms-its-CBDC-Platforms-ability-to-use-XRP-token</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18382746/Ripple-CTO-confirms-its-CBDC-Platforms-ability-to-use-XRP-token"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T15:08:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple CTO David Schwartz confirmed the company’s CBDC Platform can interact with the XRP Ledger (XRPL) and XRP token. The company released an update on its CBDC Platform on May 18 detailing improvements to the project. Crypto publication Blockworks covered the story – detailing an email...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 3 most trending cryptocurrencies as of May 19, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18382750/Top-3-most-trending-cryptocurrencies-as-of-May-19-2023</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18382750/Top-3-most-trending-cryptocurrencies-as-of-May-19-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T15:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The burgeoning crypto industry is evolving rapidly, driven by the constant emergence of new trends and market movements. To make … Continued]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Price Prediction as Shibarium Beta Transactions Approach 10 Million – SHIB Adoption on the Rise?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18382744/Shiba-Inu-Price-Prediction-as-Shibarium-Beta-Transactions-Approach-10-Million-SHIB-Adoption-on-the-Rise</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18382744/Shiba-Inu-Price-Prediction-as-Shibarium-Beta-Transactions-Approach-10-Million-SHIB-Adoption-on-the-Rise"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T15:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB), the world’s second most popular and largest crypto meme token by market capitalization that lives as an ERC-20 token on Ethereum, has been range bound in the $0.00000850-0.0000090 area over the last few days. The bears have been catching their breath after sending the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miners Sound Alarm On Proposed US Tax, CEO Warns Of Offshore Exodus]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750ff8f2df</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-miners-alarm-on-proposed-us-tax/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T15:03:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin miners face a tough predicament as Marathon Digital CEO Fred Thiel sounds the alarm on US President Joe Biden’s proposed tax policy.
 
With the potential implementation of new taxes targeting American Bitcoin miners, Thiel said that the intended revenue gains might be overshadowed by an unintended consequence.
 
Thiel sounds a cautionary note, emphasizing that this move could inadvertently drive these miners to relocate their operations outside the country. 
 
 

 
 
Biden’s Proposed Tax On Bitcoin Miners
 
Bitcoin miners are facing an imminent threat as Biden’s administration unveils a tax proposal targeting their operations. 
 
The White House Council of Economic Advisers (CEA) recently announced plans to impose a penalty that could severely impact mining companies’ profits. Unde…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Love beyond fiat – How cryptos became the new language of romance]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18382732/Love-beyond-fiat-How-cryptos-became-the-new-language-of-romance</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18382732/Love-beyond-fiat-How-cryptos-became-the-new-language-of-romance"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T15:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto has emerged to become a powerful asset class. However, is it powerful enough to dictate romantic relationships at this point?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miners Sound Alarm On Proposed US Tax, CEO Warns Of Offshore Exodus]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18382738/Bitcoin-Miners-Sound-Alarm-On-Proposed-US-Tax-CEO-Warns-Of-Offshore-Exodus</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18382738/Bitcoin-Miners-Sound-Alarm-On-Proposed-US-Tax-CEO-Warns-Of-Offshore-Exodus"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T15:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin miners face a tough predicament as Marathon Digital CEO Fred Thiel sounds the alarm on US President Joe Biden’s proposed tax policy. With the potential implementation of new taxes targeting American Bitcoin miners, Thiel said that the intended revenue gains might be overshadowed by an...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin (DOGE) Price Stuck in Limbo: Will Whales Trigger a Rebound or Reversal?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18382733/Dogecoin-DOGE-Price-Stuck-in-Limbo-Will-Whales-Trigger-a-Rebound-or-Reversal</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18382733/Dogecoin-DOGE-Price-Stuck-in-Limbo-Will-Whales-Trigger-a-Rebound-or-Reversal"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data shows that the bullish $0.1 Dogecoin (DOGE) price prediction hangs in the balance as whale investors take opposing positions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can BNB Defend the $300 Price Level, or Will It Dip Below Key Support?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18382734/Can-BNB-Defend-the-300-Price-Level-or-Will-It-Dip-Below-Key-Support</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18382734/Can-BNB-Defend-the-300-Price-Level-or-Will-It-Dip-Below-Key-Support"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Binance threads troubled regulatory waters, Whales are making bearish BNB price predictions in response to negative market sentiment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shibarium’s BONE Retests Key Level as Testnet Hits 10M Transfers]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18382708/Shibariums-BONE-Retests-Key-Level-as-Testnet-Hits-10M-Transfers</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18382708/Shibariums-BONE-Retests-Key-Level-as-Testnet-Hits-10M-Transfers"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shibarium Beta nears 10 million transactions, painting a vivid picture of the Layer-2 capabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week In Crypto: Ledger Wallet Faux Pas, XRP Prospects Bearish, and SHIB AI Predictions]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18382735/This-Week-In-Crypto-Ledger-Wallet-Faux-Pas-XRP-Prospects-Bearish-and-SHIB-AI-Predictions</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18382735/This-Week-In-Crypto-Ledger-Wallet-Faux-Pas-XRP-Prospects-Bearish-and-SHIB-AI-Predictions"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the news this week: Ledger defends seed phrase recovery option, Ripple sentiments still bearish despite overseas expansion, and Andrew Tate in hot water for promoting pump-and-dump scheme.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Today in Crypto: Bank of England to Reject Revolut's Banking Licence Application, ASX Abandons Blockchain, HashKey to Raise Funds at $1BN Valuation, Ledger Co-founder Calls Recover Service Launch a 'Horrible Mess']]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18382745/Today-in-Crypto-Bank-of-England-to-Reject-Revoluts-Banking-Licence-Application-ASX-Abandons-Blockchain-HashKey-to-Raise-Funds-at-1BN-Valuation-Ledger-Co-founder-Calls-Recover-Service-Launch-a-Horrible-Mess</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18382745/Today-in-Crypto-Bank-of-England-to-Reject-Revoluts-Banking-Licence-Application-ASX-Abandons-Blockchain-HashKey-to-Raise-Funds-at-1BN-Valuation-Ledger-Co-founder-Calls-Recover-Service-Launch-a-Horrible-Mess"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________... Read More: Today in Crypto: Bank of England to Reject Revolut's Banking Licence Application, ASX Abandons Blockchain, HashKey to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Scandal: South Korea’s Ruling Party Sends Team to Wemix Issuer]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750ff9cc9d</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/regulation/crypto-scandal-south-koreas-ruling-party-sends-team-to-wemix-issuer/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T14:57:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Friday, a delegation of lawmakers from  
South Korea's ruling People Power Party (PPP) conducted a visit to the office of Wemade, the  
issuer of play-to-earn (P2E) cryptocurrency, Wemix. The visit is part of an ongoing investigation into the crypto holdings of Kim Nam-kuk, former opposition party and now-independent lawmaker, local media Yonhap reports.
Kim reportedly had about 800,000 WEMIX coins worth about six billion won ($4.5 million) in his crypto wallet between January and February 2022. The lawmaker is alleged to have withdrawn his coin holding before South Korea implemented global anti-money laundering body Financial Action Task Force's (FAFT) travel rule in March last year.  The rule demands that crypto exchanges record and report personal data on transactions that exceed a c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Ferreira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Litecoin ($LTC) Price Surges to One-Month High as It Outperforms Other Top Cryptos]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18382707/Litecoin-LTC-Price-Surges-to-One-Month-High-as-It-Outperforms-Other-Top-Cryptos</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18382707/Litecoin-LTC-Price-Surges-to-One-Month-High-as-It-Outperforms-Other-Top-Cryptos"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T14:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jack Dorsey-backed TBD Launches New Web5 Toolkit to Decentralize the Internet]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750ffb51f7</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/05/19/jack-dorsey-backed-tbd-launches-new-web5-toolkit-to-decentralize-the-internet/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T14:47:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The official announcement by the unit of Block (SQ) was made Thursday at the Bitcoin 2023 conference in Miami Beach, Florida.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Frederick  Munawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uniswap Explains How Account Abstraction Can Make Crypto Mainstream]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18382696/Uniswap-Explains-How-Account-Abstraction-Can-Make-Crypto-Mainstream</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18382696/Uniswap-Explains-How-Account-Abstraction-Can-Make-Crypto-Mainstream"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Uniswap believes that one Ethereum Improvement Proposal holds promise to significantly boost crypto adoption.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sandwich Attacks: Stealing or Just Playing the DeFi Game?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18382691/Sandwich-Attacks-Stealing-or-Just-Playing-the-DeFi-Game</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18382691/Sandwich-Attacks-Stealing-or-Just-Playing-the-DeFi-Game"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T14:42:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sandwich attacks are eating up hapless traders’ lunch money]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk's Tweet Sends BOB up 43%: Here's What You Missed]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18382702/Elon-Musks-Tweet-Sends-BOB-up-43-Heres-What-You-Missed</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18382702/Elon-Musks-Tweet-Sends-BOB-up-43-Heres-What-You-Missed"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T14:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla and SpaceX founder sparks massive surge in this coin's price with just one emoji]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining Gets Tougher as Network Difficulty Reaches New Peak]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750fe4b676</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-mining-gets-tougher-as-network-difficulty-reaches-new-peak/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T14:37:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On May 18, 2023, at block height 790,272, Bitcoin’s difficulty reached an all-time high after rising 3.22% on Thursday. The network’s difficulty is now at an impressive 49.55 trillion, or 0.90% away from 50 trillion hashes, making it the most difficult it has ever been to discover a block reward.
 
Bitcoin’s Difficulty Rises to Uncharted Territory, Straining Miners
 
This year, Bitcoin once again broke a record as the network’s difficulty jumped by 3.22%, rising to an unprecedented height of 49.55 trillion. The network’s difficulty is a measure of how hard it is to find a hash value that meets the required criteria for a new block to be added to the Bitcoin blockchain. Notably, the recent rise in difficulty followed a 1.45% drop at block height 788,256, where the chain’s difficulty remaine…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jack Dorsey-backed TBD Launches New Web5 Toolkit to Decentralize the Internet]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18382692/Jack-Dorsey-backed-TBD-Launches-New-Web5-Toolkit-to-Decentralize-the-Internet</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18382692/Jack-Dorsey-backed-TBD-Launches-New-Web5-Toolkit-to-Decentralize-the-Internet"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T14:35:26.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin supply held by shrimps hits all-time high of 1.31 BTC]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18382669/Bitcoin-supply-held-by-shrimps-hits-all-time-high-of-131-BTC</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18382669/Bitcoin-supply-held-by-shrimps-hits-all-time-high-of-131-BTC"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T14:33:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin wallets with less than 1 BTC now hold an all-time high of 1.31 million coins. Shrimps have been adding an average of 26,000 BTC every month, data shows. The growth of the shrimp cohort is a positive development for the Bitcoin network. The amount of Bitcoin held by “shrimps” – those...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Investors Sink Into Fear, Time For A Rebound?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750fe57f27</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-investors-sink-into-fear-time-for-a-rebound/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T14:31:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data shows that Bitcoin investors have been showing signs of fearful sentiment as the price of the cryptocurrency has plunged below $27,000.
 
Bitcoin Social Dominance Spike Suggests Fear In Market
 
According to data from the on-chain analytics firm Santiment, BTC’s social dominance has seen an uplift recently. The “Bitcoin social dominance” is an indicator that measures the percentage of the total discussions involving the top 100 assets by market cap that mention BTC.
 
What this metric tells us is how the current interest in BTC among investors compares with that of the altcoins. Historically, high interest in altcoins (meaning that the social dominance of BTC is low) has been a sign of greed in the market.
 
Usually, markets gain a higher probability of moving opposite to the wider ma…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hououin Kyouma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Investors Sink Into Fear, Time For A Rebound?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18382667/Bitcoin-Investors-Sink-Into-Fear-Time-For-A-Rebound</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18382667/Bitcoin-Investors-Sink-Into-Fear-Time-For-A-Rebound"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T14:30:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data shows that Bitcoin investors have been showing signs of fearful sentiment as the price of the cryptocurrency has plunged below $27,000. Bitcoin Social Dominance Spike Suggests Fear In Market According to data from the on-chain analytics firm Santiment, BTC’s social dominance has seen an...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Lawmaker Introduces Legislation Prohibiting Fed From Issuing CBDC Without Congressional Approval]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18382657/US-Lawmaker-Introduces-Legislation-Prohibiting-Fed-From-Issuing-CBDC-Without-Congressional-Approval</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18382657/US-Lawmaker-Introduces-Legislation-Prohibiting-Fed-From-Issuing-CBDC-Without-Congressional-Approval"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T14:30:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A member of the US House of Representatives is introducing bi-partisan legislation that would explicitly prohibit the Federal Government from issuing a Central Bank Digital Currency (CBDC) without approval by Congress. During new House Floor remarks, Rep. Jake Auchincloss (D-MA) says that CBDCs...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Pepe Coin Price Dead? $COPIUM and AiDoge Might Be The Best Crypto to Buy Today]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18382673/Is-Pepe-Coin-Price-Dead-COPIUM-and-AiDoge-Might-Be-The-Best-Crypto-to-Buy-Today</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18382673/Is-Pepe-Coin-Price-Dead-COPIUM-and-AiDoge-Might-Be-The-Best-Crypto-to-Buy-Today"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T14:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin volatility reaches historically significant lows; Massive rally in store?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18382655/Bitcoin-volatility-reaches-historically-significant-lows-Massive-rally-in-store</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18382655/Bitcoin-volatility-reaches-historically-significant-lows-Massive-rally-in-store"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T14:22:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Although Bitcoin (BTC) continues to struggle with overcoming the critical psychological level at $28,000, its volatility has dropped to a … Continued]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Ledger’s New Bitcoin Key Recovery Feature Safe? Experts Have Doubts]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750fe7c7e6</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/05/19/is-ledgers-new-bitcoin-key-recovery-feature-safe-experts-have-doubts/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T14:16:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ledger believes the service will help attract customers turned off by crypto's unforgiving self-custody ethos. But critics wonder whether the concept is compatible with a real hardware wallet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anna Baydakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When In Doubt, Zoom Out: The Most Reassuring Bitcoin Chart You’ll See]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750fe0b441</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/when-in-doubt-zoom-out-bitcoin-chart/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T14:10:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin price is on the ropes after failing to make it above $30,000. The market is still fearful after a year long downtrend and 78% drop. 
 
However, as the old adage states, “when in doubt, zoom out.” In this latest look at BTCUSD, one curved median is all the reassurance needed to know that the top cryptocurrency is still on the right track long term. 
 
Zooming Out To Look At Long-Term Logarithmic Growth
 
Assets of any kind are measured in growth of price and time. Growth can be exponential or logarithmic. 
 
Exponential growth is fast and substantial, commonly associated with compound interest in finance. Growth begins slow, then sharply increases. The stock market in linear scale is a good example of what exponential growth looks like. 
 

 
 
Meanwhile, Bitcoin growth is logarithm…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tony &amp;quot;The Bull&amp;quot;</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Worldcoin Buyers Turn To Iris Scans From Cambodia, Africa – Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750fed5ede</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/worldcoin-buyers-turn-to-iris-scans-from-cambodia/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T13:39:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin, co-created by OpenAI’s Sam Altman, finds itself at the center of a controversy. Recent reports from a Chinese news site revealed that individuals in China, unable to directly participate in the forthcoming Worldcoin token distribution, are resorting to unconventional means. 
 
Taking advantage of the world’s interconnectedness, these individuals are acquiring iris scans in far-flung regions such as Cambodia and Africa.
 
This astonishing development highlights the lengths at which people are willing to go to secure their share of the digital currency. 
 
 
Controversy Erupts As Scammers Exploit Iris Scans For Token Distribution
 
In the realm of digital currencies, Worldcoin has emerged as a highly anticipated project, poised to introduce a unique token that will be distributed …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Praises Canada’s Crypto Approach as U.S. Regulatory Pressure Intensifies]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750fed8319</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/05/19/coinbase-praises-canadas-crypto-approach-as-us-regulatory-pressure-intensifies/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T13:38:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Canada is doing crypto regulation by engagement – “which we love,” said Coinbase’s VP International and Business Development Nana Murugesan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin in Stasis Below $27K Ahead of Powell Speech]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750fe89afe</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/05/19/bitcoin-in-stasis-below-26k-ahead-of-powell-speech/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T13:17:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At 15:00 GMT, Powell will speak at the "Perspectives on Monetary Policy" panel before the Thomas Laubach Research Conference hosted by the Federal Reserve.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi Projects Built on Ethereum Scaling Solution Starknet Hit $10M]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140703</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140703/defi-projects-built-ethereum-scaling-solution-starknet-hit-10m"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T13:13:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The total value locked in smart contracts using the Ethereum Layer-2 scaling solution has just hit an all-time high of over $10 million.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Privacy-Focused Network Horizen Expected to Undergo Node Upgrade in June]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750fea72de</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/05/19/privacy-focused-network-horizen-expected-to-undergo-node-upgrade-in-june/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T13:04:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The upgrade would bring enhancements to sidechains and bug fixes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Technical Analysis: BTC Remains Below $27,000, Ahead of Powell Speech]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750fd630a2</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-ethereum-technical-analysis-btc-remains-below-27000-ahead-of-powell-speech/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T12:39:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin once again fell below the $27,000 level on Friday, ahead of a panel discussion which includes Fed Chair Jerome Powell. Powell will be holding a discussion with former Chair Ben Bernanke at a conference in Washington. Ethereum was marginally lower today.
 
Bitcoin
 
Bitcoin (BTC) dropped below the $27,000 mark on Friday, ahead of a panel discussion which will include Fed Chair Jerome Powell.
 
Markets anticipate some forward guidance from Powell regarding future decisions that the Federal Reserve could take in coming months.
 
Following a high of $27,466.53 on Thursday, BTC/USD dropped to an intraday low of $26,415.10 earlier today.
 
 
Bitcoin chart by TradingView
 

 
 

 
The move, which saw the price fall by over $1,000, pushed bitcoin towards a key price floor at $26,300.
 
Friday’s slippage occurred as the 14-day relative strength index (RSI) once again dropped below a resistance of its own at the 42.00 mark.
 
Price strength is now tracking at 40.83, with bears possibly targeting a support point at the 38.00 zone.
 
 
Ethereum
 
Ethereum (ETH) was also in the red in today’s session, with prices briefly breaking out of the $1,800 level.
 
ETH/USD fell to a bottom at $1,774.20 on Friday, which comes a day after hitting a high of $1,826.90.
 
The drop in price resulted in ethereum falling below a floor at $1,790. However, it has since rebounded.
 
 
Ethereum chart by TradingView
 

 
 

 
Similar to BTC, ethereum’s RSI was unable to break out of a resistance point at 45.00, and is now at a reading of 44.83.
 
A sign of hope for bulls comes in the form of the 10-day (red) moving average, which moved closer to a crossover with its 25-day (blue) counterpart.
 
Should this occur, there is a reasonable chance that ETH could climb towards $1,900.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
Will Powell’s speech have an impact on markets? Leave your thoughts in the comments below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Mover Americas: Litecoin Might Be Trading at a Discount]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750fd1495c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/05/19/first-mover-americas-bitcoin-rebounds-amid-optimism-on-debt-ceiling/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T12:17:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest price moves in bitcoin (BTC) and crypto markets in context for May 19, 2023. First Mover is CoinDesk’s daily newsletter that contextualizes the latest actions in the crypto markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lyllah Ledesma, Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain Plans Scrapped By Australian Stock Exchange – Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750fd2bcc2</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/blockchain-plans-scrapped-by-asx/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T12:07:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain technology has been sidelined by the Australian Securities Exchange (ASX), a prominent entity in the nation’s financial domain, as it departs from its original intentions of utilizing blockchain to reconstruct its software platform.
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
This unexpected move signifies a momentous shift in the perception of a once-celebrated concept that rose to prominence alongside the growing popularity of cryptocurrencies.
 
The decision to abandon blockchain rebuild marks a significant turning point, highlighting the challenges and limitations that have become apparent during its implementation journey.
 
 
Blockchain Ditched: ASX Explores New Paths For Software Rebuild 
 
In a recent meeting (via Reuters), the ASX made a significant announcement, stating its decision to exclude bloc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Banks Not Getting Anticipated Benefits From Rate Hikes, ECB Executive Admits]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750fdf0547</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/banks-not-getting-anticipated-benefits-from-rate-hikes-ecb-executive-admits/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T11:37:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eurozone banks are profitable but the benefits from higher interest rates may be smaller than expected, according to the deputy head of the single currency area’s monetary authority. The official noted that while most of the tightening has been done already, more rate increases are to come.
 
Euro Banks Have Solid Fundamentals, ECB’s de Guindos Says, Rate Raises to Continue
 
The turmoil in the eurozone’s banking sector has been “short-lived” due to limited exposure to bank stress in the U.S. and Switzerland and shielding regulations, Vice President of the European Central Bank (ECB) Luis de Guindos said during a banking conference in Spain.
 
Euro area banks are weathering the storm also thanks to solid fundamentals in key areas such as resilience, liquidity, and profitability, the high-r…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lubomir Tassev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoin Issuers Pour Money Into DC as Crypto Legislation Hits Agendas]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140698</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140698/stablecoin-issuers-pour-money-dc-crypto-legislation-hits-agendas"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T11:36:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoin issuers Tether and Circle have been regularly paying lobbyists to stay on top of possible regulations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alys Key</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Market Recovery Unlikely Until Stablecoin Universe Stops Shrinking: JPMorgan]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750fd88d0a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/05/19/crypto-market-recovery-unlikely-until-stablecoin-universe-stops-shrinking-jpmorgan/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T11:27:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tether’s market cap has been growing at the expense of rival stablecoins such as USD Coin, the report said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Canny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['So Much Anger, So Much Hate', Says Ledger Co-Founder Amid Botched Recover Service Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140692</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140692/so-much-anger-so-much-hate-says-ledger-co-founder-amid-botched-recover-service-launch"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T11:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After Crypto Twitter took Ledger to the chopping block over its Recover service, the firm’s co-founder took to Reddit to explain his views]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mid-Term Holders Are Selling, Reason Behind Recent Price Struggle?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750fc50be2</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-mid-term-holders-selling-price-struggle/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T10:56:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data shows the Bitcoin “mid-term holders” have been selling, which may explain why the price has struggled recently.
 
Bitcoin Mid-Term Holders Have Been Shedding Their Supply Recently
 
As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant post, a holder group has been showing signs of profit-taking recently. The indicator of interest here is the “sum coin age distribution,” which tells us about how the Bitcoin supply is distributed among the various cohorts currently.
 
These cohorts are divided based on the age of the coins that they are holding in their wallets right now. The 1-3 months old group, for example, contains all the holders that have been carrying their coins since at least 1 month and at most 3 months ago.
 
In the context of the current topic, the relevant coin age group …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hououin Kyouma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ASX Abandons Blockchain-Based System to Replace CHESS]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750fc099ed</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/asx-abandons-blockchain-based-system-to-replace-chess/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T10:32:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Australian stock market operator, ASX, has abandoned its ambitious project to replace the legacy clearing and settlements system, CHESS, with a blockchain technology-based platform.  

CHESS Is a 30-Year Old System  

The decision to completely abandon the project was taken in a meeting on Wednesday, according to Reuters. The company will continue its work toward developing a CHESS replacement, but it will not involve blockchain or distributed ledger technology.  

ASX's Project Director, Tim Whiteley, said in the meeting that the next attempt to develop a CHESS replacement would "go down the more conventional route, that is, without the focus on DLT (or) blockchain," adding "while we continue to explore all the options, certainly we will need to use a more conventional technology than in …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arnab Shome</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Australia’s Stock Exchange ASX Axes Blockchain Initiative—for Good]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140689</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140689/australias-stock-exchange-asx-axes-blockchain-initiative-good"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T10:16:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The leading stock exchange Downunder no longer considers blockchain among possible technologies for its trading software upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Digital Asset Firm HashKey Group Looks to Raise up to $200M at $1B Valuation: Bloomberg]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e750fcca857</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/05/19/digital-asset-firm-hashkey-group-looks-to-raise-up-to-200m-at-1b-valuation-bloomberg/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T10:05:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The firm is looking to capitalize on Hong Kong's re-emergence as a potential crypto hub as the city has looked to formulate a clear regulatory structure for digital assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Finally Launches Subscription Service Overseas, Focuses on Staking]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140661</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140661/coinbase-finally-launches-subscription-service-focuses-on-staking"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T01:01:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The exchange has launched Coinbase One—and is accelerating its push overseas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy Looking at Bitcoin Ordinals for App Development, Says Michael Saylor]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140670</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140670/microstrategy-looking-at-bitcoin-ordinals-for-app-development-says-michael-saylor"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T00:57:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Right now, enterprises have weak security compared to Bitcoin,” Saylor told Decrypt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beeple, Bitboy, and a 'Dumping' Bored Ape: How It All Hit the Fan]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140664</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140664/beeple-bitboy-dumping-bored-ape-how-all-hit-fan"/>
        <updated>2023-05-19T00:38:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Famed digital artist Beeple waded into a Crypto Twitter mess centered on influencer Bitboy’s relationship to a controversial meme token.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jack Dorsey Leads $6 Million Raise for Bitcoin Payments Company Azteco]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140657</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140657/jack-dorsey-leads-6-million-raise-bitcoin-payments-company-azteco"/>
        <updated>2023-05-18T21:29:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Block CEO and former Twitter CEO Jack Dorsey, a noted Bitcoin aficionado, led the round for a startup focused on redeemable Bitcoin vouchers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alyssa Hertig</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Companies Must Provide 'Proof of Reserves' in Texas]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140647</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140647/texas-proof-of-reserves-for-crypto-exchanges"/>
        <updated>2023-05-18T20:26:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto exchanges with Texas customers have to provide "proof of reserves" and make sure customers funds can always be "fully withdrawn."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin 2023 Attendees in Miami Blame Bear Market Vibes for Lower Attendance]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140595</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140595/bitcoin-2023-in-miami-bear-market-lower-attendance"/>
        <updated>2023-05-18T19:45:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day one attendees said they expect crowds to look less sparse tomorrow, when general admission pass holders show up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Litecoin Activity Hits All-Time High Thanks to Ordinals Mania]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140608</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140608/litecoin-experiences-highest-blockchain-activity-thanks-to-ordinals"/>
        <updated>2023-05-18T18:55:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The blockchain is being used to mint Ordinals following Bitcoin congestion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI Debuts ChatGPT App for Apple iPhone, Says Android Coming Soon]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140609</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140609/openai-launches-chatgpt-app-for-apple-iphone"/>
        <updated>2023-05-18T18:12:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI launches free iOS ChatGPT app, enabling history sync and GPT-4 access for Plus subscribers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Custody Services Are Coming to Custodia Bank, Says CEO Caitlin Long]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140603</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140603/bitcoin-custody-services-are-coming-to-custodia-bank-says-ceo-caitlin-long"/>
        <updated>2023-05-18T17:25:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Custodia Bank CEO said she, a hardcore Bitcoiner, started a bank because the world isn't ready for "hyperbitcoinization” yet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Azra Games CEO Mark Otero is Not a Fan of "Play-to-Earn" Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/F08xddFc/why-azra-games-ceo-mark-otero-is-not-a-fan-of-play-to-earn-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/F08xddFc/why-azra-games-ceo-mark-otero-is-not-a-fan-of-play-to-earn-games"/>
        <updated>2023-05-18T16:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Each game is a miracle," says Azra Games CEO Mark Otero. In this clip, he shares his thoughts on "play-to-earn" games and gamer motivation with Decrypt's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFT Lending Platform Blend Surges Past 100,000 Ethereum in Total Volume]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140599</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140599/nft-lending-platform-blend-surges-past-100000-ethereum-total-volume"/>
        <updated>2023-05-18T15:23:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After adding two blue-chip NFT collections, Blend strengthened its market-leading position, just weeks after its launch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Europe a 'Significant Beneficiary' of US Crypto Regulatory Confusion: Ripple CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140587</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140587/europe-significant-beneficiary-us-crypto-regulatory-confusion-ripple-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-05-18T14:42:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With regulators stateside still scrambling to rein in the industry, rule makers in Europe, notably in France, are extending invitations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFT Artist and Collector OSF: 'NFTs Are Just a Medium']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140569</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140569/nft-artist-and-collector-osf-nfts-are-just-a-medium"/>
        <updated>2023-05-18T14:08:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The House of Fine Art gallery is playing host to an exhibition of pioneering NFT artists—but the word “NFT” is nowhere to be seen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Rolls Out CBDC Platform for Governments, Financial Institutions]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140584</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140584/ripple-cbdc-launching-platform-governments-financial-institutions"/>
        <updated>2023-05-18T13:28:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto firm Ripple is pushing further into the CBDC game, unveiling a new platform for creating blockchain-based digital currencies]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Australia Loses Crypto Ramp PayID ‘With Immediate Effect’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140559</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140559/binance-australia-loses-crypto-ramp-payid-immediate-effect"/>
        <updated>2023-05-18T11:18:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Australia has had to suspend PayID AUD deposits due to a decision by a third-party service provider.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi Token Synthetix Soars 10% as Community Mulls PEPE Market Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140551</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140551/defi-token-synthetix-soars-community-mulls-pepe-market-launch"/>
        <updated>2023-05-18T10:03:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SNX surged overnight as the Synthetix community weighs integrating the popular meme cryptocurrency PEPE into its DeFi offering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bankrupt Crypto Broker Voyager Cleared to Repay $1.3B to Creditors]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140547</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140547/bankrupt-crypto-broker-voyager-cleared-repay-creditors"/>
        <updated>2023-05-18T09:45:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Voyager said the initial payments will be made either in crypto through the Voyager app or in cash after a waiting period of 30 days.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gala Games Burns Over $600 Million Worth of GALA Tokens]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140539</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140539/gala-games-burns-over-600-million-worth-gala-tokens"/>
        <updated>2023-05-18T01:56:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 startup Gala Games said that it has virtually depleted its own treasury to alleviate concerns of a future token selloff.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adidas Web3 Lead Thought She ‘Could Get Fired’ for Signing Bored Ape Deal]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140527</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140527/adidas-web3-lead-thought-could-fired-signing-bored-ape-deal"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T23:13:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Erika Wykes-Sneyd joins Decrypt’s gm podcast to discuss how apparel giant Adidas approaches NFTs and emerging culture alike.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seizing Upon Ledger Stumble, Hardware Wallet Competitors Offer Discounts]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140520</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140520/ledger-recover-competitors-trezor-cold-card-blockstream-jade"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T21:57:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BitBox, Cold Card, Trezor and Blockstream all announced sale prices on their cold storage devices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Most Americans Consider AI a Threat to Humanity, New Poll Finds]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140515</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140515/most-americans-see-artificial-intelligence-as-a-threat-new-poll-finds"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T21:43:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Reuters/Ipsos poll shows that 61% of Americans believe AI to be a threat to humanity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Believes Filecoin Is a Security, Grayscale Warns Investors]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140512</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140512/sec-filecoin-security-grayscale-protocol-labs"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T20:58:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC said Grayscale has to withdraw its Filecoin Trust application because FIL is an unregistered security.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ron DeSantis Banned CBDCs in Florida—These States Could Be Next]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140505</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140505/ron-desantis-banned-cbdcs-in-florida-these-states-could-be-next"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T20:33:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Sunshine State isn’t the only one speaking out against a potential digital dollar.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enter the 'Unioverse': The Cinematic Sci-Fi Game Takes Shape on Polygon]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140474</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140474/enter-unioverse-cinematic-sci-fi-game-takes-shape-polygon"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T19:51:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PREVIEW: We go hands-on with the Unioverse Proving Grounds, a flashy playtest from former Grand Theft Auto and Call of Duty developers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Kim Asendorf: The Metallica Video Director Who Makes NFT Art Designed to Hypnotize]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140473</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140473/metallica-video-director-kim-asendorf-nft-art-designed-hypnotize"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T18:41:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Colors of Noise" is a series of 50 Ethereum NFT art pieces, and the pixelated waveforms could "disturb" viewers, Kim Asendorf tells Decrypt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ali Shutler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Activity Surges With Ordinals—But a Core DOGE Dev Is Skeptical]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140468</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140468/dogecoin-activity-surges-with-ordinals"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T17:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of DOGE's core developers said "sustained and growing pressure on Dogecoin will cause this to die off quickly."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Many Games Are Building On Solana? The Answer Might Surprise You]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/WV6HegEv/how-many-games-are-building-on-solana-the-answer-might-surprise-you</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/WV6HegEv/how-many-games-are-building-on-solana-the-answer-might-surprise-you"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T16:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Games General Manager Johnny Lee tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the current state of Solana's Web3 gaming ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether Pledges to Plow 15% of Profits into Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140461</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140461/tether-pledges-to-plow-15-of-profits-into-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T15:21:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin has ‘continually proven its resilience’ said Tether's CTO, as the stablecoin issuer adds to its $1.5 billion reserves of the cryptocurrency.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alys Key</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ledger Expands Cosmos Integration, Aims at Adding 20 New Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140452</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140452/ledger-expands-cosmos-integration-aims-adding-20-new-projects"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The hardware wallet provider claims that it’s “one of the first wallets” to offer support for Cosmos and the network's supported projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Judge Denies Motion to Seal Hinman Documents in Ripple SEC Case]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140438</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140438/judge-denies-motion-seal-hinman-documents-ripple-sec-case"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T13:11:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A judge denied the SEC’s motion to seal documents linked to a speech that explained why Bitcoin shouldn't be considered a security.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi Exchange Uniswap to Launch on Polkadot via Moonbeam Parachain]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140440</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140440/defi-exchange-uniswap-launch-polkadot-moonbeam-parachain"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T13:01:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Uniswap V3 is coming to Polkadot on the Moonbeam parachain after a near-unanimous governance vote conducted by Blockchain at Michigan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Axie Infinity Rolls Out ‘Lite' Version of Crypto Game on Apple App Store]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140437</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140437/axie-infinity-rolls-out-lite-version-crypto-game-apple-app-store"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T12:18:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starter characters on the app won't be NFTs, but the Axie Infinity COO says that users can transfer NFTs into the app.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly,Alys Key</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Acquires Crypto Custody Firm Metaco for $250M in Tokenization Push]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140428</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140428/ripple-acquires-crypto-custody-firm-metaco-250m-tokenization-push"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T12:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple expands into the institutional crypto custody market, predicting the niche will hit $10 trillion by the end of the decade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi Project Bancor Hit With Lawsuit Over Impermanent Loss Protection Promises]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=140434</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/140434/defi-project-bancor-hit-lawsuit-over-impermanent-loss-protection-promises"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T11:56:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Investors claim promises fell short, adding that Bancor’s DAO was centralized and its liquidity pools operated as unregistered securities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Problems With Being an 'On-Chain Purist'  in Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/uOwArY6a/problems-with-being-an-on-chain-purist-in-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/uOwArY6a/problems-with-being-an-on-chain-purist-in-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T15:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[InfiniGods Cofounders Owen O'Donoghue and Damon Gura keep it real with Decrypt's Kate Irwin, sharing thoughts on game balancing and what to do when in-game assets become NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Solana Won't Become A Web3 Game Publisher]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/RgSzjeSw/why-solana-wont-become-a-web3-game-publisher</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/RgSzjeSw/why-solana-wont-become-a-web3-game-publisher"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T16:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Foundation's Games General Manager Johnny Lee tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about Solana's "build together" approach as well as his thoughts on crypto firms becoming game publishers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The State Of Web3 Gaming On Hedera]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/7TTEckkZ/the-state-of-web3-gaming-on-hedera</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/7TTEckkZ/the-state-of-web3-gaming-on-hedera"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T14:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hedera VP Alex Russman tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about Hedera's Web3 gaming ecosystem and shares a game he's particularly excited about.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Mirandus is Innovating Video Game Audio]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kLHZIUsl/how-mirandus-is-innovating-video-game-audio</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kLHZIUsl/how-mirandus-is-innovating-video-game-audio"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T20:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mirandus' Lead Developer and Gala Games Cofounder Michael McCarthy tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the game's thoughtful approach to audio design and the technologies being built to support the MMORPG's immersive world.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do Gamers Hate NFTs?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/X0FtIw0j/do-gamers-hate-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/X0FtIw0j/do-gamers-hate-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin asks the InfiniGods developers Damon Gura and Owen O’Donoghue about gamers and NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: Avenged Sevenfold's M. Shadows on Deathbats, Fandom, and AI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JEgr9COw/gm-avenged-sevenfolds-m-shadows-on-deathbats-fandom-and-ai</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JEgr9COw/gm-avenged-sevenfolds-m-shadows-on-deathbats-fandom-and-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T20:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avenged Sevenfold lead singer Matt Sanders, aka M. Shadows, is rehearsing for the band's upcoming tour. He's also figuring out how to upend what it means to be a music fan. The band launched a Deathbats Club NFT collection in 2021. That is to say: They were early. The lead singer said it was timed to give fans a chance to get comfortable with Web3 technology ahead of the group's 2023 tour, when the NFT holders can use their Deathbats for early access to tickets. M. Shadows also talked to hosts Andrew Hayward and Stephen Graves about AI and bringing Web3 into gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Mojo Melee's Lore with Creator Mike Levine and Art Director Eric Campanella]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BfIB2H5e/inside-mojo-melees-lore-with-creator-mike-levine-and-art-director-eric-campanella</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BfIB2H5e/inside-mojo-melees-lore-with-creator-mike-levine-and-art-director-eric-campanella"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T22:29:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the Game Developers' Conference, Mojo Melee Creator Mike Levine and Art Director Eric Campanella tell Decrypt's Kate Irwin about their autobattler game and its unique characters, which are also NFTs on Polygon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why 'Blair Witch' Exec Producer Kevin Foxe Is '1,000% In' on Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZXj16C8r/why-blair-witch-exec-producer-kevin-foxe-is-1-000-in-on-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZXj16C8r/why-blair-witch-exec-producer-kevin-foxe-is-1-000-in-on-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T23:02:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["The Blair Witch Project" Executive Producer Kevin Foxe wants to avoid corporate overlords and enlighten fans of the dark "Mandala" graphic novel with a video game adaptation and NFTs across multiple blockchains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gala Games Co-Founder on the Aesthetic of Mirandus]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/1bQV1R6l/gala-games-co-founder-on-the-aesthetic-of-mirandus</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/1bQV1R6l/gala-games-co-founder-on-the-aesthetic-of-mirandus"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T14:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["When assets are overdone, they just feel a little dirty. It's not pretty to look at," shared Mirandus' Lead Developer and Gala Games co-founder Michael McCarthy in an interview with Decrypt's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Games GM: Play-to-Earn Games Are DeFi Products, Not Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yp7btQtl/solana-games-gm-play-to-earn-games-are-defi-products-not-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yp7btQtl/solana-games-gm-play-to-earn-games-are-defi-products-not-games"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T16:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Games' General Manager Johnny Lee offers a hot take on the first generation of Web3 gaming with Decrypt's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brycent's Advice For Gaming Content Creators]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/o19nZCeN/brycents-advice-for-gaming-content-creators</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/o19nZCeN/brycents-advice-for-gaming-content-creators"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T20:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XSET's Brycent shares his advice for Web3 content creators with Decrypt's Kate Irwin, including which social media platform is best for posting content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Behind the Scenes of Jeremy Cowart's 'Auras' NFT Event]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/C0ZeidQg/behind-the-scenes-of-jeremy-cowarts-auras-nft-event</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/C0ZeidQg/behind-the-scenes-of-jeremy-cowarts-auras-nft-event"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T22:54:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A look at the preparation behind "Auras," an event in which photographer Jeremy Cowart produced and starred in 10,000 photo-based NFTs, captured in less than 30 minutes before a live audience. Credit: Brett Carlsen for Decrypt]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jeremy Cowart Discusses 'Auras' Event, Live-Shooting 10,000 Photo NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/E3ViHsPd/jeremy-cowart-discusses-auras-event-live-shooting-10-000-photo-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/E3ViHsPd/jeremy-cowart-discusses-auras-event-live-shooting-10-000-photo-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T18:32:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jeremy Cowart speaks with Decrypt's Sander Lutz in Nashville ahead of the "Auras" event, in which the noted photographer live-shot 10,000 unique photo-based NFTs in less than 30 minutes. The NFTs will be released through OpenSea on May 9. Video credit: Brett Carlsen for Decrypt]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azra Games CEO on Putting Fun Before Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/03W3KZjM/azra-games-ceo-on-putting-fun-before-web3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/03W3KZjM/azra-games-ceo-on-putting-fun-before-web3"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T14:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["The Web3 interfaces cannot be on the foreground of the player's initial experience," says Azra Games CEO Mark Otero.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: Meet Immunefi's White Hat Whisperer]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/2vTAgpTC/gm-meet-immunefis-white-hat-whisperer</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/2vTAgpTC/gm-meet-immunefis-white-hat-whisperer"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T17:30:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Web3 bug bounty platform Immunefi launched two years ago, CEO and founder Mitchell Amador says the bug bounties weren't great and adoption was slow. But the tides started to turn because even if exploiting a smart contract nets a bigger payday than a bounty, it comes with a huge drawback. "There's a ton of risk when you engage in this, you know, wantonly criminal behavior and steal $200 million from someone else," he said. "There's no way someone's not going to come looking."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gala Games Co-Founder on Why Mirandus Will Not Have NPCs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5pey6epR/gala-games-co-founder-on-why-mirandus-will-not-have-npcs</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5pey6epR/gala-games-co-founder-on-why-mirandus-will-not-have-npcs"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T17:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lead Mirandus Developer and Gala Games Cofounder Michael McCarthy tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the Web3 MMORPG Mirandus and what its world will be like.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFC Lisbon Founder John Karp Heralds 'Level 2' Content for 2023 Event]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cYaJ25qv/nfc-lisbon-founder-john-karp-heralds-level-2-content-for-2023-event</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cYaJ25qv/nfc-lisbon-founder-john-karp-heralds-level-2-content-for-2023-event"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T09:44:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No panels, no problem. This year's NFC Lisbon from June 7 to June 9 boasts a variety of alternative formats, catering to a decentralized (and sometimes pseudonymous) NFT community. The event also plans to take a closer look into one of the faster-growing niches in NFTs: Photography and what founder John Karp calls "level 2" content. Not to be missed, as NFC Lisbon's media partner, Decrypt will be on-site for all three days. Come say hi!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Does Magic Eden Vet Web3 Games?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ogci0VQ6/how-does-magic-eden-vet-web3-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ogci0VQ6/how-does-magic-eden-vet-web3-games"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Magic Eden Chief Gaming Officer Chris Akhavan tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about how the NFT marketplace vets potential Web3 games for its platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>