<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-07-12T08:20:59.830Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-07-12T08:20:59.830Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cboe Refiles Spot Bitcoin ETFs Following Surveillance Agreement with Coinbase]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756e6a0e53</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/cboe-refiles-spot-bitcoin-etfs-following-surveillance-agreement-with-coinbase/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T08:18:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The American derivatives and securities exchange network,  
Cboe Global Markets, filed amended applications to list spot Bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) yesterday (Tuesday). The amended applications propose to include  
Coinbase as a surveillance-sharing partner for the spot Bitcoin ETFs filed on  
behalf of Fidelity, VanEck, WisdonTree, and Invesco.  
In the applications, which also included a joint proposal by Ark Invest and 21Shares for a spot Bitcoin ETF, Cboe stated that it agreed to enter into a  
surveillance-sharing agreement (SSA) with Coinbase on June 21. Additionally,  
the exchange said the agreement was expected to be implemented before the  
listing of the spot  
Bitcoin ETFs.
Cboe’s  
Surveillance-Sharing Agreement
The step is an  
attempt by Cboe to meet a requirement …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US GAO explores blockchain for SBA’s small business programs oversight]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18765463/US-GAO-explores-blockchain-for-SBAs-small-business-programs-oversight</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18765463/US-GAO-explores-blockchain-for-SBAs-small-business-programs-oversight"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T08:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[the GAO highlighted blockchain’s ability to streamline and improve annual reporting, facilitating safe loans and monitoring business development progress among others.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Korea to require firms to report crypto holdings from next year]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18765333/South-Korea-to-require-firms-to-report-crypto-holdings-from-next-year</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18765333/South-Korea-to-require-firms-to-report-crypto-holdings-from-next-year"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T07:55:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The country passed legislation last month aimed at protecting crypto investors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance US Denies BCH FUD: Crypto Influencer Seeks Proof]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18765107/Binance-US-Denies-BCH-FUD-Crypto-Influencer-Seeks-Proof</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18765107/Binance-US-Denies-BCH-FUD-Crypto-Influencer-Seeks-Proof"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T07:42:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adam Cochran, founder of the activist venture capital firm Cinneamhain Ventures (CEHV), raised concerns against Binance.US and its CEO Brian Shroder. While the platform attempted to clarify the prevailing ambiguities regarding Bitcoin Cash (BCH) FUD, Cochran questioned the long silence of the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This 'Bitcoin Family' Uses The Moon's Cycle To Score 50% Gains Since Bear Market Lows]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18765273/This-Bitcoin-Family-Uses-The-Moons-Cycle-To-Score-50-Gains-Since-Bear-Market-Lows</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18765273/This-Bitcoin-Family-Uses-The-Moons-Cycle-To-Score-50-Gains-Since-Bear-Market-Lows"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T07:41:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the picturesque town of Lagos, nestled along Portugal’s Algarve region, Didi Taihuttu starts his days on the rooftop of his villa, absorbed in cryptocurrency price charts. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cathie Wood’s ARK sells 135K Coinbase shares as price hits $90]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18765055/Cathie-Woods-ARK-sells-135K-Coinbase-shares-as-price-hits-90</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18765055/Cathie-Woods-ARK-sells-135K-Coinbase-shares-as-price-hits-90"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T07:41:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cathie Wood is taking profits from ARK Invest’s Coinbase holdings by selling a small portion of its stash.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase (COIN) Shares Jump 16% after Filing Indicates ETF Surveillance-Sharing Agreement with Cboe]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18764798/Coinbase-COIN-Shares-Jump-16-after-Filing-Indicates-ETF-Surveillance-Sharing-Agreement-with-Cboe</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18764798/Coinbase-COIN-Shares-Jump-16-after-Filing-Indicates-ETF-Surveillance-Sharing-Agreement-with-Cboe"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T07:39:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinspeaker Coinbase (COIN) Shares Jump 16% after Filing Indicates ETF Surveillance-Sharing Agreement with Cboe Coinbase will now join market surveillance sharing for Cboe ETFs even as market sentiments suggest BlackRock will win SEC approval. Coinbase (COIN) Shares Jump 16% after Filing...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao Reveals His Secret for Building ‘Tight Teams’: External Pressure]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756e56eeb3</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/binance-ceo-changpeng-zhao-reveals-his-secret-for-building-tight-teams-external-pressure/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T07:37:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Changpeng Zhao, CEO of Binance, the largest cryptocurrency exchange in volume traded, has revealed his secret for building a comprehensive team of employees for any startup. According to Zhao, external pressure has contributed to the unity of the team behind the exchange, and it also makes the Binance team more driven to its objective of increasing the “freedom of money for people all around the world.”
Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao States Pressure Contributes to Building ‘Tight Teams’
Changpeng Zhao, CEO of Binance, took to social media to explain what he believes is a “little secret” for building “tight teams” in companies. Amidst recent reports indicating that several high-level executives had left the company after a response to an ongoing investigation by the U.S. Department of Justice, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Giant Investment Company Started Selling Coinbase Shares It Has Collected For The First Time!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18764870/Giant-Investment-Company-Started-Selling-Coinbase-Shares-It-Has-Collected-For-The-First-Time</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18764870/Giant-Investment-Company-Started-Selling-Coinbase-Shares-It-Has-Collected-For-The-First-Time"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T07:33:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company, which is Coinbase's fourth-largest owner, had been buying stocks in price drops for about 11 months until June. Continue Reading: Giant Investment Company Started Selling Coinbase Shares It Has Collected For The First Time!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Binance see recovery thanks to this announcement? Details inside…]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18764782/Will-Binance-see-recovery-thanks-to-this-announcement-Details-inside</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18764782/Will-Binance-see-recovery-thanks-to-this-announcement-Details-inside"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T07:30:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance's ARKM token launch may attract new users to the exchange and improve sentiment. BNB fails to see any major positive changes in terms of price.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitter founder launches crypto mining hardware]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18764835/Twitter-founder-launches-crypto-mining-hardware</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18764835/Twitter-founder-launches-crypto-mining-hardware"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T07:29:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is expected to be available in early 2024, before the halving]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Korea Wants Companies to Disclose Crypto Holdings]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18764796/South-Korea-Wants-Companies-to-Disclose-Crypto-Holdings</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18764796/South-Korea-Wants-Companies-to-Disclose-Crypto-Holdings"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T07:27:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Companies that issue or own crypto will have to make disclosures in their financial statements from next year onwards, say draft rules.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shaping Crypto Tax Laws: US Senate Panel Seeks More Investor Input]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756e50d1cc</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-senate-panel-seeks-investor-input/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T07:21:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto tax laws have taken a positive turn as United States Senate Financial Services Committee Chair Ron Wyden and ranking member Mike Crapo recently published an open letter aimed at soliciting feedback from the digital asset community regarding the taxation of digital assets.
 
In an effort to tackle the prevailing ambiguities surrounding the tax implications of digital assets, the committee took the proactive step on Tuesday of inviting input from the public. 
 
This indicates a significant departure from the unfavorable atmosphere that has been generated by the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).
 
 
By actively seeking perspectives and insights from those involved in the digital asset space, the panel is demonstrating its commitment to fostering a more inclusive and collabor…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LBRY Final Judgment Leaves Ripple And XRP Hanging In The Balance]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756e50d1c8</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/lbry-judgment-leaves-ripple-xrp-hanging-in-balance/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T07:21:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple and the XRP community were eagerly awaiting the ruling in the LBRY case yesterday. In a court decision issued on Tuesday, July 11, the case between the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and decentralized content sharing platform LBRY Inc. reached its conclusion.
 
The LBRY team announced the final ruling on Twitter, stating that they will fully dissolve LBRY Inc. in accordance with the court order. They also emphasized that the future of LBRY is now in the hands of the community. However, the implications of this ruling have raised concerns about the potential impact on Ripple and the digital asset XRP.
 
Similar Result Possible In The Ripple Case?
 
Lawyer Jeremy Hogan, known for his involvement in the XRP community, shared his insights on the LBRY case and its potential ram…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shaping Crypto Tax Laws: US Senate Panel Seeks More Investor Input]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18764278/Shaping-Crypto-Tax-Laws-US-Senate-Panel-Seeks-More-Investor-Input</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18764278/Shaping-Crypto-Tax-Laws-US-Senate-Panel-Seeks-More-Investor-Input"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T07:19:12.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Traders Prepare for Bitcoin Volatility as Focus Shifts to U.S. CPI]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756e51e446</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/07/12/crypto-twitter-tracks-bitcoin-bollinger-bands-as-focus-shifts-to-us-cpi/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T07:12:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto traders anticipates a big move in bitcoin as Bollinger bands have tightened to the lowest level since early January.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cathie Wood’s Ark Invest sold Coinbase shares as stock rallies]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18764145/Cathie-Woods-Ark-Invest-sold-Coinbase-shares-as-stock-rallies</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18764145/Cathie-Woods-Ark-Invest-sold-Coinbase-shares-as-stock-rallies"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T07:07:12.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Trader Issues Bitcoin Warning, Says BTC Headed for Deeper Decline After ‘Savage’ Move – Here’s His Target]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18764135/Top-Trader-Issues-Bitcoin-Warning-Says-BTC-Headed-for-Deeper-Decline-After-Savage-Move-Heres-His-Target</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18764135/Top-Trader-Issues-Bitcoin-Warning-Says-BTC-Headed-for-Deeper-Decline-After-Savage-Move-Heres-His-Target"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T07:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An analyst who correctly called Bitcoin’s (BTC) 2018 bear market bottom is predicting a deeper move to the downside for the crypto king. Pseudonymous analyst Bluntz tells his 223,600 Twitter followers that BTC appears to have printed a bearish lower high setup on the four-hour chart. According...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Traders Prepare for Bitcoin Volatility as Focus Shifts to U.S. CPI]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18764073/Crypto-Traders-Prepare-for-Bitcoin-Volatility-as-Focus-Shifts-to-US-CPI</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18764073/Crypto-Traders-Prepare-for-Bitcoin-Volatility-as-Focus-Shifts-to-US-CPI"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T07:01:22.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Argo’s June Bitcoin Production and Revenue Fall by Almost 20%]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756e53835c</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/argos-june-bitcoin-production-and-revenue-fall-by-almost-20/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T06:57:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The London and  
NASDAQ-listed miner, Argo Blockchain has revealed a drop in monthly Bitcoin  
(BTC) production and revenue. Despite these setbacks, Argo is enhancing its  
total hash rate capacity and signals a stronger outlook for the future.
Argo Blockchain’s Bitcoin  
Production Falls in June
In June  
2023, Argo mined 139 Bitcoin or Bitcoin Equivalents, averaging 4.6 BTC daily.  
This represents a decrease of 17% from the 5.6 BTC mined each day in May 2023. During  
the previous month, the total number of tokens mined was 173 BTC.
June’s  
decline is attributed to increased network difficulty and a scale-down of  
operations at the Helios facility in Texas. While this curtailment limited the  
number of Bitcoin mined, Argo anticipates additional cash inflows from specific  
power trad…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Damian Chmiel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Government Tightens Regulations on AI Development]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18763740/Chinese-Government-Tightens-Regulations-on-AI-Development</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18763740/Chinese-Government-Tightens-Regulations-on-AI-Development"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T06:50:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Chinese government is considering additional regulations on artificial intelligence (AI) development, focusing on content...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celsius Sues StakeHound for Failing to Return $150M Worth of Tokens]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756e5d0bc7</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/07/12/celsius-sues-stakehound-for-failing-to-return-150m-worth-of-tokens/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T06:43:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[StakeHound has 55,000 ether, 50 million MATIC, and 66,000 DOT that Celsius wants back]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cathie Wood's Ark Offloads $12M Worth Of Bitcoin-Linked Stock Amid 10% Rally On CBOE Tie-Up]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18763875/Cathie-Woods-Ark-Offloads-12M-Worth-Of-Bitcoin-Linked-Stock-Amid-10-Rally-On-CBOE-Tie-Up</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18763875/Cathie-Woods-Ark-Offloads-12M-Worth-Of-Bitcoin-Linked-Stock-Amid-10-Rally-On-CBOE-Tie-Up"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T06:42:53.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Exchange Binance Announces This Altcoin Will Support Network Upgrade!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18763578/Bitcoin-Exchange-Binance-Announces-This-Altcoin-Will-Support-Network-Upgrade</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18763578/Bitcoin-Exchange-Binance-Announces-This-Altcoin-Will-Support-Network-Upgrade"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T06:35:06.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bad news for Ripple? LBRY judge passes ruling on if secondary crypto sales are securities]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18763569/Bad-news-for-Ripple-LBRY-judge-passes-ruling-on-if-secondary-crypto-sales-are-securities</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18763569/Bad-news-for-Ripple-LBRY-judge-passes-ruling-on-if-secondary-crypto-sales-are-securities"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T06:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ETH investors vs whales: Who will sweep this powerplay?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18763526/ETH-investors-vs-whales-Who-will-sweep-this-powerplay</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18763526/ETH-investors-vs-whales-Who-will-sweep-this-powerplay"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T06:30:37.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LBRY Final Judgment Leaves Ripple And XRP Hanging In The Balance]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18763550/LBRY-Final-Judgment-Leaves-Ripple-And-XRP-Hanging-In-The-Balance</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18763550/LBRY-Final-Judgment-Leaves-Ripple-And-XRP-Hanging-In-The-Balance"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T06:30:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple and the XRP community were eagerly awaiting the ruling in the LBRY case yesterday. In a court decision issued on Tuesday, July 11, the case between the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and decentralized content sharing platform LBRY Inc. reached its conclusion. The LBRY team...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cathie Wood's ARK Sells $12M Coinbase Shares as COIN Nears Yearly High]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756e58aae5</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/07/12/cathie-woods-ark-sells-12m-coinbase-shares-as-coin-nears-yearly-high/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T06:09:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ARK currently owns 11.03 million shares of Coinbase.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BIS Survey: 93% of the World’s Central Banks Are Engaged in CBDC Work]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756e5be537</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bis-survey-93-of-the-worlds-central-banks-are-engaged-in-cbdc-work/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T05:36:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bank for International Settlements (BIS), an organization that seeks to support the international cooperation of the world’s central banks, has released the results of its 2022 survey on central bank digital currencies (CBDC) and crypto. The survey found that 93% of the 86 banks surveyed were involved in CBDC-related work at different levels.
BIS: 93% of Central Banks Involved in CBDC Activity
The Bank for International Settlements (BIS), an institution that acts as the bank of central banks, has released the results of a 2022 survey on central bank digital currencies (CBDC) and crypto. In a recent paper titled “Making Headway,” the institution reports that 93% of the 86 banks included in the survey were “engaged in some form of CBDC work and more than half are running concrete experim…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russia’s Central Bank: BRICS Currency Requires Consent of Many Parties, Faces Implementation Challenges]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756e4f02eb</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/russias-central-bank-brics-currency-requires-consent-of-many-parties-faces-implementation-challenges/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T03:36:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The governor of Russia’s central bank says the creation of a common BRICS currency “requires the consent of many parties.” While emphasizing that the proposed BRICS currency “deserves attention,” the Russian central bank chief cautioned that this project is challenging and “will be quite difficult to implement.”
 
Bank of Russia Governor on BRICS Currency
 
Bank of Russia Governor Elvira Nabiullina talked about the proposed BRICS currency on the sidelines of the central bank’s annual Financial Congress, which took place on July 6-7 in St. Petersburg. The BRICS economic bloc comprises Brazil, Russia, India, China, and South Africa.
 
The BRICS currency initiative is expected to be one of the topics discussed at the upcoming BRICS leaders’ summit in South Africa that’s scheduled for Aug. 22-…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free Slurpee NFTs Served Up by 7-Eleven]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148232</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148232/7-eleven-slurpee-vibe-nft-solana"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T02:08:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ‘Find Your Slurpee Vibe’ Polygon collectible represents the latest snack food brand to enter Web3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robert Kiyosaki Warns US Dollar ‘Will Die’ Citing BRICS Nations’ Plan to Launch Gold-Backed Currency]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756e31a65d</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/robert-kiyosaki-warns-us-dollar-will-die-citing-brics-nations-plan-to-launch-gold-backed-currency/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T01:32:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rich Dad Poor Dad author Robert Kiyosaki has warned that the U.S. dollar will die. He expects the BRICS nations (Brazil, Russia, India, China, and South Africa) to launch a gold-backed currency that will kill the USD. The famous author further stressed that U.S. dollars will come flooding home and inflation will go through the roof.
 
Robert Kiyosaki on Death of US Dollar, BRICS Currency Launch, Inflation
 

 
Robert Kiyosaki, the author of Rich Dad Poor Dad, has weighed in on the proposed BRICS currency and its potential impact on the U.S. dollar. Rich Dad Poor Dad is a 1997 book co-authored by Kiyosaki and Sharon Lechter. It has been on the New York Times Best Seller List for over six years. More than 32 million copies of the book have been sold in over 51 languages across more than 109 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Comedian Louis CK Trolls Crypto Twitter: Only Bitcoin Isn’t A “Scam”]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756e32547a</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/comedian-louis-ck-trolls-crypto-twitter-bitcoin/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T01:24:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stand-up comedy legend Louis CK is making cracks at the expense of crypto Twitter, claiming that only Bitcoin isn’t a “scam”.
 
Find out if the funny man is serious, making a joke, or simply stirring the pot. Also, learn why CK could be holding crypto longer than you have.
 
Comedy Legend Cracks On Crypto, Calls Altcoins A “Scam”
 
A new Twitter thread by user Sir Doge of the Coin, tells the audience to start arguing in the comments. Never one to shy away from such opportunities to create outrage, comedian Louis CK jumped on the thread, calling all other cryptocurrencies “besides Bitcoin” a “scam”.
 
 
The antagonizing comment immediately resulted in other users taking the bait, responding with reasons for why Ethereum and other altcoins are legitimate, worthwhile investments.
 
Given the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tony &amp;quot;The Bull&amp;quot;</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Silk Road Bitcoin Black Market Advisor Receives Maximum Sentence of 20 Years]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756e325475</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/silk-road-bitcoin-advisor-receives-sentence/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T01:24:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roger Thomas Clark, also known as “Plural of Mongoose,” “Variety Jones,” “VJ,” and “cimon,” has been sentenced to 20 years in prison for his role as the top adviser to Ross Ulbricht, the owner and operator of the Silk Road online illicit black market. 
 
According to the press release by the Southern District Court of New York, Clark played a central role in the operation of Silk Road, advising Ulbricht on all aspects of the enterprise, including facilitating an attempted murder-for-hire. 
 
Silk Road was a secret online marketplace that operated from 2011 until 2013 and was used by thousands of drug dealers and other vendors to distribute illegal drugs and other illicit goods and services to more than 100,000 buyers and launder hundreds of millions of dollars derived from those unlawful t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Exodus: Over 855,000 BTC Withdrawn From Exchanges Since July 2020]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756e3e318c</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-exodus-over-855000-btc-withdrawn-from-exchanges-since-july-2020/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T00:39:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to current data, about 2,086,034 bitcoins were held on exchanges as of July 11, 2023. This figure is 154,160 bitcoins less than the number held on centralized trading platforms 72 days earlier, on April 30. The number of bitcoins on exchanges has significantly dropped since July 31, 2020, when nearly 3 million bitcoins were held in exchange reserves.
 
Centralized Crypto Exchanges Face Bitcoin Drain
 

 
The number of bitcoins held in exchange reserves has steadily decreased over the past two years and 11 months, data from cryptoquant.com shows. On July 31, 2020, metrics indicated that 2,941,655 bitcoins were held on exchanges. As of today, the number has decreased to 2,086,034. This means that over the past 1,075 days, customers have removed 855,621 bitcoins from centralized tra…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Mover Asia: Crypto Market Is on ‘Standby’ as Release of June Inflation Data Nears]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756e3e8407</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/07/12/first-mover-asia-crypto-market-is-on-standby-as-release-of-june-inflation-data-nears/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T00:35:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PLUS: A Freely Convertible Yuan is a Requirement for a CNY Stablecoin]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale Bitcoin Trust’s Premium Falls To 28% As Tug-Of-War With SEC Continues]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756e3f5141</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/grayscale-bitcoin-trusts-premium-falls-to-28/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T00:25:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) has been on an uncertain journey over the last year as crypto headwinds have fluctuated. This was a result of the uncertainty triggered by the Genesis Trading bankruptcy, a company under the same Digital Currency Group (DCG) umbrella, of which the GBTC is a part. However, the trust has done better as the market has moved on from this event and the discount is starting to shrink.
 
Grayscale Bitcoin Trust Discount Down To 28%
 
The crypto winter of 2022 saw the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust discount to NAV widen over a matter of months. At a point, the discount had shifted to almost 50%, meaning that at its highest premium, investors in the trust were holding BTC at a 50% price lower than the spot market price of the digital asset.
 
 
However, with BTC’s recove…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Best Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Economist Peter Schiff Warns All Banks Will Fail, People Will Suffer Massive Losses as Banking Crisis Unfolds]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756e3b64e8</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/economist-peter-schiff-warns-all-banks-will-fail-people-will-suffer-massive-losses-as-banking-crisis-unfolds/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T23:37:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Economist Peter Schiff has warned that all banks will fail and anyone having a bank account will end up losing money. “No matter what happens, people are going to lose a tremendous amount as this banking crisis unfolds,” Schiff stressed.
 
Peter Schiff Warns About All Banks Failing
 
Economist and gold bug Peter Schiff reiterated his concerns regarding the state of the U.S. economy and the impending banking crisis on the David Lin show, published last week.
 
“The whole banking sector is completely insolvent, thanks to what we’ve done over the last decade or so by loading up these banks with all this long-term, low-yielding debt. And we had all [this] deposit insurance so nobody really cared about what the banks were doing with their money because it was all insured by the government,” Sch…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bear Market Woes: NEAR Foundation’s Treasury Loses $200 Million]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756e245ce2</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/near-foundation-treasury-loses-200-million/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T23:26:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NEAR cryptocurrency’s hit in price seems to have made its way to the NEAR Foundation’s treasury. According to the foundation behind NEAR’s layer-1 blockchain, it saw a $200 million decline in its treasury at the end of the second quarter of the year.
 
NEAR Foundation’s Treasury Value Tanks In Q2
 
The Near Foundation’s treasury value dropped by over $200 million in the second quarter of 2022 alone. The foundation’s Q2 edition of its transparency report showed that the NEAR treasury now stands at $900 million, led by a fall in the price of NEAR tokens. In comparison, the Near Treasury totaled $1.1 billion in Q1 2023. 
 
 
 
At the #NEAR Foundation, transparency is at our core.
 
Check out the Foundation’s Q2 ’23 Transparency Report below for all the details on treasury, strategy, OKRs,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Innovation on the Field: Unveiling Crypto-Backed Sports Sponsorships]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756e25f047</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/innovation/innovation-on-the-field-unveiling-crypto-backed-sports-sponsorships/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T23:08:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sports have  
long been a hub of innovation and technology. Sports have embraced innovation  
to improve the game, from innovations in equipment to data analytics altering  
individual performance. A new trend has evolved in recent years, mixing the  
worlds of sports and cryptocurrency. 
Sports  
sponsorships backed by cryptocurrency are taking the sports industry by storm,  
providing intriguing potential for both clubs and cryptocurrency organizations.  
We will look at the rise of crypto-backed sports sponsorships, their benefits,  
and the consequences for the sports and cryptocurrency industries in this article.
With the rise  
of Bitcoin and other digital currencies, cryptocurrency has attracted  
substantial interest in recent years. These digital assets function on decentralized  …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FM Contributors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tokenized U.S. Treasurys Surpass $600M as Crypto Investors Capture TradFi Yield]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756e25fea8</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/07/11/tokenized-us-treasurys-surpass-600m-as-crypto-investors-capture-tradfi-yield/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T23:07:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto investors now effectively lend $614 million to the U.S. government via different tokenized Treasury products, according to real-world asset data firm RWA.xyz.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arkham CEO Defends ‘Dox-to-Earn’ Program, Says Identifying Bad Actors Is 'The Whole Point']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148208</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148208/arkham-ceo-miguel-morel-dox-to-earn-twitter-spaces"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T22:58:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Arkham focuses on strictly publicly available information to then draw connections about what entities own what wallets,” said Miguel Morel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Gran Saga: Unlimited' Is a Promising MMORPG Launching on Aptos]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148189</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148189/gran-saga-unlimited-promising-mmorpg-launching-aptos"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T22:49:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PREVIEW: Gran Saga: Unlimited is an open-world anime game that lets players fight creatures using guns, melee weapons, and magic.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Claude 2 Is Out—How Does Anthropic’s AI Chatbot Compare to ChatGPT and Google Bard?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148147</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148147/anthropic-claude-2-ai-chatbot-comparison-openai-chatgpt-google-bard"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T22:25:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic's latest entry can handle 100k of context, but will it be enough to compete?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gran Saga Unlimited Early Access: Inside the Anime MMORPG on Aptos]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JeFWMVwo/gran-saga-unlimited-early-access-inside-the-anime-mmorpg-on-aptos</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JeFWMVwo/gran-saga-unlimited-early-access-inside-the-anime-mmorpg-on-aptos"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T21:46:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin plays Gran Saga: Unlimited's second community playtest, reports her findings, and offer her opinion and insights on the upcoming game, which will offer optional Aptos NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Has Formed a 'Firm Foundation' Under $30000: Glassnode]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148181</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148181/bitcoin-price-30000-firm-foundation-glassnode"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T21:21:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[History suggests that Bitcoin may be due for many months of sideways trading, the firm said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Latest NFT Trend: Taking Out Loans on Rolexes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148099</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148099/latest-nft-trend-taking-out-loans-rolexes"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T20:42:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NFT lending protocol Arcade and escrow service 4K aim to create a global pawn shop of strangers, starting with Rolex and Patek Philippe watches.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Binance Too Big to Fail?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148031</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148031/binance-too-big-to-fail"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T20:14:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto industry has withstood what were supposed to be fatal blows before. Would Binance leave a permanent dent if it crumbles?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another $103M Disappears From Multichain in Potential ‘Rug Pull’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148133</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148133/multichain-anyswap-rug-pull-hack-103-million-chainalysis"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T20:02:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The hack of the former Anyswap platform is flagged as an inside job by Chainalysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Exec Investigated for Illegal Donations to Girlfriend's Congressional Campaign: WSJ]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148115</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148115/ftx-executive-ryan-salame-donations-investigation-girlfriend-campaign"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T18:12:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The FBI raided the home of Ryan Salame in April while investigating Sam Bankman-Fried’s political activities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feds Charge Engineer in First-Ever Decentralized Exchange Hack Case]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148097</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148097/feds-charge-engineer-first-ever-decentralized-exchange-hack-case"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T16:07:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Attorney Damian Williams today said that Shakeeb Ahmed "used his expertise to defraud" and allegedly steal $9 million in crypto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK to Exclude 'Unbacked’ Cryptocurrencies From Digital Securities Sandbox Initiative]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148082</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148082/uk-exclude-unbacked-cryptocurrencies-digital-securities-sandbox-initiative"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T14:28:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The British government does not plan to modify the existing legislative framework for derivatives and unbacked cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Are Play-to-Earn (P2E) Games?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=118693</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-are-play-to-earn-p2e-games"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T13:49:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unlike in regular games, where in-game items are held on walled-off data networks and owned by the companies that created the game, NFTs enable players to own the unique assets that they purchase.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi Project Rodeo Finance Hacked for $888,000 in Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148068</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148068/layer-2-defi-project-rodeo-finance-hacked-472-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T13:05:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An exploiter was able to run away with roughly $888,000 in Ethereum from Rodeo’s interest-bearing USDC pool.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Now Earn Bitcoin for Playing Minecraft—Here’s How]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148037</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148037/you-can-now-earn-bitcoin-playing-minecraft-heres-how"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T13:01:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Satlantis Minecraft server is now giving out over 1 million satoshis per week in partnership with Bitcoin payments startup Zebedee.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Magic Johnson-Backed SimWin Sports Infuses Fantasy Football With AI and NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148033</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148033/magic-johnson-fantasy-football-ai-nft-simwin-sports"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The platform aims to bridge eSports and fantasy sports with a 24/7 virtual football league.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFT-Powered Dan Harmon Series 'Krapopolis' Finally Gets Premiere Date]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148057</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148057/nft-powered-dan-harmon-series-krapopolis-finally-gets-premiere-date"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T12:13:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An NFT collection affiliated with Harmon’s new animated series on Fox has already generated almost $1 million in sales.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MATIC Soars 9% Ahead of Polygon 2.0 Rollout, Rebounding Network Growth]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148047</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148047/matic-soars-9-ahead-polygon-2-0-rollout-rebounding-network-growth"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T11:25:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon’s uptick can likely be attributed to rebounding on-chain growth and the completion of a $66 million sell-off by bankrupt Celsius.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paradigm Files Amicus Brief in SEC’s Lawsuit Against Bittrex]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148053</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148053/paradigm-files-amicus-brief-sec-lawsuit-against-bittrex"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T10:57:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC lacks the authority to regulate secondary markets for crypto assets, argues crypto investment firm Paradigm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Now Store Your Bitcoin Private Key as Colors]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148026</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148026/bitcoin-private-key-phrase-encoding-colors"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T00:10:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new tool for backing up your private keys could make it even harder for thieves—and the government—to seize your coins.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale Cries Foul Over SEC Approval of a Different Kind of Bitcoin ETF]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148009</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148009/grayscale-protests-sec-approval-leveraged-bitcoin-futures-not-spot-etf"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T00:02:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company says the difference between a leveraged Bitcoin future ETF and a spot Bitcoin ETF isn’t enough to stonewall the latter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix Taps AI To Push Visual Effects Beyond the Green Screen]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147986</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147986/netflix-ai-green-screen-magenta-visual-effects-movies"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T23:40:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why go for a green screen when there’s an AI-powered magenta option?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fei Protocol Discord Was Not 'Seized' Amid Class-Action Lawsuit, Says Lawyer]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147994</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147994/fei-protocol-dao-discord-not-seized-by-court"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T23:20:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A message appearing on Fei Labs' Discord alerted investors who may have been hurt by its shaky launch event in April 2021 on how to file a notice for compensation as part of an ongoing class-action lawsuit against the platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily Ordinals Inscriptions Approach All-Time High as Bitcoin Fees Remain Low]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148021</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148021/daily-ordinals-bitcoin-inscriptions-near-all-time-high-low-fees"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T23:12:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ordinals ecosystem has seen a flood of new projects, and fees have remained low.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['The Machines Arena' Adds In-Game Rewards That Can Be Minted as NFTs (Eventually)]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148008</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148008/machines-arena-adds-in-game-rewards-minted-nfts-eventually"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T22:43:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Players with lots of XP in The Machines Arena will be able to unlock character skins that can later be minted and traded.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scientists Use AI to Discover Drugs That Kill 'Zombie Cells', Fight Age-Related Diseases]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147681</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147681/ai-drug-discovery-senolytic"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T22:29:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A group of researchers used AI to do in five minutes what could have taken weeks: Discovering new drugs that can kill senescent cells.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ApeCoin Crashes to All-Time Low as Bored Ape Yacht Club NFT Prices Sink]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147982</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147982/apecoin-crashes-all-time-low-bored-ape-yacht-club-nft-prices-sink"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T20:38:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ethereum token linked to Yuga Labs' Bored Ape Yacht Club collection has now fallen nearly 93% from its peak price.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Will Reach $120K Before 2025, Standard Chartered Predicts]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147970</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147970/bitcoin-will-reach-120k-before-2025-standard-chartered-predicts"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T19:38:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The British bank believes miners will soon begin hoarding their coins and choking off available market supply.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former SEC Chair Says Bitcoin ETF Could Be Approved—If These Conditions Are Met]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147975</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147975/former-sec-chair-says-bitcoin-etf-should-be-approved-if-conditions-met"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T19:09:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The former SEC chair said that a Bitcoin ETF will be approved in the States if an applicant can prove it's an efficient way for investors to buy BTC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Staked Ethereum Now Accounts for 20% of the Total Supply]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147968</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147968/staked-ethereum-now-accounts-for-20-of-the-total-supply"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T18:17:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The amount of Ethereum pledged to secure the network has grown significantly since withdrawals were enabled in April.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vanguard Now Owns $560 Million Worth of Bitcoin Mining Stocks]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147950</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147950/vanguard-owns-560-million-bitcoin-mining-stocks"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T17:58:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The $7.2 trillion asset manager now owns half a billion dollars worth of Riot Blockchain and Marathon Digital shares.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Half a Billion Has Poured Into Bitcoin Funds in Past Three Weeks]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147925</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147925/half-a-billion-has-poured-into-bitcoin-funds-in-past-three-weeks"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T17:18:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[But exchange inflows are at a cycle low, signaling that it's primarily institutions that feel bullish.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[100 Thieves' Moe Says Blockchain Games Will 'Eventually' Be Accepted by Livestreamers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/xHhh62ID/100-thieves-moe-says-blockchain-games-will-eventually-be-accepted-by-livestreamers</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/xHhh62ID/100-thieves-moe-says-blockchain-games-will-eventually-be-accepted-by-livestreamers"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T16:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[100 Thieves content creator and gamer Moe also goes by "Yassuo" online after his favorite League of Legends character. Decrypt's Kate Irwin asks him about 100 Thieves' future crypto plans and whether Moe thinks creators like xQc and Pokimane might ever come around to blockchain games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Twitter Reacts to Arkham’s New 'Dox-to-Earn' Intelligence Exchange]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147920</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147920/crypto-twitter-reacts-arkhams-new-dox-earn-intelligence-exchange"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T16:09:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain intelligence firm Arkham is opening an exchange where data on the identities of crypto wallet owners can be traded and requested.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gutter Cat Gang Twitter Hacked, At Least $750K Worth of NFTs Swiped]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147913</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147913/gutter-cat-gang-twitter-hacked-at-least-750k-worth-nfts-swiped"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T15:34:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Twitter account for the NFT project Gutter Cat Gang were hacked to promote a fake airdrop to an audience of more than 124,000 followers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Bitcoin an Investment or a Currency ?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=5738</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/bitcoin-investment-or-currency"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T14:35:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin is being explored as three distinct ideas: a currency, an asset and a commodity. Because regulation takes place mostly at state level, Bitcoin has become all three things simultaneously in different parts of the world.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Hussey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Hashing?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=5681</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/hashing"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T14:34:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hashing is one of the most crucial pieces of technology that keeps the Bitcoin network secure. But how does it work?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Hussey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stepn Creator's Next Game Is a Social MMO Called Gas Hero]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147876</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147876/stepn-creators-next-game-social-mmo-called-gas-hero"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gas Hero, from the developer of move-to-earn game Stepn, takes place in a dystopian world where a powerful AI has triggered nuclear war.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is the Lightning Network? Bitcoin's Scalability Solution.]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=5684</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/bitcoin-lightning-network"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lightning Network is a scaling solution that attempts to address Bitcoin's slow transaction speeds and high transaction costs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Hussey,Tim Copeland,Daniel Phillips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto, Stablecoins May Pose 'Threat to Financial Stability' if Widely Used: BIS Survey]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147898</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147898/crypto-stablecoins-may-pose-threat-financial-stability-widely-used-bis-survey"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T12:23:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two dozen central banks are also expected to launch either wholesale or consumer-facing retail CBDCs by the end of the decade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Hash Rate Hits New All-Time High Amid Stagnating Prices]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147890</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147890/bitcoin-hash-rate-hits-new-all-time-high-stagnating-prices"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T12:04:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The computing power of the Bitcoin network is at its highest levels again, making the world’s largest cryptocurrency more secure than ever.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Games of the Future Are Going to Be Different," Says Splinterlands Cofounder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/sQv6zcil/games-of-the-future-are-going-to-be-different-says-splinterlands-cofounder</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/sQv6zcil/games-of-the-future-are-going-to-be-different-says-splinterlands-cofounder"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T20:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Splinterlands Cofounder Matt Rosen tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about how the game has evolved over its five-year history and why he doesn't listen to the FUD around crypto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Champions Ascension: Like 'For Honor' with NFTs?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/gvM9ajww/inside-champions-ascension-like-for-honor-with-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/gvM9ajww/inside-champions-ascension-like-for-honor-with-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T22:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plai Labs Marketing Director Payton Kaleiwahea tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about player response to the combat game Champions Ascension in development, which offers arena combat, raid bosses, AI landscape features, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Activision VP Michael Lee: Gaming Is Crypto's 'Killer App']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/M9ulXrb3/ex-activision-vp-michael-lee-gaming-is-cryptos-killer-app</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/M9ulXrb3/ex-activision-vp-michael-lee-gaming-is-cryptos-killer-app"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Activision Vice President Michael Lee is now the SVP of Growth at Matter Labs. At the 3XP gaming conference, Lee sat down with Decrypt's Kate Irwin to discuss crypto gaming and give his predictions for the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Behind the Scenes with AMGI Studios and My Pet Hooligan]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/eQ71oapI/behind-the-scenes-with-amgi-studios-and-my-pet-hooligan</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/eQ71oapI/behind-the-scenes-with-amgi-studios-and-my-pet-hooligan"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T21:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin goes to Burbank, California for a behind-the-scenes tour of AMGI Studios, the developers of upcoming game My Pet Hooligan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Legend of Arcardia Chose Sui Over EVM Chains]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/H6JSRJIk/why-legend-of-arcardia-chose-sui-over-evm-chains</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/H6JSRJIk/why-legend-of-arcardia-chose-sui-over-evm-chains"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T21:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Legend of Arcadia Executive Producer Andy Lee tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the game and why they switched from EVM to new protocol Sui.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rumble Racing Star Game Preview: Is This Mario Kart With NFTs?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/lXVkuaeq/rumble-racing-star-game-preview-is-this-mario-kart-with-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/lXVkuaeq/rumble-racing-star-game-preview-is-this-mario-kart-with-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T16:47:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin shares a first look at Delabs' upcoming lawn mower racing game Rumble Racing Star, which offers a large cast of quirky characters pulled from the worlds of Bored Ape Yacht Club, Pudgy Penguins, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Laguna Games Turned Down 'Game of Thrones' for Crypto Unicorns]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/IqET3GYs/why-laguna-games-turned-down-game-of-thrones-for-crypto-unicorns</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/IqET3GYs/why-laguna-games-turned-down-game-of-thrones-for-crypto-unicorns"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T21:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin chats with Laguna Games about why the team chose to move away from an offer with WB Games to develop a Game of Thrones licensed title—and made Crypto Unicorns instead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mythical Games CEO John Linden on NFL Rivals Topping 1M Downloads]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/nDhvMd8r/mythical-games-ceo-john-linden-on-nfl-rivals-topping-1m-downloads</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/nDhvMd8r/mythical-games-ceo-john-linden-on-nfl-rivals-topping-1m-downloads"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T23:49:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mythical Games just raised a $37 million Series C1 round on the back of the early success of NFL Rivals, which has already topped a million downloads in two months. Mythical CEO John Linden joins Decrypt's Andrew Hayward to discuss the launch and impact of NFL Rivals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Ava Labs Is Approaching Gaming on Avalanche]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/M4TqVEkK/how-ava-labs-is-approaching-gaming-on-avalanche</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/M4TqVEkK/how-ava-labs-is-approaching-gaming-on-avalanche"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T22:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At 3XP, Ava Labs Head of Gaming Ed Chang sat down with Decrypt's Kate Irwin to discuss some of the biggest Avalanche-based games on the horizon and how the company is approaching and thinking about Web3 gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ogimi Founder David Gull on Why AI Should Be Your Meditation Coach]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DnNqBruk/ogimi-founder-david-gull-on-why-ai-should-be-your-meditation-coach</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DnNqBruk/ogimi-founder-david-gull-on-why-ai-should-be-your-meditation-coach"/>
        <updated>2023-06-25T18:45:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ogimi founder David Gull speaks with Decrypt's Jason Nelson about its AI-driven meditation guides and how the technology can enable a more unique, custom-tailored meditation experience for users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VaynerSports Gaming VP Discusses Web3 Content Creators, Decentralized Streaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/1MvGbnK5/vaynersports-gaming-vp-discusses-web3-content-creators-decentralized-streaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/1MvGbnK5/vaynersports-gaming-vp-discusses-web3-content-creators-decentralized-streaming"/>
        <updated>2023-06-24T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Darren Glover, VP of Gaming at talent management agency VaynerSports, sat down with Decrypt's Kate Irwin at the 3XP expo to discuss the challenges faced by Web3-centric content creators, the current state of the esports market, and how decentralized streaming platforms can challenge centralized leaders like Twitch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NYXL Co-Founder on the State of Esports and Crypto Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/xDHUNFLB/nyxl-co-founder-on-the-state-of-esports-and-crypto-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/xDHUNFLB/nyxl-co-founder-on-the-state-of-esports-and-crypto-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-06-23T22:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rohit Gupta, co-founder of esports team NYXL, chats with Decrypt's Kate Irwin at the 3XP expo to discuss challenges faced by the esports industry and opportunities and experiments in Web3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is GameBridge? Inside Shrapnel's Gaming Innovation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/xqVjzGLr/what-is-gamebridge-inside-shrapnels-gaming-innovation</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/xqVjzGLr/what-is-gamebridge-inside-shrapnels-gaming-innovation"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marc Mercuri, Head of Platform for Web3 shooter Shrapnel, speaks with Decrypt's Kate Irwin at the 3XP expo about GameBridge, a feature that simplifies blockchain item composability and interoperability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gods Unchained Executive Producer Discusses Epic Games Store Move]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/hjLymzUL/gods-unchained-executive-producer-discusses-epic-games-store-move</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/hjLymzUL/gods-unchained-executive-producer-discusses-epic-games-store-move"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daniel Paez, Executive Producer on Immutable X-based card-battler Gods Unchained, discusses the long-running NFT game's launch on the Epic Games Store and the opportunity it provides.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Play-to-Earn Is Not Dead. It Will Never Die' Says Words with Friends Creator Paul Bettner]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/znmOo9vp/play-to-earn-is-not-dead-it-will-never-die-says-words-with-friends-creator-paul-bettner</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/znmOo9vp/play-to-earn-is-not-dead-it-will-never-die-says-words-with-friends-creator-paul-bettner"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T14:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Words With Friends and Wildcard Creator Paul Bettner tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about his perspective on Axie Infinity and Web3 games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cross the Ages Game Review: A Tough But Rewarding Card Battler]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/2PfzFDVY/cross-the-ages-game-review-a-tough-but-rewarding-card-battler</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/2PfzFDVY/cross-the-ages-game-review-a-tough-but-rewarding-card-battler"/>
        <updated>2023-06-18T12:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cross the Ages is a digital collectible card game that challenges players to duel online opponents—and you can even mint your cards as tradable NFTs. It's complex and difficult to grasp at first, but this mobile-first game has some serious strategic upside. GG contributor Ryan Gladwin puts Cross the Ages through its paces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["AI Is Game-Changing But Needs Fact-Checking": AlchemyAI Project Lead]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/HXlThlXv/ai-is-game-changing-but-needs-fact-checking-alchemyai-project-lead</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/HXlThlXv/ai-is-game-changing-but-needs-fact-checking-alchemyai-project-lead"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this interview, Decrypt's Jason Nelson chats with Alchemy product manager and AlchemyAI project lead Elan Halpern on blockchain analysis using ChatGPT, what AI means for better user experience, and the need to fact-check AI. Halpern also gives a demo of the new AlchemyAI ChatGPT plugin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fractal Is Like an Arcade, Says Twitch Co-Founder Justin Kan]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/6r6Mdwt6/fractal-is-like-an-arcade-says-twitch-co-founder-justin-kan</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/6r6Mdwt6/fractal-is-like-an-arcade-says-twitch-co-founder-justin-kan"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Justin Kan was a co-founder of Twitch and now works on Fractal, a Web3 gaming startup. Kan tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about his new company and what he's up to.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>