<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-12-16T04:18:01.701Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-12-16T04:18:01.701Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IMF Chief Calls for Clear Crypto Regulation — Warns High Crypto Adoption Could Undermine Financial Stability]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748f90c829</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/imf-chief-calls-for-clear-crypto-regulation-warns-high-crypto-adoption-could-undermine-financial-stability/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T04:09:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The head of the International Monetary Fund (IMF) has called for clear crypto regulations worldwide, cautioning that high crypto adoption could undermine macro-financial stability. “Our goal is to make a more efficient, interoperable, and accessible financial system by providing rules to avoid the risks of crypto, and infrastructure by leveraging some of its technologies,” she stressed.
 
IMF on Crypto Adoption and Financial Stability
 
International Monetary Fund (IMF) Managing Director Kristalina Georgieva called for the establishment of clear regulations and robust infrastructure worldwide to mitigate the risks associated with crypto assets at an international conference in Seoul on Thursday. The two-day conference, titled “Digital Money: Navigating a Changing Financial Landscape,” was …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Live: Exploring Bitcoin & Self-Sovereignty with Graham Wardle & BTC Sessions]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19113421/Live-Exploring-Bitcoin-Self-Sovereignty-with-Graham-Wardle-BTC-Sessions</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19113421/Live-Exploring-Bitcoin-Self-Sovereignty-with-Graham-Wardle-BTC-Sessions"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T03:48:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to our live coverage of 'The Saturday SAT Market' from the heart of Calgary! Today, we're featuring an exclusive Fireside Chat and Q&A session with Graham Wardle, celebrated actor from 'Heartland', and BTC Sessions, a renowned figure in the Bitcoin community. Tune in at 11am to delve...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[National Security at Stake – U.K. AI Institute Urges Caution in Deploying Generative AI Technologies]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19113417/National-Security-at-Stake-UK-AI-Institute-Urges-Caution-in-Deploying-Generative-AI-Technologies</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19113417/National-Security-at-Stake-UK-AI-Institute-Urges-Caution-in-Deploying-Generative-AI-Technologies"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T03:43:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a move, the Alan Turing Institute, the U.K.’s foremost national institute for artificial intelligence, has issued a comprehensive report urging the government to set ‘red lines’ for the deployment of generative AI, especially in contexts where the technology could take irreversible actions...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI-Generated Hallucinations: A Growing Health Concern in 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19113416/AI-Generated-Hallucinations-A-Growing-Health-Concern-in-2023</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19113416/AI-Generated-Hallucinations-A-Growing-Health-Concern-in-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T03:40:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The proliferation of artificial intelligence (AI) has ushered in an unsettling phenomenon: AI-generated hallucinations. The term “hallucinate” has taken on a new and alarming meaning in the digital age, as AI systems can produce false information that can impact individuals and society. In 2023,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI in Dentistry: Transforming Dental Care with Confidence]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19113404/AI-in-Dentistry-Transforming-Dental-Care-with-Confidence</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19113404/AI-in-Dentistry-Transforming-Dental-Care-with-Confidence"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T03:24:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Innovations in healthcare technology have brought artificial intelligence (AI) into the dental care landscape, garnering growing acceptance and confidence among patients. Recent findings from a survey conducted by VideaHealth, a dental AI software firm, shed light on the potential of AI to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wondery Faces Backlash Over ‘Striker’ – The AI Sports Podcast Host Stirring Debate]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19113405/Wondery-Faces-Backlash-Over-Striker-The-AI-Sports-Podcast-Host-Stirring-Debate</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19113405/Wondery-Faces-Backlash-Over-Striker-The-AI-Sports-Podcast-Host-Stirring-Debate"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T03:22:27.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Japanese Scientists Generate Mental Images from Brain Activity Using AI]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19113399/Japanese-Scientists-Generate-Mental-Images-from-Brain-Activity-Using-AI</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19113399/Japanese-Scientists-Generate-Mental-Images-from-Brain-Activity-Using-AI"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T03:11:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Japanese scientists have achieved a remarkable milestone by generating mental images of objects and landscapes directly from human brain activity through the application of artificial intelligence (AI) technology. This cutting-edge research, conducted by a collaborative team from the National...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leading Altcoin Could Surge Over 25% After Forming Bullish Pattern, Popular Crypto Analyst Suggests]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19113398/Leading-Altcoin-Could-Surge-Over-25-After-Forming-Bullish-Pattern-Popular-Crypto-Analyst-Suggests</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19113398/Leading-Altcoin-Could-Surge-Over-25-After-Forming-Bullish-Pattern-Popular-Crypto-Analyst-Suggests"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T03:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Popular cryptocurrency analyst Ali Martinez has recently noted that the native token of Binance’s ecosystem Binance Coin, could be forming a head and shoulders pattern that could see its price rise more than 25%. According to Martinez, Binance Coin’s head and shoulders pattern could “ignite a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Denied Recognition – Copyright Office Rejects AI-Generated Work Application, Board Cites Lack of Human Authorship]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19113388/Denied-Recognition-Copyright-Office-Rejects-AI-Generated-Work-Application-Board-Cites-Lack-of-Human-Authorship</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19113388/Denied-Recognition-Copyright-Office-Rejects-AI-Generated-Work-Application-Board-Cites-Lack-of-Human-Authorship"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T02:56:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a significant development on December 11, 2023, the United States Copyright Office Review Board declined a Second Request for reconsideration concerning the registration of an AI-generated work, challenging the notion of human authorship. Photographer Ankit Sahni’s application, revolving...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Finance Professor Blasts SEC’s Potential Cash-Only Rule for Spot Bitcoin ETFs Citing Benefits of In-Kind Model]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748f9fb089</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/finance-professor-blasts-secs-potential-cash-only-rule-for-spot-bitcoin-etfs-citing-benefits-of-in-kind-model/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T02:39:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A finance professor at Georgetown University has urged the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to avoid micromanaging the creation/redemption process for spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs). While the SEC proposed the cash creation method, applicants like Blackrock and Fidelity have advocated for the in-kind creation method. “Now that the Commission has seemingly become comfortable with allowing spot bitcoin ETFs to trade in the U.S., it should not squander this positive development by forcing a suboptimal product (cash-only creation/redemption) to come to market,” said the professor.
 
Georgetown Professor Urges SEC to Let Spot Bitcoin ETFs Use In-Kind Creation Method
 
James Angel, an Associate Professor of Finance at Georgetown University, penned a letter to the U.S. Sec…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Voice Generating Startup Resemble AI Promises to Restore Old Audio]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210063</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210063/resemble-ai-voice-enhance-recordings"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T01:34:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An AI startup has built a tool that it says can make low-fidelity speech recordings sound like new.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Voice Generating Startup Resemble AI Promises to Restore Old Audio]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19113350/Voice-Generating-Startup-Resemble-AI-Promises-to-Restore-Old-Audio</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19113350/Voice-Generating-Startup-Resemble-AI-Promises-to-Restore-Old-Audio"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T01:34:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An AI startup has built a tool that it says can make low-fidelity speech recordings sound like new.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Analyst Points to Rare Bullish Pattern to Suggest ‘Parabolic Move is Imminent’]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19113349/XRP-Analyst-Points-to-Rare-Bullish-Pattern-to-Suggest-Parabolic-Move-is-Imminent</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19113349/XRP-Analyst-Points-to-Rare-Bullish-Pattern-to-Suggest-Parabolic-Move-is-Imminent"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T01:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Reaches Settlement With Qatari Billionaire In Crypto Scam Ad Case]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748f86a5cc</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/meta-reaches-settlement-with-qatari-crypto-scam-ad/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T01:08:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to a report by the Financial Times, Meta (formerly known as Facebook) has publicly apologized to Qatari billionaire Wissam al Mana and pledged to provide additional safeguards after his image was exploited in crypto scam advertisements on the platform.
 
The prominent businessman, also known as the former husband of pop star Janet Jackson, took legal action against Meta in Dublin, Ireland, over the past three years, alleging significant reputational damage, distress, and embarrassment caused by the fraudulent ads.
 
Meta Admits Publishing False And Defamatory Crypto Ads
 
During a court hearing in Dublin on Friday, Meta admitted that “false, misleading, and defamatory advertisements” featuring Wissam al Mana’s image were published on Facebook without his knowledge or consent. The…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Chair Gensler Reveals Regulator Is ‘Taking a New Look’ at Spot Bitcoin ETF Filings]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748f86b1a9</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/sec-chair-gensler-reveals-regulator-is-taking-a-new-look-at-spot-bitcoin-etf-filings/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T01:07:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Chairman Gary Gensler has revealed that the regulator is taking a new look at spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) applications based on recent court rulings. “We had in the past denied a number of these applications, but the courts here in the District of Columbia weighed in on that,” Gensler explained.
 
Gensler: ‘We’re Taking a New Look’
 
The chairman of the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), Gary Gensler, answered some questions regarding spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) applications in an interview with CNBC on Thursday.
 
“We have, I think, between eight and a dozen filings … that’s going through the process right now,” Gensler explained, emphasizing that as the chairman of the SEC, he’s not going to prejudge any pa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Billion-Dollar Bank Sending $5,000,000 to Customers After Illegally Harvesting Millions in Fees: CFPB]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19113327/Billion-Dollar-Bank-Sending-5000000-to-Customers-After-Illegally-Harvesting-Millions-in-Fees-CFPB</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19113327/Billion-Dollar-Bank-Sending-5000000-to-Customers-After-Illegally-Harvesting-Millions-in-Fees-CFPB"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T01:04:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A US bank with $20.5 billion in assets, loans, and deposits will send at least $5 million to thousands of customers after allegedly harvesting millions of dollars in illegal overdraft fees. The Consumer Financial Protection Bureau (CFPB) says Atlantic Union Bank enrolled thousands of people in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arbitrum Network Faces Major Outage, ARB Token Faces 4% Decline]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19113326/Arbitrum-Network-Faces-Major-Outage-ARB-Token-Faces-4-Decline</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19113326/Arbitrum-Network-Faces-Major-Outage-ARB-Token-Faces-4-Decline"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T01:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Under-the-Radar Altcoin Surges by 58% This Week Amid New Perpetual Contract Listing]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19113319/Under-the-Radar-Altcoin-Surges-by-58-This-Week-Amid-New-Perpetual-Contract-Listing</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19113319/Under-the-Radar-Altcoin-Surges-by-58-This-Week-Amid-New-Perpetual-Contract-Listing"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T01:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Would you go back in time to buy bitcoin? (part 3) #bitcoin #crypto #shorts]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19113317/Would-you-go-back-in-time-to-buy-bitcoin-part-3-bitcoin-crypto-shorts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19113317/Would-you-go-back-in-time-to-buy-bitcoin-part-3-bitcoin-crypto-shorts"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T01:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum's Price Edges Toward $2,500: Surge or Mirage Ahead?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19113328/Ethereums-Price-Edges-Toward-2500-Surge-or-Mirage-Ahead</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19113328/Ethereums-Price-Edges-Toward-2500-Surge-or-Mirage-Ahead"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T01:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum aiming for next resistance level, even though it needs another push]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Vitalik Buterin’s plans for Ethereum came to fruition]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19113304/How-Vitalik-Buterins-plans-for-Ethereum-came-to-fruition</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19113304/How-Vitalik-Buterins-plans-for-Ethereum-came-to-fruition"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T00:30:53.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Has Hit New all-Time Highs In Six Countries]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748f83d0fe</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-price-new-all-time-highs/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T00:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bitcoin price has risen around 80% this year, bringing it to its highest levels of 2023. However, the leading cryptocurrency has still not reached its all-time high of $69,000. Nevertheless, this has not stopped the asset from hitting multiple new all-time high prices in as many as six countries.
 
Six Countries See New Bitcoin All-Time Highs
 
The official X (formerly Twitter) account of Middle-Eastern restaurant Tahini’s, which has been a staunch supporter of Bitcoin, took to the social media platform to share an interesting development. Tahini’s post which came with multiple screenshots showed how Bitcoin has risen to new all-time highs across six countries.
 
 
 
This is what #Bitcoin looks like for the citizens of Turkey, Egypt, Nigeria, Argentina, Lebanon and Pakistan. 
A combine…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Best Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Is Huge For Crypto Holders | Dec 18 Dont Miss!!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19113289/THIS-IS-HUGE-FOR-CRYPTO-HOLDERS-DEC-18-DONT-MISS</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19113289/THIS-IS-HUGE-FOR-CRYPTO-HOLDERS-DEC-18-DONT-MISS"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T00:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Has Hit New all-Time Highs In Six Countries]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19113290/Bitcoin-Price-Has-Hit-New-all-Time-Highs-In-Six-Countries</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19113290/Bitcoin-Price-Has-Hit-New-all-Time-Highs-In-Six-Countries"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T00:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Trade Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19113284/How-To-Trade-Crypto</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19113284/How-To-Trade-Crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T23:59:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to trade crypto – a question that resonates with many in the rapidly evolving digital asset space. Whether you’re a novice eager to learn how to crypto trade or an experienced crypto trader looking to refine your strategies, this guide is your comprehensive resource. From understanding the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK financial heavyweights embrace blockchain for payments revolution]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19113273/UK-financial-heavyweights-embrace-blockchain-for-payments-revolution</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19113273/UK-financial-heavyweights-embrace-blockchain-for-payments-revolution"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T23:36:52.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Crimes Highlighted in IRS Criminal Investigation’s 2023 Top 10 Criminal Cases]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748f8ea52f</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/crypto-crimes-highlighted-in-irs-criminal-investigations-2023-top-10-criminal-cases/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T23:35:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the IRS’s list of top 10 criminal cases for 2023, cryptocurrency frauds are featured, ranging from multi-million dollar tax evasions to elaborate money laundering schemes.
 
Crypto Scams Among Most Significant Financial Crimes in IRS Criminal Investigation’s 2023 Report
 
The IRS Criminal Investigation (CI) division has released its annual list of the top 10 criminal cases for the year 2023, highlighting a significant focus on cryptocurrency-related crimes. The list, which was announced on the IRS website and IRS CI’s social media platforms, includes a variety of financial crimes ranging from international tax fraud to massive Covid-19 relief scams.
 
CI Chief Jim Lee underscored the range and complexity of this year’s cases, emphasizing the billions of dollars involved and the global i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Sencil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Happens If Dogecoin Replicates Its Largest 170% Single-Day Move?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748f892a82</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-replicates-170-move/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T23:07:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in 2021, Dogecoin had put on its largest single-day move at a time when DOGE euphoria was at its peak. This had pushed the price from around $0.17 to over $0.47 in the space of a single day. This remains the most momentous 24 hours for the meme coin, and a repeat would be explosive for its price.
 
A 170% Single-Day Move For Dogecoin?
 
Dogecoin is trading considerably lower than its all-time high of $0.7 back in 2021. However, it is still a long way from its starting point in early 2021 when it traded at around $0.0018. The current $0.096 value at the time of this writing is also around a 30% increase in the price in the span of two months, which puts it on a bullish trajectory.
 
 
Nevertheless, Dogecoin is yet to carry out the kind of move that would satisfy investors who have pati…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not That Grok: Musician Grimes and OpenAI Launch Plush Toy with AI Inside]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210024</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210024/grok-ai-twitter-toy-elon-musk-grimes-trademark"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T22:36:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk’s ex partners with Curio to launch a line of AI-powered toys designed to cut back on screen time and enhance interaction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jupiter Airdrop Set for January With a Billion JUP for Solana DeFi Users]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210017</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210017/jupiter-airdrop-set-january-billion-jup-solana-defi-users"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T22:10:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Half of the 10 billion JUP supply will ultimately go to the Jupiter community, with 10% landing in Solana wallets during the first airdrop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miner Hive Diversifies Into AI, Acquires 96 Nvidia GPUs to Boost High-Performance Computing Operations]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748f77272c</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-miner-hive-diversifies-into-ai-acquires-96-nvidia-gpus-to-boost-high-performance-computing-operations/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T22:05:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Friday, Hive Digital, based in Vancouver and specializing in bitcoin mining and high-performance computing (HPC), announced its foray into artificial intelligence (AI) and HPC technologies. This strategic move involves acquiring 96 Nvidia H100 graphics processing units (GPUs).
 
From Bitcoin Mining to AI Expansion: Hive Digital Acquires Nvidia GPUs for HPC Enhancement
 
Hive Digital (Nasdaq: HIVE), elaborated on its strategy to incorporate these GPUs into a dozen HGX servers. Each server will be equipped with eight H100 GPUs featuring SXM connectivity. This initiative is set to enhance Hive’s existing GPU division, which presently operates 2,600 GPUs in partnership with HPC platforms.
 
The recent addition enables clients to access Hive’s Nvidia GPUs for various timeframes. Frank Holmes…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Weighs Demand for Saga Phones After Sellout Amid BONK Boom]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210036</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210036/solana-weighs-demand-saga-phones-after-sellout-amid-bonk-boom"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T21:51:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Saga is sold out in the U.S. and EU supplies are nearly tapped out. Solana Labs told Decrypt how it’s assessing next moves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Envisions $5 Trillion Worth Of CBDCs In Major Economies by 2030, New White Paper Unveils]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748f72030f</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ripple-envisions-5-trillion-worth-of-cbdcs/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T21:38:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain company Ripple has recently released a comprehensive white paper shedding light on central bank digital currencies (CBDCs). The document offers an analysis of CBDCs’ potential benefits, associated risks, and hurdles to adoption.
 
G20 Nations At The Forefront
 
According to Ripple’s white paper, CBDC projects are gaining momentum worldwide. Currently, 130 countries, representing 98% of the global gross domestic product (GDP), are actively exploring or pursuing CBDC initiatives. 
 
Several countries, including the United States, South Africa, and various European Union members, have entered exploratory phases. China has progressed to a pilot phase and is nearing full-scale launch in certain areas. 
 
The white paper highlights that 19 of the G20 countries are in advanced project …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon Stops Work on 'Edge,' Used to Build Dogechain, as Focus Turns to ZK]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748f72e6a4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/12/15/polygon-stops-work-on-edge-used-to-build-dogechain-as-focus-turns-to-zk/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T21:29:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon Labs, a developer of scaling networks for Ethereum, has shifted toward "Polygon CDK," a blockchain-development kit powered by zero-knowledge cryptography. The older "Polygon Edge" was used by Dogechain, in an unofficial effort to build a Dogecoin-oriented smart-contracts network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bradley Keoun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Tech Giant Alibaba Unveils New AI Video Tool]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210018</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210018/alibaba-ai-text-to-video-generative-cloud"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T21:07:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alibaba says its I2VGen-XL model can handle “visualization, sampling, training, inference, join training using images and videos, acceleration, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin at Risk of Snapping Historic Winning Streak, but 'Perfect Storm' Brews for a Strong 2024]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748f7d7cab</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/12/15/bitcoin-at-risk-of-snapping-historic-winning-streak-but-perfect-storm-brews-for-a-strong-2024/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T21:04:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Investors moved the highest amount of BTC to exchanges since March, IntoTheBlock noted, signaling profit-taking after bitcoin's first eight-week streak of gains since 2017.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Tried to Rein in a Renegade SEC That's Trying to Rein in a Renegade Industry]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748f7f6954</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/12/15/coinbase-tried-to-rein-in-a-renegade-sec-thats-trying-to-rein-in-a-renegade-industry/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T20:46:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC rejected Coinbase's petition for crypto rulemaking, marking yet another refusal to provide regulatory clarity for an industry that badly wants it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Kuhn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JPMorgan Analysts Predict Ether Will Outperform Bitcoin Next Year; Halving Priced In]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748f788958</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/jpmorgan-analysts-predict-ether-will-outperform-bitcoin-next-year-halving-priced-in/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T20:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JPMorgan analysts predict ether, the main asset of the smart contracts enabled Ethereum blockchain, will likely outperform bitcoin next year. A note released this week explains that Proto-Danksharding, an update coming to Ethereum next year to address the network’s operative capacity, will influence the token’s performance.
JPMorgan Predicts Ether Will Outperform Other Cryptocurrencies in 2024
JPMorgan has predicted that ether, the second largest cryptocurrency by market cap, is set to outperform bitcoin and other alternatives in 2024. In a recent note prepared by analysts led by Nikolaos Panigirtzoglou, a managing director of global market strategy at JPMorgan, the bank predicts Ethereum to rise again and “recapture market share within the crypto ecosystem.”
Explaining the reasons behind …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Foundation’s Trademark Application Receives Shocking Response From USPTO]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748f7b8fcc</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-foundation-trademark/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T20:08:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The efforts by the Dogecoin Foundation to trademark the term ‘Dogecoin’ seem to have come to a complete halt following an announcement by the United States Patent and Trademark Office (USPTO). Apparently, the government agency has marked the application as abandoned after not hearing back from the foundation.
 
USPTO Says Dogecoin Trademark Application Is Abandoned
 
An X (formerly Twitter) user took to the platform to share the latest development in the trademark application by the Dogecoin Foundation. According to the screenshot of the email shared, the USPTO has dropped the application as it believes it has been abandoned.
 
 
The email which was dated December 13, 2023, explains that the reason for this move was because it had not received any timely response from the foundation to “Of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitch Walks Back Changes After Surge in Nudity: 'We Went Too Far']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209998</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209998/twitch-walks-back-changes-after-surge-nudity-went-too-far"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T19:37:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, Twitch announced it would allow artistic nudity. Now, it’s blocked again, in part because of concerns around AI realism.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitget Forecasts BTC to Reach $100,000 and ORDI’s Ascent in Next Bull Market]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748f629ca0</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitget-forecasts-btc-to-reach-100000-and-ordis-ascent-in-next-bull-market/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T19:05:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a newly published prediction report, Bitget, a leading derivatives crypto exchange, forecasts a vibrant future for the Bitcoin ecosystem, with BTC potentially soaring to $100,000 and the ORDI BRC20 token climbing the ranks in the next bull market. Bitget researchers say this expansion is set to revolutionize the crypto world, offering unprecedented growth opportunities.
 
Bitget’s Ordinal and Bitcoin Predictions
 

 
Bitget‘s latest report paints an optimistic picture for the Bitcoin blockchain, predicting a robust expansion of the network’s ecosystem. The report predicts that the surge in demand is expected to catapult the price of BTC beyond its previous highs, potentially reaching the landmark figure of $100,000 in the upcoming bull market. The report states:
 

If the Bitcoin ecosys…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum In Peril? ‘ETH May Not Even Be A Listed Asset In 10 years,’ Says Legendary trader]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748f6e3ff5</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-in-peril-eth-may-not-even-be-listed-asset/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T18:35:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Renowned trader and investor Peter Brandt has recently voiced a surprisingly pessimistic view of Ethereum’s future. Brandt, known for his trading acumen, has expressed doubts about Ethereum’s longevity as a major digital currency, especially when contrasted with Bitcoin (BTC).
 
Ethereum’s Uncertain Future According To Brandt
 
Brandt’s forecast for ETH, which he shared in a post on X, centers around his belief that ETH lacks the attributes of a solid store of value. Unlike Bitcoin, which has garnered widespread acceptance as a digital gold equivalent, ETH’s functionality and escalating gas fees cast shadows on its long-term viability.
 
 
Brandt went as far as to describe Ethereum as a “piece of junk,” a bold statement considering Ethereum’s status as the second-largest cryptocurrency by …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Plans to Challenge SEC Denial of Crypto Rulemaking Petition]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209997</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209997/coinbase-plans-challenge-sec-denial-crypto-rulemaking"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T18:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC today denied crypto exchange Coinbase's petition to clarify new crypto rules for the digital assets industry. Coinbase isn't taking "no" for an answer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining Can Help Fight Methane Emissions]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748f692eb9</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/technical/bitcoin-mining-can-help-fight-methane-emissions"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T18:14:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Traditionally, the mining industry has been vilified for its environmental impact and energy use. This article describes the industry where mining can have an immediate positive impact – fossil fuel operations. 
Background
The run-up to November 2023 COP28 in Dubai has seen a flurry of activity from the world’s three largest economies on the question of energy sector methane. That month, China published its long-awaited Methane Emissions Control Action Plan, followed by the China-US Sunnylands Statement on Enhancing Cooperation to Address the Climate Crisis and the European Council and Parliament announcing a deal on new rules to cut methane emissions in the energy sector. Prolific emitters, like Kazakhstan and Turkmenistan, added themselves to the 150 signatories of the Global Methane Ple…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrii Garanin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Scaler Arbitrum Suffers Outage—And Inscriptions Are to Blame]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209996</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209996/ethereum-scaler-arbitrum-suffers-outage-inscriptions-blame"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T18:12:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arbitrum and other chains have recently been bombarded by users making "inscriptions" as on Bitcoin, even though such networks support NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Rejects Coinbase's Call for Crypto-Specific Regulations, Citing Existing Laws]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748f6b5e54</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/sec-rejects-coinbases-call-for-crypto-specific-regulations-citing-existing-laws/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T17:58:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The  
US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has denied Coinbase Global's  
petition for the establishment of new rules governing the digital asset  
industry. Coinbase, a major crypto exchange, had sought tailored regulations  
for the crypto sector, arguing that current U.S. securities laws were  
inadequate. 
However,  
SEC Chair Gary Gensler, in a letter to Coinbase's chief legal officer,  
expressed disagreement with the assertion that existing securities regulations  
are unworkable for the crypto sector.
SEC  
Chair Gensler Affirms Existing Laws Apply to Crypto Securities
In  
a statement on the SEC's website, Gensler emphasized that current laws already  
apply to crypto securities markets, citing the flexibility of the Supreme  
Court's Howey test, which has been successfully…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tareq Sikder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Celebrates One Year of Ordinal Inscriptions With 48 Million Mark Hit, Signaling Longevity Despite Ongoing Debate]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748f56285c</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-celebrates-one-year-of-ordinal-inscriptions-with-48-million-mark-hit-signaling-longevity-despite-ongoing-debate/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T17:37:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Dec. 15, 2023, a significant milestone was achieved in the Bitcoin blockchain world, just a day shy of the anniversary of the first Ordinal inscription. The total count of Ordinal inscriptions has impressively hit the 48 million mark. Despite initial skepticism about their longevity, these inscriptions have not only persisted but now make up half of all BTC transactions confirmed daily.
 
Bitcoin Marks 1st Anniversary of Ordinals: 48M Milestone Achieved
 

 
2023 has seen Ordinal inscriptions gain immense traction, significantly impacting Bitcoin’s ecosystem and vying with other blockchains in the non-fungible token (NFT) space. This journey began almost a year prior, on Dec. 16, 2022, marking the creation of the first-ever Ordinal inscription on Bitcoin’s distributed ledger.
 

 
These…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI's Sam Altman Champions Worldcoin amid $50M Funding Plans: Report]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748f564267</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/openais-sam-altman-champions-worldcoin-amid-50m-funding-plans-report/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T17:36:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI's Chief Executive Officer, Sam Altman, has  
highlighted his plans for Worldcoin, a cryptocurrency venture to  
establish a worldwide identity and a financial network. This project, led by  
Tools For Humanity, has gained significant attention amid reports indicating  
its pursuit of a substantial investment of $50 million. 
According to Altman's remarks during a virtual  
Q&A hosted by FT Partners, as reported by The Business Times, identifying users in an AI-dominated world is increasingly relevant. 
Over 2.6 million people have reportedly consented  
to scan irises using Worldcoin's "orb" devices. This project offers  
digital IDs and cryptocurrency rewards in exchange for participation.
Funding Endeavors and Project Strategy
Reports suggest that Tools For Humanity actively seeks…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gary Gensler: SEC 'Taking a New Look' at Bitcoin ETF Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209964</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209964/gary-gensler-sec-taking-new-look-bitcoin-etf-applications"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T16:06:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC chair stated that the regulator is reviewing spot Bitcoin ETF applications in light of a recent court ruling.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BONK Spikes 101% Amid Solana Saga Sales Frenzy to Claim Airdrop]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209966</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209966/bonk-spikes-101-amid-solana-saga-sales-frenzy-to-claim-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T15:40:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana-based meme coin BONK has continued to soar in value and hit new all-time highs—and the Saga smartphone is an unexpected beneficiary.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SocialFi Startup Reach Aims to Improve Crypto Twitter With Anti-Bot Protocol]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209903</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209903/socialfi-reach-crypto-twitter-anti-bot-protocol-token"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T15:01:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest addition to the "point" meta seeks to address the challenges of Crypto Twitter with the support of Seedphrase, Pranksy, Gmoney, and Zeneca.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SafeMoon Files for Bankruptcy, SFM Token Crashes 50% to All-Time Low]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209951</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209951/safemoon-files-for-bankruptcy-sfm-token-crashes-50-to-all-time-low"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T10:08:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Chapter 7 bankruptcy filing comes after SafeMoon's founders were indicted by the DOJ for a "multi-million dollar international fraud scheme."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Casio Drops Virtual G-Shock Watches as Ethereum NFTs—With Exclusive Perks]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209939</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209939/casio-drops-virtual-g-shock-watches-ethereum-nfts-exclusive-perks"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T03:02:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The G-Shock watch brand debuts a pair of fantastical digital designs on Ethereum, with a variety of special benefits for holders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vatican Says AI Is the ‘Highest-Stakes Gamble of Our Future’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209925</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209925/pope-declares-ai-the-highest-stakes-gamble-of-our-future"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T00:46:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pope Francis urged global leaders to work together to adopt a binding international treaty that regulates AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grindr Dating App Adds an AI ‘Wingman’ to Help Users Find Love]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209919</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209919/grindr-dating-app-adds-an-ai-wingman-to-help-users-find-love"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T00:18:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“If you’re not first to market with something in AI, you’re going to miss out," says Grindr CEO George Arison.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Devs Got a BONK Airdrop Worth $300 Last Christmas—It's Now Worth $500,000]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209906</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209906/solana-devs-bonk-airdrop-worth-300-last-christmas-now-worth-500000"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T23:01:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers in LamportDAO received a gift of billions of BONK last year. It helped some pay rent—and others get crypto-rich (maybe).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Instagram Adds Generative AI That Swaps Image Backgrounds]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209868</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209868/instagram-adds-generative-ai-that-swaps-image-backgrounds"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T21:59:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The green screen-like Backdrop feature lets users replace their messy kitchens with lush tropical forests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Native Bitcoin Staking on Ethereum and Solana Could Soon Be a Reality]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209867</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209867/native-bitcoin-staking-ethereum-solana-soon-reality-babylon"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T21:24:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto startup Babylon says it's developed a way to stake Bitcoin on any proof-of-stake blockchain. Here's how it works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana DeFi Hacker Pleads Guilty in First-Ever Smart Contract Fraud Conviction]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209859</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209859/solana-defi-hacker-pleads-guilty-smart-contract-fraud-conviction"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T21:01:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's the "first ever conviction for such a hack,” according to the DOJ. The hacker will be sentenced in March.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Did Michael Cohen Let AI Write His Legal Briefs?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209869</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209869/did-michael-cohen-let-ai-write-his-legal-briefs"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T20:53:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cohen's attorneys must prove the existence of cases they cited as speculation swirls around potential AI-generated content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emerge 2023 Project of the Year: OpenAI ChatGPT 3.5]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209784</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209784/emerge-2023-project-of-the-year-openai-chatgpt"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T19:37:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In barely over a year, ChatGPT rocketed from obscure, largely academic roots to the embodiment of a global revolution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Kawailani Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana's BONK Becomes 69th Largest Coin as Market Cap Tops $1 Billion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209850</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209850/solanas-bonk-69th-largest-coin-market-cap-tops-1-billion"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T18:55:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BONK continues its recent boom with a 64% surge on the day, landing in the meme-friendly #69 spot on CoinGecko’s market ranking.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Farcana Raises $10 Million for NFT Esports Shooter That Pays Out Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209817</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209817/farcana-raiases-10-million-nft-esports-shooter-pays-out-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T18:36:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Exclusive: The sci-fi, team-based hero shooter Farcana is still in early development. Now, it has a fresh round of capital to tap into.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a Single Phishing Link Unleashed Chaos on Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209838</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209838/single-phishing-link-unleashed-chaos-on-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T18:14:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ledger has confirmed the attack began because “a former Ledger employee fell victim to a phishing attack.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin and Ethereum Rebound From Wallet Hack Wobble]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209814</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209814/bitcoin-ethereum-rebound-after-wallet-hack-wobble"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T17:40:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin had briefly dipped, but it and the rest of the market has bounced back.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nintendo Switch 2 Preview: Everything You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197793</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197793/nintendo-switch-2-rumors-leaks-latest-news"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T16:46:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATE: Will the Nintendo Switch 2 get Grand Theft Auto 6? Technical experts weigh in on whether the hardware can even handle GTA 6.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fetch AI, SingularityNET Team Up to Squash AI Hallucinations]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209790</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209790/fetch-ai-singularitynet-team-up-to-squash-ai-hallucinations"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The two companies aim to use decentralized technology to make AI more dependable and intelligent, reducing inaccurate or irrelevant outputs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Stop Using Dapps': Ledger Library 'Compromised' With Wallet Drainer]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209804</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209804/ledger-library-compromised-with-wallet-drainer"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T13:47:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ledger has warned users not to connect to any dapps after a malicious version of its Connect Kit was identified.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JP Morgan: Ethereum to Outperform Bitcoin in 2024, Halving ‘Priced In’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209786</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209786/jp-morgan-ethereum-to-outperform-bitcoin-in-2024-halving-priced-in"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T11:53:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bank’s 2024 crypto outlook is cautious, with Bitcoin overbought amid “excessive optimism” over a spot Bitcoin ETF approval.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Axie Infinity NFTs Can Soon Evolve Like Pokémon—Here's How]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209166</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209166/axie-infinity-nfts-can-soon-evolve-like-pokemon-heres-how"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T07:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Exclusive: You can finally power-up your Axies and give them a new look with upgraded parts, but it'll take money, materials, and time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2023 Will Be the ‘Last Year You’ll Know A Song Was Written by a Human’: Queen Guitarist]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209761</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209761/2023-will-be-the-last-year-youll-know-a-song-was-written-by-a-human-queen-guitarist"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T01:16:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Legendary guitarist and astrophysicist Brian May reflects on AI's current and future impact on the music industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI Joins Rolling Stone Publisher to Merge AI With Journalism]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209754</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209754/openai-joins-rolling-stone-publisher-to-merge-ai-with-journalism"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T00:08:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Readers get better summaries, and LLMs get more training data—could AI enhance journalism while disrupting it?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Lords of Light' NFT Game Studio Raini Reveals New Owners, RST Token on Beam]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209730</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209730/lords-light-nft-game-studio-raini-reveals-new-owners-launches-rst-token-beam"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T23:29:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Raini Studios is now part of a joint venture, and the firms have already begun development on a new unannounced combat game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Meme Coin BONK Hits Another All-Time High Ahead of Coinbase Listing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209745</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209745/solana-meme-coin-bonk-hits-another-all-time-high-ahead-of-coinbase-listing"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T23:10:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BONK bounces back, jumping 21% on the day after top exchange Coinbase said it would list the Solana token on Thursday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Social Giant Line Raises $140 Million for NFT Push, 'Brown and Friends' Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209736</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209736/social-giant-line-raises-140-million-nft-push-brown-friends-games"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T22:26:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Japanese messaging firm Line is advancing its NFT plans with a raise led by Crescendo, with Line Friends crypto games in the works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No Gas for Gamers: Ethereum Scaler Immutable zkEVM Will Let Developers Cover Fees]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=205906</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/205906/no-gas-gamers-ethereum-scaler-immutable-zkevm-developers-cover-fees"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T22:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eliminating transaction fees will make blockchain games more accessible and appealing to mainstream gamers, Immutable believes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating peaceful money & taking over your local government w/ Joseph Schiarizzi]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zb0VG27G/creating-peaceful-money-taking-over-your-local-government-w-joseph-schiarizzi</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zb0VG27G/creating-peaceful-money-taking-over-your-local-government-w-joseph-schiarizzi"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T23:23:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week our host Reza Jafery is joined by Joseph Schiarizzi, founder of OpenDollar and prolific solidity developer. 


We discuss: 
- Onchain beer
- Taking over your local government
- His Emmy and 3 patents?!?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INTERVIEW: Ember Sword CEO Says NFT Games Are More 'Transparent']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/M9OHCVpA/interview-ember-sword-ceo-says-nft-games-are-more-transparent</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/M9OHCVpA/interview-ember-sword-ceo-says-nft-games-are-more-transparent"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T21:58:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ember Sword CEO Mark Laursen shares why some big game studios "irk" him—and why he got into game development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Director Jordan Bayne on the State of Film3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZLoEDkL9/director-jordan-bayne-on-the-state-of-film3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZLoEDkL9/director-jordan-bayne-on-the-state-of-film3"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T00:11:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the 2023 Film3 Summit, Jordan Bayne—director and founder of The Squad—spoke with Decrypt's Sander Lutz about how the Film3 world has progressed over the last year and what decentralized technologies can offer to creators that want to buck the Hollywood system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Questions With SCENE: Phil Mohun]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TwOjXfOR/5-questions-with-scene-phil-mohun</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TwOjXfOR/5-questions-with-scene-phil-mohun"/>
        <updated>2023-12-01T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bright Moments co-founder Phil Mohun joins 5 Questions With SCENE to recount some favorite moments from the road, including negotiating with Patagonian gauchos, falling in love with Tokyo, and gaining a newfound appreciation for shrooms chocolate bars.

Shot and edited by Vincent Roazzi Jr.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are NFTs Ever Coming Back?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qLmFpNKE/are-nfts-ever-coming-back</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qLmFpNKE/are-nfts-ever-coming-back"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T18:38:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this weeks episode we sit down with Cashtro from Arcade.xyz to discuss NFTs, shitcoins, what collections have held onto their floor prices, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Summit: Will Web3 Gaming Ever be Mainstream?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OvVWhGbW/web-summit-will-web3-gaming-ever-be-mainstream</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OvVWhGbW/web-summit-will-web3-gaming-ever-be-mainstream"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T19:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animoca Brands CEO Robby Yung, EndeavorXR CEO Amy Peck and Gamee co-founder CEO Bozena Rezab joined Decrypt's Stephen Graves on stage at Web Summit to talk about the future of Web3 gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Allie Eve Knox on Spankchain and the life of a Crypto Financial Dominatrix]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/16rVeg6o/allie-eve-knox-on-spankchain-and-the-life-of-a-crypto-financial-dominatrix</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/16rVeg6o/allie-eve-knox-on-spankchain-and-the-life-of-a-crypto-financial-dominatrix"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T21:20:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the first IRL episode of This Time Will Be Different!

In this week's episode, our host, Reza Jafery, is joined by Allie Eve Knox, the Spankchain Chief of Staff and FinDomme. 

They discuss
- How to sell feet pics
- If crypto is really as permissionless as it seems
- the intersections between crypto and sex work]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Questions With SCENE: Jeff Davis]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PChJu1R8/5-questions-with-scene-jeff-davis</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PChJu1R8/5-questions-with-scene-jeff-davis"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artist Jeff Davis joins 5 Questions with SCENE to answer burning questions about his artistic practice, the path that brought him to Art Blocks, and his quietly sophisticated DJ abilities.

Video shot and edited by Vincent Roazzi Jr.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Heatbit Founder Alex Busarov on the Bitcoin Miner That Heats Your Home]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DJuHqcGT/heatbit-founder-alex-busarov-on-the-bitcoin-miner-that-heats-your-home</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DJuHqcGT/heatbit-founder-alex-busarov-on-the-bitcoin-miner-that-heats-your-home"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T18:12:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt joined Heatbit founder Alex Busarov at Web Summit for a walkthrough of the firm's flagship product, a Bitcoin miner that acts as a domestic space heater—aimed at the casual user.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nym CEO Harry Halpin on Privacy, Decentralized VPNs and Tornado Cash]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/aLTtY2aq/nym-ceo-harry-halpin-on-privacy-decentralized-vpns-and-tornado-cash</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/aLTtY2aq/nym-ceo-harry-halpin-on-privacy-decentralized-vpns-and-tornado-cash"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T18:08:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The founder of privacy-preserving mixnet Nym sat down with Decrypt at Web Summit to talk about its new decentralized VPN, the Web3 privacy landscape and why "devs should be defended" in the wake of the Tornado Cash crackdown.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>