<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-09-13T04:17:34.961Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-09-13T04:17:34.961Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s Path to Money: Menger’s Theory and the Debate on Medium of Exchange vs. Store of Value]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7543bf6e92</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoins-path-to-money-mengers-theory-and-the-debate-on-medium-of-exchange-vs-store-of-value/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T04:08:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past ten years, fervent supporters of digital currency have engaged in intense debates: Is bitcoin (BTC) designed as peer-to-peer electronic cash as illustrated in Satoshi’s groundbreaking white paper, or does it serve as a digital store of value, similar to gold? Additionally, a central question emerges regarding the primary role of money: should its capacity as a medium of exchange take precedence over its value preservation attributes? The following Learning and Insights explainer delves into the Austrian school of economics, shining a spotlight on Carl Menger’s “On the Origins of Money.”
 
From Spontaneous Social Institution to Currency: Menger’s Insight Into Money’s Evolution
 
Rather than debating whether bitcoin (BTC) should function as a medium of exchange (MoE) or a store…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CBDC Resistance: Republican Bill Takes Aim At Federal Reserve’s Digital Dollar Plans]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7543b91e7c</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/cbdc-resistance-bill-takes-federal-reserves-plans/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T03:50:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to a recent Fox Business report, in a significant move to counter the growing momentum behind Central Bank digital currency (CBDC), House Majority Whip Tom Emmer is set to reintroduce the Central Bank Digital Currency Anti-Surveillance State Act. 
 
The Republican-backed bill aims to thwart the Federal Reserve (Fed) and its member banks from issuing a digital version of the US dollar and leveraging it for monetary policy implementation. 
 
Clash Over CBDC Issuance Sparks Political Showdown
 
The global interest in the digital form of a country’s fiat currency has surged over the past few years, with as many as 130 countries, accounting for 98% of the global economy, exploring the possibility of digitalizing their currencies. 
 
 
11 nations, including China, have already fully im…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Chair Gary Gensler Is Still Reviewing 'Multiple Filings' Around Bitcoin ETF — Another $1.4T Asset Giant Joins The Race]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18899091/SEC-Chair-Gary-Gensler-Is-Still-Reviewing-Multiple-Filings-Around-Bitcoin-ETF-Another-14T-Asset-Giant-Joins-The-Race</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18899091/SEC-Chair-Gary-Gensler-Is-Still-Reviewing-Multiple-Filings-Around-Bitcoin-ETF-Another-14T-Asset-Giant-Joins-The-Race"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T03:42:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Chair Gary Gensler on Wednesday confirmed that the agency is still evaluating a court’s decision regarding Grayscale Investments’ pursuit of a spot Bitcoin (CRYPTO: BTC) exchange-traded fund (ETF). read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking Bitcoin & Ethereum ETF News!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18898981/Breaking-Bitcoin-Ethereum-ETF-News</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18898981/Breaking-Bitcoin-Ethereum-ETF-News"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T03:35:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Bitcoin and Ethereum ETF News, and the latest on Solana. 🔥 GET MY FREE NEWSLETTER 👉 https://cryptolark.co/WEALTHMASTERY💸 BYBIT $30,030 BONUS & FEE DISCOUNT 👉 https://cryptolark.co/BYBIT💡💡💡 ESSENTIAL CRYPTO KNOWLEDGE 💡💡💡🔥 GET MY FREE NEWSLETTER 👉 https://cryptolark.co/WEALTHMASTERY💎 BITCOIN...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinDesk Indices Expands Into Asia-Pacific Through Deal With Major Exchange Operator ICE]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7543bbbb42</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/09/13/coindesk-indices-expands-into-apac-region-in-deal-with-ice-futures-singapore/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T03:23:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ICE Futures Singapore's bitcoin futures contracts will now be known as CoinDesk Bitcoin Futures contracts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen  Alpher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Assets Slump Ahead Of US Inflation Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18899062/Crypto-Assets-Slump-Ahead-Of-US-Inflation-Report</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18899062/Crypto-Assets-Slump-Ahead-Of-US-Inflation-Report"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T03:23:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US Court Will Deliver Verdict On FTX’s Planned Asset Sales On Wednesday]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zero-knowledge technology is ready. Why isn’t it more widely used?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18899045/Zero-knowledge-technology-is-ready-Why-isnt-it-more-widely-used</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18899045/Zero-knowledge-technology-is-ready-Why-isnt-it-more-widely-used"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T03:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ZK is a complex but game-changing cryptographic technique for blockchain scalability and privacy. Here's how the industry can make it more accessible.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CBDC Resistance: Republican Bill Takes Aim At Federal Reserve’s Digital Dollar Plans]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18899042/CBDC-Resistance-Republican-Bill-Takes-Aim-At-Federal-Reserves-Digital-Dollar-Plans</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18899042/CBDC-Resistance-Republican-Bill-Takes-Aim-At-Federal-Reserves-Digital-Dollar-Plans"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T03:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to a recent Fox Business report, in a significant move to counter the growing momentum behind Central Bank digital currency (CBDC), House Majority Whip Tom Emmer is set to reintroduce the Central Bank Digital Currency Anti-Surveillance State Act. The Republican-backed bill aims to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OneCoin Co-Founder Receives 20-Year Sentence and $300M Fine]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18899059/OneCoin-Co-Founder-Receives-20-Year-Sentence-and-300M-Fine</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18899059/OneCoin-Co-Founder-Receives-20-Year-Sentence-and-300M-Fine"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T02:59:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On September 12, a judge sentenced a key co-founder of OneCoin to 20 years in prison for masterminding a massive cryptocurrency scam that defrauded millions of investors out of over $4 billion worldwide. Karl Sebastian Greenwood marketed OneCoin as a legitimate Bitcoin alternative. However, the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance US CEO Brian Shroder Steps Down Amid Layoffs: Bloomberg]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156150</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156150/binance-us-ceo-brian-shroder-steps-down-amid-layoffs-bloomberg"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T02:52:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Norman Reed, Chief Legal Officer of Binance US, will take the helm after the abrupt executive departure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Chair Gensler’s Testimony Sparks Crypto Community Speculation]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7543a6e2a0</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/sec-chair-gensler-crypto-community-speculation/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T02:49:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In his recent testimony before the United States Senate on Banking, Housing, and Urban Affairs, SEC Chair Gary Gensler made statements that have ignited speculation within the crypto community. 
 
While the SEC has been known for its tough stance on the crypto industry, Gensler’s words have sparked hope among supporters of cryptocurrencies, especially regarding the regulation of crypto assets and the potential approval of Bitcoin Spot exchange-traded funds (ETFs).
 
Gensler’s Remarks On Crypto Raise Questions And Hope
 
SEC Chair Gensler emphasized the need to prioritize investor protection and ensure compliance with securities laws within the crypto asset securities markets. Gensler highlighted that the legal definition of a security, established in the 1930s, includes the term “investmen…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum, Dogecoin Spike After Franklin Templeton Files for BTC Spot ETF: Analyst Say If King Crypto Holds This Level, It Could Reach $30K Soon]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18899028/Bitcoin-Ethereum-Dogecoin-Spike-After-Franklin-Templeton-Files-for-BTC-Spot-ETF-Analyst-Say-If-King-Crypto-Holds-This-Level-It-Could-Reach-30K-Soon</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18899028/Bitcoin-Ethereum-Dogecoin-Spike-After-Franklin-Templeton-Files-for-BTC-Spot-ETF-Analyst-Say-If-King-Crypto-Holds-This-Level-It-Could-Reach-30K-Soon"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T02:35:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Major cryptocurrencies experienced a significant surge on Tuesday evening, following a rapid decline and subsequent rebound in their prices. However, this volatile market movement has resulted in substantial losses for traders, with Coinglass data revealing liquidation losses amounting to a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$BTC: BlackRock’s Bitcoin ETF Could Trigger $150 Billion Crypto Boom, Says Bloomberg Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18899027/BTC-BlackRocks-Bitcoin-ETF-Could-Trigger-150-Billion-Crypto-Boom-Says-Bloomberg-Analyst</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18899027/BTC-BlackRocks-Bitcoin-ETF-Could-Trigger-150-Billion-Crypto-Boom-Says-Bloomberg-Analyst"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T02:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A senior exchange-traded fund (ETF) analyst from Bloomberg has suggested that a potential $150 billion influx of capital into the Bitcoin ($BTC) market could occur over the next couple of year, contingent on the green light for BlackRock’s proposed spot Bitcoin ETF. During a recent interview...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terra Classic turns bullish: Will its gains sustain?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18899018/Terra-Classic-turns-bullish-Will-its-gains-sustain</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18899018/Terra-Classic-turns-bullish-Will-its-gains-sustain"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T02:30:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LUNC has passed the proposal for its new update that will be pushed when total blocks reach 14,514,000. Buyers respond favorably, pushing its price upwards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[50 US Lawmakers Reintroduce ‘CBDC Anti-Surveillance State Act’ to Protect ‘the American Way of Life’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7543a2c4d0</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/50-us-lawmakers-reintroduce-cbdc-anti-surveillance-state-act-to-protect-the-american-way-of-life/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T02:08:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fifty U.S. lawmakers have reintroduced the CBDC Anti-Surveillance State Act to prohibit the Federal Reserve from issuing a retail central bank digital currency “while protecting innovation and any future development of true digital cash.” Congressman Tom Emmer stressed: “President Biden is willing to compromise the American people’s right to financial privacy for a surveillance-style CBDC. I don’t believe in compromising Americans’ rights.”
 
CBDC Anti-Surveillance State Act Updated, Reintroduced
 
U.S. Congressman Tom Emmer (R-MN) announced Tuesday that he and 49 other lawmakers have reintroduced the CBDC Anti-Surveillance State Act “to halt the efforts of unelected bureaucrats in Washington, D.C. from issuing a central bank digital currency (CBDC) that dismantles Americans’ right to fina…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[zkSync Airdrop Farmer Deploys 21,877 Wallets]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18898991/zkSync-Airdrop-Farmer-Deploys-21877-Wallets</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18898991/zkSync-Airdrop-Farmer-Deploys-21877-Wallets"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T02:01:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Determined zkSync Era Airdrop Opportunist Launched Private DEX and Token To Trade Between Wallets]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Chair Gensler’s Testimony Sparks Crypto Community Speculation]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18898988/SEC-Chair-Genslers-Testimony-Sparks-Crypto-Community-Speculation</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18898988/SEC-Chair-Genslers-Testimony-Sparks-Crypto-Community-Speculation"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T02:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In his recent testimony before the United States Senate on Banking, Housing, and Urban Affairs, SEC Chair Gary Gensler made statements that have ignited speculation within the crypto community. While the SEC has been known for its tough stance on the crypto industry, Gensler’s words have sparked...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Curve (CRV) Trading Volume Plunge 97% In 2 Months]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18898992/Curve-CRV-Trading-Volume-Plunge-97-In-2-Months</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18898992/Curve-CRV-Trading-Volume-Plunge-97-In-2-Months"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T02:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MetaMask Snaps Open Beta Launches, Developers To Deploy Features, Functionalities]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7543ac8bac</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/metamask-snaps-open-beta-launches/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T01:48:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MetaMask, the non-custodial wallet with more than 21 million monthly active users, is launching the Snaps feature in Open Beta. In a statement on September 12, MetaMask said the release marks the first steps of creating a “fully permissionless ecosystem. ” 
 
MetaMask Releases Snaps To Decentralize Development
 
The wallet developer also revealed that they were building from the idea that developers could anchor on the wallet to create what the provider described as the “hardest problems on Web3.” 
 
MetaMask, through Snaps, invites the developer community to release independent features and functionalities, effectively expanding its ecosystem since the wallet has become modular. 
 
This implies that over 21 million users can create and launch their features or functions on MetaMask withou…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dalmas Ngetich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[White House Signs 8 More Companies to Safe AI Pledge]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156145</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156145/white-house-signs-8-more-companies-to-its-safe-ai-pledge"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T01:35:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NVIDIA, IBM, and Adobe are among the eight companies promising to focus on safety, security, and trust in advancing artificial intelligence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[White House Signs 8 More Companies to Safe AI Pledge]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18898969/White-House-Signs-8-More-Companies-to-Safe-AI-Pledge</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18898969/White-House-Signs-8-More-Companies-to-Safe-AI-Pledge"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T01:35:23.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Ethereum’s 6-month low may not be the end]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18898968/Why-Ethereums-6-month-low-may-not-be-the-end</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18898968/Why-Ethereums-6-month-low-may-not-be-the-end"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T01:30:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The drop in Ethereum's MCA affirms the position that a big fall could be close. But relief could come to ETH after the downtrend.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized exchanges a magnet for crypto wash traders: Solidus Labs]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18898938/Decentralized-exchanges-a-magnet-for-crypto-wash-traders-Solidus-Labs</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18898938/Decentralized-exchanges-a-magnet-for-crypto-wash-traders-Solidus-Labs"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T01:07:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Token deployers and liquidity providers wash-traded over $2 billion worth of crypto on Ethereum-based DEXs since 2020, a Solidus Labs report claims.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MetaMask Snaps Open Beta Launches, Developers To Deploy Features, Functionalities]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18898936/MetaMask-Snaps-Open-Beta-Launches-Developers-To-Deploy-Features-Functionalities</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18898936/MetaMask-Snaps-Open-Beta-Launches-Developers-To-Deploy-Features-Functionalities"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T01:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mark Moss: Blackrock will NOT be the catalyst to bitcoin mass adoption #bitcoin #crypto #shorts]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18898942/Mark-Moss-Blackrock-will-NOT-be-the-catalyst-to-bitcoin-mass-adoption-bitcoin-crypto-shorts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18898942/Mark-Moss-Blackrock-will-NOT-be-the-catalyst-to-bitcoin-mass-adoption-bitcoin-crypto-shorts"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T01:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blackrock or not, honey Badger don’t care! Buy bitcoin and keep it in self custody.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinDesk Indices Expands Into Asia-Pacific Through Deal With Major Exchange Operator ICE]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18898937/CoinDesk-Indices-Expands-Into-Asia-Pacific-Through-Deal-With-Major-Exchange-Operator-ICE</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18898937/CoinDesk-Indices-Expands-Into-Asia-Pacific-Through-Deal-With-Major-Exchange-Operator-ICE"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T01:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ICE Futures Singapore's bitcoin futures contracts will now be known as CoinDesk Bitcoin Futures contracts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[83.7% Of Bitcoin Short-Term Holders Are Now In Loss: Glassnode]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7543a9f9b2</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/83-7-bitcoin-short-term-holders-now-loss-glassnode/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T00:48:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data from Glassnode suggests that 83.7% of the Bitcoin short-term holder supply is currently being held at an unrealized loss.
 
Bitcoin Short-Term Holder Supply Has Plummeted Into Losses
 
According to the latest weekly report from Glassnode, only 16.3% of the short-term holder supply is in profit right now. The relevant indicator here is the “percent supply in profit,” which measures the percentage of the total circulating Bitcoin supply carrying some gains.
 
This metric works by going through the on-chain history of each coin in circulation to see what price it was last moved/transferred at. If this previous selling price was less than the current spot price, then that particular coin currently carries a profit.
 
The counterpart indicator to the supply in profit is the “suppl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hououin Kyouma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ether bounce back; altcoins recover after FTX panic]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18898927/Bitcoin-Ether-bounce-back-altcoins-recover-after-FTX-panic</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18898927/Bitcoin-Ether-bounce-back-altcoins-recover-after-FTX-panic"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T00:47:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin rose on Wednesday morning in Asia to near US$26,000. Ether also bounced back to near US$1,600. All other top 10 non-stablecoin tokens logged gains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance.US CEO Brian Shroder Reportedly Departs, Along With 100 Jobs Axed]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18898924/BinanceUS-CEO-Brian-Shroder-Reportedly-Departs-Along-With-100-Jobs-Axed</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18898924/BinanceUS-CEO-Brian-Shroder-Reportedly-Departs-Along-With-100-Jobs-Axed"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T00:47:01.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance.US CEO Has Left, Crypto Exchange Cuts 1/3 of Workforce]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7543940b49</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/09/13/binanceus-ceo-has-left-crypto-exchange-cuts-13-of-workforce/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T00:25:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Company says its actions give it "seven years of financial runway."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Baker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zodia Custody Looks to Drive Institutional Access to Polkadot Ecosystem]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754394991e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/09/12/zodia-custody-looks-to-drive-institutional-access-to-polkadot-ecosystem/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T00:19:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company plans to provide custody for the Polkadot ecosystem, offering digital asset storage services for financial institutions]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried Remains Stuck in Jail]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7543949912</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/09/12/sam-bankman-fried-remains-stuck-in-jail/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T00:19:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried lost a bid to be released from jail ahead of his trial next month. All hope isn’t lost for him, but time is running out for the FTX founder.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rising Interest Rates Could Actually Pump Bitcoin: Arthur Hayes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156139</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156139/rising-interest-rates-could-actually-pump-bitcoin-arthur-hayes"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T00:19:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s price may rise if central banks worldwide continue tightening monetary policies, according to the BitMEX co-founder.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JPMorgan CEO Jamie Dimon Warns of Recession — Says ‘Huge Mistake’ to Think US Economy Will Boom for Years]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7543957515</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/jpmorgan-ceo-jamie-dimon-warns-of-recession-says-huge-mistake-to-think-us-economy-will-boom-for-years/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T00:10:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jamie Dimon, chairman and CEO of JPMorgan Chase, has warned that it is “a huge mistake” to think that the U.S. economy will boom “for years” given that there are so many risks out there. The executive stressed: “I just think people make a mistake to look at real-time numbers and not look at the future. And the future has quantitative tightening. We’ve been spending money like drunken sailors around the world.”
 
Jamie Dimon’s Economic Warning
 
JPMorgan Chase CEO Jamie Dimon warned about where the U.S. economy is headed at the Barclays 21st Annual Global Financial Services Conference in New York on Monday.
 
The executive cautioned: “I just think people make a mistake to look at real-time numbers and not look at the future. And the future has quantitative tightening. We’ve been spending money like drunken sailors around the world, this war in Ukraine is still going on.” Dimon emphasized:
 

To say the consumer is strong today, meaning you are going to have a booming environment for years, is a huge mistake.
 
“If and when you have a recession, which you’re eventually going to have, you’ll have a normal credit cycle, which I think is quite predictable. In a normal credit cycle, something always does worse than normal,” he described.
 
The JPMorgan boss opined: “There’s a lot of fiscal stimulus taking place out there. And the large one from Covid is still running through. The largest QE is still running through. So we’re still living on that, and that’s really strong. And of course, that drives everything, including business results.”
 
 
Dimon further explained that “businesses feel pretty good because they look at their current results” and see that “they’re not so bad.” However, he cautioned:
 

But those things change. And we don’t know what the full effect of all these things are going to be 12 or 18 months from now.
 
Do you agree with JPMorgan Chase CEO Jamie Dimon? Let us know in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Massive Whale Selling Pushes ARB Price To All-Time Low, Primed For Reversal?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7543978667</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/arb-price-reversal/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T23:48:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since its launch earlier this year, the price of Arbitrum (ARB) has struggled tremendously. The altcoin launched into a budding bear market and as the bears have assumed more control, the ARB token price has dumped even further. This constant decline in price has led to high volumes of panic-selling, and it seems the whales have joined the bandwagon as well.
 
Whales Sell Dump ARB Despite Losses
 
As ARB’s price has continued on a downward trajectory, whales have been selling their holdings into the blood. A report from on-chain tracker Lookonchain shows that some of the largest whales have been selling millions of ARB despite losing millions of dollars in the process.
 
 
Lookonchain first flagged a transaction from Wintermute Trading after it sent 4.35 million tokens worth $3.36 million …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Best Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple iPhone 15 Pro Will Have Ray Tracing, Support Ubisoft and Capcom Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156100</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156100/apple-iphone-15-pro-gaming-ray-tracing-ubisoft-capcom"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T23:45:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple calls the forthcoming iPhone 15 Pro “a monster win for gaming.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Celsius CEO Challenges FTC: Seeks Dismissal Of Lawsuit, Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75439da9fc</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ex-celsius-ceo-challenges-ftc-dismissal-of-lawsuit/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T22:47:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent development surrounding the high-profile Federal Trade Commission (FTC) case against the crypto platform Celsius, former CEO Alex Mashinsky requested that a New York district court dismiss the charges against him.
 
The core of his argument rests on the timeline of his resignation from the firm and the subsequent charges by the FTC.
 
 
Why Mashinsky Seeks Dismissal
 
In a recent court filing, Mashinsky’s legal team argued that the FTC’s case against their client should be dismissed. The legal defense bases its argument on the assertion that the regulatory body cannot “substantiate a claim that Mashinsky ‘is violating’ or is ‘about to violate’ the law.” 
 
This is primarily because he relinquished his position as the CEO of Celsius on September 27, 2023. Such nuances in legal p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can El Salvador Duplicate Singapore's Road To Success?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75439ece6b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/el-salvador-bitcoin-news/can-el-salvador-duplicate-singapores-road-to-success"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T22:36:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Few stories in global development are as compelling as that of Singapore, a small city-state that moved "From Third World to First" within just a few decades. The strategic vision of its founding father, Lee Kuan Yew, combined with the country's commitment to a robust business environment, education, and stringent anti-corruption measures, all contributed to this remarkable transition.
El Salvador, a country currently grappling with significant political and economic changes, is arguably on a parallel course. Its recent political developments, particularly the adoption of Bitcoin as legal tender under President Nayib Bukele, is a daring move that could either be a game-changer or an uncalculated risk. This article presents a comparative analysis of the political transitions in Singapore an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ed Juline</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bull Bitcoin Now Allows Costa Ricans To Buy BTC With Country's Primary Payment System]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75439ece66</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/bull-bitcoin-now-allows-costa-ricans-to-buy-btc-with-countrys-primary-payment-system"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T22:36:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin only exchange Bull Bitcoin, has announced that it has expanded its services to enable Costa Ricans and foreigners to buy and sell Bitcoin using SINPE Movil, the country's primary fiat payment system, in partnership with circular BTC economy project Bitcoin Jungle, according to a press release sent to Bitcoin Magazine. This collaboration not only opens up new opportunities for those looking to utilize Bitcoin in the country but also simplifies the process of converting Costa Rican colones to BTC and vice versa.
Bull Bitcoin is now the first and only Bitcoin exchange in Costa Rica to facilitate seamless transactions using SINPE Movil, the payment network widely embraced by over an estimated 90% of Costa Rican consumers. This development represents a significant milestone, as it grant…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nik Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Firms Should Adopt KYC Policies to Combat Misuse, Microsoft Exec Suggests]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156118</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156118/ai-companies-kyc-policies-combat-ai-abuse-microsoft-president"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T22:34:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft President Brad Smith suggests banking-style identity verification could stem abuse and misinformation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fortress CEO Clears the Air on Security Breach and Stolen Funds]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156117</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156117/fortress-ceo-clears-the-air-on-security-breach-and-stolen-funds"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T22:24:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scott Purcell admits that “shit happened”—but says Fortress and Ripple handled things well.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Champions Arena Beginner's Guide: How to Start Playing the NFT Fantasy Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155847</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/champions-arena-beginners-guide-how-start-playing-nft-fantasy-game"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T22:22:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking to dive into a mobile RPG with optional NFTs? Here's how to get started in Gala Games' Champions Arena.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lightspark CEO David Marcus Profiles Bitcoin as Global Payment Network]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75439a0160</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/lightspark-ceo-david-marcus-profiles-bitcoin-as-global-payment-network/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T22:08:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Marcus, CEO of Lightspark and co-creator of Diem, Meta’s failed cryptocurrency project, explained his intentions of turning Bitcoin into a global payments network. Marcus explained that there was no universal protocol for sending value over the internet and that we were still in the “fax era” of global payments.
Lightspark CEO David Marcus Wants to Get Payments out of the ‘Fax Era’
David Marcus, CEO of Lightspark and co-creator of the defunct Diem cryptocurrency project, has talked about how Bitcoin might become a global payments network. In an interview on CNBC’s Squawk Box, Marcus detailed the need for a universal platform to allow money transfers to be as easy as text or video communication using today’s messaging apps.
When consulted about the need for a global payment system, Ma…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sony Reveals Blockchain Plans to 'Connect Souls Across Generations']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156082</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156082/sony-reveals-blockchain-plans-connect-souls-across-generations"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T22:01:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sony subsidiary Sony Network Communications has established a joint venture with Startale Labs, makers of the Astar blockchain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fear of FTX-Spurred Crypto Crash Is Overblown, Analysts Say]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75439ae3af</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/09/12/fear-of-ftx-spurred-crypto-crash-is-overblown-analysts-say/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T22:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto markets slumped Monday, possibly in part due to fears of FTX unloading its $3.4 billion crypto assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Deepfakes Pose ‘Real Risk’ to Markets, Says SEC Chair Gary Gensler]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156074</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156074/ai-deepfakes-pose-real-risk-to-markets-says-sec-chair-gary-gensler"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T21:48:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wall Street’s top regulator is again warning about the dangers of AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Experiences $300 Million Monthly Crypto Fund Outflows – What’s Going On?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7543842d89</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-sustains-300m-crypto-fund-outflows/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T21:47:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum, the world’s second-largest cryptocurrency, is facing a challenging year as institutional investors have been rapidly shedding their holdings. In a surprising turn of events, ETH has experienced significant outflows from institutional investors in 2023, with sales reaching over $108 million year-to-date. 
 
This staggering figure marks Ethereum as the most sold digital asset among large entities, raising questions about its future performance and investor sentiment.
 
According to data from leading digital asset management firm CoinShares, digital asset investment products witnessed outflows of $59.3 million in the past week alone. This adds to a troubling trend, with nearly $300 million in total outflows over the last four weeks. 
 
 
ETH, in particular, has fallen out of favor w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Judge Denies Sam Bankman-Fried's Bid for Release From Jail Ahead of Trial]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7543866388</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/09/12/us-judge-denies-sam-bankman-frieds-bid-for-release-from-jail-ahead-of-trial/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T21:27:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A federal judge refused Sam Bankman-Fried's bid to be released from jail ahead of trial on Tuesday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are AI Models Approaching Consciousness? New Research Reignites Debate]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156093</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156093/are-ai-models-approaching-consciousness-new-research-reignites-debate"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T21:17:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With "sophisticated out-of-context reasoning," AI can tell humans what they want to hear—before changing course.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoin Market Continues To Drain Capital, But USDT Expands]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7543830c18</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/stablecoin-market-drain-capital-but-usdt-expands/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T20:47:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data shows the stablecoin sector as a whole has continued to observe net outflows recently, but Tether (USDT) has only expanded further.
 
USDT’s Dominance Among The Stablecoins Has Now Grown To Nearly 70%
 
In its latest weekly report, the on-chain analytics firm Glassnode has looked into the capital flows into and out of the cryptocurrency market to see how the sector has been doing recently.
 
To check for these capital flows, the firm has considered the change in the valuations of three asset classes, Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH), and stablecoins, since these three make up most of the digital asset sector.
 
Now, here is a chart that displays the data for these netflows over the last few years:
 

 
 
As shown in the above graph, the stablecoin netflows have been negative since April …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hououin Kyouma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Bitboy' Ben Armstrong Files Suit Against Former Hit Network Colleagues]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156083</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156083/bitboy-ben-armstrong-sues-hit-network-employees"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T20:44:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto influencer has sued those who ousted him from his media brand and its parent company.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[House Republicans Reintroduce Bill to Outlaw Digital Dollar CBDC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156088</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156088/house-republicans-reintroduce-bill-outlaw-digital-dollar-cbdc"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T20:23:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduced by House Majority Whip Tom Emmer, the updated anti-CBDC bill includes new provisions not in the original version from February.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Crypties Returns for 2023 to Celebrate Crypto's Top Projects and Creators]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155828</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155828/crypties-returns-2023-celebrate-cryptos-top-projects-creators"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T18:11:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The premier crypto industry awards ceremony is back—and token holders get to vote on who wins The Crypties.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LACMA's Latest NFT Experiment Brings Fresh Eyes to Paul Klee's Art]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155981</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155981/lacmas-latest-nft-experiment-brings-fresh-eyes-to-paul-klees-art"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T17:10:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new generative art collection by William Mapan is the latest in a LACMA series that invites digital artists to engage with classic works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gensler Slams Crypto Markets as Lawmakers Raise Questions About Bitcoin ETF]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156071</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156071/gensler-slams-crypto-markets-lawmakers-raise-questions-bitcoin-etf"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T17:03:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Chair Gary Gensler was asked Tuesday by the Senate Banking Committee what he needs to see in a filing to approve a spot Bitcoin ETF.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Rodgers Injury Sends DraftKings NFTs Soaring for Backup QB]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156055</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156055/aaron-rodgers-injury-sends-draftkings-nfts-soaring-backup-qb"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T16:44:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NFTs associated with the Jets' backup QB surged on Monday after Aaron Rodgers fell to a season-ending injury.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Franklin Templeton Latest Wall Street Giant to File for Bitcoin ETF]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156054</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156054/franklin-templeton-latest-wall-street-giant-file-bitcoin-etf"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T15:10:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Franklin Templeton is the latest high-profile fund manager hoping to get a spot Bitcoin ETF approved by the SEC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Support Comes to MetaMask With Solflare Integration]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156015</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156015/solana-support-comes-to-metamask-with-solflare-integration"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After years of incompatibility, a new bridge allows Solana portfolios to be managed directly from the popular Web3 wallet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Connor Sephton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimism Flips Arbitrum Market Cap Amid Crypto Market Downturn]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156018</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156018/optimism-flips-arbitrum-market-cap-amid-crypto-market-downturn"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T13:25:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The market caps of two leading Ethereum layer-2 tokens flipped during Monday’s negative crypto price action.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diesel Offers Access to Milan Fashion Week Show With Latest NFT Drop]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156017</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156017/diesel-offers-access-milan-fashion-week-show-latest-nft-drop"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T13:07:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Diesel x Public Pressure drop on Polkadot and Polygon offers various perks, including a ticket to the fashion brand's next runway.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephanie Hirschmiller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unicorn Avatar Startup Genies Reveals $500K Digital Fashion Fund]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155948</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155948/unicorn-avatar-startup-genies-reveals-500k-digital-fashion-fund"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Genies will give digital fashion creators a chance to earn cash while potentially co-creating with artists like Khalid and Banks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephanie Hirschmiller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Flatcoins 'New Thing On the Horizon': Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155775</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155775/flatcoins-new-thing-on-the-horizon-coinbase-ceo-brian-armstrong"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T11:31:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Flatcoins are a type of stablecoin designed to move in line with inflation, instead of being pegged to a currency or asset.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Hussey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celsius Boss Mashinsky Seeks to Have FTC Case Dropped]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156010</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156010/former-celsius-boss-mashinsky-seeks-to-have-ftc-case-dropped"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T10:45:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alex Mashinsky’s lawyers argue that the FTC case against the former CEO of the Celsius Network should be dismissed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PayPal Launches Crypto to USD Off-Ramps]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156008</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156008/paypal-launches-crypto-to-usd-off-ramps"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T10:15:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The launch of the new feature follows PayPal's introduction last month of a crypto on-ramp service through MetaMask and Ledger.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin: SIM Swap Attack Behind $700,000 Twitter Hack]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156000</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156000/vitalik-buterin-sim-swap-attack-behind-700000-twitter-hack"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T09:21:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ethereum co-founder’s account was hacked and used to promote a fake NFT giveaway that stole $691,000 from his followers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Hussey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[People Won't Use Bitcoin To Buy Things, Says PayPal Co-Founder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155961</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155961/bitcoin-payments-david-marcus-lightning-network"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T00:32:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Marcus says Bitcoin's lightning network will be a universal money protocol for transacting multiple currencies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Launches $20 Million Fund to Support Responsible AI Development]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155970</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155970/responsible-ai-development-google-digital-futures-project-fund-20-million"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T00:20:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Digital Futures Project aims to include diverse perspectives in AI development, tackling bias, fairness, and workforce impact.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI's Thirst for Power May Be Draining Water Supplies]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155965</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155965/artificial-intelligence-water-use-data-centers"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T23:23:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin mining isn't the only environmental scourge—time to rage against AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Is Losing Favor Among Institutional Investors: CoinShares]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155964</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155964/ethereum-is-losing-favor-among-institutional-investors-coinshares"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T22:59:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With $108 million worth of selling in 2023, it is the “least loved digital asset.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gensler Decries ‘Wide-Ranging Noncompliance’ In Crypto Ahead of Oversight Testimony]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155967</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155967/gensler-cites-wide-ranging-noncompliance-ahead-of-oversight-testimony"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T22:45:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite bipartisan criticism for his agency’s approach to crypto, SEC Chair Gary Gensler is doubling down.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitfinex and Tether CTO Paolo Ardoino to Testify in Market Manipulation Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155935</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155935/bitfinex-tether-cto-paolo-ardoino-market-manipulation-lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T21:26:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ardoino will be deposed this week after the court denied his counsel’s request for more time to prepare.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Drops to 3-Month Low While Ethereum Takes Harder Hit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155931</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155931/ethereum-bitcoin-altcoin-values-drop-as-ftx-pursues-crypto-liquidation"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T21:06:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price slump comes as bankrupt crypto exchange FTX looks to liquidate its crypto holdings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla Up 10% on Prediction Its AI Chips Will Outperform Nvidia's]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155924</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155924/tesla-up-10-on-prediction-its-ai-chips-will-outperform-nvidias"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T20:46:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla's new supercomputing system could position it as a strong rival to NVIDIA, according to Morgan Stanley.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Is Racist, Experts Say. Here's Why]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155929</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155929/ai-racist-experts-say-heres-why"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T20:33:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI has the ability to be racist if left unchecked, and it could mean terrible things for our future, according to AI builders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hologram Runway Wows Crowds at Amsterdam Fashion Week]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155851</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155851/hologram-runway-wows-crowds-at-amsterdam-fashion-week"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T19:55:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Future Front Row seeks to chart an immersion-first path forward for the digital fashion industry after packing the house in Amsterdam.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pahdo Labs Raises $15M to Let Players Make Anime Games With AI Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155895</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155895/pahdo-labs-raises-15-million-players-make-anime-games-ai-tools"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T19:23:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The studio behind anime game Halcyon Zero will launch generative AI tools for content creation after raising funding led by Andreessen Horowitz.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Is Building AI Data Centers to Power ChatGPT Competitor: WSJ]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155899</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155899/meta-is-building-ai-data-centers-to-power-chatgpt-competitor-wsj"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T19:06:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A person familiar with Meta said the company has hired a new team and is stocking a data center with Nvidia H100s to compete with OpenAI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt AI, Edited by Stacy Elliot</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Reveals Xbox Mastercard That Helps You Earn Free Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155855</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155855/microsoft-reveals-xbox-mastercard-helps-you-earn-free-games"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T18:10:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Barclays will begin issuing Xbox Mastercards to select U.S. applicants later this month, allowing holders to earn points for gaming perks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sushi Expands to Aptos in 'Milestone' Move]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155839</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155839/sushi-expands-to-aptos-in-milestone-move"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T17:24:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The move to Aptos is the first time DEX has been accessible on a blockchain that is not compatible with the Ethereum Virtual Machine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Mino Games is Using Artificial Intelligence]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/SrT1Afj7/how-mino-games-is-using-artificial-intelligence</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/SrT1Afj7/how-mino-games-is-using-artificial-intelligence"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T22:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mino Games CEO Sasha McKinnon tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about how the studio's upcoming game Dimensionals will use real-time AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INTERVIEW: How Will Aurory Use NFTs and Crypto?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qv3VwNmM/interview-how-will-aurory-use-nfts-and-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qv3VwNmM/interview-how-will-aurory-use-nfts-and-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T15:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Natoli, Aurory's Head of Marketing and Business Development, tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how the Aurory games will use NFTs and crypto and shares the studio's broader stance on the tech.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Cloud's James Tromans on the Intersection of AI and Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OeD4uoLj/google-clouds-james-tromans-on-the-intersection-of-ai-and-web3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OeD4uoLj/google-clouds-james-tromans-on-the-intersection-of-ai-and-web3"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google's Global Head of Google Cloud for Web3 James Tromans sat down with Decrypt's Jason Nelson to discuss how AI can help Web3 companies come to market faster and the real value of Web3 tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastering NFT Trading - Degen U]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/HQGt1Vrq/mastering-nft-trading-degen-u</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/HQGt1Vrq/mastering-nft-trading-degen-u"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T07:08:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Take Degen U's new course, Mastering NFT Trading, and earn an on-chain certificate. A top instructor will help you identify trends, seize the right moment to trade, weed out scams—and have fun while doing it!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Space Nation CEO on Working With 'Independence Day' Director Roland Emmerich]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LpznLhtx/space-nation-ceo-on-working-with-independence-day-director-roland-emmerich</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LpznLhtx/space-nation-ceo-on-working-with-independence-day-director-roland-emmerich"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T17:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jerome Wu, CEO of Space Nation, tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the upcoming Space Nation Online game in development and shares details on Space Nation Cofounder Roland Emmerich's role in the project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GAME REVIEW: Champions Arena from Gala Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qUE1RlDx/game-review-champions-arena-from-gala-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qUE1RlDx/game-review-champions-arena-from-gala-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Champions Arena is a turn-based fantasy RPG from Gala Games, where characters can become NFTs and crypto can be used to purchase gems, one of the game's synthetic currencies. Decrypt's Kate Irwin takes us inside the game for her thoughts on the fun, mobile-first title.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apex Legends Voice Actor Ben Prendergast on the Future of Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/X3RKdsaG/apex-legends-voice-actor-ben-prendergast-on-the-future-of-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/X3RKdsaG/apex-legends-voice-actor-ben-prendergast-on-the-future-of-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T18:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Voice actor Ben Prendergast, who's voiced characters in games like Apex Legends and God of War Ragnarok, shares his opinions on the tech space's history of "bubbles" and whether blockchain gaming has a future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The future of AI Stardom and Robotics with SingularityNET COO Janet Adams and Desdemona]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yVQaZI71/the-future-of-ai-stardom-and-robotics-with-singularitynet-coo-janet-adams-and-desdemona</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yVQaZI71/the-future-of-ai-stardom-and-robotics-with-singularitynet-coo-janet-adams-and-desdemona"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T16:45:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this interview, SingularityNET COO Janet Adams explains the intricate details that went into creating the Desdemona robot AI from Hanson Robotics and future plans for the AI Diva.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto a 'No-Brainer' for Video Games, Says Mino Games CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rdynom8C/crypto-a-no-brainer-for-video-games-says-mino-games-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rdynom8C/crypto-a-no-brainer-for-video-games-says-mino-games-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T18:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mino Games CEO Sasha MacKinnon, developer of the upcoming Dimensionals game, tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the studio's approach to digital collectibles.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Wagner's 'Controversial Take' on Crypto in Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tc2nKeqA/michael-wagners-controversial-take-on-crypto-in-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tc2nKeqA/michael-wagners-controversial-take-on-crypto-in-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T16:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Solana's PlayGG, Star Atlas CEO Michael Wagner shares his "controversial take" on crypto in games, shares the challenges of developing the upcoming scifi game, and how crypto's volatility has changed his perspective with Decrypt's Jason Nelson.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interview: Angelic CEO on Building the Sci-Fi RPG on Solana and Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/uCzW3K7P/interview-angelic-ceo-on-building-the-sci-fi-rpg-on-solana-and-ethereum</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/uCzW3K7P/interview-angelic-ceo-on-building-the-sci-fi-rpg-on-solana-and-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T15:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Angelic is a sci-fi roleplay game in development that will be free-to-play and offer optional, opt-in crypto features on Solana and Ethereum and a governance token. Metaverse Game Studios CEO and Founder Erkan Bayol tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how he sees AAA traditional games as Angelic's main competitors and shares his vision for the game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apex Legends Voice Actor on AI's Impact on Video Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IOIrmb0N/apex-legends-voice-actor-on-ais-impact-on-video-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IOIrmb0N/apex-legends-voice-actor-on-ais-impact-on-video-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T17:28:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ben Prendergast is an actor who has voiced characters like Apex Legends' Fuse, God of War Ragnarok's Tyr, and Patroclus in Hades. But as debates swirl around the use of artificial intelligence in entertainment in light of the SAG-AFTRA and WGA strikes, Prendergast gives Decrypt's Kate Irwin his honest take on the potential use of AI actors in games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Star Atlas CEO on Developing an MMO Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/WQCaahmH/star-atlas-ceo-on-developing-an-mmo-game</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/WQCaahmH/star-atlas-ceo-on-developing-an-mmo-game"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T13:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Jason Nelson speaks with Star Atlas Founder and CEO Michael Wagner about the MMO game's approach to development, marketing, and blockchain integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aurory's Origin Story: How JRPGs Inspired the Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/O0S201TB/aurorys-origin-story-how-jrpgs-inspired-the-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/O0S201TB/aurorys-origin-story-how-jrpgs-inspired-the-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T16:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Jason Nelson talks to Aurory's Head of Marketing and Business Development Michael Natoli about the origins of the Aurory crypto games at the Solana PlayGG event.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>