<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-06-20T01:19:55.331Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-06-20T01:19:55.331Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin gains ground, Ether rises, Solana leads winners, BNB little-changed to lower]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18609926/Bitcoin-gains-ground-Ether-rises-Solana-leads-winners-BNB-little-changed-to-lower</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18609926/Bitcoin-gains-ground-Ether-rises-Solana-leads-winners-BNB-little-changed-to-lower"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T01:02:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin rose on Tuesday morning in Asia to hold above support at US$26,000. Ether also logged gains along with most other top 10 non-stablecoin tokens.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russia’s Ministry of Energy Pushes to Legalize Crypto Mining]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18609925/Russias-Ministry-of-Energy-Pushes-to-Legalize-Crypto-Mining</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18609925/Russias-Ministry-of-Energy-Pushes-to-Legalize-Crypto-Mining"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T01:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Russia’s Ministry of Energy is pushing for the legalization of industrial crypto mining, and wants lawmakers to press ahead with a much-anticipated mining-related bill. Per the Russian news agency Tass, the ministry made the comments at the weekend, during the St. Petersburg International...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Mover Asia: Bitcoin 'Looks Vulnerable': Analyst]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75732be5f1</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/06/20/first-mover-asia-bitcoin-looks-vulnerable-analyst/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T00:58:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The largest crypto by market value ticked upward to $26.8K as Asia markets opened. ALSO: A Financial Times report Monday raised fresh questions about the appropriateness of crypto exchanges operating market makers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin reaches 50% market dominance for first time in 2 years]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18609913/Bitcoin-reaches-50-market-dominance-for-first-time-in-2-years</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18609913/Bitcoin-reaches-50-market-dominance-for-first-time-in-2-years"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T00:45:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blackrock’s spot ETF filing and the Securities and Exchange Commission's crackdown on crypto are driving investors toward Bitcoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Mover Asia: Bitcoin 'Looks Vulnerable': Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18609916/First-Mover-Asia-Bitcoin-Looks-Vulnerable-Analyst</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18609916/First-Mover-Asia-Bitcoin-Looks-Vulnerable-Analyst"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T00:44:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The largest crypto by market value ticked upward to $26.8K as Asia markets opened. ALSO: A Financial Times report Monday raised fresh questions about the appropriateness of crypto exchanges operating market makers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Zimbabwe’s Central Bank Set to Launch P2P Platform for Facilitating Gold-Backed Digital Currency Transactions]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75731561e0</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/report-zimbabwes-central-bank-set-to-launch-p2p-platform-for-facilitating-gold-backed-digital-currency-transactions/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T00:42:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Reserve Bank of Zimbabwe has said it is getting close to launching a peer-to-peer platform which will facilitate digital gold token transactions. The central bank said the launch of the platform is expected to help reduce local demand for the greenback. Governor John Mangudya said the tokens have a value which is “linked to the London Bullion Market Association (LBMA).”
 
‘Gold Token’ Bank Accounts
 
The Zimbabwean central bank has said it is “finalizing” the establishment of a peer-to-peer (P2P) platform which is expected to facilitate digital gold token transactions. According to a June 17 Sunday Mail report, the Reserve Bank of Zimbabwe (RBZ) hopes to launch the platform towards the end of the month.
 
The P2P platform is part of the central bank’s measures which seek to diminish lo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PEPE Down 78% From May Peaks But Holder Count Rising]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18609904/PEPE-Down-78-From-May-Peaks-But-Holder-Count-Rising</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18609904/PEPE-Down-78-From-May-Peaks-But-Holder-Count-Rising"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T00:30:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While PEPE is down 78% from its May 2023 peaks, token holders continue to rise. As of June 19, there are now 119,229 unique addresses holding the token, an increase from early June, Etherscan data shows.   The meme token is based on Pepe the Frog meme, created by Matt Furie in 2005.  Falling...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Loses Key Litigator Amid Lawsuit Over Dogecoin Insider Trading Claims]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145368</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145368/elon-musk-loses-key-litigator-amid-lawsuit-over-dogecoin-insider-trading-claims"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T00:28:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The withdrawal of Adam Gabor comes after a letter last week regarding his newest in-house attorney, Allison Huebert.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IMF Is Working Hard on a Global CBDC Concept, Director Georgieva Said: Bloomberg News]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18609887/IMF-Is-Working-Hard-on-a-Global-CBDC-Concept-Director-Georgieva-Said-Bloomberg-News</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18609887/IMF-Is-Working-Hard-on-a-Global-CBDC-Concept-Director-Georgieva-Said-Bloomberg-News"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T00:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AiDoge, Scam, Planet, Unleash, 4Chan, 5 Top Trending Uniswap Coins On DEXTools Above Pepe]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18609869/AiDoge-Scam-Planet-Unleash-4Chan-5-Top-Trending-Uniswap-Coins-On-DEXTools-Above-Pepe</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18609869/AiDoge-Scam-Planet-Unleash-4Chan-5-Top-Trending-Uniswap-Coins-On-DEXTools-Above-Pepe"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T00:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robert Kiyosaki Says More US Banks Are About To Fail, Warns One Mortgage Lender Is ‘On the Ropes’]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18609872/Robert-Kiyosaki-Says-More-US-Banks-Are-About-To-Fail-Warns-One-Mortgage-Lender-Is-On-the-Ropes</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18609872/Robert-Kiyosaki-Says-More-US-Banks-Are-About-To-Fail-Warns-One-Mortgage-Lender-Is-On-the-Ropes"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T00:04:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rich Dad Poor Dad author Robert Kiyosaki says that the crisis in the banking industry is far from over. Kiyosaki tells his 2.4 million Twitter followers that he believes the California-based mortgage lender LoanDepot is likely on the verge of bankruptcy. LoanDepot reportedly lost $610.40 million...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA) Downtrend Could Last Five More Months, Says Analyst Benjamin Cowen – Here’s His Outlook]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18609873/Cardano-ADA-Downtrend-Could-Last-Five-More-Months-Says-Analyst-Benjamin-Cowen-Heres-His-Outlook</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18609873/Cardano-ADA-Downtrend-Could-Last-Five-More-Months-Says-Analyst-Benjamin-Cowen-Heres-His-Outlook"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T00:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Proof of Talk 2023: Restoring Trust in the Web3 Industry]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75731d09b4</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/proof-of-talk-2023-restoring-trust-in-the-web3-industry/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T23:09:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. Paris, June 19th 2023 – Over 1,500+ attendees, VCs, founders, start-ups, industry leaders, students, developers coming from Asia, Europe and the US gathered in Paris for the Proof of Talk Summit. In a rapidly evolving and challenging crypto landscape, they discussed the pressing issues and opportunities to shape a better future for the Web3 space.
 
As a result of these two days of intensive talks, the Proof of Talk constitution was presented, 10 commitments to truly revolutionize the Web3 industry: transparency, community engagement, education, ethical conduct, best practices, collaboration, inclusivity, long-term vision, accountability, and advocating for positive change.
 
“These two days of talks have shown us that the Web3 industry, which is based on a strong sense of c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The dollar OFFICIALLY in decline means you should buy Bitcoin #bitcoin #crypto #shorts]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18609842/The-dollar-OFFICIALLY-in-decline-means-you-should-buy-Bitcoin-bitcoin-crypto-shorts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18609842/The-dollar-OFFICIALLY-in-decline-means-you-should-buy-Bitcoin-bitcoin-crypto-shorts"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T23:09:51.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Remain Online, Hackers Cripple A Leading European Bank]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75731d1755</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-ethereum-online-hackers-cripple-bank/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T23:08:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The European Investment Bank (EIB), a triple-A-rated credit institution secured by the European Union (EU), is under attack. In a tweet on June 19, the long-term lending arm of the EU said they were facing a cyber-attack that had affected the availability of some of its key websites. 
 
While some of the bank’s sites have been rendered inaccessible, possibly inconveniencing some of its clientele base, Bitcoin and Ethereum, two of the world’s largest cryptocurrency networks, have proven immune to cyber-attacks and continue to operate with nearly 100% reliability and uptime.
 
European Investment Bank Under Attack 
 
It could not be immediately ascertained why the EIB was being targeted. However, what’s evident is that the lender plays a vital role in the European Union’s financial infrastru…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dalmas Ngetich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Remain Online, Hackers Cripple A Leading European Bank]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18609833/Bitcoin-Ethereum-Remain-Online-Hackers-Cripple-A-Leading-European-Bank</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18609833/Bitcoin-Ethereum-Remain-Online-Hackers-Cripple-A-Leading-European-Bank"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T23:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The European Investment Bank (EIB), a triple-A-rated credit institution secured by the European Union (EU), is under attack. In a tweet on June 19, the long-term lending arm of the EU said they were facing a cyber-attack that had affected the availability of some of its key websites. While some...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu ($SHIB) Price Recovery Pushes 18.58 Trillion Tokens into Profitability]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18609792/Shiba-Inu-SHIB-Price-Recovery-Pushes-1858-Trillion-Tokens-into-Profitability</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18609792/Shiba-Inu-SHIB-Price-Recovery-Pushes-1858-Trillion-Tokens-into-Profitability"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T22:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The meme-inspired cryptocurrency Shiba Inu ($SHIB) has recently started charting an impressive rally that has seen its price outperform that of most other major digital assets, and lifted over a trillion of its tokens out of the red and back into profitability. According to available...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining Difficulty On The Rise Again: What You Need To Know]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75731a74fb</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-mining-difficulty-on-the-rise-again/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T22:07:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As additional miners join the Bitcoin network and existing miners continue to deploy new mining rigs, the difficulty of mining BTC is expected to reach a new all-time high within the month. According to data from Coinwarz, a Bitcoin mining monitoring platform, it looks like there’s likely to be another surge in mining difficulty in the coming weeks.
 
Bitcoin Mining Difficulty Increase: What Does It Mean?
 
The process of mining Bitcoin becomes increasingly harder as more miners join the network. The Bitcoin algorithm automatically adjusts to ensure that one block is mined every 10 minutes. When there are more miners competing, the difficulty goes up to make it harder to find a block. 
 
 
The higher the difficulty, the more hash power miners need to solve blocks and earn BTC. As difficult…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining Difficulty On The Rise Again: What You Need To Know]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18609771/Bitcoin-Mining-Difficulty-On-The-Rise-Again-What-You-Need-To-Know</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18609771/Bitcoin-Mining-Difficulty-On-The-Rise-Again-What-You-Need-To-Know"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T22:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking: Joe Biden Wants To Pump Bitcoin And Crypto Into The Election??]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18609782/BREAKING-JOE-BIDEN-WANTS-TO-PUMP-BITCOIN-AND-CRYPTO-INTO-THE-ELECTION</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18609782/BREAKING-JOE-BIDEN-WANTS-TO-PUMP-BITCOIN-AND-CRYPTO-INTO-THE-ELECTION"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T21:56:44.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto.com Refutes Accusations of Proprietary Trading (Report)]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18609764/Cryptocom-Refutes-Accusations-of-Proprietary-Trading-Report</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18609764/Cryptocom-Refutes-Accusations-of-Proprietary-Trading-Report"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T21:52:47.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Core Devs Weigh Pros and Cons of Raising Validator Threshold From 32 ETH to 2,048 ETH]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7573050efd</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ethereum-core-devs-weigh-pros-and-cons-of-raising-validator-threshold-from-32-eth-to-2048-eth/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T21:39:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum’s core developers are engaged in discussions about raising the validator threshold from 32 ETH to 2,048 ETH. This proposal, put forward by Michael Neuder, a researcher from the Ethereum Foundation, aims to address concerns related to decentralization, inflation, and the size of the validator set. Neuder acknowledges that the existing threshold promotes decentralization, but he also highlights the drawbacks of inflation and the substantial number of validators that it entails.
 
Ethereum Developers Want to Raise the Validator Threshold
 
During the latest Ethereum core developer consensus meeting, a gathering of ETH software engineers and researchers, an intriguing notion emerged for elevating the validator threshold from 32 ether to 2,048 ether. As it stands, aspiring validators m…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 'Napoleon Dynamite' Cast Is Finally Back Together. You Can Thank NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145267</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145267/napoleon-dynamite-cast-finally-back-together-thank-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T21:36:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt was onsite as the cast of cult classic "Napoleon Dynamite" reunited for an animated pilot set to release exclusively to NFT holders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 'Napoleon Dynamite' Cast Is Finally Back Together. You Can Thank NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18609737/The-Napoleon-Dynamite-Cast-Is-Finally-Back-Together-You-Can-Thank-NFTs</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18609737/The-Napoleon-Dynamite-Cast-Is-Finally-Back-Together-You-Can-Thank-NFTs"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T21:36:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt was onsite as the cast of cult classic "Napoleon Dynamite" reunited for an animated pilot set to release exclusively to NFT holders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK Moves Closer to Crypto Laws with Parliament’s Upper House Approval]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757305692e</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/uk-moves-closer-to-crypto-laws-with-parliaments-upper-house-approval/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T21:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The United Kingdom  
is getting closer to treating cryptocurrency as a regulated activity, with promotion  
of digital assets closely monitored. On Monday, lawmakers from the Parliament’s  
upper chamber, House of Lords, ratified the Financial Services and Markets Bill  
(FSMB). 
House of Lords Approves Crypto Laws
FSMB  
outlines the UK’s economic strategy post-Brexit. The bill originally proposes  
to regulate stablecoins under the payments industry. However, provisions to  
deal with crypto as a regulated activity and to oversee crypto ads were added  
in subsequent amendments. 
The  
approval means that the bill, which was sanctioned by the lower chamber House  
of Commons in October last year, is now set for the final stages. This stage  
includes a last reading by both chambers, with…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Solomon Oladipupo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Mover Americas: Bitcoin Trades Flat, Altcoins Nurse Losses]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757306906c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/06/19/first-mover-americas-bitcoin-trades-flat-altcoins-nurse-losses/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T21:23:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest price moves in bitcoin (BTC) and crypto markets in context for June 19, 2023. First Mover is CoinDesk’s daily newsletter that contextualizes the latest actions in the crypto markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lyllah Ledesma, Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robert Breedlove | Bitcoin's Power Against FED & CBDC]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18609739/Robert-Breedlove-Bitcoins-Power-Against-FED-CBDC</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18609739/Robert-Breedlove-Bitcoins-Power-Against-FED-CBDC"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T21:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Did Elon Musk Just CRASH this Crypto!? MAJOR Crypto Whale Accumulation & Ripple CEO Lashes out....]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18609725/Did-Elon-Musk-Just-CRASH-this-Crypto-MAJOR-Crypto-Whale-Accumulation-Ripple-CEO-Lashes-out</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18609725/Did-Elon-Musk-Just-CRASH-this-Crypto-MAJOR-Crypto-Whale-Accumulation-Ripple-CEO-Lashes-out"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T21:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Coinbase CTO Warns G7 Countries Will Seize Crypto, Cites Apples, Microsoft, Google as ‘Risk Factors.’]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18609713/Ex-Coinbase-CTO-Warns-G7-Countries-Will-Seize-Crypto-Cites-Apples-Microsoft-Google-as-Risk-Factors</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18609713/Ex-Coinbase-CTO-Warns-G7-Countries-Will-Seize-Crypto-Cites-Apples-Microsoft-Google-as-Risk-Factors"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T21:04:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Balaji Srinivasan shares that countries could soon seize crypto thanks to Apple, Google, and Microsoft’s dominance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Resistance At $26,600: A Make Or Break Moment For Bulls]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18609714/Bitcoin-Resistance-At-26600-A-Make-Or-Break-Moment-For-Bulls</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18609714/Bitcoin-Resistance-At-26600-A-Make-Or-Break-Moment-For-Bulls"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T21:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improbable Opens Up the Tech Behind the Bored Ape Metaverse]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145332</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145332/improbable-opens-up-tech-behind-bored-ape-metaverse"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T20:38:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The “stupidly ambitious” MSquared project, as Improbable CEO Herman Narula describes it, launches its metaverse-building tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Reclaims Over 50% Market Dominance Following BlackRock ETF Filing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145334</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145334/bitcoin-reclaims-over-50-market-dominance-following-blackrock-etf-filing"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T20:33:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC’s crackdown against altcoins is boosting Bitcoin’s share of the crypto market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Etherscan Touts ChatGPT Integration But Highlights The Chatbot's Flaws]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145324</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145324/etherscan-touts-chatgpt-integration-but-highlights-the-chatbots-flaws"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T20:20:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adding ChatGPT to its new Code Reader tool, Etherscan aims to enhance understanding of Ethereum source code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale Bitcoin Trust Gets a Bullish Bump After BlackRock ETF Filing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145326</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145326/grayscale-bitcoin-trust-gets-a-bullish-bump-after-blackrock-etf-filing"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T20:06:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) jumped more than 12% on Friday in reaction to BlackRock filing its Bitcoin ETF application.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rumors Of Imminent Approval Swirl Around BlackRock’s Bitcoin ETF]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75730e16b5</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/imminent-approval-swirl-blackrocks-bitcoin-etf/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T20:06:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Bailey, a well-known figure in the cryptocurrency industry, has suggested that BlackRock’s Bitcoin (BTC) Exchange-Traded Fund (ETF) could be approved imminently by the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), after years of failed attempts by other firms.
 
Bailey, the CEO of BTC Inc. and a board member at the University of Alabama believes that BlackRock’s entry into the Bitcoin ETF market could tip the scales in favor of regulatory acceptance.
 
David Bailey’s recent comments about BlackRock’s potential BTC ETF approval come from the asset management firm’s filing with the SEC on June 15th.
 
If approved, the ETF would provide investors with a means of gaining exposure to Bitcoin without holding the cryptocurrency directly, which could significantly impact BTC’s price.
 
 
Coul…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance’s Financial Aid To ZachXBT In Defamation Lawsuit Fuels Debate In Crypto Circle]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75730e16a8</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/binance-aid-to-zachxbt-lawsuit-fuels-debate-crypto/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T20:06:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amid Binance’s ups and downs in the crypto market, the exchange’s recent donation to prominent crypto on-chain sleuth ZachXBT has sparked controversy among the crypto community. Last Friday, ZachXBT was sued by Jeffrey Huang, also known under his pseudonym, MachiBigBrother over a defamation case.
 
Following the lawsuit, the crypto detective disclosed that battling the case could cost more than $1 million. He then asked his followers to donate funds to a wallet dedicated to his legal costs. So far, the wallet has amassed more than $1 million in donations with the likes of Binance also contributing.
 
However, among the notable names that have donated, the crypto community has appeared to initiate a heated discussion about Binance’s financial support to ZachXBT.
 
Binance’s Donation And Its…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Indonesia Grants XRP An Official Tradable Status In Crypto Market]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757cf47a3c</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/indonesia-grants-xrp-an-official-tradable-status/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T19:04:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Indonesia’s government has deepened the country’s crypto adoption with a list of tradable assets. It added Ripple native token, XRP, among the 501 digital assets on the list. With the new revelation, XRP and other listed tokens have received the license to be traded in the country.
 
Indonesia Authorities Update Regulatory Document For Tradable Crypto Tokens
 
According to the released regulatory document, the Indonesian government amended the country’s former Trade Controlling Agency Regulations Commodity Futures Number 11 of 2022.
 
Related Reading: Trillions Of Shiba Inu Tokens Hit Break-Even As Meme Coin Price Leaps 10%
 
The amendment marked a great move toward crypto adoption. Notably, the listed crypto tokens have received the country’s approval as legally tradable cryptocurrencies.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Dambel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Etherscan Unveils Code Reader: An AI-Powered Tool That Aims to Bolster Smart Contract Analysis]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757cf72f71</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/etherscan-unveils-code-reader-an-ai-powered-tool-that-aims-to-bolster-smart-contract-analysis/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T18:40:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After the Ethereum block explorer Etherscan introduced an advanced filter for blockchain exploration, the team announced a new tool called Code Reader, powered by artificial intelligence (AI). Essentially, the service leverages AI to enable users to retrieve and interpret the source code of a specific contract address.
 
Etherscan Introduces an AI-Powered Code Reader for Smart Contract Analysis
 
On June 19, 2023, Etherscan announced a new feature that integrates artificial intelligence (AI) into its blockchain explorer’s capabilities. Code Reader beta harnesses “the power of AI to seamlessly learn about any smart contract source code,” Etherscan said on Twitter. Additionally, Etherscan has introduced documentation on how to use the Code Reader service.
 
“By selecting a contract address, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain Security Firm CertiK Found an Infinite Loop Bug in Sui Network]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757cf138d8</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/06/19/blockchain-security-firm-certik-found-an-infinite-loop-bug-in-sui-network/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T18:22:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bug was found before Sui mainnet was live and the foundation granted a $500,000 award for the discovery.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anna Baydakova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Binance Canceled Its UK License, Continues European Market Exit]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757cf365d8</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/binance-canceled-uk-license-exits-european-market/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T18:03:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The world’s largest crypto exchange Binance continues to pull out from the European market. According to the United Kingdom’s Financial Conduct Authority (FCA), the company canceled its license to operate in the country. 
 
 
The U.K. regulator stated in its June 7, 2023 update:
 

Binance Markets Limited has recently submitted a cancellation request of their FCA permissions which was completed on 30 May 2023 and is reflected on the FCA Register. Following the completion of the cancellation of permissions the firm is no longer authorised by the FCA. No other entity in the Binance Group holds any form of UK authorisation or registration to conduct regulated business in the UK.
 
 
Binance On Preservation Mode?
 
Binance has had a troublesome history with the U.K. regulator. The government e…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reynaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock Bitcoin ETF Prospects Boost Institutional Investor Sentiment]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145268</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145268/blackrock-bitcoin-etf-prospects-boost-institutional-investor-sentiment"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T17:23:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock’s ETF gambit is significant news, but not enough to tip institutional investors back into crypto funds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Laws Enter Final Stages of UK Parliamentary Process]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145300</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145300/crypto-laws-enter-final-stages-of-uk-parliamentary-process"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T17:10:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoins and cryptocurrency regulation are set to become UK law as the Financial Services and Markets Bill enters its final stages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[B2Broker Announces NDF Asset Class Addition, Reduced Margin Requirements, and Updates to PoP Liquidity Offering Package]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757cfa8f49</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/b2broker-announces-ndf-asset-class-addition-reduced-margin-requirements-and-updates-to-pop-liquidity-offering-package/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T17:08:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. B2Broker, a prominent global liquidity provider in the FX and crypto industry, proudly declares the inclusion of Non-Deliverable Forwards (NDFs) in its extensive range of liquidity offerings. This strategic expansion further strengthens the company’s commitment to furnishing comprehensive asset coverage and unparalleled risk management solutions for all B2Broker customers.
 
As a multi-asset liquidity provider, B2Broker supports all major asset classes, which include:
 
 
Rolling Spot FX & Precious Metals
 
Equity Indices
 
Energies
 
Commodities
 
Crypto Derivatives/CFDs
 
Single Stocks/CFDs
 
ETFs
 
NDFs
 
 
This accomplishment consolidates B2Broker’s leading position in the industry, demonstrating its steadfast commitment to meeting the diverse requirements of its clients…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto.com Is Trading on Its Own Exchange, Insists That’s Totally Fine]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145243</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145243/crypto-com-has-internal-trading-team-making-money-report"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T17:08:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency exchange Crypto.com has staff trading tokens for profit, the Financial Times has reported.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Long-Term Holders Refuse To Budge As Movements Remain Low]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757cfb2de5</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-long-term-holders-refuse-budge-remain-low/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T17:04:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data shows that Bitcoin long-term holders have remained adamant recently as their movements remain at low levels.
 
Bitcoin Binary CDD Has Continued To Be At Low Values Recently
 
According to data from the on-chain analytics firm Glassnode, mature coins aren’t showing much movement despite the recent volatility in the asset’s price. The relevant indicator here is the “Coin Days Destroyed” (CDD), which, to understand the concept of “coin days,” needs to be looked at first.
 
A coin day is a quantity that 1 BTC accumulates when it remains dormant on the blockchain for 1 day. When any coin that has remained dormant for some number of days, and hence, has accumulated some coin days, is finally transferred on the network, its coin days counter naturally resets back to zero.
 
The coin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hououin Kyouma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terra’s Do Kwon Receives 4-Month Jail Sentence in Montenegro for Counterfeit Passport Usage]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757ce6dec1</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/terras-do-kwon-receives-4-month-jail-sentence-in-montenegro-for-counterfeit-passport-usage/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T16:38:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Montenegro’s court has determined that Do Kwon, the co-founder of Terraform Labs, is guilty of using a counterfeit Costa Rican passport. As a result, he has been sentenced to four months in jail for the offense.
 
Do Kwon Sentenced to 122 Days in Prison, Defendant Has 8 Days to Appeal
 
According to the Montenegrin court, Do Kwon, also known as Kwon Do-Hyung, has been convicted of possessing and attempting to use a counterfeit passport. The court’s announcement specifies that Kwon has been found guilty of the criminal offense of document forgery. Montenegrin law enforcement authorities will seize Kwon’s travel documents, which include a Costa Rican passport, a Belgian passport, and two other forms of identification.
 
The court has imposed a four-month jail sentence on Kwon, as stated in a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Centric-AI “Spirit Of Satoshi” Unveiled]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757ce13763</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/bitcoin-centric-ai-spirit-of-satoshi-unveiled"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T16:23:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Spirit of Satoshi, the world's first Bitcoin-centric AI, has been announced, promising to revolutionize the understanding and accessibility of Bitcoin knowledge.
According to a press release shared with Bitcoin Magazine, “It’s a Large Language Model being built from first principles, oriented on the core values of Bitcoin, trained on the best bitcoin data in the world, and fine-tuned by the global bitcoin community.” The release stated that development is driven by the need to provide an alternative to mainstream, generalized language models and preserve the collective intelligence of the Bitcoin community.
"We believe it's imperative to build an alternative to mainstream, generalized large language models, and in particular, there needs to be a place where the entire collective global intelligence and knowledge of Bitcoin is preserved and made accessible to everyone," said a representative of The Spirit of Satoshi project.
The goal of this initiative is to orange-pill, or introduce Bitcoin to, the next billion people, using efficient and effective tools that can operate at scale while remaining impactful on an individual level. In the coming weeks, the model will be open-sourced, the release stated, and the entire Bitcoin community will be engaged to assist in training and fine-tuning it. The project also plans to offer sats bounties to incentivize participation.
By providing an alternative system and powerful tools, The Spirit of Satoshi project said it aims to combat potential threats such as “Iris Scanning Central Bank Digital Currencies” (CBDCs), mainstream education limitations and generalized AI that restricts knowledge within narrow boundaries.
To learn more about The Spirit of Satoshi and contribute to its mission, interested individuals can visit SpiritofSatoshi.ai.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BtcCasey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Liquid Bitcoin Versus Wrapped Bitcoin: A Comparative Analysis]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757ce13759</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/guides/liquid-vs-wrapped-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T16:23:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Given the increasing transaction fees caused by Ordinals activity in the Bitcoin timechain, many Bitcoiners have sought alternative solutions to keep their transaction fees low during these periods. While Bitcoin Layer 2 options like the Lightning Network offer low transaction fees, it may not be practical for Bitcoin hodlers to migrate their entire holdings to Lightning, as many Lightning wallets are custodial, meaning users must rely on a trusted third party to hold their funds. While this custodial approach may be suitable for small amounts that users are likely to spend, many Bitcoiners will feel uneasy about not having self-custody of their bitcoin. Additionally, achieving self-custody of a substantial stack on Lightning would require significant technical knowledge and still necessit…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jaime García</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Issues Cease And Desist To Nigerian Impersonator]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757ce3beae</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/binance-issues-cease-and-desist-to-impersonator/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T16:06:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao has taken to Twitter to deny any association with Binance Nigeria Limited which has been mistaken as part of the exchange. As a result, the exchange has now issued a cease and desist notice to the impersonator(s).
 
False Binance Nigeria Platform Exposed
 
On June 9, the Nigerian Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) posted a circular warning citizens to steer clear of Binance Nigeria Limited, a platform where individuals can trade cryptocurrencies. The SEC revealed that the platform was not “registered nor regulated” and as such has been operating illegally in the country.
 
 
The entity was falsely associated with the global cryptocurrency exchange Binance and CEO Changpeng Zhao has now publicly denounced Binance Nigeria Limited.
 
The platform has been shut…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance UK Subsidiary Cancels Unused FCA Permissions]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145253</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145253/binance-uk-subsidiary-withdraws-fca-registration"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T14:42:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The UK subsidiary of the world’s largest crypto exchange has canceled its registration with the Financial Conduct Authority (FCA).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bank of England-Backed Project: CBDCs Could Enable 'Programmability' for Money]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145247</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145247/bank-of-england-backed-project-cbdcs-could-enable-programmability-for-money"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T14:26:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ‘Project Rosalind’ software trial found that central bank digital currencies could enable smart contract-like features for transactions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alys Key</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Animoca Brands CEO Robby Yung: Expect ‘Triple-A Console-Style’ Web3 Games in 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144941</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144941/animoca-brands-ceo-robby-yung-expect-triple-a-console-style-web3-games-in-2024"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T12:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Web3 gaming mogul expects to see a hybrid model emerge for the industry, encompassing casual titles, triple-A games and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Issues Cease and Desist to Nigerian ‘Scammer Entity’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145223</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145223/binance-issues-cease-and-desist-to-nigerian-scammer-entity"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T11:56:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao denounced "Binance Nigeria Limited" as a fraudulent company in a post on Twitter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Payments Firm Wyre Winding Down Due to ‘Market Conditions’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145218</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145218/crypto-payments-firm-wyre-winding-down-due-to-market-conditions"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T11:08:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto payments firm is ceasing operations less than a year after it was valued at $1.5 billion in an abortive acquisition by Bolt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terra Co-Founder Do Kwon Sentenced to Four Months in Prison for Forged Passports]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145213</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145213/terra-co-founder-do-kwon-denies-forged-passport-allegations"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T10:51:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Labs’ CEO Do Kwon told a court in Montenegro he never had any intentions of forging his travel documents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Explain This Bob’ AI Twitter Bot  Suspended After Elon Musk Calls it ‘Scam Crypto Account’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145206</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145206/explain-this-bob-ai-twitter-bot-suspended-after-elon-musk-calls-it-scam-crypto-account"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T10:35:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The move marks an abrupt about-face for Musk, who had previously engaged with the bot's content on Twitter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$95K CryptoPunk NFT Burned by Bitcoin Bandits, Revived as Ordinals Inscription]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145172</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145172/95k-cryptopunk-nft-burned-by-bitcoin-bandits-revived-as-ordinals-inscription"/>
        <updated>2023-06-18T21:15:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a so-called teleburn, the asset’s holders symbolically shifted the Punk from Ethereum to Bitcoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ordinals Brought Inscriptions to Bitcoin—Now Ethscriptions Land on Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145153</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145153/ethscriptions-ethereum-ordinals-bitcoin-inscriptions"/>
        <updated>2023-06-18T19:18:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new protocol to inscribe images on the Ethereum main chain has drawn strong interest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Sleuth ZachXBT Receives Over $1 Million in Donations Following Defamation Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145146</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145146/crypto-sleuth-zachxbt-receives-over-1-million-in-donations-following-defamation-lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2023-06-18T18:33:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[High-profile crypto leaders Changpeng Zhao and Justin Sun are among his supporters.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week on Crypto Twitter: The SEC Registration Hallucination]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145124</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145124/this-week-on-crypto-twitter-sec-binance-coinbase-week-2"/>
        <updated>2023-06-18T17:57:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC was always the industry’s bete noire, but is it now the final battle?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Fortnite Adding Nike NFTs? Apparel Giant Teases Gaming Collab]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145112</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145112/fortnite-nike-nft-apparel-giant-gaming-collab"/>
        <updated>2023-06-18T16:50:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nike’s .Swoosh platform on Polygon may be coming to the massive online shooter Fortnite. Here’s what we know so far.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Cross the Ages' Is a Tough But Rewarding Fantasy Card Battler]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145012</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145012/cross-ages-tough-rewarding-fantasy-card-battler"/>
        <updated>2023-06-18T13:11:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[REVIEW: Complex competitive game Cross the Ages lets you battle with decks of digital cards—and mint your favorites as NFTs, too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cross the Ages Game Review: A Tough But Rewarding Card Battler]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/2PfzFDVY/cross-the-ages-game-review-a-tough-but-rewarding-card-battler</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/2PfzFDVY/cross-the-ages-game-review-a-tough-but-rewarding-card-battler"/>
        <updated>2023-06-18T12:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cross the Ages is a digital collectible card game that challenges players to duel online opponents—and you can even mint your cards as tradable NFTs. It's complex and difficult to grasp at first, but this mobile-first game has some serious strategic upside. GG contributor Ryan Gladwin puts Cross the Ages through its paces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Slams 'Evasive Response' from SEC to Court Order]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145088</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145088/coinbase-slams-evasive-response-from-sec-to-court-order"/>
        <updated>2023-06-18T00:15:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC was told to respond to a Coinbase petition, but its response was noncommittal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Is Helping HR Departments Write Termination Letters]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145083</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145083/ai-is-helping-hr-departments-write-termination-letters"/>
        <updated>2023-06-17T20:46:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As tech industry layoffs continue, even human resources departments find themselves in need of help.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Markets Recover as Inflation Cools Down]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145076</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145076/this-week-in-coins-markets-recover-as-inflation-cools-down"/>
        <updated>2023-06-17T19:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s the second week of Binance and Coinbase versus the SEC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance US Made a 'Burdensome' Deal With SEC, Former SEC Official Says]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145069</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145069/binance-us-made-a-burdensome-deal-with-sec-former-sec-official-says"/>
        <updated>2023-06-17T17:56:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The agreement is "unprecedented, exhaustive, and onerous," declares a former SEC enforcement chief.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta's New AI Speech Tool Is Ready-Made for Deepfakes—So It's Not Being Released]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145034</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145034/meta-new-ai-speech-tool-ready-made-deepfakes"/>
        <updated>2023-06-17T15:53:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The apparently powerful new AI tool isn't being released yet due to what Meta acknowledges are "potential risks of misuse."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Uncensor Any AI Large Language Model Like ChatGPT]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145017</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145017/how-uncensor-large-language-model-llm-chatgpt"/>
        <updated>2023-06-17T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All it takes to turn your conservative ChatGPT bot into an unapologetic, full-on NSFW machine is a simple phrase in the prompt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Denies Owning Dogecoin Stash Linked to Insider Trading]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145043</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145043/elon-musk-dogecoin-wallets-insider-trading"/>
        <updated>2023-06-17T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Musk’s lawyer says the claim that the Tesla CEO is secretly a DOGE whale is “without basis.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Sleuth ZachXBT Sued, Doxxed by Former Target]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145025</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145025/crypto-sleuth-zachxbt-sued-doxxed-by-former-target"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T22:50:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jeffrey Huang filed suit over allegations that he stole $38M in crypto. Now ZachXBT has enlisted Johnny Depp's lawyers to fight the claims.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock Bitcoin ETF Is the ‘Real Deal’—Is This Finally the One?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145000</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145000/blackrock-bitcoin-etf-real-deal"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T22:02:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For 10 years, crypto startup after crypto startup has tried its luck with the SEC. Now Wall Street’s heaviest hitter is lending its weight.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beeple Says It's Time to Delete Your JPEGs—Here's Why]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144980</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144980/beeple-says-time-delete-your-jpegs-heres-why"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T21:17:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Was the $11 million Sotheby's auction on Thursday the "final hurrah" for NFTs? Leading artists and collectors in the space push back.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Look at the Reserve Statements That Tether Tried to Conceal]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144994</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144994/a-look-at-the-reserve-statements-that-tether-tried-to-conceal"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T21:17:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Documents released from the New York Attorney General's investigation into Tether confirmed rumors that it held securities issued by Chinese companies to support its USDT reserves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Abra Cease-and-Desist Reveals Ties to Binance and Prime Trust]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144947</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144947/abra-cease-and-desist-reveals-ties-to-binance-and-prime-trust"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T19:42:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Texas regulator claims Abra has ties to Binance and Prime Trust, and roughly $70M stuck on Babel, Genesis, and 3AC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Europe Moves on AI Regulation to 'Counter Dangers to Democracy']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144973</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144973/europe-moves-ai-regulation-counter-dangers-democracy"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T19:29:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the United States stalls on AI regulation, the European Parliament is moving along after passing a draft law on Wednesday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donovan Choy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Predicts 'Catastrophic Outcome' Without AI Regulation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144959</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144959/elon-musk-predicts-catastrophic-outcome-without-ai-regulation"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T18:52:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk is warning again that unchecked development of artificial intelligence can lead to a "catastrophic outcome" for humanity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Weeknd and Binance Enter the Metaverse]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144944</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144944/weeknd-launches-metaverse-game-amid-binance-backed-tour"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T18:10:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The digital experience arrives amid The Weeknd's Binance-sponsored, "crypto-powered" world tour, which is currently in Europe.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lucy Harley-McKeown</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bakkt to Delist Solana, Cardano and Polygon Following SEC Lawsuits]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144945</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144945/bakkt-to-delist-solana-cardano-and-polygon-following-sec-lawsuits"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T17:34:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The publicly-listed company is waiting for further regulatory clarity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jack Dorsey Pledges $5M to Help Bitcoin Core Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144932</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144932/jack-dorsey-pledges-5m-to-help-bitcoin-core-developers"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T13:57:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The funding will come from his charity, Start Small, and will be disbursed $1 million at a time over the next five years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alyssa Hertig</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[French Authorities Investigating Binance for ‘Aggravated Money Laundering’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144927</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144927/french-authorities-investigating-binance-for-aggravated-money-laundering"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T12:52:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[France’s financial judicial investigation service is reportedly investigating Binance for offenses including “aggravated money laundering.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["AI Is Game-Changing But Needs Fact-Checking": AlchemyAI Project Lead]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/HXlThlXv/ai-is-game-changing-but-needs-fact-checking-alchemyai-project-lead</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/HXlThlXv/ai-is-game-changing-but-needs-fact-checking-alchemyai-project-lead"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this interview, Decrypt's Jason Nelson chats with Alchemy product manager and AlchemyAI project lead Elan Halpern on blockchain analysis using ChatGPT, what AI means for better user experience, and the need to fact-check AI. Halpern also gives a demo of the new AlchemyAI ChatGPT plugin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fractal Is Like an Arcade, Says Twitch Co-Founder Justin Kan]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/6r6Mdwt6/fractal-is-like-an-arcade-says-twitch-co-founder-justin-kan</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/6r6Mdwt6/fractal-is-like-an-arcade-says-twitch-co-founder-justin-kan"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Justin Kan was a co-founder of Twitch and now works on Fractal, a Web3 gaming startup. Kan tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about his new company and what he's up to.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are NFTs the Next SEC Target?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/YaGgY87J/are-nfts-the-next-sec-target</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/YaGgY87J/are-nfts-the-next-sec-target"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T20:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin discusses the current regulatory climate in the U.S. with Gala Games' President of Blockchain Jason Brink.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Collab.Land Co-Founder Said There Was No ‘Aha Moment’ When Launching DAO Toolkit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/kcBRKFGk/collabland-co-founder-said-there-was-no-aha-moment-when-launching-dao-toolkit</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/kcBRKFGk/collabland-co-founder-said-there-was-no-aha-moment-when-launching-dao-toolkit"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T09:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CCO and co-founder of Collab.Land Anjali Young explained at this year’s NFC Lisbon the origins of the crypto community tool kit, which industry niches are turning to its suite of products, and what’s next for the project since its token distribution event last February.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Buying a Slice of H.R. Giger's 'Alien' Is Fine Art, Not Memorabilia: Particle CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/VACG0WVg/buying-a-slice-of-hr-gigers-alien-is-fine-art-not-memorabilia-particle-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/VACG0WVg/buying-a-slice-of-hr-gigers-alien-is-fine-art-not-memorabilia-particle-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T08:49:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With H.R. Giger's original "Alien" statue on full display at this year's NFC Lisbon, Particle CEO Harold Eytan told Decrypt that owning an NFT-ified slice of the piece isn't just for fans of the iconic creature and movie series but also for fine art collectors. Interested in owning a piece? Be prepared to cough up half an ETH for one of the 500 tranches of the digitized sculpture.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Community Co-Creation 'Is a Big Step for Fashion Brands' Entering the Metaverse: BNV Founder and CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/z6NSMnNm/community-co-creation-is-a-big-step-for-fashion-brands-entering-the-metaverse-bnv-founder-and-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/z6NSMnNm/community-co-creation-is-a-big-step-for-fashion-brands-entering-the-metaverse-bnv-founder-and-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T08:49:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The founder and CEO of metaverse fashion platform BNV Richard Hobbs said big brands are still nervous to let fans and community members customize their favorite garments. Still, he believes that as long as you can meet a firm's commercial bottom lines while stirring engagement, there's nothing to lose.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Standard Crypto VC Co-Founder on NFTs and Their Stigma in Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/bmtrrLio/standard-crypto-vc-co-founder-on-nfts-and-their-stigma-in-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/bmtrrLio/standard-crypto-vc-co-founder-on-nfts-and-their-stigma-in-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T18:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alok Vasudev is a co-founder of venture capital firm Standard Crypto. In an interview with Decrypt's Kate Irwin, he shares his thoughts on NFT marketing, NFT utility in gaming, and the stigma that pervades the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ava Labs Announces Avalanche Arcad3 for Game Developers at 3XP]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XPHp9r4j/ava-labs-announces-avalanche-arcad3-for-game-developers-at-3xp</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XPHp9r4j/ava-labs-announces-avalanche-arcad3-for-game-developers-at-3xp"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T15:21:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ava Labs Head of Gaming Ed Chang shares news with Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the crypto firm's latest push to help traditional game developers break into blockchain gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Like a Middle Finger to Western Culture’: YuYu Unpacks Inspiration Behind NFT Expo GAG]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Vuoplr6a/like-a-middle-finger-to-western-culture-yuyu-unpacks-inspiration-behind-nft-expo-gag</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Vuoplr6a/like-a-middle-finger-to-western-culture-yuyu-unpacks-inspiration-behind-nft-expo-gag"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T13:33:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At this year’s NFC Lisbon, multimedia artist and photographer YuLiang "YuYu" Liu broke down how themes from traditional painting and BDSM informed his latest NFT exhibition called “GAG.” He also shared exclusively with Decrypt a yet-to-be-launched drop for fans of his work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Competition Was Rather Low' in Mobile Wallet Space, Says Zerion Head of Growth]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/vCg8O2oy/competition-was-rather-low-in-mobile-wallet-space-says-zerion-head-of-growth</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/vCg8O2oy/competition-was-rather-low-in-mobile-wallet-space-says-zerion-head-of-growth"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T13:33:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zerion's move to launch a mobile-first crypto wallet not only helped NFT users swap jpegs on the go but was also a play to get away from crypto's desktop-centric user experience. And with such little competition, Zerion's head of growth Alexander Guy told Decrypt at NFC Lisbon it's managed to rake in 150,000 funded wallets. Next step? Taking on MetaMask and contending as a browser-extension wallet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘We’ve Never Seen Anything Like This in VR’, Says The Sandbox COO on Apple’s Vision Pro Headset]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/GQ29RaHw/weve-never-seen-anything-like-this-in-vr-says-the-sandbox-coo-on-apples-vision-pro-headset</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/GQ29RaHw/weve-never-seen-anything-like-this-in-vr-says-the-sandbox-coo-on-apples-vision-pro-headset"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T13:33:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Sandbox COO Sebastien Borget told Decrypt at this year’s NFC Lisbon that despite the high price point, Apple’s new VR headset is nonetheless “groundbreaking.” And though the tech giant never used the term “metaverse” in its reveal, Borget is sure that the technology will be key in growing participation in various digital worlds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Gala Safe? Gala Games Head of Blockchain on GALA, Crypto, and SEC Regulatory Turmoil]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5bcrE8nL/is-gala-safe-gala-games-head-of-blockchain-on-gala-crypto-and-sec-regulatory-turmoil</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5bcrE8nL/is-gala-safe-gala-games-head-of-blockchain-on-gala-crypto-and-sec-regulatory-turmoil"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T15:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gala Games President of Blockchain shares his thoughts on the GALA token upgrade and the latest SEC turmoil with Decrypt's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Artists Adopting NFTs Has Been ‘Really Market Dependent’, Says NFT Club Berlin’s Rebekka Revel]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/QKlIVlj3/artists-adopting-nfts-has-been-really-market-dependent-says-nft-club-berlins-rebekka-revel</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/QKlIVlj3/artists-adopting-nfts-has-been-really-market-dependent-says-nft-club-berlins-rebekka-revel"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T15:07:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Getting non-crypto artists to make the leap into Web3 comes in ebbs and flows according to the market’s bear and bull waves, says co-founder of NFT Club Berlin and Superteam Germany Rebekka Revel. But she’s hoping to change that by changing the narrative around digital collectibles, regardless of the market, one word at a time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big Brands Exploring Web3 to ‘Scale Up Their Super-fan Base’: Superduper Co-founder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/he6UzJwz/big-brands-exploring-web3-to-scale-up-their-super-fan-base-superduper-co-founder</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/he6UzJwz/big-brands-exploring-web3-to-scale-up-their-super-fan-base-superduper-co-founder"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T14:49:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Co-founder and co-CEO of Web3 media brand Superduper Dom Smith says big brands are eager to enter the space—they just don’t know how. Still, they all maintain a thesis of turning their communities into “super fans” that generate value for users as well as a firm’s bottom line.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How 1 Simple Question Kickstarted Performance Artist Foodmasku's Plunge Into NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/w86DMn3p/how-1-simple-question-kickstarted-performance-artist-foodmaskus-plunge-into-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/w86DMn3p/how-1-simple-question-kickstarted-performance-artist-foodmaskus-plunge-into-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T10:10:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As his food mask creations went viral on the Internet during the COVID lockdowns, reposted on TikTok and Instagram without his consent, he soon asked: "How do I protect my digital files?" Performance artist Foodmasku describes at this year's NFC Lisbon how that simple question spiraled into a minting collection after collection of his edible works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arianee CEO Pegs Wine and Spirits as Next 'Exciting' Industry to Make Web3 Leap]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Bo2NeG9Z/arianee-ceo-pegs-wine-and-spirits-as-next-exciting-industry-to-make-web3-leap</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Bo2NeG9Z/arianee-ceo-pegs-wine-and-spirits-as-next-exciting-industry-to-make-web3-leap"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T09:28:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CEO and co-founder of Arianee Pierre Nicolas Hurstel unpacks the wide spectrum of digital collectibles from 10,000 PFP collections to access passes for exclusive events. And with an unannounced big brand soon joining, Hurstel revealed at NFC Lisbon which kind of NFTs big brands are moving towards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why 'Words With Friends' Creator Paul Bettner is 'Allergic' to Pay-to-Win NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JkfOleb4/why-words-with-friends-creator-paul-bettner-is-allergic-to-pay-to-win-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JkfOleb4/why-words-with-friends-creator-paul-bettner-is-allergic-to-pay-to-win-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T20:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Words With Friends and Wildcard creator Paul Bettner tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about his perspective on what to do when NFTs become in-game characters and assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitch Co-Founder Justin Kan: 18 Months is 'Several Decades' in Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rKVvsPFb/twitch-co-founder-justin-kan-18-months-is-several-decades-in-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rKVvsPFb/twitch-co-founder-justin-kan-18-months-is-several-decades-in-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fractal and Twitch co-founder Justin Kan gives Decrypt's Kate Irwin an update on all things Fractal and his perspective on blockchain technology in gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Playing for Money in Web3 Games Not 'Durable,' Says Fractal's Justin Kan]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MQG3SaBM/playing-for-money-in-web3-games-not-durable-says-fractals-justin-kan</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MQG3SaBM/playing-for-money-in-web3-games-not-durable-says-fractals-justin-kan"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twitch and Fractal co-founder Justin Kan and Fractal co-founder Dan Borstelmann share their perspectives on Web3 gaming's changing landscape with Decrypt's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>