<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-09-13T15:19:35.053Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-09-13T15:19:35.053Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin 'anxiety stage' risks more September losses, but there’s a silver lining]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19899901/Bitcoin-anxiety-stage-risks-more-September-losses-but-theres-a-silver-lining</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19899901/Bitcoin-anxiety-stage-risks-more-September-losses-but-theres-a-silver-lining"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T15:13:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s "anxiety stage" suggests more potential September downside before the next leg up, the latest price analysis suggests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consumer Watchdog Calls Tether a 'Disaster for Consumers Waiting to Happen']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249323</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249323/consumer-watchdog-calls-tether-a-disaster-for-consumers-waiting-to-happen"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T15:10:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Tether has many of the same issues that FTX and Celsius had before their collapse," the watchdog wrote on its letter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consumer Watchdog Calls Tether a 'Disaster for Consumers Waiting to Happen']]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19899892/Consumer-Watchdog-Calls-Tether-a-Disaster-for-Consumers-Waiting-to-Happen</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19899892/Consumer-Watchdog-Calls-Tether-a-Disaster-for-Consumers-Waiting-to-Happen"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T15:10:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Tether has many of the same issues that FTX and Celsius had before their collapse," the watchdog wrote on its letter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FLOKI Investors Dive Into New Memecoin Priced $0.00021 Rivalling FLOKI’s Previous Success]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e745ce6683e</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/floki-investors-dive-into-new-memecoin-priced-0-00021-rivalling-flokis-previous-success/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T15:08:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the world of memecoins, Floki (FLOKI) has been a significant player, capturing the hearts of investors with its Viking-inspired branding and rapid growth. However, a new contender, GoodEgg (GEGG), is set to rival Floki (FLOKI)’s success with its fresh A.I-powered dating platform and a price of just $0.00021 in its presale. Investors who saw massive returns with Floki (FLOKI) are now eyeing GoodEgg (GEGG), hoping to replicate those gains as GEGG makes waves in the memecoin market.
 
Why FLOKI Holders Are Turning to GoodEgg (GEGG) 
Floki (FLOKI) investors are no strangers to success. The memecoin made headlines with its impressive market performance, driven by a passionate community and high-profile partnerships. However, with the GoodEgg (GEGG) presale gaining traction and raising $250k …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Price Prediction: More Gains To Made In New SOL Rival GoodEgg (GEGG)]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e745ce66839</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/solana-price-prediction-more-gains-to-made-in-new-sol-rival-goodegg-gegg/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T15:08:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana (SOL) has been a powerhouse in the cryptocurrency world, often regarded as a leading competitor to Ethereum due to its fast transaction speeds and low fees. However, in recent news, the Solana ecosystem faces challenges as selling pressure looms due to developments involving the FTX/Alameda exchange. At the same time, investors are increasingly turning their attention to GoodEgg (GEGG), an emerging AI-based dating platform in the crypto space, as it positions itself to rival Solana (SOL) in 2024 and beyond.
 
Solana’s Selling Pressure: A Warning for Traders 
Solana (SOL), currently trading at around $134.80, has recently faced potential selling pressure due to a large unstaking event linked to the now-bankrupt FTX exchange. A crypto wallet, associated with the bankrupt FTX and Alame…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 Reasons Solana Holders Are Entering New A.I Dating Presale, SOL Price Prediction For September]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e745ce66831</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/3-reasons-solana-holders-are-entering-new-a-i-dating-presale-sol-price-prediction-for-september/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T15:08:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana (SOL) has seen significant growth in its ecosystem, and now, investors are looking for the next big thing. Recently, many Solana (SOL) holders have been turning their attention to GoodEgg (GEGG), a future A.I dating cryptocurrency that promises massive returns. But why are Solana (SOL) holders entering the presale of this new crypto platform, and what can we expect from Solana in the upcoming months?
 
Here are three key reasons why Solana (SOL) investors are getting involved in the GoodEgg (GEGG) presale:
 
 
 
 Solana’s Growing Ecosystem and DeFi Success 
 
 
The Solana (SOL) ecosystem has been experiencing remarkable growth, especially within decentralized exchanges (DEX). According to Tristan Frizza, Founder of Zeta Markets, Solana (SOL) has reached $1.811 billion in DEX trading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top memecoin GoodEgg (GEGG) Challenges Dogecoin and Shiba Inu Legacy With Major Upcoming Bullrun]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e745ce6682e</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/top-memecoin-goodegg-gegg-challenges-dogecoin-and-shiba-inu-legacy-with-major-upcoming-bullrun/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T15:08:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the world of cryptocurrency, Dogecoin (DOGE) and Shiba Inu (SHIB) have long been at the forefront of the memecoin market, dominating the space with massive communities and considerable market capitalization. However, the rise of GoodEgg (GEGG), an innovative new A.I-driven dating cryptocurrency, is now posing a challenge to these giants. With a rapidly growing presale and significant investor interest, GoodEgg (GEGG) is poised to take the memecoin world by storm.
 
Dogecoin Profitability Remains Unmatched 
Since its inception, Dogecoin (DOGE) has been the memecoin to beat. Launched as a joke, it has since evolved into the largest memecoin in the crypto space, with a loyal following and a stronghold on the market. As of now, Dogecoin (DOGE) is leading the pack in terms of profitability. …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance BNB Traders Take Position in New A.I Dating Cryptocurrrency Priced $0.00021, BNB Profits To Be Made]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e745ce66829</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/binance-bnb-traders-take-position-in-new-a-i-dating-cryptocurrrency-priced-0-00021-bnb-profits-to-be-made/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T15:08:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cryptocurrency market continues to evolve, and savvy investors are always on the lookout for the next big opportunity. Recently, Binance Coin (BNB) traders have taken notice of GoodEgg (GEGG), a new AI-powered dating cryptocurrency. With BNB trading profits, these traders are looking to diversify into GEGG, which is currently priced at a highly attractive $0.00021.
 
Binance Coin (BNB) Performs Despite Bearish Trends 
Despite recent market challenges, Binance Coin (BNB) has seen a resurgence, breaking past significant resistance levels. Over the past week, BNB saw an 8% increase, climbing above its 20-day Exponential Moving Average (EMA), which had been a significant resistance point at $524.50.
 
However, while the BNB price action appears promising, there are signs of caution. The Ch…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) Fees Skyrocket: Here's Key Reason Behind It]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19899888/Ethereum-ETH-Fees-Skyrocket-Heres-Key-Reason-Behind-It</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19899888/Ethereum-ETH-Fees-Skyrocket-Heres-Key-Reason-Behind-It"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T15:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum total fees surged 60%]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether taps former PayPal and Chainalysis exec Jesse Spiro to lead policy and regulatory engagement]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19899886/Tether-taps-former-PayPal-and-Chainalysis-exec-Jesse-Spiro-to-lead-policy-and-regulatory-engagement</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19899886/Tether-taps-former-PayPal-and-Chainalysis-exec-Jesse-Spiro-to-lead-policy-and-regulatory-engagement"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T15:06:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spiro brings over six years of experience in government and regulatory relations within the blockchain space, according to a blog post.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale's Bold XRP Trust Sparks ETF Buzz and Market Frenzy]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19899884/Grayscales-Bold-XRP-Trust-Sparks-ETF-Buzz-and-Market-Frenzy</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19899884/Grayscales-Bold-XRP-Trust-Sparks-ETF-Buzz-and-Market-Frenzy"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T15:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale's new XRP Trust offers accredited investors a way to invest in XRP without the risks of direct ownership.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Stellar's Price Increased More Than 3% Within 24 hours]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19899918/Cryptocurrency-Stellars-Price-Increased-More-Than-3-Within-24-hours</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19899918/Cryptocurrency-Stellars-Price-Increased-More-Than-3-Within-24-hours"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T15:02:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stellar's (CRYPTO: XLM) price has increased 3.11% over the past 24 hours to $0.10. Over the past week, XLM has experienced an uptick of over 8.0%, moving from $0.09 to its current price. As it stands right now, the coin's all-time high is $0.88. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency POL (ex-MATIC)'s Price Increased More Than 14% Within 24 hours]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19899915/Cryptocurrency-POL-ex-MATICs-Price-Increased-More-Than-14-Within-24-hours</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19899915/Cryptocurrency-POL-ex-MATICs-Price-Increased-More-Than-14-Within-24-hours"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T15:02:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meme Coin Layer 2 Project Pepe Unchained Raises $13M in Presale – Next Crypto to Explode?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e745ce71502</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/meme-coin-layer-2-project-pepe-unchained-raises-13m-in-presale-next-crypto-to-explode/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T15:02:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s a golden era for Ethereum layer 2s. On-chain activity is exploding, and new innovations are releasing daily. Not least is the meme coin-focused Ethereum layer 2 Pepe Unchained ($PEPU), which has just cleared the $13 million total raised milestone at presale. This comes as Coinbase announced its new brainchild, cbBTC, a wrapped version of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wazirx Users May Face Delays Amid Binance Dispute and Moratorium Uncertainty]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e745ce71500</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/wazirx-users-may-face-delays-amid-binance-dispute-and-moratorium-uncertainty/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T15:02:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Indian cryptocurrency exchange Wazirx has warned users that they may have to wait until the dispute with Binance is resolved if the moratorium, filed in Singapore, is not granted. Wazirx explained that Zettai holds the cryptocurrency tokens under protest. “If Binance is deemed the owner, it becomes liable for users’ account balances. If Zettai is […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Litecoin Rises More Than 3% In 24 hours]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19899914/Cryptocurrency-Litecoin-Rises-More-Than-3-In-24-hours</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19899914/Cryptocurrency-Litecoin-Rises-More-Than-3-In-24-hours"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T15:01:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past 24 hours, Litecoin's (CRYPTO: LTC) price has risen 3.66% to $64.04. This is contrary to its negative trend over the past week where it has experienced a 0.0% loss, moving from $64.07 to its current price. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FLOKI Investors Dive Into New Memecoin Priced $0.00021 Rivalling FLOKI’s Previous Success]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19899855/FLOKI-Investors-Dive-Into-New-Memecoin-Priced-000021-Rivalling-FLOKIs-Previous-Success</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19899855/FLOKI-Investors-Dive-Into-New-Memecoin-Priced-000021-Rivalling-FLOKIs-Previous-Success"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T15:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the world of memecoins, Floki (FLOKI) has been a significant player, capturing the hearts of investors with its Viking-inspired branding and rapid growth. However, a new contender, GoodEgg (GEGG), is set to rival Floki (FLOKI)’s success with its fresh A.I-powered dating platform and a price...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu and Dogecoin Investors Flock Into New A.I Dating Cryptocurrency Positioned For Tier1 Listings]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19899864/Shiba-Inu-and-Dogecoin-Investors-Flock-Into-New-AI-Dating-Cryptocurrency-Positioned-For-Tier1-Listings</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19899864/Shiba-Inu-and-Dogecoin-Investors-Flock-Into-New-AI-Dating-Cryptocurrency-Positioned-For-Tier1-Listings"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T15:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the competitive world of memecoins, Dogecoin (DOGE) and Shiba Inu (SHIB) have reigned supreme for years, captivating both the crypto community and mainstream audiences. However, with new projects entering the market, investors are starting to diversify their portfolios. One of the most...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Standard Chartered Launches Digital Asset Custody Service in UAE]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19899870/Standard-Chartered-Launches-Digital-Asset-Custody-Service-in-UAE</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19899870/Standard-Chartered-Launches-Digital-Asset-Custody-Service-in-UAE"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T15:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Standard Chartered, a major player in financial services, is launching a new digital asset custody service in the UAE after receiving regulatory approval.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin vs GoodEgg (GEGG): Dogecoin Give Up On DOGE 100X Dreams and Join New A.I Dating Cryptocurrency]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19899862/Dogecoin-vs-GoodEgg-GEGG-Dogecoin-Give-Up-On-DOGE-100X-Dreams-and-Join-New-AI-Dating-Cryptocurrency</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19899862/Dogecoin-vs-GoodEgg-GEGG-Dogecoin-Give-Up-On-DOGE-100X-Dreams-and-Join-New-AI-Dating-Cryptocurrency"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T15:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin (DOGE), once the reigning meme coin, now finds itself in a struggle to retain its momentum, leaving many long-term holders reconsidering their faith in the cryptocurrency. With recent data showing dwindling returns for Dogecoin investors, a new player has emerged in the space—GoodEgg...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Price Prediction: More Gains To Made In New SOL Rival GoodEgg (GEGG)]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19899854/Solana-Price-Prediction-More-Gains-To-Made-In-New-SOL-Rival-GoodEgg-GEGG</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19899854/Solana-Price-Prediction-More-Gains-To-Made-In-New-SOL-Rival-GoodEgg-GEGG"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T15:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana (SOL) has been a powerhouse in the cryptocurrency world, often regarded as a leading competitor to Ethereum due to its fast transaction speeds and low fees. However, in recent news, the Solana ecosystem faces challenges as selling pressure looms due to developments involving the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BNB vs GEGG: Binance Whales Take Position In A.I Dating Cryptocurrency]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19899830/BNB-vs-GEGG-Binance-Whales-Take-Position-In-AI-Dating-Cryptocurrency</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19899830/BNB-vs-GEGG-Binance-Whales-Take-Position-In-AI-Dating-Cryptocurrency"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T15:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cryptocurrency landscape is rapidly evolving, with new trends emerging and key players constantly shifting their strategies. Two tokens currently gaining attention are Binance Coin (BNB) and GoodEgg (GEGG), an AI-powered dating platform token. Binance whales, known for their significant...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 Reasons Solana Holders Are Entering New A.I Dating Presale, SOL Price Prediction For September]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19899853/3-Reasons-Solana-Holders-Are-Entering-New-AI-Dating-Presale-SOL-Price-Prediction-For-September</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19899853/3-Reasons-Solana-Holders-Are-Entering-New-AI-Dating-Presale-SOL-Price-Prediction-For-September"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T15:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana (SOL) has seen significant growth in its ecosystem, and now, investors are looking for the next big thing. Recently, many Solana (SOL) holders have been turning their attention to GoodEgg (GEGG), a future A.I dating cryptocurrency that promises massive returns. But why are Solana (SOL)...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top memecoin GoodEgg (GEGG) Challenges Dogecoin and Shiba Inu Legacy With Major Upcoming Bullrun]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19899852/Top-memecoin-GoodEgg-GEGG-Challenges-Dogecoin-and-Shiba-Inu-Legacy-With-Major-Upcoming-Bullrun</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19899852/Top-memecoin-GoodEgg-GEGG-Challenges-Dogecoin-and-Shiba-Inu-Legacy-With-Major-Upcoming-Bullrun"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T15:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the world of cryptocurrency, Dogecoin (DOGE) and Shiba Inu (SHIB) have long been at the forefront of the memecoin market, dominating the space with massive communities and considerable market capitalization. However, the rise of GoodEgg (GEGG), an innovative new A.I-driven dating...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Rises More Than 3% In 24 hours]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19899913/Shiba-Inu-Rises-More-Than-3-In-24-hours</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19899913/Shiba-Inu-Rises-More-Than-3-In-24-hours"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T15:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past 24 hours, Shiba Inu's (CRYPTO: SHIB) price has risen 3.24% to $0.000014. This continues its positive trend over the past week where it has experienced a 5.0% gain, moving from $0.000013 to its current price. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance BNB Traders Take Position in New A.I Dating Cryptocurrrency Priced $0.00021, BNB Profits To Be Made]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19899827/Binance-BNB-Traders-Take-Position-in-New-AI-Dating-Cryptocurrrency-Priced-000021-BNB-Profits-To-Be-Made</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19899827/Binance-BNB-Traders-Take-Position-in-New-AI-Dating-Cryptocurrrency-Priced-000021-BNB-Profits-To-Be-Made"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cryptocurrency market continues to evolve, and savvy investors are always on the lookout for the next big opportunity. Recently, Binance Coin (BNB) traders have taken notice of GoodEgg (GEGG), a new AI-powered dating cryptocurrency. With BNB trading profits, these traders are looking to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sky Proposes Full Offboarding of Wrapped Bitcoin Due to Justin Sun Controversy]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19899829/Sky-Proposes-Full-Offboarding-of-Wrapped-Bitcoin-Due-to-Justin-Sun-Controversy</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19899829/Sky-Proposes-Full-Offboarding-of-Wrapped-Bitcoin-Due-to-Justin-Sun-Controversy"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T14:58:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sky (formerly Maker) plans to remove Wrapped Bitcoin ($WBTC) as collateral due to concerns over Justin Sun's involvement in the asset’s restructuring. Key points: Proposal from BA Labs: Sky is considering fully offboarding $WBTC. Justin Sun's alleged control: Concerns about Sun’s hidden...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Bitcoin Follow Alts?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19899865/Will-Bitcoin-Follow-Alts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19899865/Will-Bitcoin-Follow-Alts"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T14:56:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We've got a wealth of free resources to help you master the art of trading. See how we can help at https://www.chartguys.com/discover-more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy Just Bought Another $1.1 Billion Worth of Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249319</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249319/microstrategy-just-bought-another-1-1-billion-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T14:54:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Saylor's software firm MicroStrategy now holds over $14 billion worth of Bitcoin after four years of buying up BTC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will McCurdy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon's POL (MATIC) Token Spikes 15% on Binance Listing]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e745ce1919d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/09/13/polygons-pol-matic-token-spikes-15-on-binance-listing/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T14:46:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon introduced last week the upgraded version the network's token, POL, migrating from its longstanding token MATIC with some tokenomics changes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken Pushes for Jury Trial in SEC Lawsuit, Rails Against 'Crypto Asset Securities' Claims]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249313</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249313/kraken-pushes-for-jury-trial-in-sec-lawsuit-rails-against-crypto-asset-securities-claims"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T14:30:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken accused the SEC of blocking efforts to register or cooperate, saying they were "stonewalled" by inconsistent rulings and guidance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vismaya V</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Political Prediction Markets :Why Kalshi's Court Victory Matters]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e745cef2596</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/opinion/2024/09/13/us-political-prediction-markets-why-kalshis-court-victory-matters/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T14:10:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If it turns out that the judge's ruling preempts the CFTC’s proposed rulemaking, election event contracts may now be completely legal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aaron Brogan, Matthew Homer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu vs GoodEgg: Crypto Experts Settle On GEGG To 100X In 2024 As Shiba Inu Faces Decline]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e745cef5796</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-vs-goodegg-crypto-experts-settle-on-gegg-to-100x-in-2024-as-shiba-inu-faces-decline/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T14:08:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB) has been a household name in the meme cryptocurrency space, but recent market trends are signaling potential struggles for the popular coin. Over the last 24 hours, Shiba Inu (SHIB) has seen its burn rate drop dramatically, with only 2.5 million SHIB being transferred to burn wallets, marking a burn rate decrease of nearly 20%. This substantial drop in burns may be directly linked to the slowing activity on Shibarium, Shiba Inu (SHIB)’s Layer 2 blockchain.
 
In contrast to its previous massive 8,193% increase in burns just days ago, the current trend presents concerns. Shibarium, once lauded as a significant contributor to SHIB burns, has seen transaction counts dip. Although Shibarium transactions surged by 187% in a brief window, the count still pales compared to the hig…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GoodEgg A.I Dating Platform Gains Major Solana Whale Investment As GEGG Presale Raises $250K In 24hrs]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e745cef5792</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/goodegg-a-i-dating-platform-gains-major-solana-whale-investment-as-gegg-presale-raises-250k-in-24hrs/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T14:08:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The rapidly evolving cryptocurrency space is always full of surprises, and this time, GoodEgg (GEGG), a future-focused A.I-powered dating platform, has become the center of attention. In just 24 hours, GoodEgg’s presale raised an impressive $250,000, signaling massive investor interest in its innovative approach to merging social interaction with blockchain technology. What’s more, Solana (SOL) whales have taken notice, adding GoodEgg to their portfolios as they prepare for a potential market disruption.
 
Solana (SOL) Stability Amid FTX Uncertainty 
In the world of cryptocurrency, Solana (SOL) is a force to be reckoned with. Known for its high-speed blockchain and strong community support, Solana (SOL) has managed to hold its ground despite market challenges. Recent data shows that FTX, a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana vs A.I Cryptocurrency GoodEgg (GEGG): SOL Investors Add Future A.I Dating Platform To Long Term Holdings]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e745cef5791</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/solana-vs-a-i-cryptocurrency-goodegg-gegg-sol-investors-add-future-a-i-dating-platform-to-long-term-holdings/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T14:08:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cryptocurrency market continues to experience shifts, and Solana (SOL) remains one of the key players making headlines. With its innovative technology and strong network performance, Solana (SOL) has attracted a wide array of traders and investors, including those looking to diversify their portfolios. One of the latest opportunities capturing their attention is GoodEgg (GEGG), an A.I-powered dating platform that is making waves in the crypto space. Priced at just $0.00021, GoodEgg (GEGG) is seen as a future contender for a Tier 1 exchange listing in 2024, with the potential for explosive growth.
 
Solana’s Impressive On-Chain Activity 
Solana (SOL) has been showing remarkable on-chain activity, with a tripling of daily active addresses (DAA) in recent weeks. This surge in activity, ac…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Recovers After CPI Data Drop, But Is It Sustainable?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e745cef578f</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-recovers-cpi-sustainable/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T14:08:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following the release of the Consumer Price Index (CPI) data for the month of August, the Bitcoin price saw a major rebound. From trending around the $55,000 level, the price has since recovered and bulls continue to fight to turn the $58,000 resistance into support. However, despite the strength being shown by Bitcoin during this time, there is still skepticism surrounding the recovery. Mainly, the questions have been on whether this is a true recovery or if the BTC price is headed for further decline.
 
CPI Brings Fresh Hope
 
The Consumer Price Index (CPI) data represents how much consumers are paying for consumer goods and services at different times. Basically, it calculates the change in the price of these goods and services, showing whether purchasing power has gone up on down.
 
Fo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HNT Investors Purchase GoodEgg Presale With Helium Profits; GEGG Raises 250k In Hours]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e745cef578d</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/hnt-investors-purchase-goodegg-presale-with-helium-profits-gegg-raises-250k-in-hours/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T14:08:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Helium (HNT) continues its strong rise toward the $9 mark, savvy investors are using their gains to diversify their portfolios. The latest investment avenue catching their attention is GoodEgg (GEGG), an A.I-powered dating platform that raised an impressive $250,000 in just a few hours during its presale. With Helium (HNT) establishing itself as a major player in the Internet of Things (IoT) sector, its investors are now exploring new, innovative projects like GoodEgg (GEGG) to capitalize on the booming decentralized finance (DeFi) ecosystem.
 
Helium’s Ascent and Profitable Gains 
The recent performance of Helium (HNT) has been nothing short of remarkable. As the token approaches $9, driven by the rapid expansion of its decentralized IoT network, investors have been reaping substantial…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Helium Gains Momentum As HNT Investors Add New A.I Dating Cryptocurrency To Holdings With Helium Profits]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e745cef578c</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/helium-gains-momentum-as-hnt-investors-add-new-a-i-dating-cryptocurrency-to-holdings-with-helium-profits/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T14:08:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2024 has proven to be a significant year for Helium (HNT) as it experienced its first breakout past the $10.00 mark since 2022, sparking renewed interest in the decentralized network that powers the Internet of Things (IoT). This rise in price has not only invigorated the market but also attracted investors to new and emerging projects like GoodEgg (GEGG), an A.I-driven dating cryptocurrency platform. With GoodEgg (GEGG)‘s presale raising $250,000 in just 24 hours, it’s clear that Helium (HNT) investors are seeking innovative ways to diversify their profits.
 
Helium’s Price Surge and Future Potential 
The price trajectory for Helium (HNT) in 2024 has been one of volatility and excitement. Surpassing $10.00 was a major milestone, and although the token has since retraced to $6.33, the over…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Faces Challenges as Price Stagnates: Coinbase Report]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e745ce8277d</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ethereum-faces-challenges-as-price-stagnates-coinbase-report/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T14:01:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) has recently struggled in comparison to its peers, according to a report by Coinbase Institutional. The analysis suggests that market dynamics, network activity, and inflationary factors are influencing the cryptocurrency’s current performance. Coinbase Institutional: Ethereum Lags Behind Crypto Peers In its September 2024 outlook, Coinbase researchers pointed out that the cryptocurrency market is […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Money, Get Away: Fake Celebrity Meme Coin Linked to Pink Floyd and Neymar Is 'Saddest Launch' Ever]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249290</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249290/money-get-away-fake-celebrity-meme-coin-linked-to-pink-floyd-and-neymar-is-saddest-launch-ever"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T13:45:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["The celebrity meta is officially dead," Bubblemaps CEO says after celeb-pushed token fails to break $20,000 market cap.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinDesk 20 Performance Update: ICP and RNDR Each Drop 3.6%, Leading Index Lower]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e745ceb5246</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2024/09/13/coindesk-20-performance-update-icp-and-rndr-each-drop-36-leading-index-lower/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T13:40:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CoinDesk 20 inched lower, despite 10.6% gains by Polygon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CoinDesk Indices, Tracy Stephens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Dogecoin Community Join The Gambling ICO Mpeppe (MPEPE) Market Strategist Foresees 150x Gains]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e745ceb68c5</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/the-dogecoin-community-join-the-gambling-ico-mpeppe-mpepe-market-strategist-foresees-150x-gains/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T13:39:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Dogecoin (DOGE) community, known for its enthusiasm and unity, has found its next big investment: Mpeppe (MPEPE). With Mpeppe (MPEPE) launching a new gambling ICO, excitement is building among Dogecoin (DOGE) holders as market strategists predict potential 150x gains. The unique features of Mpeppe (MPEPE) and its innovative approach to gambling have caught the attention of the crypto world, making it a popular choice for those looking to diversify.
 
Mpeppe (MPEPE)’s Crypto Gambling Platform: What Makes It Stand Out? 
Mpeppe (MPEPE) is revolutionizing the online gambling landscape by integrating cryptocurrency advantages into its platform. Enhanced security and privacy are at the forefront of its offerings. Unlike traditional payment methods, Mpeppe (MPEPE)’s use of blockchain technolo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[After Dogecoin (DOGE)’s Recent Performance Can They Keep Up Mpeppe (MPEPE)’s Rapid Growth and Unique Features]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e745ceb68c4</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/after-dogecoin-doges-recent-performance-can-they-keep-up-mpeppe-mpepes-rapid-growth-and-unique-features/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T13:39:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin (DOGE) has become one of the most well-known meme coins in the crypto world, thanks to its vibrant community and impressive performance. Over the years, DOGE has delivered significant returns for its investors and gained mainstream recognition. However, with new players like Mpeppe (MPEPE) emerging and rapidly growing, the question arises: Can Dogecoin (DOGE) keep up with the innovative and fast-paced features of Mpeppe (MPEPE)?
 
Mpeppe (MPEPE)’s Integration of DeFi Protocols: A Game-Changer for Users 
Mpeppe (MPEPE) is not just another meme coin; it is positioning itself as a serious contender in the decentralized finance (DeFi) space. By integrating DeFi protocols, Mpeppe (MPEPE) offers users access to a wide range of financial services such as lending, borrowing, trading, and …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Helium Investors Become Bullish With New Casino Coin Before Price Increases To $0.00235]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e745ceb68c0</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/helium-investors-become-bullish-with-new-casino-coin-before-price-increases-to-0-00235/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T13:39:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mpeppe (MPEPE) is catching the attention of investors, especially those who have already profited from Helium (HNT). As Mpeppe (MPEPE)‘s presale inches closer to a price increase to $0.00235, the coin’s exciting features and strong community backing have sparked increased interest from both seasoned and new investors. Here’s why this could be the next big gamble in the crypto space.
 
MPEPE: A Gambling Coin with Massive Potential 
Meme cryptocurrencies have a reputation for taking the market by storm, and Mpeppe (MPEPE) is no different. What sets Mpeppe (MPEPE) apart is its integration into online gambling, offering its users a dual benefit of trading in the token and engaging in a decentralized gambling ecosystem.
 
Helium (HNT) investors are particularly bullish on Mpeppe (MPEPE) because…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Are Today’s ‘X Empire’ Elon Musk Game Daily Combo and Riddle]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241078</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/todays-musk-empire-stock-exchange-daily-combo"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T13:15:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking for the X Empire daily combo and riddle solution for Friday, September 13? Here are the latest boosts for the Telegram game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Are Today’s ‘Rocky Rabbit’ Enigma and SuperSet Daily Combo Solutions]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=245981</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/here-are-todays-rocky-rabbit-enigma-superset-daily-combo-solutions"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T13:10:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can earn millions of free in-game coins in the Telegram game Rocky Rabbit. Here are the solutions for Friday, September 13.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Are Today's ‘Hamster Kombat’ Daily Combo and Cipher Code]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=239305</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/todays-hamster-kombat-daily-combo-cipher-code"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T13:05:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking for the daily combo and cipher code for Friday, September 13? Here’s what you need to make bank in Telegram game Hamster Kombat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Ethereum Founder Vitalik Buterin Defines 'Stage 1+' Layer-2 Networks]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249281</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249281/how-ethereum-founder-vitalik-buterin-defines-stage-1-layer-2-networks"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T12:43:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“It doesn't matter if I invested, or if you're my friend; stage 1 or bust,” he said in a recent tweet. Here's what that means.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will McCurdy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Stagnates as Analysts Forecast Potential Bottom For Ethereum Before End of Year]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249278</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249278/bitcoin-stagnates-as-analysts-forecast-potential-bottom-for-ethereum-before-end-of-year"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T10:11:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Traders should monitor medium-term reversal indicators such as RSI and Stochastics," to catch signs of assets being oversold, said 10X Research.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI Launches New ‘01’ Model That Outperforms ChatGPT-4o]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249227</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249227/openai-launches-new-01-model-that-outperforms-chatgpt-4o"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T01:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AI developer said it is “resetting the counter” for its product names as its latest set of models excel across its tests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bill to Fight AI Deepfakes Reaches US House as Entertainment Industry Cheers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249254</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249254/entertainment-industry-celebrates-as-no-fakes-act-moves-to-congress"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T00:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With backing from both parties, the legislation follows the intrduction of its counterpart in the U.S. Senate earlier this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Hamster Kombat’ and ‘Catizen’ Telegram Token Demand Could Disrupt TON, Devs Warn]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249203</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249203/hamster-kombat-catizen-token-airdrops-ton-issues"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T23:01:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Airdrop season on The Open Network is nearly here, and developers admit that demand could get the better of the Telegram-linked network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Napolitano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adobe Pushes Into Generative Video With Firefly Amid AI Controversy]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249181</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249181/adobe-pushes-into-generative-video-with-firefly-amid-ai-controversy"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T22:43:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adobe’s Firefly Video Model, set for release in beta later this year, introduces new generative AI capabilities to its Premiere Pro video suite.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Magic Muffins’ Game Launches on Telegram to Take on ‘Hamster Kombat’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249215</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249215/magic-muffins-game-telegram-take-on-hamster-kombat"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T22:15:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earn Alliance’s Telegram game Magic Muffins delivers a tap-based combat experience that’s tied to the platform’s upcoming ALLY token launch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kalshi's US Election Prediction Markets Go Live as CFTC Seeks Appeal]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249204</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249204/kalshi-us-election-prediction-markets-go-live-cftc-seeks-appeal"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T21:38:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Legal and regulated U.S. prediction markets platform Kalshi has launched its first election pools after the court win over the CFTC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Napolitano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Dollar Is Taking Over the World Thanks to Stablecoins: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249197</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249197/stablecoins-drive-us-dollar-dominance-globally"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T21:16:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Survey data shows that stablecoins are inciting net flows into dollar instruments where U.S. dollar banking is unavailable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Wrapped Bitcoin Sparks Pushback from Justin Sun]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249189</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249189/coinbase-wrapped-bitcoin-sparks-pushback-from-justin-sun"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T20:31:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The TRON founder's connection to  WBTC has driven interest in alternatives, and Sun is not a fan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Hamster Kombat’ Will Give Out Billions of Tokens via Binance in Telegram Game Airdrop]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249171</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249171/hamster-kombat-give-out-billions-tokens-binance-telegram-game-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T18:54:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance users will be able to earn a share of 3 billion HMSTR in the lead-up to Hamster Kombat’s token launch on TON.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana’s Pump.Fun Has Launched Millions of Tokens—Fewer Than 100 Are Worth Much at All]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249107</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249107/fewer-than-100-pump-fun-tokens-above-1m-market-cap-amid-meme-coin-lull"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T17:55:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pump.fun is “stale,” traders believe, as the protocol fails to keep more than 100 tokens above a $1 million market cap.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fuse Plugs Solana Token Into Energy Distribution DePIN Play]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=248985</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/248985/fuse-plugs-solana-token-energy-distribution-depin-play"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T17:32:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With a new $12 million fundraising round, the renewable energy company aims to reward customers for supporting the power grid.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[European Central Bank Drops Interest Rates Again as Bitcoin, Stocks Bounce Back]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249154</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249154/european-central-bank-drops-interest-rates-again-bitcoin-up"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T16:58:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Fed is likely to drop rates next, potentially setting up Bitcoin for another "Uptober" after a shaky start to September.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 198 - THE GREAT APE HEIST!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/RJ6YcMxP/fomo-hour-198-the-great-ape-heist</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/RJ6YcMxP/fomo-hour-198-the-great-ape-heist"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T16:28:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto rises with stocks after CPI falls again. Bitfinex BTC longs continue to grow. SUI again leads L1s, up 18%. FTX estate unstakes $24m SOL, still has $943m. Binance introduces SOL liquid staking. SWIFT introduces infrastructure for RWA transfers. Pendle launches Bitcoin yield pools. UK makes crypto legal property. India leads crypto adoption for second year. Vitalik won’t advertise L2s with multi-sig security. Based rollups seen as alternative future for ETH. Blockchain music start up raises $50m. Ford & Toyota file blockchain patents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale Debuts XRP Trust Following Bitcoin and Ethereum ETF Launches]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249124</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249124/grayscale-debuts-xrp-trust-bitcoin-ethereum-etfs"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T16:12:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto asset manager Grayscale launched the XRP Trust, a new product giving investors exposure to the Ripple-aligned asset.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Eve Frontier’ Survival Game Is Being Built on Ethereum, CCP Reveals]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249126</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249126/eve-frontier-survival-game-ethereum-ccp-reveals"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T15:57:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eve Online maker CCP Games has rebranded Project Awakening, which is being built on Ethereum layer-2 network Redstone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Will Hit New High Price If Trump or Harris Wins, Says Analyst—But Bettors Favor Kamala]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249073</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249073/bitcoin-hit-new-high-price-trump-or-harris-wins-bettors-favor-kamala"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T14:07:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kamala Harris has pulled ahead of Donald Trump on Polymarket, but Standard Chartered sees a new Bitcoin peak if either candidate wins the election.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gary Gensler Under Fire for Alleged Political Favoritism in SEC Appointments]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249095</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249095/gary-gensler-under-fire-for-alleged-political-favoritism-in-sec-appointments"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T13:47:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["The SEC appears to be unlawfully considering an applicant’s political ideology when hiring bureaucrats," the lawmakers wrote.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vismaya V</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[eToro Will Only Offer Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Bitcoin Cash in US After Settling SEC Charges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249074</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249074/etoro-only-offer-bitcoin-ethereum-bitcoin-cash-us-settling-sec-charges"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T13:19:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC announced that eToro has settled securities charges, and will pay a penalty alongside curtailing offered crypto assets in the U.S.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward,André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gameloft Reveals 'Claynosaurz' Mobile Game Based on Solana NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249031</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249031/gameloft-claynosaurz-mobile-game-solana-nfts"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T13:01:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana NFT collection Claynosaurz is expanding into gaming via a team-up with mobile giant Gameloft. Here's what to expect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erika Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood Is Well Positioned as Investors Increasingly Prefer Crypto, Says Bernstein]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249053</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249053/robinhood-is-well-positioned-as-investors-increasingly-prefer-crypto-says-bernstein"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T12:37:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The way younger investors prefer to invest will "determine what the financial platforms of the future look like,” analysts write.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Launches Wrapped Bitcoin Token Following BitGo WBTC Controversy]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=248997</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/248997/coinbase-launches-wrapped-bitcoin-token-following-bitgo-wbtc-controversy"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T11:01:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The leading exchange puts forward cbBTC as a formidable new option in the DeFi space.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Climbs But Experts Say Bullish Sentiment Is Waning]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249039</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249039/bitcoin-climbs-above-58000-but-experts-say-bullish-sentiment-is-waning"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T10:58:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Bitcoin’s bullish momentum appears to be fading," says a lead analyst at CEX.IO.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fomo Hour 197 - Debate Disaster]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rMxl1cgJ/fomo-hour-197-debate-disaster</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rMxl1cgJ/fomo-hour-197-debate-disaster"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T19:15:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto falls slightly after Presidential debate. Exchanges see highest BTC outflow since May. Be wary of Yen move for BTC: Hayes. SOL active addresses hit ATH. At least 5 massive SOL announcements coming: Mert. Binomial to introduce restaking on BNB. Indonesian exchange hacked for $22m. Atomic Wallet wins lawsuit over $100m hack. Lawyers argue Ellison shouldn’t go to jail. ENS integrated with Venmo & PayPal. Galaxy & State Street launch 3 crypto ETFs. Standard Chartered begins UAE crypto custody. AAVE leads resurgence in DeFi coins.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 196 - THE INFLOWS RETURN!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/e9F8zYRp/fomo-hour-196-the-inflows-return</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/e9F8zYRp/fomo-hour-196-the-inflows-return"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T22:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETFs: +$29m, ETH ETFs: -$5m. BTC rallies, ETF has first inflow in 9 trading days. BTC may have put in first higher low in 6 months. Saylor predicts $13m price for BTC. Wealth advisors quickly adopting BTC: BitWise CEO. Binance among few firms to get Indonesia license. Spot trading on CEXs up 30% in August. SEC made $4.68bn from crypto firms in 2023. $5.6bn lost to scams in 2023. XRP security status may be unchallenged in appeal. EtherFi announces credit card on Scroll. Base has more DEX users than other L2s combined. Tether & Tron create taskforce against crime. TIA still only making $585 in daily fees. WLD investigated by Singapore police.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 195 - CAN WE GET A BOUNCE?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/m7JRnQJc/fomo-hour-195-can-we-get-a-bounce</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/m7JRnQJc/fomo-hour-195-can-we-get-a-bounce"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T22:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC: 55.3k (+2%), ETH: 2320 (+1%), SOL: 130 (0%). Top Gainers: FTM, TAO, BTT, AAVE, TON, ATOM. Crypto mini-bounce continues, BTC reclaims $55k. BTC RSI hits lowest level since July 2021. Bitfinex longs continue to grow aggressively. BTC hashrate hits another ATH. BTC could hit $90k on Trump election: Bernstein. BlackRock settles intraday BTC trades off-chain. Spot BTC ETFs have been a failure: Bianco. Power giant Tepco explores Bitcoin mining. ETH Foundation & Vitalik continue to sell ETH. Farcaster DAU’s down 95%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Presenting MYRIAD, a prediction market and digital media engagement ecosystem]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/Rwj71okY/presenting-myriad-a-prediction-market-and-digital-media-engagement-ecosystem</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/Rwj71okY/presenting-myriad-a-prediction-market-and-digital-media-engagement-ecosystem"/>
        <updated>2024-09-09T14:28:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Media company DASTAN, the parent company of Decrypt and Rug Radio, is embarking on the next stage of its evolution with the launch of MYRIAD, a prediction market and engagement ecosystem that aims to “transform the digital media landscape.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 194 - ARE NFTS BACK?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5oNbWn5H/fomo-hour-194-are-nfts-back</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5oNbWn5H/fomo-hour-194-are-nfts-back"/>
        <updated>2024-09-07T12:02:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto weak after continued ETF outflows. Durov breaks silence, TON bounces 3%. Telegram will start moderating private chats. Hayes & Brandt flip bearish on BTC. Coinbase shares hit 7 month lows. 90% of crypto firm applications rejected in UK. Japan’s 3 largest banks to trial stablecoins. Trump promises again to embrace crypto. INJ launches BlackRock BUIDL index. DWF to launch synthetic stablecoin. Vitalik to donate all L2 tokens to charity. Most VCs in crypto ‘will disappear’.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Researcher Explains Meme Coin Mania]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tC2Oz5H9/crypto-researcher-explains-meme-coin-mania</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tC2Oz5H9/crypto-researcher-explains-meme-coin-mania"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T18:59:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Head of Research at CoinMarketCap, Alice Liu, breaks down the highs and lows of meme coin mania in 2024. We’ve seen meme coins like Dogwifhat (WIF) soar to huge market caps and we’ve seen political meme coins crash as the candidate drops out (BODEN). Liu explains the data behind all of this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 193 - NVIDIA DROPS-OFF]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LxNEmmjX/fomo-hour-193-nvidia-drops-off</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LxNEmmjX/fomo-hour-193-nvidia-drops-off"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T17:05:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto falls on macro wobble, Yen fears. OI wiped in BTC drop to $56k, funding negative. Altcoins down 13% YTD, stablecoin supply up 30%. BTC mining profitability at record low: JP Morgan. FBI says North Korea targeting BTC ETF issuers. Trump family to launch DeFi project on ETH. Trump project linked to AVAX’s Dough Finance. Trump family members hacked during launch. AI coins underperform after Nvidia investigation. MATIC upgrade to POL begins. TON falls as Telegram faces issues in many countries. VC funding & BTC correlation breaks down. We have entered crypto’s ‘corporate phase’. Gensler will leave regardless of election: Ripple CEO. Harris campaign has asked Coinbase for advice. Penpie DeFi project hacked for $27m. Galois Capital settles with SEC over FTX custody.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 192 - WTF IS ETHERVISTA]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/xOt72jL2/fomo-hour-192-wtf-is-ethervista</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/xOt72jL2/fomo-hour-192-wtf-is-ethervista"/>
        <updated>2024-09-03T19:24:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OI continues to rise as BTC stabilises. BTC still best performing assets class this year. FTX to distribute $16bn to creditors starting in Q4. Qatar introduces regulatory framework for crypto. ETH L1s fees down 90%, L2 activity ATH. Base hits 14m monthly users, many may be Sybil. ETH is in death spiral: Krueger. SOL to see significant unlocks in Q1. Japan considers dropping crypto tax to 20%. Rate cuts won’t help BTC: Hayes. BTC should double after rate cuts: Tapiero. Mr 100 linked back to Upbit wallet. WazirX hacker moves funds to Tornado. SUI to launch handheld gaming device. Sony & PYTH announce collaboration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Millionaire Explains How Neiro United Meme Coins]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LjhyvMyI/dogecoin-millionaire-explains-how-neiro-united-meme-coins</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LjhyvMyI/dogecoin-millionaire-explains-how-neiro-united-meme-coins"/>
        <updated>2024-08-31T13:16:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kabosu, the dog many know as Doge and the mascot of Dogecoin, sadly passed away earlier this year. Its owner later adopted another Shiba Inu called Neiro which caused a long blockchain civil war with multiple tokens battling it out for liquidity. Now a month later SlumDOGE, the man who became a millionaire off Dogecoin (but never sold), explains why Neiro is a moment for the dog coin community to unite.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 191 - CRYPTO STABLE]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/VM5OAovR/fomo-hour-191-crypto-stable</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/VM5OAovR/fomo-hour-191-crypto-stable"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T17:27:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETFs: -$72m, ETH ETFs: -$2m. BTC weekly volatility returns to multi-year lows. BlackRock BTC ETF sees first outflow in months. ETH dominance hits 4-year low. Vitalik linked wallet sells $2m ETH. Bukele talks up BTC impact in Time interview. CBoE files for ETH & BTC ETF options. Elon & Tesla win DOGE manipulation lawsuit. Macron denies inviting Durov to France. Trump promises to make US the ‘crypto capital’. Trump advertises Liberty Financial DeFi project. DeFi mindshare continues to grow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 190 - OPENSEA VS SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/g3scPNlK/fomo-hour-190-opensea-vs-sec</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/g3scPNlK/fomo-hour-190-opensea-vs-sec"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T16:17:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC: 59.7k (0%), ETH: 2545 (0%), SOL: 146 (-1%). Top Gainers: HNT, IMX, ICP, ADA, KCS. BTC ETFs: -$105m, ETH ETFs: +$6m. Bitcoin in tight liquidation range, ETH outperforms. ETH ETF sees first in flow in 10 days. Funding rates all turn negative. Mr 100 buys 500 BTC in dip. France formally charges Durov, can’t leave country. TON jumps 6% after Durov release. TON faces another outage related to DOGS. AI coins fall after Nvidia earnings. Crypto payments about to soar: Armstrong. Binance denies freezing Palestinian accounts. CryptoCom & Standard Chartered partner.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 189 - TRUMP LAUNCHES MORE NFTS]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/xUt5dSH4/fomo-hour-189-trump-launches-more-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/xUt5dSH4/fomo-hour-189-trump-launches-more-nfts"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T20:05:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETFs: -$127m, ETH ETFs: -$3m. BTC hits $58k after ETF outflows, then bounces. BTC sees largest exchange outflow in a year. Divergence between BTC & stocks grows. TON stops producing blocks briefly, price bounces. TON outage linked to DOGS launch. Maker DAO rebrands as Sky. USDS upgrade from DAI will have freezing function. Robinhood readds SOL support. SEC charges 2 brothers with $60m crypto scam. Nasdaq pitches options on BTC ETFs. Full-time open source devs under 8k in crypto. Crypto owners more likely to be ‘psychopaths’.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 188 - TON CONTINUES TO FALL]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/UhURASRQ/fomo-hour-188-ton-continues-to-fall</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/UhURASRQ/fomo-hour-188-ton-continues-to-fall"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T16:36:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock ETF sees biggest inflow in 35 days. BTC ETFs have 12 straight days of inflows. ETH ETFs have 8 straight days of outflows. ETH/BTC ratio continues to hit new lows. Russia to start using crypto for trade this week. Stablecoin TVL hits ATH of $168bn. Durov faces several serious charges in France. Telegram also under investigation in India. TRX flips TON, enters top 10 crypto coins. Crypto is the currency of AI: Naval. 84k new crypto millionaires created this year. SEC lawsuit against Kraken to proceed to trial. Aave proposes integration with BlackRock BUIDL. Celsius has repaid $2.5bn in assets so far.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 187 - AI TOKENS LEADING]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/M7IhK60K/fomo-hour-187-ai-tokens-leading</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/M7IhK60K/fomo-hour-187-ai-tokens-leading"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T16:11:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI tokens lead ahead of Nvidia earnings. Crypto funds saw $533m inflows last week. BTC ‘bull market’ back on in IFP index. BTC close to ‘parabolic zone’ soon. Many coins ‘flipping back to bullish’ indicators. Open Interest begins to creep back up again. Binance Labs to focus on AI investments. 51 L2s now built on OP stack alone. Some exchanges rejected for Hong Kong license. Vitalik questions DeFi yields in crypto. New malware steals crypto on MacOS. Avalanche Discord hacked after Polygon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Meme Coin That Became a REAL Religion!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/szDuQcIw/the-meme-coin-that-became-a-real-religion</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/szDuQcIw/the-meme-coin-that-became-a-real-religion"/>
        <updated>2024-08-24T17:42:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pastor Kelby created a meme coin on Pumpdotfun which has since registered a church and developed its own religious theories and philosophies. Twice a day Kelby heads a sermon on Twitter where he spreads lessons from books that have personally helped him achieve happiness.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 186 - AVAX LEADS PUMP]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JRqyT8vz/fomo-hour-186-avax-leads-pump</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JRqyT8vz/fomo-hour-186-avax-leads-pump"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T17:14:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETFs: +$65m, ETH ETFs: -$1m. Crypto stays range-bound ahead of Powell speech. Russia plans stablecoins of BRICS countries. El Salvador buys 162 BTC with daily buys. AVAX up 15% as Grayscale launches trust. Tron removes 12k BTC from USDD reserves. Trump promotes crypto DeFi project. Crypto half of corporate political donations. Tether abandons plan to launch its own blockchain. Sony backed L2 set to launch in weeks. Babylon launches BTC staking. CZ leaves prison for ‘halfway house’. PayPal & Anchorage partner for bank crypto rewards. Bitcoin mining market worth $74bn: JP Morgan. Bitfarms buys Stronghold in ‘strategic defence’.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 185 - KAMALA 'SUPPORTS' CRYPTO?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/u48y6NBU/fomo-hour-185-kamala-supports-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/u48y6NBU/fomo-hour-185-kamala-supports-crypto"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T17:14:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETFs: +$40m, ETH ETFs: -$18m. BTC breaks channel, ripe for ‘short squeeze’. BTC OI rises $1.3bn post Fed minutes. Kamala ‘supports crypto policies’ says advisor. Vitalik ‘bull posts’ ETH. Story Protocol raises $80m for L1. WazirX halts open orders after problems with Rupee. Coinbase & Ripple lead political donations. Salame claims government reneged on plea deal. EigenLayer team claimed coins despite being in US.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 184 - PUNKS ARE FLYING!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ILpzl0Wk/fomo-hour-184-punks-are-flying</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ILpzl0Wk/fomo-hour-184-punks-are-flying"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T17:21:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETFs: +$88m, ETH ETFs: -$7m. BTC funding negative in ‘short squeeze’ setup. BTC dominance up 18% in 2 years. TRX leads L1s as memecoin activity soars. Chance of SOL ETF is zero in 2024: Bloomberg. Another SOL ETF approved in Brazil. Binance & CZ face new class action lawsuit. Tether to launch UAE-Dirham stablecoin. Mt Gox moves $700m in BTC. CRV founder faces backlash on DAO proposal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 183 - WE ARE NOW SHITCOINING ON TRON]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/GMxAt3Zm/fomo-hour-183-we-are-now-shitcoining-on-tron</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/GMxAt3Zm/fomo-hour-183-we-are-now-shitcoining-on-tron"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T17:54:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto follows stocks higher, BTC rallies to $61k. SOL funds saw largest weekly outflow ever. Tether mints another $1bn on Tron. SEC blocked SOL ETF from CBoE. China classifies crypto for money laundering. DNC platform doesn’t mention crypto. Rumours Gensler may be Treasury Secretary pick. Chrome extension ‘Bull Checker’ leads to exploits. Genesis-linked wallet hacked for $238m. ADA drops out of the top 10 coins.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>