<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-04-23T08:17:54.496Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-04-23T08:17:54.496Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BAYC Creator Yuga Labs Emerges Victorious In Copyright Case – A Win For Web3?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e751f79182a</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bayc-creator-victorious-in-copyright-case/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-23T07:37:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yuga Labs, creator of the famous Bored Ape Yacht Club (BAYC) NFT collection, has claimed legal victory in its trademark infringement case against Ryder Ripps and Jeremy Cahen. A federal judge, in a pre-trial summary judgment, declared that Yuga Labs is entitled to an injunction and damages from the duo.
 
Yuga Labs described the court judgment as not a just triumph for them but “a win for the entire Web3 industry”.
 
 
BAYC Creator Yuga Labs Wins Copyright Case
 
The RR/BAYC NFT collection is a creation that contains identical copies of Bored Apes and used marketing material similar to that of the Bored Ape Yacht Club. According to Ripps and Cahen, the RR/BAYC NFT collection is merely a satirical and critical response to Yuga Labs. The duo claims that the Bored Ape NFTs depict racist and s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Opeyemi Sule</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BAYC Creator Yuga Labs Emerges Victorious In Copyright Case – A Win For Web3?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18175614/BAYC-Creator-Yuga-Labs-Emerges-Victorious-In-Copyright-Case-A-Win-For-Web3</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18175614/BAYC-Creator-Yuga-Labs-Emerges-Victorious-In-Copyright-Case-A-Win-For-Web3"/>
        <updated>2023-04-23T07:30:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yuga Labs, creator of the famous Bored Ape Yacht Club (BAYC) NFT collection, has claimed legal victory in its trademark infringement case against Ryder Ripps and Jeremy Cahen. A federal judge, in a pre-trial summary judgment, declared that Yuga Labs is entitled to an injunction and damages from...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google DeepMind restructuring aims to deliver next-gen AI breakthroughs]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18175403/Google-DeepMind-restructuring-aims-to-deliver-next-gen-AI-breakthroughs</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18175403/Google-DeepMind-restructuring-aims-to-deliver-next-gen-AI-breakthroughs"/>
        <updated>2023-04-23T07:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new unit, Google Deepmind, was formed by merging the Brain team from Google Research and DeepMind, a London-based AI company Google had purchased in 2014.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to play and earn in CryptoKitties]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18175404/How-to-play-and-earn-in-CryptoKitties</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18175404/How-to-play-and-earn-in-CryptoKitties"/>
        <updated>2023-04-23T07:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CryptoKitties is a blockchain-based game where players can buy, sell and breed digital cats with unique attributes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trader Who Recently Unloaded Crypto Positions Warns Repeat of 2021 Bitcoin Meltdown – Here’s His Downside Target]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18175179/Trader-Who-Recently-Unloaded-Crypto-Positions-Warns-Repeat-of-2021-Bitcoin-Meltdown-Heres-His-Downside-Target</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18175179/Trader-Who-Recently-Unloaded-Crypto-Positions-Warns-Repeat-of-2021-Bitcoin-Meltdown-Heres-His-Downside-Target"/>
        <updated>2023-04-23T07:04:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A crypto strategist who masterfully rode the crypto rally this year is issuing a warning, saying that a local top might be in for Bitcoin (BTC). Pseudonymous analyst DonAlt tells his 479,300 Twitter followers that he believes Bitcoin’s rally above $30,000 is a range deviation. According to the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russia to Work With Digital Currencies of Other Nations]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e751f65bcb6</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/russia-to-work-with-digital-currencies-of-other-nations/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-23T06:40:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The platform developed for the digital ruble will be able to operate with different state-issued digital currencies, the Bank of Russia said. Mechanisms for interaction with digital coins minted by the central banks of other countries are already under development, the monetary authority unveiled.
 
Digital Ruble Platform to Support Integration With Other CBDCs, Bank of Russia
 
The system underpinning the issuing and circulation of Russia’s central bank digital currency (CBDC) may well work with the digital legal tenders of other nations, representatives of the Russian monetary policy regulator indicated this week.
 
Speaking with Russian lawmakers, the central bank officials remarked that the matter still needs to be worked out but emphasized that various models for interaction between t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lubomir Tassev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trust Wallet Announces $170,000 Loss Due To Security Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e751f661be9</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/trust-wallet-announces-170000-loss-vulnerability/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-23T06:36:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Wallet provider Trust Wallet has reported a security vulnerability that led to the loss of $170,000 of user funds. According to a thread from their official Twitter handle, Trust Wallet states that an anonymous security researcher reported the security risk back in November 2022 through the company’s bug bounty program.
 
Based on this security report, Trust Wallet was informed of a WebAssembly vulnerability in their open-source library Wallet Core. Although the security risk has now been neutralized, Trust Wallet reports it did lead to two exploits that resulted in customers losing about $170,000.
 
According to the statement by the wallet service provider, all new wallet addresses created by browser extension between November 14 to November 23, 2022, are the main hosts of this vul…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Semilore Faleti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trust Wallet Announces $170,000 Loss Due To Security Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18174778/Trust-Wallet-Announces-170000-Loss-Due-To-Security-Vulnerability</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18174778/Trust-Wallet-Announces-170000-Loss-Due-To-Security-Vulnerability"/>
        <updated>2023-04-23T06:36:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Wallet provider Trust Wallet has reported a security vulnerability that led to the loss of $170,000 of user funds. According to a thread from their official Twitter handle, Trust Wallet states that an anonymous security researcher reported the security risk back in November 2022 through...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden's comms director barred from former crypto clients: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18174539/Bidens-comms-director-barred-from-former-crypto-clients-Report</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18174539/Bidens-comms-director-barred-from-former-crypto-clients-Report"/>
        <updated>2023-04-23T06:12:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized exchange UniSwap and venture capital firm Andressen Horowitz were revealed as former clients of LaBolt in a recently published public financial disclosure report.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Foundation exec weighs in on ‘safe’ memecoin, SEC’s crypto-regulations]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18174114/Dogecoin-Foundation-exec-weighs-in-on-safe-memecoin-SECs-crypto-regulations</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18174114/Dogecoin-Foundation-exec-weighs-in-on-safe-memecoin-SECs-crypto-regulations"/>
        <updated>2023-04-23T05:30:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin's "joke competition" to Bitcoin may have exempted it from being on the SEC radar. Nonetheless, its founding team suggests that it could displace many projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized Twitter Alternatives Bluesky and Nostr Are Growing, With Some Growing Pains]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137589</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137589/decentralized-twitter-alternatives-bluesky-and-nostr-are-growing-with-some-growing-pains"/>
        <updated>2023-04-23T05:26:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Early adopters are rejoicing in brand new social spaces, but wrestling with establishing new norms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized Twitter Alternatives Bluesky and Nostr Are Growing, With Some Growing Pains]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18174140/Decentralized-Twitter-Alternatives-Bluesky-and-Nostr-Are-Growing-With-Some-Growing-Pains</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18174140/Decentralized-Twitter-Alternatives-Bluesky-and-Nostr-Are-Growing-With-Some-Growing-Pains"/>
        <updated>2023-04-23T05:26:33.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[#Binance will resume the spot trailing stop order function on April 24, 2023, at 09:00 UTC.]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18174373/Binance-will-resume-the-spot-trailing-stop-order-function-on-April-24-2023-at-0900-UTC</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18174373/Binance-will-resume-the-spot-trailing-stop-order-function-on-April-24-2023-at-0900-UTC"/>
        <updated>2023-04-23T04:01:42.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China and Singapore team up to scale green and transition financing]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18173974/China-and-Singapore-team-up-to-scale-green-and-transition-financing</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18173974/China-and-Singapore-team-up-to-scale-green-and-transition-financing"/>
        <updated>2023-04-23T03:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[China and Singapore will collaborate “on concrete initiatives that will catalyze capital flows to support a credible and inclusive transition to a low carbon future for our countries and the region.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Burn Rate Spikes But Price Continues To Tank, But Why?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e751f6aceb8</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-burn-rate-spikes-but-price-continues-to-tank-but-why/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-23T03:42:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Shiba Inu community has continued its burning transactions in the past few days. Recently, more than 27 million SHIB tokens entered the dead wallet in six transactions. Shibburn data shows that one wallet burned 15 million out of the total tokens.
 
 
The SHIB burn tracker Shibburn shared the update on Twitter, disclosing the number of burned tokens in the past seven days. 
 
SHIB Token Burns Continue To Soar Amid Market Downtrend
 
According to the post, the Shiba Inu community burned 1,826,262,961 in seven days. Around 24 hours later, on April 21, 27,575,359 million tokens entered the dead wallet.
 
Out of the total tokens, a single wallet burned 15 million SHIBs through two separate transactions. The wallet held 2.26 billion SHIBs before the burn transaction. The first transaction w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China Warns of Global Financial Instability From US Economic Policies]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e751f6adea0</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/china-warns-of-global-financial-instability-from-us-economic-policies/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-23T03:40:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[China has urged the U.S. and other developed nations to assess the spillover effects of their economic and financial policies. “The economic and financial policies of the U.S. pose the biggest challenge to global financial stability,” according to the Chinese Ministry of Foreign Affairs.
 
China Cautions About U.S. Economic and Financial Policies
 
Wang Wenbin, a spokesperson for China’s Ministry of Foreign Affairs, expressed concerns over the state of the global economy at a press conference Thursday.
 
Commenting on the recent International Monetary Fund (IMF) Global Financial Stability report pointing out that the turmoil in the U.S. banking sector has increased the risk of global financial stability, the Chinese official said: “Global financial stability bears on the recovery and devel…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Burn Rate Spikes But Price Continues To Tank, But Why?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18173967/Shiba-Inu-Burn-Rate-Spikes-But-Price-Continues-To-Tank-But-Why</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18173967/Shiba-Inu-Burn-Rate-Spikes-But-Price-Continues-To-Tank-But-Why"/>
        <updated>2023-04-23T03:35:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Shiba Inu community has continued its burning transactions in the past few days. Recently, more than 27 million SHIB tokens entered the dead wallet in six transactions. Shibburn data shows that one wallet burned 15 million out of the total tokens. Related Reading: Crypto Scammers Allegedly...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Identifying the why and how of Arbitrum flipping Ethereum on this front]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18173966/Identifying-the-why-and-how-of-Arbitrum-flipping-Ethereum-on-this-front</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18173966/Identifying-the-why-and-how-of-Arbitrum-flipping-Ethereum-on-this-front"/>
        <updated>2023-04-23T03:30:11.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Dollar ‘Finished’, American Empire in Peril As Strategic Rivals Target USD: Ex-Goldman Executive]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18173959/US-Dollar-Finished-American-Empire-in-Peril-As-Strategic-Rivals-Target-USD-Ex-Goldman-Executive</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18173959/US-Dollar-Finished-American-Empire-in-Peril-As-Strategic-Rivals-Target-USD-Ex-Goldman-Executive"/>
        <updated>2023-04-23T03:08:36.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TikTok Videos On Crypto Investments Highly Misleading, Study Finds]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e751f559430</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/tiktok-videos-on-crypto-investments-highly-misleading-study-finds/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-23T03:02:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Research has revealed that 30% of TikTok videos on crypto investments share wrong messages. The videos sport crypto-related hashtags such as investing, trading, and advice.
 
 
Also, the researchers discovered that TikTok influencers promoting Bitcoin and digital asset investments had recorded billions of views on their videos cumulatively. 
 
Crypto Influencers On TikTok Post Misleading Information 
 
TikTok is a popular video-based platform where many people search for information besides Google. But dappGambl researchers have discovered that many digital influencers post misleading information about digital investments on TikTok. 
 
dappGambl analyzed more than 1,161 TikTok videos and discovered that one out of every 10 warned the viewers of crypto investment risks. The rest failed to a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TikTok Videos On Crypto Investments Highly Misleading, Study Finds]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18173948/TikTok-Videos-On-Crypto-Investments-Highly-Misleading-Study-Finds</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18173948/TikTok-Videos-On-Crypto-Investments-Highly-Misleading-Study-Finds"/>
        <updated>2023-04-23T02:56:06.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Economist Peter Schiff Warns ‘Death Blow’ Coming for US Dollar — USD to Lose Reserve Currency Status]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e751f52c4a3</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/economist-peter-schiff-warns-death-blow-coming-for-us-dollar-usd-to-lose-reserve-currency-status/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-23T01:41:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Economist Peter Schiff has warned that a death blow is coming for the U.S. dollar and the USD will lose its global reserve currency status in this financial crisis. “People are still reluctant to call it a financial crisis, but that’s exactly what it is, except it’s bigger in scale and it’s going to be far more impactful than the 2008 crisis,” Schiff stressed.
 
Peter Schiff on U.S. Dollar’s ‘Death Blow’
 
Economist and gold bug Peter Schiff explained that a death blow is coming for the U.S. dollar as a global reserve currency in a recent interview with Commodity Culture, which he shared this week.
 
Regarding whether de-dollarization is happening and whether it’s a real threat to the U.S. dollar’s global reserve currency status, Schiff said: “The only thing that’s surprising about the dol…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SBF’s lawyers unable to tap his parent’s phones to meet bail conditions]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18173918/SBFs-lawyers-unable-to-tap-his-parents-phones-to-meet-bail-conditions</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18173918/SBFs-lawyers-unable-to-tap-his-parents-phones-to-meet-bail-conditions"/>
        <updated>2023-04-23T01:38:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new cell phones purchased for Bankman-Fried's parents cannot "automatically photograph the device's users every five minutes as required by the Order," according to a recent court filing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Crypto Analyst Updates Outlook on Bitcoin and Ethereum, Warns Altcoins Headed for ‘Deeper Declines’]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18173913/Top-Crypto-Analyst-Updates-Outlook-on-Bitcoin-and-Ethereum-Warns-Altcoins-Headed-for-Deeper-Declines</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18173913/Top-Crypto-Analyst-Updates-Outlook-on-Bitcoin-and-Ethereum-Warns-Altcoins-Headed-for-Deeper-Declines"/>
        <updated>2023-04-23T01:34:21.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Are NFTs Selling for $MILLIONS?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18173899/Why-Are-NFTs-Selling-for-MILLIONS</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18173899/Why-Are-NFTs-Selling-for-MILLIONS"/>
        <updated>2023-04-23T01:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[American Currency Dominance at Risk As China, Russia and Iran Conspire To Dump Dollar: Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18173868/American-Currency-Dominance-at-Risk-As-China-Russia-and-Iran-Conspire-To-Dump-Dollar-Treasury-Secretary-Janet-Yellen</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18173868/American-Currency-Dominance-at-Risk-As-China-Russia-and-Iran-Conspire-To-Dump-Dollar-Treasury-Secretary-Janet-Yellen"/>
        <updated>2023-04-23T00:04:51.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rich Dad Poor Dad Author Robert Kiyosaki Shares Why He Loves Bitcoin — Expects BTC to Hit $100K]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e751f5a93ca</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/rich-dad-poor-dad-author-robert-kiyosaki-shares-why-he-loves-bitcoin-expects-btc-to-hit-100k/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-22T23:40:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rich Dad Poor Dad author Robert Kiyosaki has shared why he loves bitcoin and when he began investing in the cryptocurrency. Expecting to see $100K per bitcoin, he emphasized that the crypto does not need the Fed or government bailout because it’s “people’s money.”
 
Why Robert Kiyosaki Loves Bitcoin
 
The author of Rich Dad Poor Dad, Robert Kiyosaki, shared on Twitter Thursday why he loves bitcoin. He expects to see the price of BTC hit $100K. Rich Dad Poor Dad is a 1997 book co-authored by Kiyosaki and Sharon Lechter. It has been on the New York Times Best Seller List for over six years. Over 32 million copies of the book have been sold in over 51 languages across more than 109 countries.
 
Kiyosaki tweeted Thursday explaining that years ago, he watched the price of the largest cryptocurr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Price Maintains Key Support While Analysts Foresee a 380% Upswing]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18173856/Shiba-Inu-Price-Maintains-Key-Support-While-Analysts-Foresee-a-380-Upswing</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18173856/Shiba-Inu-Price-Maintains-Key-Support-While-Analysts-Foresee-a-380-Upswing"/>
        <updated>2023-04-22T23:22:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu demonstrates resilience, holding above a crucial support level. With an expanding ecosystem, vibrant community, and high-profile endorsements, analysts predict a potential 380% price surge for SHIB.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pepe Token Surges 77% in 24 Hours, Leading the Top 10 Meme Coins’ Market Gains]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e751f465c85</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/pepe-token-surges-77-in-24-hours-leading-the-top-10-meme-coins-market-gains/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-22T22:39:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the aftermath of a downturn in the wider crypto market, the top crypto assets bitcoin and ethereum have each risen modestly, between 1.2% to 1.6%, over the past 24 hours. However, the meme token pepe (PEPE) has surged 77% against the U.S. dollar, and its market capitalization has swelled to $141 million, just $24 million shy of its all-time high valuation. Other top meme coin assets, including dogecoin and shibu inu, have risen by 1.2% to 1.4% today, while baby doge coin has experienced a 10% increase in value over the past day.
 
While the Meme Coin Market Is Down, Pepe and Babypepe Tokens Jump in Value
 
The meme coin market has declined 3.1% against the U.S. dollar over the past 24 hours and currently stands at $18.9 billion. On Saturday, eight of the top ten meme coins saw daily gai…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We held an exclusive fireside chat in celebration of Ramadan last month.

Two of our senior leaders took the stage…]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18174377/We-held-an-exclusive-fireside-chat-in-celebration-of-Ramadan-last-month-Two-of-our-senior-leaders-took-the-stage</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18174377/We-held-an-exclusive-fireside-chat-in-celebration-of-Ramadan-last-month-Two-of-our-senior-leaders-took-the-stage"/>
        <updated>2023-04-22T22:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do Kwon Challenges SEC’s Jurisdiction in Multibillion-Dollar Crypto Securities Fraud Case]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e751f41aa6f</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/do-kwon-challenges-secs-jurisdiction-in-multibillion-dollar-crypto-securities-fraud-case/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-22T21:49:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Attorneys defending the co-founder of Terraform Labs, Do Hyeong Kwon, also known as Do Kwon, have presented their argument that says the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has no jurisdiction in the matter. The legal team asserts that U.S. law precludes regulators “from using federal securities law to assert jurisdiction over the digital assets in this case.”
 
Terraform Labs Co-Founder’s Legal Team Claims SEC Lacks Jurisdiction Over Digital Assets in Terra Case
 
As per Bloomberg, Kwon’s lawyers have filed a motion to dismiss the lawsuit, citing that the SEC’s case relies on outdated regulations and that the agency’s definition of digital assets as securities is far from clear. In fact, Patrick McHenry (R-NC), the House Financial Services Committee chairman, recently expressed …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bored Ape Creator Yuga Labs Claims 'Landmark Legal Victory' Over Copycat NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137577</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137577/bored-ape-creator-yuga-labs-claims-landmark-legal-victory-over-copycat-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-04-22T21:13:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yuga Labs declares victory over "scammers and counterfeiters" after winning a key legal battle over a Bored Ape Yacht Club copycat project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto AI Economy Suffers $730 Million Loss in 2 Months as Interest Wanes]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e751f4a54ce</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/crypto-ai-economy-suffers-730-million-loss-in-2-months-as-interest-wanes/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-22T19:45:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Less than two months ago, a collection of 74 listed cryptocurrencies centered around artificial intelligence (AI) amassed an impressive $4 billion valuation. However, the intervening weeks have seen a sharp decline in crypto-AI economy gains, with losses of $730 million. The three most prominent AI-driven crypto projects have all suffered double-digit losses, ranging from 10% to 29.58%, against the U.S. dollar over the last 30 days.
 
Interest in the Combination of Crypto and Artificial Intelligence Has Declined, Crypto-AI Token Economy Sheds $730M
 
Various data points suggest that interest in and value of crypto-AI projects has waned. Global search trends for “crypto ai” peaked in early February 2023, with a Google Trends’ score of 100. Despite the rise, over the past 90 days, the score …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Stamps Surpass 18,000 Collectibles, Creativity Takes Center Stage]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e751f3c03d0</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-stamps-surpass-18000-collectibles-creativity-takes-center-stage/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-22T17:45:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the latest non-fungible token (NFT) trend on the Bitcoin blockchain, known as Bitcoin Stamps, users have issued more than 18,000 digital collectibles on the network. While this figure falls short of the number of Ordinal inscriptions, stamp creators are exploring new ways to leverage this technology.
 
Number of Bitcoin Stamps Rises Above 18,000
 
A mere 17 days ago, Bitcoin.com News reported on the trend of Bitcoin Stamps, as more than 8,000 stamps had been minted on the Bitcoin blockchain. Since then, the tally has grown to 18,443 stamps. The trend of creating stamps began following the craze of Ordinal inscriptions, and proponents of stamp technology argue that it enhances permanence, as stamps cannot be pruned like witness or signature data.
 
Stamp creation comes with a higher pr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bored Apes, CryptoPunks Fall Below $100K as NFT Momentum Stalls]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137545</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137545/bored-apes-cryptopunks-fall-below-100k-nft-momentum-stalls"/>
        <updated>2023-04-22T17:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Blue chip” NFT projects are losing value as some trading metrics across NFT marketplaces fell to nearly two-year lows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Market Slumps as Bitcoin and Ethereum Drop Over 10%]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137574</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137574/this-week-in-coins-bitcoin-ethereum-crash-bittrex-sec-gensler-hearings"/>
        <updated>2023-04-22T17:15:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Markets were cautious this week as regulators continued the debate over crypto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Judge Rules Bored Ape Yacht Club Ripoff NFTs Violated Yuga Copyright]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e751f387ed8</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/web3/2023/04/22/judge-rules-bored-ape-yacht-club-ripoff-nfts-violated-yuga-copyright/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-04-22T16:54:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Use of BAYC trademarks by Ripps’ RR/BAYC was intended to confuse consumers, a U.S. judge in California has ruled]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Citi Analysts Predict ‘Near-Perfect Conditions’ for Silver’s Ongoing Bull Market; Experts Suggest $30 an Ounce a Possibility]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e751f26fd1d</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/citi-analysts-predict-near-perfect-conditions-for-silvers-ongoing-bull-market-experts-suggest-30-an-ounce-a-possibility/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-22T15:44:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price of silver fell 2.85% against the U.S. dollar last week. However, taking a broader perspective, the precious metal has made significant gains this year. Over the past six months, silver has risen more than 29% against the greenback, and as of April 22, 2023, it was hovering around $25.08 per ounce. Citi analysts recently projected that silver prices could increase to $30 per ounce this year, citing “near-perfect conditions for the ongoing bull market” in silver markets.
 
Analysts See Potential for Silver Market to Take Off
 
Although silver has experienced a recent decline, the precious metal has made significant gains in 2023. Last week, Citi analysts, led by Maximilian Layton, told Forbes writer Jonathan Ponciano that the U.S. dollar still has room to weaken. In a recent note, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Copy Michael Saylor and Create Your Own Bitcoin Lightning Email Address]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137557</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137557/how-michael-saylor-create-bitcoin-lightning-email-address"/>
        <updated>2023-04-22T15:08:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wanna know how Saylor was able to start sending Bitcoin payments to his email address? Just follow these easy steps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alyssa Hertig</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Are Six New Projects Looking to Mitigate Bitcoin Mining’s Energy Footprint]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e751f232eac</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/04/22/here-are-six-new-projects-looking-to-mitigate-bitcoin-minings-energy-footprint/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-04-22T15:01:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From technical improvement efficiencies to novel market-based solutions, a plethora of projects are trying to improve the bitcoin mining’s environmental footprint.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliza Gkritsi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biggest Movers: DOGE, SHIB Drop to Multi-Week Lows, Following Crypto Red Wave]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e751f2a8040</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/biggest-movers-doge-shib-drop-to-multi-week-lows-following-crypto-red-wave/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-22T13:43:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin dropped to a multi-week low on Saturday, as a red wave continues to wash away recent crypto bulls. The meme coin dropped below a key price floor at $0.080 following today’s plunge. Shiba inu was also lower to start the weekend, falling by as much as 3%.
 
Dogecoin (DOGE)
 
Dogecoin (DOGE) moved to a three-week low to start the weekend, as bears pushed the meme coin below a key price level.
 
Following a high of $0.08435 on Friday, DOGE/USD dropped to a bottom at $0.07752 in today’s session.
 
Saturday’s decline saw DOGE fall below a long-term support point at $0.080, hitting its weakest point since April 3.
 
 
From the chart, it appears that dogecoin has found a new floor at near the $0.0760 mark, which comes as the relative strength index (RSI) also consolidated.
 
At the time of writing this, the index is now tracking at 43.21, which is close to a support point at 42.00.
 
The next visible resistance level looks to be at 51.00, and should bulls begin to move towards this, DOGE will soon be back above $0.090.
 
 
Shiba Inu (SHIB)
 
Another meme coin in the red on Saturday was shiba inu (SHIB) which also slipped to a multi-week low.
 
SHIB/USD dropped to a low of $0.00001012 to start the weekend, less than 24 hours after trading at a peak of $0.00001064
 
This is the lowest level that shiba inu has hit since March 11, and comes following a four-day losing streak.
 
 
The recent mini-bear run has now pushed the 10-day (red) moving average to the brink of a downward cross with its 25-day (blue) counterpart.
 
As of writing this, shiba inu continues to hover close to an area of support at the $0.00001020 level.
 
Price strength is also marginally above a floor of its own at 37.00.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
Do you expect further declines in meme coins during the weekend? Let us know your thoughts in the comments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How An Ordinals Collection Could Accelerate El Salvador’s Bitcoin Progress]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e751f14ac06</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/el-salvador-bitcoin-ordinal-collection"/>
        <updated>2023-04-22T13:21:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An official Ordinals collection by El Salvador could accelerate the progress its making with Bitcoin and confer unique benefits on investors.
 
         
         
         
         
    
This is an opinion editorial by Steven Hay, a writer, former trader and art dealer.
I’m a long-time Bitcoiner, preparing to travel and hopefully relocate permanently to El Salvador in 2023. Like many Bitcoiners, I wish to be a part of the amazing changes happening in this country. And I’d like to share an idea which I strongly believe has the potential to accelerate those changes.
Similar to the volcano bond concept, this idea employs Bitcoin-linked assets to raise funds for the building of Bitcoin City, or any other worthy project. Unlike bonds, however, these relatively-straightforward assets impose no…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steven Hay</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Technical Analysis: ETH Falls Under the $1,900 Level to Start the Weekend]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e751f131048</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-ethereum-technical-analysis-eth-falls-under-the-1900-level-to-start-the-weekend/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-22T12:14:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum started the weekend trading below $1,900 for the first time in two weeks, as cryptocurrency markets continued to fall. The global market cap is down by close to 3% at the time of writing this. Bitcoin was also in red, as it moved closer to $27,000.
 
Bitcoin
 
Bitcoin (BTC) was in the red for a fourth consecutive session, as prices neared a breakout below $27,000.
 
BTC/USD plunged to a low of $27,169.57 to start the weekend, a day after trading at a high of $28,291.60.
 
Saturday’s drop in price resulted in bitcoin falling to its lowest point in roughly three and a half weeks.
 
 
Looking at the chart, this latest downturn has pushed the 10-day (red) moving average closer to a cross with its 25-day (blue) counterpart.
 
In addition to this, the relative strength index is now tracking at 41.73, which is marginally higher than its long-term floor at 41.00.
 
If price strength were to slip below this point, there is a good chance that BTC will move toward $26,000.
 
 
Ethereum
 
Ethereum (ETH) continued to trend lower on Saturday, as the world’s second-largest cryptocurrency dropped below $1,900.
 
Following a high of $1,926.30 on Friday, ETH/USD fell to an intraday low at $1,827.79 earlier in the day.
 
As a result of this move, ethereum started the weekend by declining to its weakest level since April 9.
 
 
Today’s price slippage also resulted in ETH briefly breaking out of an interim support point at $1,830.
 
Bulls swiftly reentered the market seemingly buying the dip, and this has resulted in ethereum now trading at $1,848.66.
 
Although there is likely to be further declines in the coming days, once this current red wave passes, there may be a significant reversal.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
Could ethereum drop below $1,700 this weekend Leave your thoughts in the comments below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LUNA On-Chain Metrics Show Drop In Development Activity Despite Upgrade]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e751f139d6f</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/luna-metrics-show-drop-in-dev-activity/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-22T12:09:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LUNA recently underwent a successful upgrade to v2.3.1, thanks to a strong show of support for proposal 4717. While the Terra community celebrated the milestone on Twitter, on-chain metrics tell a different story. 
 
Development activity for the blockchain has been steadily declining for the past two months, raising concerns about the future of Terra’s growth and adoption. 
 
As the blockchain world evolves rapidly, can Terra find a way to reverse this trend?
 
 
Bearish Outlook For LUNA
 
Terra’s LUNA coin is currently priced at $1.21 on CoinMarketCap, with a 24-hour trading volume of $38,388,955. Unfortunately, the last 24 hours have been very challenging for the cryptocurrency, as it has experienced a 4.29% decrease in value.
 
Despite the bullish rally of 2023, LUNA failed to regain mo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Treasury Secretary Yellen Says US Government Will Take ‘Any Steps Necessary’ to Preserve Its Financial Dominance]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e751f1bd67b</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/treasury-secretary-yellen-says-us-government-will-take-any-steps-necessary-to-preserve-its-financial-dominance/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-22T10:41:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to U.S. Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen, the United States government is prepared to take the steps necessary to ensure its financial system remains the world’s strongest and safest. Yellen said that the U.S. government will not hesitate to punish Chinese companies that violate its Russian sanctions policy. 
 
U.S. Ready to Shore up Its Financial System
 
The U.S. Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen said while her country’s financial system is still in good shape the United States government is still prepared to take “any necessary steps” to ensure it remains the most dominant, a report has said.
 
In her speech at the Johns Hopkins University’s School of Advanced International Studies, Yellen also touted the recent actions taken to shore up the financial system by U.S. authorities f…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFT Twitter Is All Good Vibes Again—On Bluesky]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137520</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137520/nft-twitter-all-good-vibes-again-bluesky"/>
        <updated>2023-04-21T23:43:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Buzzy Twitter rival Bluesky is attracting prominent Web3 creators, artists, and collectors, some of whom are praising its early atmosphere.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson,Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Scammers Used AI to Create Fake CEO, Regulators Say]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137519</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137519/crypto-scammers-used-ai-create-fake-ceo-regulators-say"/>
        <updated>2023-04-21T23:23:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[California regulators are stamping out alleged AI-tinged crypto scams—including a firm that supposedly generated a fake CEO for YouTube.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uniswap Trades Soar as Pepe Mania Grips Meme Coin Market]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137509</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137509/uniswap-trades-soar-pepe-mania-meme-coin"/>
        <updated>2023-04-21T22:27:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Transactions on the decentralized exchange have spiked by more than 66% from the previous all-time high, according to a Uniswap researcher.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arthur Hayes: Market Makers Knew They’d Be Front-Run on FTX—It Was 'Common Knowledge']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137506</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137506/arthur-hayes-market-makers-ftx-front-running"/>
        <updated>2023-04-21T21:07:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BitMEX founder Arthur Hayes claims that "market makers did not want to trade on FTX," suggesting pro traders always knew the exchange was "a little bit shady."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto VC Funding Down 82% Compared to Last Year]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137503</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137503/crypto-vc-funding-down-82-percent"/>
        <updated>2023-04-21T20:03:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The evaporating funding means "a lot of companies are doing their down rounds," said the founder of Delta Blockchain Fund.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeremy Nation</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Whale Moves Nearly $8M After 10 Years of Inactivity]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137493</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137493/bitcoin-whale-moves-nearly-8m-after-10-years-inactivity"/>
        <updated>2023-04-21T18:13:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A holder who hadn’t touched their crypto for a decade just moved over 279 BTC, or $7.8 million worth of the crypto, to new wallets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Texas ‘Proof of Reserves’ Bill Passes House of Representatives]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137482</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137482/texas-proof-of-reserves-bill-passes-house-of-representatives"/>
        <updated>2023-04-21T16:48:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bill would require cryptocurrency exchanges to maintain reserves ‘in an amount sufficient to fulfill all obligations to customers.’]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Bluesky? The Twitter Alternative With Promising Networking Technology]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137463</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-bluesky-the-twitter-alternative-with-promising-networking-technology"/>
        <updated>2023-04-21T13:16:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While Bluesky seems like Twitter on the surface, the AT protocol architecture it is run on — and the functionality it enables — have the potential to be revolutionary.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Euny Hong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Correction: Rewarded.tv Has No Channel With Rhett &#038; Link, Deal Was Misrepresented]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137442</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137442/youtube-stars-rhett-link-launch-web3-channel-with-token-rewards"/>
        <updated>2023-04-21T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The channel was reportedly available on the service via syndication, but then pulled by Mythical once the news came to light.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Warns Advisers to Apply 'Heightened Scrutiny' When Recommending Crypto Assets]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137461</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137461/sec-warns-advisers-to-apply-heightened-scrutiny-when-recommending-crypto-assets"/>
        <updated>2023-04-21T12:59:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Protecting retail investors, including those seeking exposure to cryptocurrencies, remains a priority for the SEC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Now Measures Network Carbon Emissions Data in Real Time]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137441</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137441/solana-now-measures-network-carbon-emissions-data-in-real-time"/>
        <updated>2023-04-21T12:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Solana Foundation claims that it is the first "major smart contract blockchain network" to broadcast its environmental impact as such.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Merges AI Teams Under DeepMind Banner]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137448</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137448/google-merges-ai-teams-under-deepmind-banner"/>
        <updated>2023-04-21T11:14:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google parent company Alphabet is bringing its Brain and DeepMind AI teams under one roof with the launch of Google DeepMind.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Drops to $28,000 as Macro Pressures Bite]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137449</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137449/bitcoin-drops-to-28000-as-marco-pressures-bite"/>
        <updated>2023-04-21T10:14:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto market’s negative streak continued as prices dipped for a third consecutive day, with Bitcoin briefly slipping below $28,000.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Has Most Americans Scared About Privacy, Job Losses]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137421</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137421/ai-has-most-americans-scared-about-privacy-job-losses"/>
        <updated>2023-04-21T01:14:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using AI is one thing, but having AI being used on you—when your job could be on the line—is another.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[F1 Legend Michael Schumacher’s Family Threatens Lawsuit Over Faked AI Interview]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137415</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137415/f1-legend-michael-schumachers-family-threatens-lawsuit-faked-ai-interview"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T22:42:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A German magazine promoted an exclusive interview with seven-time Formula 1 champion Michael Schumacher—but it was an AI-based fake.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining Pools Will Have Less Power With This Upgrade]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137402</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137402/bitcoin-mining-pools-less-power-upgrade"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T22:01:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stratum v2 aims to change a key feature in the way Bitcoin mining is done, making it much harder for mining pools to collectively censor transactions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alyssa Hertig</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Monkey Business IP Acquired by DAO of NFT Holders]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137393</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137393/solana-monkey-business-ip-acquired-dao-nft-holders"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T21:17:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prominent NFT project Solana Monkey Business is now owned by the independent collective of holders that formed around it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PUBG Creator to Launch NFT Metaverse Game This Year]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137387</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137387/pubg-creator-to-launch-nft-metaverse-game-this-year"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T18:46:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Krafton, the studio behind the smash battle royale game PUBG, said that its metaverse gaming platform will launch in 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CryptoPunks NFT in Centre Pompidou ‘Quite a Surprise’: Larva Labs Co-Founder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137094</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137094/quite-surprise-seeing-cryptopunks-nft-pompidou-larva-labs-co-founder"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T16:56:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The world-renowned art museum in Paris has made special room for the emerging NFT space, adding a exhibition of blockchain-related art.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Leads Meme Coin Rally With Pepe and Baby Doge]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137372</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137372/dogecoin-surges-over-the-week-bringing-meme-coin-market-with-it-as-bitcoin-slumps"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T16:16:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin is on a run this week—and so its meme coin compatriots, PEPE and BABYDOGE.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Print Is Dead? Why NFT Platform Zora Is Launching a Magazine]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137327</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137327/print-is-dead-why-nft-platform-zora-is-launching-a-magazine"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T16:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Only 2,500 copies of Print Issue 001 will be published, made redeemable via collectible NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Receives Bermuda License, Outlines Global Expansion Plans]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137367</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137367/coinbase-receives-bermuda-license-outlines-global-expansion-plans"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T14:02:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The exchange is also in talks with Abu Dhabi Global Market regulators about opening a regulated exchange there.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: Arthur Hayes Says Crypto Failures Are A Sign of The System Cleansing Itself]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZHyccGKp/gm-arthur-hayes-says-crypto-failures-are-a-sign-of-the-system-cleansing-itself</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZHyccGKp/gm-arthur-hayes-says-crypto-failures-are-a-sign-of-the-system-cleansing-itself"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T13:47:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arthur Hayes says the speed at which projects like Terra grow and implode is a feature of the crypto industry, not a bug. He founded crypto exchange Bitmex in 2014 and then became the original crypto bad boy. In 2021 the DOJ charged him in with violating the U.S. Bank Secrecy Act for not implementing an anti-money laundering program at Bitmex. He plead guilty and was sentenced to two years probation and six months of home detention. In fact, he was still sporting an ankle bracelet on a recent cover of New York Magazine. Now he's living in Singapore, offering up his views on the crypto industry with long form, meme-filled essays, and still thinks the crypto industry will save investors from what he calls a broken banking system. "I don't care if you're capitalist or you're a communist. Everybody put on a lot of debt. We've passed the point where that debt is becoming useful," he said. "And therefore everyone is going to take an L unless they get some crypto or some gold—some hard asset that's outside of the traditional banking system."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dutch Court Agrees to Free Tornado Cash Dev Alex Pertsev Pending Trial]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137355</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137355/dutch-court-agrees-to-free-tornado-cash-dev-alex-pertsev-pending-trial"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T13:22:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The developer of coin mixer Tornado Cash, Alex Pertsev, is set to be released on bail after nine months in detention without a trial.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Esports Brand XSET Signs Web3 Gaming Content Creator Brycent]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137307</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137307/esports-brand-xset-signs-web3-gaming-content-creator-brycent"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T13:01:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brycent tells Decrypt that he plans to double down on Web3 gaming content with XSET, which is known for popular streamers and esports teams.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Staking Provider P2P.org Raises $23M Series A]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137353</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137353/ethereum-staking-provider-p2p-org-raises-23m-series-a"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Founder Konstantin Lomashuk credits the recent Shanghai upgrade, which it says has increased institutional interest in Ethereum staking.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonah Elkowitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is PepeCoin (PEPE)?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137346</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-pepecoin-pepe"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T12:23:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PEPE’s official Twitter account describes the token as the “most memeable memecoin in existence."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Reiff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bluesky, Jack Dorsey's Decentralized Twitter Rival, Launches An Android App]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137345</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137345/bluesky-jack-dorseys-decentralized-twitter-rival-launches-an-android-app"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T12:21:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The decentralized social media platform is now available to both iOS and Android users—but you'll need an invite code to sign up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EU Lauds 'Comprehensive Regulation' as MiCA Crypto Law Passes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137339</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137339/european-parliament-approves-mica-law"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T12:05:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto firms welcomed the passing of the landmark legislation by the European Parliament, which bring in new rules for the industry across the bloc.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alys Key</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bankrupt Crypto Lender Voyager Seals Fed Deal for $1 Billion Binance US Acquisition]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137338</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137338/bankrupt-crypto-lender-voyager-seals-fed-deal-for-1-billion-binance-us-acquisition"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T11:11:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Insolvent crypto lender Voyager has struck a deal with the U.S. federal government, allowing it to sell its assets to Binance.US.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Are Meme Coins and Tokens?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=74098</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-are-meme-coins-and-tokens"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T08:31:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Inspired by Internet memes and current events, and promoted by influencers, meme coins and tokens have shot to prominence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adriana Hamacher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried's Legal Team Can't Figure Out How to Install Spyware on His Parents’ Smartphones]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137330</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137330/sam-bankman-fried-smartphone-monitoring-spyware"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T02:13:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The disgraced FTX founder was supposed to be automatically monitored across devices, but some have proven resistant.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What the Next Level of Bitcoin Mining Difficulty Will Bring]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137313</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137313/bitcoin-mining-difficulty-increase-terahash"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T23:54:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin mining difficulty will increase again tomorrow. What do major mining companies expect for the industry over the long term?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Judge Says DOJ Can Call OpenSea NFT Case 'Insider Trading', Sets Trial Date]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137303</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137303/judge-opensea-nft-insider-trading-trial-date"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T22:57:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Chastain’s arguments about use of the term 'insider trading' are moot," the judge wrote in a memo filed yesterday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeremy Nation</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brycent on Web3 Games and the Problem with 'NFT Value']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/P97zCeID/brycent-on-web3-games-and-the-problem-with-nft-value</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/P97zCeID/brycent-on-web3-games-and-the-problem-with-nft-value"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T22:33:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XSET gamer and content creator Brycent tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the problem with gaming NFTs—and what needs to happen instead in the next generation of Web3 games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brycent on Meeting Gary Vaynerchuk through Web3 Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/xL8pz64R/brycent-on-meeting-gary-vaynerchuk-through-web3-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/xL8pz64R/brycent-on-meeting-gary-vaynerchuk-through-web3-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T22:23:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XSET gamer and content creator Brycent tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about how entrepreneur and VeeFriends creator Gary Vaynerchuk first reached out to him.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sotheby's to Auction CryptoPunk, Other NFTs Owned by Bankrupt Three Arrows Capital]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137285</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137285/sothebys-auction-cryptopunk-other-nfts-owned-three-arrows-capital"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T20:51:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fine art auction house Sotheby's announced Wednesday that it will sell NFT artwork seized from bankrupt hedge fund, Three Arrows Capital.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Drake and The Weeknd AI Mashup Backs Spotify, Apple Into a Copyright Corner]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137293</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137293/drake-the-weekend-heart-sleeve-ai-artificial-intelligence-spotify-apple-music-copyright"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T20:07:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Universal Music Group demanded "Heart On My Sleeve" be removed from all streaming platforms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: Anthony Scaramucci Is More Bullish on Bitcoin Than Ever]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PqLOXL47/gm-anthony-scaramucci-is-more-bullish-on-bitcoin-than-ever</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PqLOXL47/gm-anthony-scaramucci-is-more-bullish-on-bitcoin-than-ever"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T18:58:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthony Scaramucci of hedge fund SkyBridge Capital got burned by Sam Bankman-Fried: he co-hosted SALT conferences with FTX and sold a 30% stake in SkyBridge to FTX Ventures. And yet "The Mooch" tells Dan Roberts and Stacy Elliott "I'm more bullish now than I have ever been" on crypto as an investment case. He discusses his frustration with SBF, how wrong he thinks politicians like Elizabeth Warren and Gary Gensler are about crypto and how to regulate it, what he sees happening next with adoption, and talks about Trump. Watch and make sure to subscribe to the gm podcast on Apple or Spotify.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Chief Legal Officer: The Problem With SEC's Howey Test Isn't Its Age]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/woZFLgib/coinbase-chief-legal-officer-the-problem-with-secs-howey-test-isnt-its-age</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/woZFLgib/coinbase-chief-legal-officer-the-problem-with-secs-howey-test-isnt-its-age"/>
        <updated>2023-04-10T16:25:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Chief Legal Officer Paul Grewal discussed the "Howey Test," which the SEC uses as its yard stick for whether a crypto asset should be regulated as a security, and told Decrypt's Stacy Elliott and Dan Roberts the issue with it isn't that it's old (the case is from 1946) but how it's being applied to modern technology. Watch and make sure to subscribe to the gm podcast on Apple or Spotify.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized Pictures Plots Its Next Web3 Grant for Filmmakers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/WlVsgaOs/decentralized-pictures-plots-its-next-web3-grant-for-filmmakers</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/WlVsgaOs/decentralized-pictures-plots-its-next-web3-grant-for-filmmakers"/>
        <updated>2023-04-08T13:15:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leo Matchett from Web3 film funding platform Decentralized Pictures tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson at Outer Edge LA about DCP's just announced iPhone Filmmaking Initiative, which will support aspiring filmmakers who create a short film on their iPhones, and will be determined via DCP's crypto-native on-chain voting system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 YouTuber CryptoStache: Gaming Will Be the Catalyst That Takes NFTs Mainstream]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Exb7eWKj/web3-youtuber-cryptostache-gaming-will-be-the-catalyst-that-takes-nfts-mainstream</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Exb7eWKj/web3-youtuber-cryptostache-gaming-will-be-the-catalyst-that-takes-nfts-mainstream"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T02:51:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 gaming YouTuber CryptoStache talks to Decrypt's Jason Nelson at Outer Edge LA about why Web3 gaming will bring NFTs mainstream, the partnerships that prove it's already happening, how gamers will change their tune on NFTs, and how the terminology is likely to change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fordefi Aims to Dramatically Simplify the Institutional Crypto Wallet]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/LGxyFJP5/fordefi-aims-to-dramatically-simplify-the-institutional-crypto-wallet</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/LGxyFJP5/fordefi-aims-to-dramatically-simplify-the-institutional-crypto-wallet"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T02:39:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Steve H., VP of sales from Fordefi, which raised $18 million in funding last year, tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson at Outer Edge LA how Fordefi uses multi-party computation to make signing transactions on an institutional crypto wallet much simpler—no seed phrase needed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: Canadian Bitcoin Miner Hut 8 Is Heading West]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5AGD2ifd/gm-canadian-bitcoin-miner-hut-8-is-heading-west</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5AGD2ifd/gm-canadian-bitcoin-miner-hut-8-is-heading-west"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T21:40:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Toronto-based Bitcoin mining company Hut 8 recently announced a merger with U.S. Bitcoin Corp that will take it into Texas, Nebraska, and New York. Hut 8 CEO Jaime Leverton joined Dan Roberts and Stacy Elliott to talk expanding into the U.S., dealing with regulatory pushback post-FTX, why Texas is such a hotspot, and where she'd like to expand globally down the road (the climates may surprise you). Watch and make sure to subscribe to the gm podcast on Apple or Spotify.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: Kevin Owocki Wants to Regenerate DeFi]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/knbMLd17/gm-kevin-owocki-wants-to-regenerate-defi</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/knbMLd17/gm-kevin-owocki-wants-to-regenerate-defi"/>
        <updated>2023-04-01T14:23:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Move over, DeFi—ReFi is coming? Gitcoin founder Kevin Owocki has stepped away from DeFi grant-giving machine Gitcoin as it fully decentralizes and is now focused on regenerative finance (huh?) and ReFi incubator Supermodular. He aims to "regenerate the regenerators." He explained it all to Dan Roberts and Liam Kelly, and also talks DAO structure, crypto factions, NFT use cases, his book "Greenpilled," and much more. Watch and make sure to subscribe to the gm podcast on Apple or Spotify.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Aurory's Head of Production Left Ubisoft for Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PqJHF0N9/why-aurorys-head-of-production-left-ubisoft-for-web3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PqJHF0N9/why-aurorys-head-of-production-left-ubisoft-for-web3"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T21:24:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aurory executive producer and head of production Jonathan Campeau tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin at GDC about how the first-generation of Web3 games came out of DeFi and are now evolving.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['We Don't Really Do the Corporate Thing Very Well' Says Jason Brink on Gala Games Approach]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/EDzHoKrt/we-dont-really-do-the-corporate-thing-very-well-says-jason-brink-on-gala-games-approach</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/EDzHoKrt/we-dont-really-do-the-corporate-thing-very-well-says-jason-brink-on-gala-games-approach"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T21:14:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With roughly 50 video games in its pipeline, Gala Games is all-in on Web3. Gala's President of Blockchain Jason Brink told Decrypt's Kate Irwin at GDC about the studio's ethos and weighs in on the different approaches to Web3 gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: Coinbase's Top Lawyer Gets Real on SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mB7DMx7l/gm-coinbases-top-lawyer-gets-real-on-sec</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mB7DMx7l/gm-coinbases-top-lawyer-gets-real-on-sec"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T16:36:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paul Grewal is the Chief Legal Officer at Coinbase and a former U.S. magistrate judge in Northern California. He gave Dan Roberts and Stacy Elliott his candid takes on Sam Bankman-Fried and FTX, the SEC's crackdown on staking, the sanctioning of Tornado Cash, and more alpha on how Coinbase is approaching the current unfriendly US regulatory environment. Watch and make sure to subscribe to the gm podcast on Apple or Spotify.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Founder of Rotten Tomatoes Says Web3 Entertainment Isn’t Nearly Entertaining Enough Yet]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/ri2LLifZ/the-founder-of-rotten-tomatoes-says-web3-entertainment-isnt-nearly-entertaining-enough-yet</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/ri2LLifZ/the-founder-of-rotten-tomatoes-says-web3-entertainment-isnt-nearly-entertaining-enough-yet"/>
        <updated>2023-03-25T02:44:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rotten Tomatoes founder Patrick Lee, who has led companies at the intersection of technology and entertainment from Web1 to Web3, spoke to Decrypt's Sander Lutz at Outer Edge LA about the current state of decentralized gaming, film and television.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: How Gnosis Has Endured and Evolved]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Kxfs2Dmd/gm-how-gnosis-has-endured-and-evolved</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Kxfs2Dmd/gm-how-gnosis-has-endured-and-evolved"/>
        <updated>2023-03-24T20:58:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gnosis first launched in 2015 as a decentralized prediction market built on Ethereum. Now it's a DAO, a multi-sig wallet, a staking chain, and a vibrant community with its own GNO governance token. Co-founder and COO Friederike Ernst talked to Dan Roberts and Stacy Elliott about the careful evolution of Gnosis, decentralization impostors, account abstraction, DeFi UX failures, why Ethereum is the "Manhattan of crypto," and much more. Watch and make sure to subscribe to the gm podcast on Apple or Spotify.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>