<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-07-11T16:21:28.953Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-07-11T16:21:28.953Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin exchanges now hold the same BTC supply share as in late 2017]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18761227/Bitcoin-exchanges-now-hold-the-same-BTC-supply-share-as-in-late-2017</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18761227/Bitcoin-exchanges-now-hold-the-same-BTC-supply-share-as-in-late-2017"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T16:15:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC supply dynamics are pointing firmly in Bitcoin bulls' favor, as an analyst says that "true price discovery" may come as a result.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto investors in advanced economies love CEXs and disregard white papers: Survey]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18761194/Crypto-investors-in-advanced-economies-love-CEXs-and-disregard-white-papers-Survey</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18761194/Crypto-investors-in-advanced-economies-love-CEXs-and-disregard-white-papers-Survey"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T16:09:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While Canadians were the most likely to hold a lot of crypto on average, it seems the true crypto degens are in the US and particularly the UK]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exclusive: Animoca Brands CEO urges community focus in web3 gaming evolution]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18761202/Exclusive-Animoca-Brands-CEO-urges-community-focus-in-web3-gaming-evolution</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18761202/Exclusive-Animoca-Brands-CEO-urges-community-focus-in-web3-gaming-evolution"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T16:09:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robby Yung, the CEO of NFT and web3 gaming giant Animoca Brands, believes that the adoption of games leveraging blockchain is “not as far away as we might think” while asking the community to consider what it means to be a “web3 game.” Yung discussed the emerging world of web3 gaming at...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feds Charge Engineer in First-Ever Decentralized Exchange Hack Case]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148097</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148097/feds-charge-engineer-first-ever-decentralized-exchange-hack-case"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T16:07:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Attorney Damian Williams today said that Shakeeb Ahmed "used his expertise to defraud" and allegedly steal $9 million in crypto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JUST IN: Coinbase Announces To List Helium (HNT) Token – Price Rises]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18761209/JUST-IN-Coinbase-Announces-To-List-Helium-HNT-Token-Price-Rises</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18761209/JUST-IN-Coinbase-Announces-To-List-Helium-HNT-Token-Price-Rises"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T16:04:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase announced in its statement that it will list the Helium (HNT) altcoin on its exchange. Continue Reading: JUST IN: Coinbase Announces To List Helium (HNT) Token – Price Rises]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arkham Intel Mocked: Called ‘Dox to Earn,’ Accused of Leaking Email Ids]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18761207/Arkham-Intel-Mocked-Called-Dox-to-Earn-Accused-of-Leaking-Email-Ids</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18761207/Arkham-Intel-Mocked-Called-Dox-to-Earn-Accused-of-Leaking-Email-Ids"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T16:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arkham’s Intel Exchange has faced an onslaught of criticism with many scornfully calling it the “dox to earn” and “snitch to earn” marketplace. Blockchain intelligence platform Akham Intelligence revealed plans to launch what it calls the world’s first on chain “intelligence exchange” earlier...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former security engineer arrested in NY after allegedly defrauding a DeFi exchange, stealing $9 million]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18761206/Former-security-engineer-arrested-in-NY-after-allegedly-defrauding-a-DeFi-exchange-stealing-9-million</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18761206/Former-security-engineer-arrested-in-NY-after-allegedly-defrauding-a-DeFi-exchange-stealing-9-million"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T16:01:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A former security engineer was arrested on Tuesday morning over what law enforcement says is the “first criminal case” involving an attack on a smart contract that was operated by a decentralized exchange.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon’s Top 1 DEX - Quickswap]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18761226/Polygons-Top-1-DEX-Quickswap</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18761226/Polygons-Top-1-DEX-Quickswap"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T16:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most of us are familiar with the top decentralized finance protocols on Ethereum, but what about the other Layer 1 and 2 chains, such as BNB Chain, Polygon, and Arbitrum? 🤔In this video, let's explore the Top 1 project built on PolygonCheck out the full video here 👉...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Magic Johnson-Backed Virtual Pro Sports League Partners With Immutable, Aims For 'Mass Adoption Of Web3 Gaming']]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18761224/Magic-Johnson-Backed-Virtual-Pro-Sports-League-Partners-With-Immutable-Aims-For-Mass-Adoption-Of-Web3-Gaming</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18761224/Magic-Johnson-Backed-Virtual-Pro-Sports-League-Partners-With-Immutable-Aims-For-Mass-Adoption-Of-Web3-Gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T16:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A virtual sports league for daily fantasy and esports announced a partnership Tuesday with Immutable, one of the world’s top Web3 gaming platforms. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Threads Got 100 Million Users When Other Twitter Rivals Could Not]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18761160/Why-Threads-Got-100-Million-Users-When-Other-Twitter-Rivals-Could-Not</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18761160/Why-Threads-Got-100-Million-Users-When-Other-Twitter-Rivals-Could-Not"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T15:49:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Network effects and ease of use rule the day. And, a lot of people clearly don’t care about decentralization and privacy all that much, says CoinDesk’s Emily Parker.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unchained Announces New Signature Private Client Service]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756ff20405</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/unchained-announces-new-signature-private-client-service"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T15:47:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unchained, a Bitcoin custodial services company, has announced the launch of its private client service with collaborative custody. According to a press release sent to Bitcoin Magazine, the new platform called “Unchained Signature” is a “membership-based service that helps high-net-worth individuals, institutions and corporations invest in and manage their bitcoin.”
The company compares the experience to that of premium banking services, but with the added twist of multi-signature custodial models that Unchained is known for. “The fact that clients hold their own bitcoin keys, even when they get a loan with their bitcoin used as collateral, is an assurance that Unchained is not able to singularly move or rehypothecate client funds, as many now-defunct crypto firms did prior to their collapse,” the press release stated.
Dedicated account management features described include private trade execution, multi-million dollar loans and retirement and estate planning — plus technical support, even to the extent that advisors will travel in-person for assistance during emergencies. In addition, Signature clients will receive early access to Unchained’s latest products as well as exclusive access to networking events. 
“As the best performing asset of the last decade, bitcoin continues to draw in new high-net-worth individuals and institutions, many of whom have previously shied away from crypto due to technical barriers and third-party risks,” said Joe Kelly, co-founder and CEO of Unchained, as he described the company’s opportunity. “Unchained Signature exists to help these investors buy, secure, and grow their bitcoin with as much technical and logistical assistance as they need — all without compromising security.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BtcCasey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Spikes 10% on Cboe Agreement]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18761155/Coinbase-Spikes-10-on-Cboe-Agreement</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18761155/Coinbase-Spikes-10-on-Cboe-Agreement"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T15:47:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase shares (COIN) are up by 9.5% to an 11 month high of $90 with the crypto exchange once again significantly outperforming bitcoin and other assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Latest attack on Arbitrum network costs Rodeo Finance $885k in ETH]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18761154/Latest-attack-on-Arbitrum-network-costs-Rodeo-Finance-885k-in-ETH</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18761154/Latest-attack-on-Arbitrum-network-costs-Rodeo-Finance-885k-in-ETH"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T15:46:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest attack on Rodeo comes just days after the DeFi protocol lost $90,000 via a vulnerability in its mintProtocolReserves function.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Near Foundation treasury drops to $900M as token price plunges]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18761147/Near-Foundation-treasury-drops-to-900M-as-token-price-plunges</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18761147/Near-Foundation-treasury-drops-to-900M-as-token-price-plunges"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T15:44:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The $200 million decline was mostly due to a drop in the price of Near tokens, in line with the crypto bear market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another $103 million in crypto assets transferred away from Multichain: Beosin]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18761125/Another-103-million-in-crypto-assets-transferred-away-from-Multichain-Beosin</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18761125/Another-103-million-in-crypto-assets-transferred-away-from-Multichain-Beosin"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T15:39:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data revealed a significant outflow of $103 million worth of crypto assets from the Multichain bridge on Monday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Stitch Together +300k Followers on Threads: Have Binance-Level Marketing]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18761121/How-to-Stitch-Together-300k-Followers-on-Threads-Have-Binance-Level-Marketing</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18761121/How-to-Stitch-Together-300k-Followers-on-Threads-Have-Binance-Level-Marketing"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T15:38:20.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PwC Report: Digital Asset Custody Industry Faces Security Challenges and Insurance Concerns]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18761127/PwC-Report-Digital-Asset-Custody-Industry-Faces-Security-Challenges-and-Insurance-Concerns</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18761127/PwC-Report-Digital-Asset-Custody-Industry-Faces-Security-Challenges-and-Insurance-Concerns"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T15:36:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The digital asset industry experienced significant growth, reaching a peak of over $3 trillion in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dubai Regulators Cancel BitOasis License – Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756ffc0b93</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dubai-regulators-cancel-bitoasis-license/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T15:35:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On July 10, BitOasis, the first crypto exchange to receive an operating license in Dubai, lost its license due to failure to meet mandated conditions. The Dubai crypto regulator Virtual Assets Regulatory Authority (VARA) suspended the license and issued two different alerts about the exchange which was granted the conditional license on April 12 with a period to meet its requirements. 
 
BitOasis Crypto Exchange Failed To Meet License Conditions
 
According to the recent alerts from the VARA, the BitOasis crypto exchange is now under review. This comes after the authority had granted the conditionals license to BitOasis, allowing it to operate in the country. But it mandated the exchange to meet its requirements within 30-60 days. 
 
 
However, the crypto exchange failed to meet the condit…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kent Glory</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Market Remains in ‘Bitcoin Season’ as ‘Altcoin Season’ Drought Hits Record Two-Year Mark]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756ffc3c1b</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/crypto-market-remains-in-bitcoin-season-as-altcoin-season-drought-hits-record-two-year-mark/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T15:34:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to data, the cryptocurrency ecosystem has endured its longest stretch without an altcoin season. So far, it has been more than two years without an altcoin season, and there have been no signals indicating one might emerge.
 
Altcoin Season Eludes Cryptocurrency Market for 2 Years
 
Recently, social media and cryptocurrency-related forums have been abuzz with discussions about an “altcoin season” and the unprecedented duration without one. Essentially, an altcoin season is a period in the cryptocurrency market when the prices of alternative cryptocurrencies, known as altcoins, surge in comparison to bitcoin (BTC) for several weeks or months. The Altcoin Season Index, available on blockchaincenter.net, notes that if 75% of the top 50 coins perform better than bitcoin over the last…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kiyosaki Projects $120k BTC as BRICS Plan to Unveil Gold-backed Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18761126/Kiyosaki-Projects-120k-BTC-as-BRICS-Plan-to-Unveil-Gold-backed-Crypto</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18761126/Kiyosaki-Projects-120k-BTC-as-BRICS-Plan-to-Unveil-Gold-backed-Crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T15:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent tweet, renowned author and investor Robert Kiyosaki hinted at an imminent announcement by the BRICS nations, including Brazil, Russia, India, China, and South Africa, regarding a revolutionary gold-backed cryptocurrency. Kiyosaki foresees a significant challenge to the US dollar’s...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Soars After Reaching Cboe Surveillance Sharing Agreement for 5 Bitcoin ETF Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18761119/Coinbase-Soars-After-Reaching-Cboe-Surveillance-Sharing-Agreement-for-5-Bitcoin-ETF-Applications</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18761119/Coinbase-Soars-After-Reaching-Cboe-Surveillance-Sharing-Agreement-for-5-Bitcoin-ETF-Applications"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T15:33:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shares of Coinbase jumped as much as 16% Tuesday after the crypto exchange reached an agreement with Cboe’s BZX Exchange to maintain a surveillance-sharing agreement for five of its spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brevan Howard Joins $12M Round for Liquid Staking Protocol Alluvial]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18761120/Brevan-Howard-Joins-12M-Round-for-Liquid-Staking-Protocol-Alluvial</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18761120/Brevan-Howard-Joins-12M-Round-for-Liquid-Staking-Protocol-Alluvial"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T15:33:48.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dubai Regulators Cancel BitOasis License – Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18761118/Dubai-Regulators-Cancel-BitOasis-License-Heres-Why</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18761118/Dubai-Regulators-Cancel-BitOasis-License-Heres-Why"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T15:30:26.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Metaverse, Web 4.0 Strategy Unveiled by European Commission]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18761098/Metaverse-Web-40-Strategy-Unveiled-by-European-Commission</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18761098/Metaverse-Web-40-Strategy-Unveiled-by-European-Commission"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T15:27:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The European Commission adopted a robust strategy on Web 4.0 and the metaverse on July 11. This initiative is designed to create a digital environment that is open, secure and inclusive, reflecting the principles of the EU:https://twitter.com/EU_Commission/status/1678771461086117896 The strategy...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biggest Movers: MATIC up 8%, as SOL Nears Fresh 2-Month High]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756fff929d</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/biggest-movers-matic-up-8-as-sol-nears-fresh-2-month-high/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T15:14:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon was a notable mover on Tuesday, as the token surged by as much as 8% in today’s session. The move saw the cryptocurrency hit a one-month high, following a recent five-day bull run. Solana also rose higher, following a sell-off to start the week.
 
Polygon (MATIC)
 
Polygon (MATIC) rose by as much as 8% earlier in today’s session, hitting a one-month high in the process.
 
Following a low of $0.7033 earlier in the day, MATIC/USD jumped to an intraday peak of $0.7473 on Tuesday.
 
As a result of this surge, MATIC hit its highest point since June 9, which is the last time the token broke out of a ceiling at $0.7480.
 
 
MATIC bulls were unable to breach this ceiling in today’s session, with the price retreating from an earlier high.
 
This comes despite the relative strength index (RSI) marginally breaking out of a ceiling at 59.00, with a current reading of 59.31.
 
In the event the index continues to strengthen, the odds of a breakout above $0.7480 will greatly increase.
 
 
Solana (SOL)
 
After dropping by nearly 7% to start the week, solana (SOL) bulls moved to buy the dip, with price now closing in on a fresh multi-month high.
 
SOL/USD jumped to a high of $22.29 earlier in the day, which is less than 24 hours after almost falling below $20.00.
 
Tuesday’s peak sees the world’s ninth largest cryptocurrency $0.20 away from a recent two-month high at $22.49.
 
 
Looking at the chart, it seems that traders reentered the market after the RSI hit a support level at 65.00
 
As of writing, price strength is at a reading of 69.05, with the next visible resistance zone at 72.00.
 
Should today’s momentum extend throughout the week, there is a good chance that solana will climb past $23.00.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
Do you expect solana bulls to maintain current market sentiment? Let us know your thoughts in the comments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon Adoption Accelerates As MATIC Rises 10%]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756fe55d20</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/polygon-adoption-accelerates-as-matic-rises-10/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T14:35:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data suggests that Polygon adoption has been accelerating as MATIC has enjoyed an increase of 10% during the past day.
 
Polygon Network Growth Has Been Steadily Rising Recently
 
According to data from the on-chain analytics firm Santiment, MATIC addresses are being created at an increasingly faster rate. The relevant indicator here is the “network growth,” which measures the total amount of new Polygon addresses that are coming online on the blockchain.
 
New addresses may be considered analogous to new users coming into the network, so this metric can provide us with hints about how the adoption of the cryptocurrency is coming along.
 
When the value of the indicator is high, it means that a large number of new addresses are being created on the network right now. Naturally, th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hououin Kyouma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK to Exclude 'Unbacked’ Cryptocurrencies From Digital Securities Sandbox Initiative]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148082</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148082/uk-exclude-unbacked-cryptocurrencies-digital-securities-sandbox-initiative"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T14:28:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The British government does not plan to modify the existing legislative framework for derivatives and unbacked cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Canadian WonderFi, Coinsquare, and Coinsmart Merge]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756fe7be30</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/canadian-wonderfi-coinsquare-and-coinsmart-merge/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T14:19:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Three cryptocurrency exchanges based in Canada, WonderFi,  
CoinSmart, and Coinsquare, have reportedly completed a merger deal. The  
combined entity plans to invest in SmartPay, a digital asset payments platform  
launched by Coinsmart in 2020.
WonderFi is a public  
company listed on the Toronto Stock Exchange. The company operates several  
brands, including Coinsquare and Coinsmart. Coinsquare is a crypto marketplace  
that allows users to trade and manage their financial assets, while Coinsmart  
provides digital asset services for institutional investors.
The new entity resulting  
from the business combination will reportedly focus on consolidating Bitbuy and Coinsquare, according to Binu Koshy, a spokesperson of the  
companies quoted by the Financial Post.
Coinsmart Payment  
Plat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[India’s External Affairs Minister Shuns BRICS Currency Talks, Prioritizes Rupee’s Strength Instead]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756fe0b455</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/indias-external-affairs-minister-shuns-brics-currency-talks-prioritizes-rupees-strength-instead/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T14:13:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Members of the BRICS alliance are meeting at a summit in Johannesburg, South Africa, in August, focusing attention on the potential for the BRICS bloc to create a gold-backed reserve currency. However, Subrahmanyam Jaishankar, India’s external affairs minister, said India isn’t interested in issuing a common BRICS currency. Instead, he said India is more concerned with strengthening the rupee.
 
India Snubs Common Currency Idea, Reduces Russian Oil Imports While Increasing U.S. Crude Purchases
 
In recent times, a great deal of interest is aimed at the BRICS nations — Brazil, Russia, India, China, and South Africa. In August, BRICS ministers plan to discuss adding new members to the alliance and creating a gold-backed common currency. Last week, Rasoul Mousavi, a representative from Iran’s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Are Play-to-Earn (P2E) Games?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=118693</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-are-play-to-earn-p2e-games"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T13:49:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unlike in regular games, where in-game items are held on walled-off data networks and owned by the companies that created the game, NFTs enable players to own the unique assets that they purchase.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFT Lender Gondi Goes Live, Raises $5.3M Round Led by Hack.vc]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756fedb9dd</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/web3/2023/07/11/nft-lender-gondi-goes-live-raises-53m-round-led-by-hackvc/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T13:37:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer Florida Street's seed round features Hack.vc, Foundation Capital, Dragonfly Capital, Pantera Capital, 6th Man Ventures and others.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cross-Chain Protocol Axelar to Develop Web3 Services With Microsoft Azure]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756fedb9c6</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/07/11/cross-chain-protocol-axelar-to-develop-web3-services-with-microsoft-azure/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T13:37:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Axelar said further plans with Microsoft include connecting private and public blockchains that use OpenAI services to create Web3 products.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Mover Americas: GBTC Discount Narrows to Lowest Since May 2022]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756fedb9b9</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/07/11/first-mover-americas-gbtc-discount-narrows-to-lowest-since-may-2022/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T13:37:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest price moves in bitcoin (BTC) and crypto markets in context for July 11, 2023. First Mover is CoinDesk’s daily newsletter that contextualizes the latest actions in the crypto markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lyllah Ledesma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MetaMask Developer ConsenSys Brings Layer 2 Blockchain ‘Linea’ to Ethereum Mainnet]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756fedb99f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/07/11/metamask-developer-consensys-brings-layer-2-blockchain-linea-to-ethereum-mainnet/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T13:37:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The rollup chain from ConsenSys, known as a zkEVM, joins a growing field of projects aiming to expand access to Ethereum using zero-knowledge cryptography.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Kessler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Marex Unveils Bitcoin, Ether-Linked Long Strategy With Dollar Index as Hedge]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756fedb994</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/07/11/marex-unveils-bitcoin-ether-linked-long-strategy-with-dollar-index-as-hedge/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T13:37:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["The dollar index futures act a robust complement to the long-only portfolio from both a thematic and empirical perspective," Marex's Mark Arasaratnam said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aave DAO to Vote on Gho Stablecoin Deployment on Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756fedb98d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/07/11/aave-dao-to-vote-on-gho-stablecoin-deployment-on-ethereum/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T13:37:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GHO has been in the works for over a year and was issued on a testnet earlier this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi Protocol Holding 55% of Algorand Value to Shut Down]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756fedb981</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/07/11/defi-protocol-holding-55-of-algorand-value-to-shut-down/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T13:37:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Algofi, the largest decentralized finance protocol on layer-1 blockchain Algorand, said it will shut down and plans to halt lending, borrowing and trading imminently.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK Treasury Starts Consultation on Five-Year Digital Securities Trial]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756fedb978</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/07/11/uk-treasury-starts-consultations-on-five-year-digital-securities-trial/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T13:37:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The pilot will relax regulations for digital bonds and equities – but not unbacked crypto, like bitcoin or ether.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack Schickler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multichain’s Recent Struggles Raise Suspicion Of A Rug Pull: Chainalysis]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756fedcb59</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/multichain-recent-struggles-suspicion-of-a-rug-pull/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T13:37:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In one of the biggest crypto attacks, cross-chain bridge protocol Multichain recently experienced unauthorized withdrawals of millions worth of crypto assets from its repositories. 
 
On July 6, 2023, more than $125 million worth of different cryptocurrencies were lost to this attack. Almost $120 million of that figure came from Multichain’s Fantom bridge, with the remaining coming from the Dogecoin, Moonriver, Kava, and Conflux bridges. Assets removed from the cross-chain protocol include wrapped Ether (wETH), wrapped Bitcoin (wBTC), USDC, and USDT.
 
However, contrary to popular beliefs of an outside attack, blockchain analytics company Chainalysis believes this multi-million dollar exploit could have been a hack or rug pull orchestrated by insiders, due in part to Multichain’s recent is…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Opeyemi Sule</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Trading Volume Continues To Rise, Now 75% Higher Than FTX Lows]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756fedcb56</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-trading-volume-rise-75-higher-ftx-lows/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T13:37:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data shows the Bitcoin transfer volume has recently reached levels 75% higher than the FTX crash lows as it continues its uptrend.
 
Bitcoin Total Transfer Volume Has Continued To Go Up Recently
 
According to the latest weekly report from Glassnode, the BTC transfer volume has increased to $4.2 billion per day now. The “transfer volume” here refers to the total amount of Bitcoin (in USD) that’s being involved in transactions on the blockchain.
 
When the value of this metric is high, it means that holders are moving around a significant number of coins on the network. Such a trend is generally a sign that the traders are actively participating in the market.
 
On the other hand, low values imply the blockchain isn’t registering much activity right now. This kind of trend may sugg…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hououin Kyouma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Rewards On Minecraft? This Partnership Makes It Possible]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756fedcb54</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-rewards-minecraft-partnership-make-possible/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T13:37:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin transactions have been enabled on the popular videogame Minecraft. The number one cryptocurrency by market cap has seen developments, innovations, and expansion in its ecosystem, and a new partnership could push adoption one step closer to the mainstream with the legendary title. 
 
 
Bitcoin On Minecraft, One Step Closer To The Mainstream
 
According to a press release shared with Bitcoinist, payment processor ZEBEDEE announced a partnership with Bitcoin education company Satlantis. The partners will allow Minecraft users to earn BTC rewards through a Satlantis server.
 
Per the announcement, over 150,000 sats will be rewarded to players daily. Reward payments will be fully processed on the Bitcoin network within the Minecraft platform.
 
Any gamer can earn rewards by spending tim…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reynaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Faces Backlash: Bank Of England Governor Expresses Disapproval]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756fedcb4d</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-slammed-by-boe-governor/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T13:37:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies have long been a subject of debate and scrutiny within the financial world. Bank of England Governor Andrew Bailey recently added his voice to the conversation, expressing skepticism about their status as true currencies. 
 
In a speech delivered at the Financial and Professional Services Dinner in London, Bailey asserted that Bitcoin and its counterparts fall short of meeting the standards necessary to be recognized as legitimate forms of money. Instead, he proposed an alternative concept: enhanced digital money. 
 
 
Bailey’s remarks shed light on the ongoing struggle to define the future of currency and highlight the growing interest in exploring innovative solutions beyond traditional fiat currencies. In a world increasingly driven by digitalization, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi Project Rodeo Finance Hacked for $888,000 in Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148068</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148068/layer-2-defi-project-rodeo-finance-hacked-472-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T13:05:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An exploiter was able to run away with roughly $888,000 in Ethereum from Rodeo’s interest-bearing USDC pool.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Now Earn Bitcoin for Playing Minecraft—Here’s How]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148037</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148037/you-can-now-earn-bitcoin-playing-minecraft-heres-how"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T13:01:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Satlantis Minecraft server is now giving out over 1 million satoshis per week in partnership with Bitcoin payments startup Zebedee.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Magic Johnson-Backed SimWin Sports Infuses Fantasy Football With AI and NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148033</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148033/magic-johnson-fantasy-football-ai-nft-simwin-sports"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The platform aims to bridge eSports and fantasy sports with a 24/7 virtual football league.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[As Zimbabwe’s Fiat Currency Crashes Again, Bitcoin Adoption Is Poised To Last]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756fd4a08d</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/with-return-of-zimbabwe-inflation-bitcoin-adoption-will-stick"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T12:48:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is an opinion by Thabo P. Ncube, a Bitcoiner who lived through Zimbabwe’s hyperinflation in 2008.
The Reserve Bank of Zimbabwe (RBZ), the fiat custodian and lender of last resort in the country, recently “liberalized” its much-vaunted foreign exchange auction trading system in hopes of selling foreign currencies at market-determined exchange rates through regulated banks.
Zimbabwe uses a multi-currency system, with 80% of its economy being dollarized, according to economists. The black-market rate for the U.S. dollar (USD) has recently been twice as high or even higher than the official rate backed by the RBZ.
In January 2023, the local Zimbabwean dollar (ZWL) was trading at about ZWL$705 to $1, but on June 7, 2023, just after the bank’s pivot, the official price was about ZWL$4,868 t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thabo P. Ncube</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFT-Powered Dan Harmon Series 'Krapopolis' Finally Gets Premiere Date]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148057</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148057/nft-powered-dan-harmon-series-krapopolis-finally-gets-premiere-date"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T12:13:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An NFT collection affiliated with Harmon’s new animated series on Fox has already generated almost $1 million in sales.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MATIC Soars 9% Ahead of Polygon 2.0 Rollout, Rebounding Network Growth]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148047</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148047/matic-soars-9-ahead-polygon-2-0-rollout-rebounding-network-growth"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T11:25:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon’s uptick can likely be attributed to rebounding on-chain growth and the completion of a $66 million sell-off by bankrupt Celsius.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paradigm Files Amicus Brief in SEC’s Lawsuit Against Bittrex]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148053</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148053/paradigm-files-amicus-brief-sec-lawsuit-against-bittrex"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T10:57:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC lacks the authority to regulate secondary markets for crypto assets, argues crypto investment firm Paradigm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Now Store Your Bitcoin Private Key as Colors]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148026</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148026/bitcoin-private-key-phrase-encoding-colors"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T00:10:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new tool for backing up your private keys could make it even harder for thieves—and the government—to seize your coins.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale Cries Foul Over SEC Approval of a Different Kind of Bitcoin ETF]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148009</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148009/grayscale-protests-sec-approval-leveraged-bitcoin-futures-not-spot-etf"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T00:02:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company says the difference between a leveraged Bitcoin future ETF and a spot Bitcoin ETF isn’t enough to stonewall the latter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix Taps AI To Push Visual Effects Beyond the Green Screen]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147986</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147986/netflix-ai-green-screen-magenta-visual-effects-movies"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T23:40:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why go for a green screen when there’s an AI-powered magenta option?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fei Protocol Discord Was Not 'Seized' Amid Class-Action Lawsuit, Says Lawyer]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147994</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147994/fei-protocol-dao-discord-not-seized-by-court"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T23:20:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A message appearing on Fei Labs' Discord alerted investors who may have been hurt by its shaky launch event in April 2021 on how to file a notice for compensation as part of an ongoing class-action lawsuit against the platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily Ordinals Inscriptions Approach All-Time High as Bitcoin Fees Remain Low]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148021</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148021/daily-ordinals-bitcoin-inscriptions-near-all-time-high-low-fees"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T23:12:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ordinals ecosystem has seen a flood of new projects, and fees have remained low.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['The Machines Arena' Adds In-Game Rewards That Can Be Minted as NFTs (Eventually)]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=148008</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/148008/machines-arena-adds-in-game-rewards-minted-nfts-eventually"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T22:43:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Players with lots of XP in The Machines Arena will be able to unlock character skins that can later be minted and traded.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scientists Use AI to Discover Drugs That Kill 'Zombie Cells', Fight Age-Related Diseases]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147681</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147681/ai-drug-discovery-senolytic"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T22:29:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A group of researchers used AI to do in five minutes what could have taken weeks: Discovering new drugs that can kill senescent cells.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ApeCoin Crashes to All-Time Low as Bored Ape Yacht Club NFT Prices Sink]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147982</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147982/apecoin-crashes-all-time-low-bored-ape-yacht-club-nft-prices-sink"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T20:38:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ethereum token linked to Yuga Labs' Bored Ape Yacht Club collection has now fallen nearly 93% from its peak price.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Will Reach $120K Before 2025, Standard Chartered Predicts]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147970</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147970/bitcoin-will-reach-120k-before-2025-standard-chartered-predicts"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T19:38:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The British bank believes miners will soon begin hoarding their coins and choking off available market supply.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former SEC Chair Says Bitcoin ETF Could Be Approved—If These Conditions Are Met]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147975</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147975/former-sec-chair-says-bitcoin-etf-should-be-approved-if-conditions-met"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T19:09:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The former SEC chair said that a Bitcoin ETF will be approved in the States if an applicant can prove it's an efficient way for investors to buy BTC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Staked Ethereum Now Accounts for 20% of the Total Supply]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147968</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147968/staked-ethereum-now-accounts-for-20-of-the-total-supply"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T18:17:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The amount of Ethereum pledged to secure the network has grown significantly since withdrawals were enabled in April.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vanguard Now Owns $560 Million Worth of Bitcoin Mining Stocks]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147950</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147950/vanguard-owns-560-million-bitcoin-mining-stocks"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T17:58:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The $7.2 trillion asset manager now owns half a billion dollars worth of Riot Blockchain and Marathon Digital shares.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Half a Billion Has Poured Into Bitcoin Funds in Past Three Weeks]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147925</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147925/half-a-billion-has-poured-into-bitcoin-funds-in-past-three-weeks"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T17:18:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[But exchange inflows are at a cycle low, signaling that it's primarily institutions that feel bullish.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[100 Thieves' Moe Says Blockchain Games Will 'Eventually' Be Accepted by Livestreamers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/xHhh62ID/100-thieves-moe-says-blockchain-games-will-eventually-be-accepted-by-livestreamers</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/xHhh62ID/100-thieves-moe-says-blockchain-games-will-eventually-be-accepted-by-livestreamers"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T16:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[100 Thieves content creator and gamer Moe also goes by "Yassuo" online after his favorite League of Legends character. Decrypt's Kate Irwin asks him about 100 Thieves' future crypto plans and whether Moe thinks creators like xQc and Pokimane might ever come around to blockchain games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Twitter Reacts to Arkham’s New 'Dox-to-Earn' Intelligence Exchange]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147920</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147920/crypto-twitter-reacts-arkhams-new-dox-earn-intelligence-exchange"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T16:09:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain intelligence firm Arkham is opening an exchange where data on the identities of crypto wallet owners can be traded and requested.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gutter Cat Gang Twitter Hacked, At Least $750K Worth of NFTs Swiped]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147913</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147913/gutter-cat-gang-twitter-hacked-at-least-750k-worth-nfts-swiped"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T15:34:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Twitter account for the NFT project Gutter Cat Gang were hacked to promote a fake airdrop to an audience of more than 124,000 followers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Bitcoin an Investment or a Currency ?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=5738</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/bitcoin-investment-or-currency"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T14:35:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin is being explored as three distinct ideas: a currency, an asset and a commodity. Because regulation takes place mostly at state level, Bitcoin has become all three things simultaneously in different parts of the world.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Hussey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Hashing?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=5681</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/hashing"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T14:34:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hashing is one of the most crucial pieces of technology that keeps the Bitcoin network secure. But how does it work?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Hussey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stepn Creator's Next Game Is a Social MMO Called Gas Hero]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147876</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147876/stepn-creators-next-game-social-mmo-called-gas-hero"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gas Hero, from the developer of move-to-earn game Stepn, takes place in a dystopian world where a powerful AI has triggered nuclear war.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is the Lightning Network? Bitcoin's Scalability Solution.]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=5684</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/bitcoin-lightning-network"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lightning Network is a scaling solution that attempts to address Bitcoin's slow transaction speeds and high transaction costs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Hussey,Tim Copeland,Daniel Phillips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto, Stablecoins May Pose 'Threat to Financial Stability' if Widely Used: BIS Survey]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147898</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147898/crypto-stablecoins-may-pose-threat-financial-stability-widely-used-bis-survey"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T12:23:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two dozen central banks are also expected to launch either wholesale or consumer-facing retail CBDCs by the end of the decade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Hash Rate Hits New All-Time High Amid Stagnating Prices]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147890</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147890/bitcoin-hash-rate-hits-new-all-time-high-stagnating-prices"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T12:04:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The computing power of the Bitcoin network is at its highest levels again, making the world’s largest cryptocurrency more secure than ever.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recovering Funds Transferred Via Bitcoin ATMs Is 'Virtually Untraceable', Say Iowa Authorities]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147884</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147884/recovering-funds-transferred-bitcoin-atms-is-virtually-untraceable-say-iowa-authorities"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T10:28:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Although they account for a fraction of the illicit transactions done in crypto, Bitcoin ATMs are disproportionately popular among scammers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PEPE Leads Meme Coin Losses as Fresh Token Launches Grab Trader’s Attention]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147889</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147889/pepe-leads-meme-coin-losses-fresh-token-launches-grab-traders-attention"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T10:15:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The top meme coins are facing pressures due to the arrival of new meme coins coupled with losses in Bitcoin and Ethereum.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sarah Silverman Sues Meta, OpenAI for Training AI Models on Her Book]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147885</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147885/sarah-silverman-sues-meta-openai-training-ai-models-her-book"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T10:06:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The comedian and two other authors say their work was used to train AI-powered chatbots without their permission.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alys Key</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Code Commits Drop Despite Rising Prices]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147853</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147853/open-source-crypto-developer-statistics"/>
        <updated>2023-07-09T23:50:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A decrease in the amount of development activity could be attributed to the explosive popularity of artificial intelligence technologies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Will Make Games 'Faster, Cheaper and Better': Unity CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147849</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147849/ai-will-make-games-faster-cheaper-and-better-unity-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-07-09T20:11:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“I don't think anybody's job on the creation side is going to be taken by an AI, but it will get taken by a human using AI."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donovan Choy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Booster Robert F. Kennedy Jr. Bought Bitcoin Despite Recent Claim: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147843</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147843/robert-f-kennedy-hodl-bought-own-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-07-09T19:42:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kennedy’s campaign also flip-flopped on who in his family owned the classic cryptocurrency.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Inventor Vitalik Buterin Has Advice for Bitcoiners]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147842</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147842/ethereum-inventor-vitalik-buterin-bitcoin-advice"/>
        <updated>2023-07-09T19:31:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If Bitcoin wants to become more than payments, it needs to experiment more, says the blockchain innovator.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Instagram Minus Pics’: Musk and Zuckerberg Trade Taunts as Twitter Threat Threads Nears 100 Million Users]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147836</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147836/instagram-minus-pics-musk-zuckerberg-trade-taunts-twitter-threat-threads-100-million-users"/>
        <updated>2023-07-09T18:44:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI, the metaverse, and self-driving cars dropped off the radar as the tech founders grappled for social media dominance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week on Crypto Twitter: Winklevoss Calls on Silbert to Negotiate, Sues Him 3 Days Later]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147823</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147823/this-week-on-crypto-twitter-winklevoss-silbert-cz-fud-mark-cuban"/>
        <updated>2023-07-09T18:16:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[And Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao once again told his followers to ignore FUD.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Games of the Future Are Going to Be Different," Says Splinterlands Cofounder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/sQv6zcil/games-of-the-future-are-going-to-be-different-says-splinterlands-cofounder</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/sQv6zcil/games-of-the-future-are-going-to-be-different-says-splinterlands-cofounder"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T20:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Splinterlands Cofounder Matt Rosen tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about how the game has evolved over its five-year history and why he doesn't listen to the FUD around crypto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Champions Ascension: Like 'For Honor' with NFTs?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/gvM9ajww/inside-champions-ascension-like-for-honor-with-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/gvM9ajww/inside-champions-ascension-like-for-honor-with-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T22:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plai Labs Marketing Director Payton Kaleiwahea tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about player response to the combat game Champions Ascension in development, which offers arena combat, raid bosses, AI landscape features, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Activision VP Michael Lee: Gaming Is Crypto's 'Killer App']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/M9ulXrb3/ex-activision-vp-michael-lee-gaming-is-cryptos-killer-app</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/M9ulXrb3/ex-activision-vp-michael-lee-gaming-is-cryptos-killer-app"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Activision Vice President Michael Lee is now the SVP of Growth at Matter Labs. At the 3XP gaming conference, Lee sat down with Decrypt's Kate Irwin to discuss crypto gaming and give his predictions for the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Behind the Scenes with AMGI Studios and My Pet Hooligan]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/eQ71oapI/behind-the-scenes-with-amgi-studios-and-my-pet-hooligan</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/eQ71oapI/behind-the-scenes-with-amgi-studios-and-my-pet-hooligan"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T21:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin goes to Burbank, California for a behind-the-scenes tour of AMGI Studios, the developers of upcoming game My Pet Hooligan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Legend of Arcardia Chose Sui Over EVM Chains]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/H6JSRJIk/why-legend-of-arcardia-chose-sui-over-evm-chains</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/H6JSRJIk/why-legend-of-arcardia-chose-sui-over-evm-chains"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T21:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Legend of Arcadia Executive Producer Andy Lee tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the game and why they switched from EVM to new protocol Sui.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rumble Racing Star Game Preview: Is This Mario Kart With NFTs?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/lXVkuaeq/rumble-racing-star-game-preview-is-this-mario-kart-with-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/lXVkuaeq/rumble-racing-star-game-preview-is-this-mario-kart-with-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T16:47:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin shares a first look at Delabs' upcoming lawn mower racing game Rumble Racing Star, which offers a large cast of quirky characters pulled from the worlds of Bored Ape Yacht Club, Pudgy Penguins, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Laguna Games Turned Down 'Game of Thrones' for Crypto Unicorns]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/IqET3GYs/why-laguna-games-turned-down-game-of-thrones-for-crypto-unicorns</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/IqET3GYs/why-laguna-games-turned-down-game-of-thrones-for-crypto-unicorns"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T21:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin chats with Laguna Games about why the team chose to move away from an offer with WB Games to develop a Game of Thrones licensed title—and made Crypto Unicorns instead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mythical Games CEO John Linden on NFL Rivals Topping 1M Downloads]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/nDhvMd8r/mythical-games-ceo-john-linden-on-nfl-rivals-topping-1m-downloads</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/nDhvMd8r/mythical-games-ceo-john-linden-on-nfl-rivals-topping-1m-downloads"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T23:49:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mythical Games just raised a $37 million Series C1 round on the back of the early success of NFL Rivals, which has already topped a million downloads in two months. Mythical CEO John Linden joins Decrypt's Andrew Hayward to discuss the launch and impact of NFL Rivals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Ava Labs Is Approaching Gaming on Avalanche]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/M4TqVEkK/how-ava-labs-is-approaching-gaming-on-avalanche</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/M4TqVEkK/how-ava-labs-is-approaching-gaming-on-avalanche"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T22:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At 3XP, Ava Labs Head of Gaming Ed Chang sat down with Decrypt's Kate Irwin to discuss some of the biggest Avalanche-based games on the horizon and how the company is approaching and thinking about Web3 gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ogimi Founder David Gull on Why AI Should Be Your Meditation Coach]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DnNqBruk/ogimi-founder-david-gull-on-why-ai-should-be-your-meditation-coach</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DnNqBruk/ogimi-founder-david-gull-on-why-ai-should-be-your-meditation-coach"/>
        <updated>2023-06-25T18:45:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ogimi founder David Gull speaks with Decrypt's Jason Nelson about its AI-driven meditation guides and how the technology can enable a more unique, custom-tailored meditation experience for users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VaynerSports Gaming VP Discusses Web3 Content Creators, Decentralized Streaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/1MvGbnK5/vaynersports-gaming-vp-discusses-web3-content-creators-decentralized-streaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/1MvGbnK5/vaynersports-gaming-vp-discusses-web3-content-creators-decentralized-streaming"/>
        <updated>2023-06-24T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Darren Glover, VP of Gaming at talent management agency VaynerSports, sat down with Decrypt's Kate Irwin at the 3XP expo to discuss the challenges faced by Web3-centric content creators, the current state of the esports market, and how decentralized streaming platforms can challenge centralized leaders like Twitch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NYXL Co-Founder on the State of Esports and Crypto Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/xDHUNFLB/nyxl-co-founder-on-the-state-of-esports-and-crypto-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/xDHUNFLB/nyxl-co-founder-on-the-state-of-esports-and-crypto-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-06-23T22:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rohit Gupta, co-founder of esports team NYXL, chats with Decrypt's Kate Irwin at the 3XP expo to discuss challenges faced by the esports industry and opportunities and experiments in Web3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is GameBridge? Inside Shrapnel's Gaming Innovation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/xqVjzGLr/what-is-gamebridge-inside-shrapnels-gaming-innovation</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/xqVjzGLr/what-is-gamebridge-inside-shrapnels-gaming-innovation"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marc Mercuri, Head of Platform for Web3 shooter Shrapnel, speaks with Decrypt's Kate Irwin at the 3XP expo about GameBridge, a feature that simplifies blockchain item composability and interoperability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gods Unchained Executive Producer Discusses Epic Games Store Move]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/hjLymzUL/gods-unchained-executive-producer-discusses-epic-games-store-move</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/hjLymzUL/gods-unchained-executive-producer-discusses-epic-games-store-move"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daniel Paez, Executive Producer on Immutable X-based card-battler Gods Unchained, discusses the long-running NFT game's launch on the Epic Games Store and the opportunity it provides.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Play-to-Earn Is Not Dead. It Will Never Die' Says Words with Friends Creator Paul Bettner]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/znmOo9vp/play-to-earn-is-not-dead-it-will-never-die-says-words-with-friends-creator-paul-bettner</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/znmOo9vp/play-to-earn-is-not-dead-it-will-never-die-says-words-with-friends-creator-paul-bettner"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T14:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Words With Friends and Wildcard Creator Paul Bettner tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about his perspective on Axie Infinity and Web3 games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cross the Ages Game Review: A Tough But Rewarding Card Battler]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/2PfzFDVY/cross-the-ages-game-review-a-tough-but-rewarding-card-battler</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/2PfzFDVY/cross-the-ages-game-review-a-tough-but-rewarding-card-battler"/>
        <updated>2023-06-18T12:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cross the Ages is a digital collectible card game that challenges players to duel online opponents—and you can even mint your cards as tradable NFTs. It's complex and difficult to grasp at first, but this mobile-first game has some serious strategic upside. GG contributor Ryan Gladwin puts Cross the Ages through its paces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["AI Is Game-Changing But Needs Fact-Checking": AlchemyAI Project Lead]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/HXlThlXv/ai-is-game-changing-but-needs-fact-checking-alchemyai-project-lead</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/HXlThlXv/ai-is-game-changing-but-needs-fact-checking-alchemyai-project-lead"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this interview, Decrypt's Jason Nelson chats with Alchemy product manager and AlchemyAI project lead Elan Halpern on blockchain analysis using ChatGPT, what AI means for better user experience, and the need to fact-check AI. Halpern also gives a demo of the new AlchemyAI ChatGPT plugin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fractal Is Like an Arcade, Says Twitch Co-Founder Justin Kan]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/6r6Mdwt6/fractal-is-like-an-arcade-says-twitch-co-founder-justin-kan</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/6r6Mdwt6/fractal-is-like-an-arcade-says-twitch-co-founder-justin-kan"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Justin Kan was a co-founder of Twitch and now works on Fractal, a Web3 gaming startup. Kan tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about his new company and what he's up to.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are NFTs the Next SEC Target?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/YaGgY87J/are-nfts-the-next-sec-target</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/YaGgY87J/are-nfts-the-next-sec-target"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T20:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin discusses the current regulatory climate in the U.S. with Gala Games' President of Blockchain Jason Brink.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>