<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-12-21T20:15:24.923Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-12-21T20:15:24.923Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Economist Harry Dent’s Grim Prediction — 2024 Market Crash to Eclipse Great Depression]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7483193cb5</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/economist-harry-dents-grim-prediction-2024-market-crash-to-eclipse-great-depression/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T20:09:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent interview with Fox News, renowned economist Harry Dent issued a dire prediction for the global economy, forecasting 2024 to be the year of the most significant financial crash in living memory. Citing a combination of overvalued markets, excessive stimulus spending, and artificial inflation of asset prices, Dent’s analysis paints a grim picture of the near future. With his reputation for contrarian yet often accurate forecasts, Dent’s warnings carry weight in financial circles.
 
Harry Dent Anticipates Severe Financial Turmoil in 2024
 
Harry Dent, known for his unconventional yet insightful market analyses, told Fox News that the current economic situation is “100% artificial,” driven by unprecedented levels of money printing and deficit spending amounting to $27 trillion over…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fake AI Ripple CEO Ad Targets XRP Holders on YouTube]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19125801/Fake-AI-Ripple-CEO-Ad-Targets-XRP-Holders-on-YouTube</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19125801/Fake-AI-Ripple-CEO-Ad-Targets-XRP-Holders-on-YouTube"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T20:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The deceptive ad is promoting a fraudulent 100m XRP giveaway, asking investors to engage by sending up to 500,000 tokens.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Appeals Court Officially Confiscates 69,370 Bitcoins from Silk Road]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19125805/US-Appeals-Court-Officially-Confiscates-69370-Bitcoins-from-Silk-Road</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19125805/US-Appeals-Court-Officially-Confiscates-69370-Bitcoins-from-Silk-Road"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T20:03:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent development, a U.S. appeals court has successfully completed the legal proceedings required...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Above Resistance!!! Live from St Louis - CryptoWorld, ZPods & Bare Wood!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19125804/Bitcoin-Above-Resistance-Live-from-St-Louis-CryptoWorld-ZPods-Bare-Wood</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19125804/Bitcoin-Above-Resistance-Live-from-St-Louis-CryptoWorld-ZPods-Bare-Wood"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T20:03:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://Unconfiscatable.com was Streamed Live on this Channel!The Financial Summit will be back in the Maldives: https://TheFinancialSummit.comCryptoWorld: https://twitter.com/shopcryptoworld?lang=enZPods: https://www.zpodsforsleep.com/Bare Wood: https://barewoodspirits.com/Promo Video:...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Neon EVM Hits Record-High 730 TPS On Mainnet]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19125784/Neon-EVM-Hits-Record-High-730-TPS-On-Mainnet</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19125784/Neon-EVM-Hits-Record-High-730-TPS-On-Mainnet"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T20:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the rapidly evolving landscape of blockchain technology, Neon EVM, a smart contract on Solana (SOL) has emerged as a frontrunner by introducing a landmark parallel processing architecture on its mainnet.  This approach has enabled Neon EVM to achieve an increase in performance, scalability,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum’s Dencun upgrade set for 2024 testnet launch]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19125800/Ethereums-Dencun-upgrade-set-for-2024-testnet-launch</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19125800/Ethereums-Dencun-upgrade-set-for-2024-testnet-launch"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T20:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum developers have tentatively decided on Jan. 17, 2024, for the upcoming “Dencun” upgrade’s first testnet deployment during the latest bi-weekly dev meeting on Dec. 21. Originally slated for the last quarter of 2023, the ‘Dencun upgrade was pushed to 2024 due to the engineering...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Argentina Confirms Crypto Milestone, OKs Bitcoin-Denominated Financial Contracts]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19125797/Argentina-Confirms-Crypto-Milestone-OKs-Bitcoin-Denominated-Financial-Contracts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19125797/Argentina-Confirms-Crypto-Milestone-OKs-Bitcoin-Denominated-Financial-Contracts"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T19:50:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Argentine government has confirmed that financial contracts can now be denominated in Bitcoin. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Got a Solana Saga Before They Sold Out? Here Are All the Airdrops You Can Claim]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19125779/Got-a-Solana-Saga-Before-They-Sold-Out-Here-Are-All-the-Airdrops-You-Can-Claim</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19125779/Got-a-Solana-Saga-Before-They-Sold-Out-Here-Are-All-the-Airdrops-You-Can-Claim"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T19:48:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond BONK: Solana Saga owners can now claim multiple token airdrops and other perks, with more in the works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price Could See $48,000, Top Trader Says]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19125792/Bitcoin-BTC-Price-Could-See-48000-Top-Trader-Says</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19125792/Bitcoin-BTC-Price-Could-See-48000-Top-Trader-Says"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T19:38:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top traders have identified key patterns suggesting a potential Bitcoin (BTC) surge]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MATIC Set for Major Price Move as Whale Activity Spikes]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19125762/MATIC-Set-for-Major-Price-Move-as-Whale-Activity-Spikes</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19125762/MATIC-Set-for-Major-Price-Move-as-Whale-Activity-Spikes"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T19:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MATIC whales are on the move hinting at a major price shake up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockdaemon integrates LayerZero to bring cross-chain capabilities to self-custodial wallet]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19125742/Blockdaemon-integrates-LayerZero-to-bring-cross-chain-capabilities-to-self-custodial-wallet</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19125742/Blockdaemon-integrates-LayerZero-to-bring-cross-chain-capabilities-to-self-custodial-wallet"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T19:28:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blockdaemon will integrate the cross-chain messaging capabilities of LayerZero into its self-custodial wallet. The partnership further enhances LayerZero’s security, Ryan Zarick, CTO of LayerZero Labs said. Blockchain infrastructure firm Blockdaemon is partnering with LayerZero Labs, the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JUST IN! Coinbase Announces It Will Suspend Trading in These Four Altcoins!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19125738/JUST-IN-Coinbase-Announces-It-Will-Suspend-Trading-in-These-Four-Altcoins</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19125738/JUST-IN-Coinbase-Announces-It-Will-Suspend-Trading-in-These-Four-Altcoins"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T19:15:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In its latest post, Coinbase announced that it will suspend the trading of altcoins named ATA, DREP, MONA and SYLO. Continue Reading: JUST IN! Coinbase Announces It Will Suspend Trading in These Four Altcoins!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Circle, Coinbase receive French regulatory approvals]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19125734/Circle-Coinbase-receive-French-regulatory-approvals</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19125734/Circle-Coinbase-receive-French-regulatory-approvals"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T19:12:16.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Will Outperform Bitcoin in Next Bull Market, Says Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19125719/Ethereum-Will-Outperform-Bitcoin-in-Next-Bull-Market-Says-Analyst</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19125719/Ethereum-Will-Outperform-Bitcoin-in-Next-Bull-Market-Says-Analyst"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T19:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Influencer and cryptocurrency analyst Lark Davis expressed his optimism that Ether (ETH), the second-largest digital asset by market cap, will outperform Bitcoin (BTC) in the anticipated bull market. Davis made this statement in a recent interview where he argued that Ethereum’s performance will...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano Founder Calls Out Omission From Biggest Crypto Report Of The Year]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7483001c0f</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/cardano-omission-crypto-report/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T19:07:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano founder Charles Hoskinson has responded to what seems to be a deliberate exclusion of the network from one of the biggest crypto reports of the year. The Messari seventh annual crypto report titled “Crypto Theses for 2024” is a 200-page report covering a range of topics from Layer 1 blockchains to decentralized finance (DeFi), among other things. However, the Cardano community was quick to notice that the network was not mentioned and has taken to social media to demand answers.
 
Cardano Founder Responds To Messari’s Omission
 
Following the release of the Messari crypto report, one community member took to X (formerly Twitter) to call out the platform for omitting Cardan. In the post, @StakeWithPride points out each blockchain and how many times they were mentioned in the article…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Take a Cautious Approach’ – Santiment Issues Warning on Solana, NEAR Protocol and One Bitcoin Ecosystem Altcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19125718/Take-a-Cautious-Approach-Santiment-Issues-Warning-on-Solana-NEAR-Protocol-and-One-Bitcoin-Ecosystem-Altcoin</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19125718/Take-a-Cautious-Approach-Santiment-Issues-Warning-on-Solana-NEAR-Protocol-and-One-Bitcoin-Ecosystem-Altcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T19:05:58.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Set to Approve First Bitcoin Spot ETF in January 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19125717/SEC-Set-to-Approve-First-Bitcoin-Spot-ETF-in-January-2024</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19125717/SEC-Set-to-Approve-First-Bitcoin-Spot-ETF-in-January-2024"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T19:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A closer look at the SEC's possible approval of a Bitcoin ETF in January and its impact on the market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Public Company Will Follow Saylor's Bitcoin Strategy? | EP 893]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19125082/What-Public-Company-Will-Follow-Saylors-Bitcoin-Strategy-EP-893</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19125082/What-Public-Company-Will-Follow-Saylors-Bitcoin-Strategy-EP-893"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T19:04:32.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Bittensor Falls More Than 5% In 24 hours]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19125730/Cryptocurrency-Bittensor-Falls-More-Than-5-In-24-hours</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19125730/Cryptocurrency-Bittensor-Falls-More-Than-5-In-24-hours"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T19:02:40.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Algorand's Price Increased More Than 7% Within 24 hours]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19125731/Cryptocurrency-Algorands-Price-Increased-More-Than-7-Within-24-hours</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19125731/Cryptocurrency-Algorands-Price-Increased-More-Than-7-Within-24-hours"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T19:02:32.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Stacks Decreases More Than 8% Within 24 hours]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19125732/Cryptocurrency-Stacks-Decreases-More-Than-8-Within-24-hours</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19125732/Cryptocurrency-Stacks-Decreases-More-Than-8-Within-24-hours"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T19:01:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stacks's (CRYPTO: STX) price has decreased 8.6% over the past 24 hours to $1.4. This is contrary to the coins performance over the past week where it has experienced an up-trend of 32.0%, moving from $1.08 to its current price. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano Founder Calls Out Omission From Biggest Crypto Report Of The Year]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19125710/Cardano-Founder-Calls-Out-Omission-From-Biggest-Crypto-Report-Of-The-Year</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19125710/Cardano-Founder-Calls-Out-Omission-From-Biggest-Crypto-Report-Of-The-Year"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T19:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Phantom Expands Web3 Wallet to Embrace Bitcoin, Ordinals, and BRC20 Tokens Amid Soaring Demand]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74830372ef</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/phantom-expands-web3-wallet-to-embrace-bitcoin-ordinals-and-brc20-tokens-amid-soaring-demand/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T18:39:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Phantom, the Web3 cryptocurrency wallet initially developed for Solana, has expanded to include Ethereum and Polygon, and is now introducing support for Bitcoin, Ordinal inscriptions, and BRC20 tokens. Users of Phantom have the ability to integrate their existing bitcoin wallets, allowing them to manage their Bitcoin-centric digital collectibles and fungible tokens through the Web3 platform’s interface.
 
From Solana to Bitcoin: Phantom Wallet’s Latest Expansion Embraces Inscriptions and BRC20s
 
In 2023, Ordinals and BRC20 tokens, developed atop Bitcoin, have gained considerable traction, leading numerous companies to adopt the supporting infrastructure. As of December 21, 2023, the Bitcoin blockchain boasts over 50 million inscriptions.
 
On Wednesday, Phantom, the Web3 wallet that secured $109 million in Series B funding from key investors last year, announced its foray into the Bitcoin realm. Phantom acknowledges Bitcoin’s foundational role, stating that without it, there would be no Solana, Ethereum, or Web3.
 
“Introducing Bitcoin on Phantom,” the company said in a post shared on X. “You can now buy, sell, trade, transfer, and HODL Bitcoin, Ordinals, and BRC20 tokens with your favorite multi-chain wallet.”
 
 
Phantom’s integration of Ordinals and BRC20s coincides with a surge in demand for Bitcoin digital collectibles and fungible tokens. Recent data from cryptoslam.io reveals that Bitcoin-based NFT sales have exceeded $400 million in the past week.
 
Phantom’s Bitcoin feature is currently in beta and available on an opt-in basis. Users can also link with the NFT marketplaces Magic Eden and Unisat, and Phantom indicates that additional “trusted” applications will be introduced shortly.
 
What do you think about Phantom supporting Bitcoin, Ordinals, and BRC20 tokens? Share your thoughts and opinions about this subject in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grimace Community Triumphs: MEXC’s Multimillion-Dollar Capitulation]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74830f7f7a</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/grimace-community-triumphs-mexcs-multimillion-dollar-capitulation/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T18:07:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. On December 19, Grimace’s creator staged a New Year’s miracle live, gifting his followers millions of dollars. The MEXC exchange funded this entire giveaway, as they went against Grimace’s user base and listed the token on their futures market without approval.
 
The Start of It All: The Complete Story of the Dispute
 
In spring 2023, Grimace emerged as one of the year’s standout crypto projects, quickly gaining fame and enriching its early backers, who were also actively donating to charity. Money was freely given away on the streets, and competitions in poker, chess, Dota 2, Counter-Strike, and even rap battles were held, each with prizes in the tens of thousands of dollars.
 
Grimace first appeared on MEXC on June 12, 2023. Initially, users appreciated the exchange for it…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Argentina's Minister of Foreign Affairs Affirms Bitcoin Acceptance for Contract Agreements]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74830fd238</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/argentinas-minister-of-foreign-affairs-affirms-bitcoin-acceptance-for-contract-agreements"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T18:05:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a groundbreaking statement, Argentina's Minister of Foreign Affairs, Diana Mondino, has confirmed the country's stance on embracing Bitcoin for contractual agreements.



Mondino's declaration outlined the government's willingness to accept and formalize contracts denominated in Bitcoin, heralding a pivotal moment for legal recognition of BTC within Argentina. The move demonstrates Argentina's progressive approach towards integrating Bitcoin in the country.
"And also any other crypto and/or species such as kilos of steer or liters of milk," Mondino continued. "Art 766. - Obligation of the debtor. The debtor must deliver the corresponding amount of the designated currency, whether the currency is legal tender in the Republic or not."
This announcement arrives a month after Javier Milei, who has made very positive comments about Bitcoin in the past, won Argentina's presidential candidacy. Milei has previously stated, "The central bank is a scam, a mechanism by which politicians cheat the good people with inflationary tax.” Then saying Bitcoin "represents the return of money to its original creator, the private sector,” and that "it prevents politicians from robbing you through inflation."
The Minister's assertion further underlines Argentina's efforts to leverage the potential of Bitcoin to stimulate economic growth and innovation. By accepting Bitcoin as a valid form of contractual agreement, the government aims to foster an environment conducive to investment and business development within the country.
While the details regarding the implementation and legal nuances remain to be outlined, Mondino's statement marks a crucial step forward in legitimizing Bitcoin as a recognized means of conducting formal agreements within Argentina. The move may also serve as a catalyst, encouraging other nations to consider similar initiatives in integrating Bitcoin into their legal frameworks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nik Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Approved as Virtual Asset Services Provider in France]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74830b45cf</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/12/21/coinbase-approved-as-virtual-asset-services-provider-in-france/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T17:39:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The third-largest crypto exchange has said it wants to become regulated in countries with clear policies for the industry while it argues with the Securities and Exchange Commission for bespoke rules in the U.S.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camomile Shumba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Makes Massive XRP Transactions As Price Bounces]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74830b81ca</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ripple-performs-massive-xrp-transactions/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T17:37:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the world’s leading blockchain-based payment companies Ripple Labs has been observed making large XRP transactions amid the crypto asset’s recovery from a decline earlier this week.
 
Ripple Transfers Massive XRP Tokens To Exchanges
 
According to reports from on-chain crypto tracker Whale Alert, the firm recently performed three massive transfers of XRP. The tracker took to X (formerly Twitter) to alert the crypto community about the whale transfer as each one was made.
 
 
The massive XRP transfer coincides with the cryptocurrency’s significant comeback, following nearly two days of bearish decline. The first transfer which is the biggest saw about 120,000,000 XRP moved, valued at $73,838,616 as of the time of the transfer.
 
The funds were transferred from one of Ripple Labs’ wal…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Godspower Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Emerges as a Key Blockchain for Tokenized Real-World Assets]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748cf430a2</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/12/21/ethereum-emerges-as-a-key-blockchain-for-tokenized-real-world-assets/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T17:32:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The pace of real world asset tokenization picked up steadily in 2023. That’s likely to increase next year, with Ethereum well placed to benefit, says Cristiano Ventricelli, of Moody’s.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cristiano Ventricelli</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Circle Secures Conditional Registration as DASP with French Regulatory Recognition]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748cf4c8b4</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/circle-secures-conditional-registration-as-dasp-with-french-regulatory-recognition/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T17:28:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Circle,  
the global financial technology firm and issuer of USDC and EURC, has announced  
the attainment of a conditional registration as a Digital Asset Service  
Provider (DASP) with the French Financial Markets Authority. Alongside  
this achievement, the company has revealed the appointment of payments industry  
veteran Coralie Billmann to lead its licensed operations in France, pending  
regulatory approval.
European  
Regulatory Platform with Conditional DASP Registration
To  
proceed with operations in France, Circle must meet the conditions of its  
registration by obtaining approval as a payment services provider (PSP) or as  
an agent of a PSP. The company has applied for an Electronic Money Institution  
license to fulfill this requirement.
Newly  
appointed, Billmann brings …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tareq Sikder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto for Advisors: The 2024 Year Ahead]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748cf5a0bc</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/12/21/crypto-for-advisors-the-2024-year-ahead/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T17:21:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Advisors now have a better – but still nascent – array of investment options to help avoid the pitfalls of early-adopter risk and exploit a generational opportunity in 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Morton, Connor Farley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Founders’ Assets Frozen amid Hedge Fund Collapse]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748cf0e181</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/crypto-founders-assets-frozen-amid-hedge-fund-collapse/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T16:58:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A court has  
frozen up to $1.14 billion in assets belonging to the founders of Three Arrows  
Capital (3AC), a now-defunct cryptocurrency hedge fund. The order prevents Su  
Zhu, Kyle Davies, and Davies' wife, Kelly Chen, from transferring or selling  
these assets.
Crypto Founders' Assets  
Frozen amid Hedge Fund Collapse
The freeze  
comes as Three Arrows Capital faces liquidation. The firm was once one of the  
largest crypto-focused hedge funds before a series of risky bets led to its  
demise last year, amid a broader crypto market rout.
According  
to liquidator Teneo, the freeze order was issued by a British Virgin Islands  
court. Teneo estimates that 3AC creditors are owed about $3.3 billion. The  
liquidator alleges that Zhu and Davies should be held responsible for the hedge  
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Damian Chmiel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free As In Freedom Is Not Free As In Beer]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748cf16e11</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/technical/free-as-in-freedom-is-not-free-as-in-beer"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T16:54:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoiners Need The Guillotine
As Scottish economist and philosopher David Hume observed in A Treatise of Human Nature, nothing we know about what is true can tell us what ought to be true and nothing we know about what ought to be true can tell us what is true. The world of objective fact and moral truth are entirely separate. Hume called this the is/ought problem and his argument that descriptive and normative reasoning should be separated is known as Hume’s guillotine. 
Hume’s guillotine is a philosophical razor – a rule of thumb for reasoning about the world. It is a way of cutting apart two lines of reasoning that become entangled when they intertwine. An argument where one side argues about what is true and the other side argues about what ought to be true is a useless argument. Thos…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>knifefight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin NFTs Skyrocket With $425M in Sales This Week; Key Collections Cement Strong Floor Values]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748cfc033e</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-nfts-skyrocket-with-425m-in-sales-this-week-key-collections-cement-strong-floor-values/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T16:36:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the last week, markets for non-fungible tokens (NFTs) minted on top of Bitcoin have generated approximately $425.63 million in sales. The leading ten NFT collections over the seven-day period all originate from the Bitcoin blockchain. Several collections of Ordinal inscriptions based on Bitcoin are witnessing substantial trading volumes, establishing strong baseline values for these digital collectibles.
 
Bitcoin NFT Market Continues to Evolve
 
In the past six weeks, Bitcoin-based NFTs, also known as Ordinal inscriptions, have been selling at an impressive rate. In November, NFT sales from Bitcoin exceeded those from Ethereum, and this trend has persisted into December.
 
Data from cryptoslam.io this week reveals that Bitcoin achieved $425.63 million in NFT sales, surpassing the runne…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When Is The Bitcoin Top? Cycle Analyst’s Cheat Sheet Answers]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748cf89a63</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-cycle-analyst-reveals-the-btc-cheat-sheet/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T16:06:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Bitcoin cycle analyst has revealed a “cheat sheet” for the cryptocurrency’s price based on the data of an on-chain indicator.
 
Bitcoin 4-Year Cycles Have Followed An Interesting Pattern
 
In a new post on X, cycle analyst Root has shared a Bitcoin chart that breaks down the phases that the cryptocurrency’s price has gone through over the different 4-year cycles.
 
In order to separate between bullish and bearish periods, the analyst has made use of an on-chain indicator called the “short-term holder cost basis.” Now, what do these terms mean?
 
 
First, the short-term holders (STHs) refer to the fickle-minded side of the BTC market who buy and sell often. Typically, the investors who bought within the last six months are included in this cohort.
 
The cost basis (also called the “realiz…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Targets January for First Testnet Deployment of Next Big Upgrade, 'Dencun']]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748cfb4f6d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/12/21/ethereum-targets-january-for-first-testnet-deployment-of-next-big-upgrade-dencun/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T15:48:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers also penciled in the end of February as a soft target for the upgrade to hit the main Ethereum blockchain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Margaux Nijkerk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoin Issuer Circle Conditionally Registered for Digital Asset Services in France]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748ce56a32</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/12/21/stablecoin-issuer-circle-conditionally-registered-for-digital-asset-services-in-france/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T15:33:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[France has been encouraging crypto companies to set up shop within its borders and take advantage of the clearer industry regulation than in the U.S.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camomile Shumba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prometheum Earns Final Regulatory Nod to Try Hand at Fully-Compliant Crypto]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748ce6ba47</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/12/21/prometheum-earns-final-regulatory-nod-to-try-hand-at-fully-compliant-crypto/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T15:24:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prometheum Inc., with the latest regulatory notch on its belt, is about to finally test whether a viable crypto platform can operate entirely within U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) regulations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Animoca-Backed Game Wallet Wars Delegates Release Decision to DAO Vote]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748ce3fef3</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/web3/2023/12/21/animoca-backed-game-wallet-wars-delegates-release-decision-to-dao-vote/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T14:47:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The decision to launch Wallet Wars, a Web3 iteration of the 1970s arcade game Space Invaders, was taken by a vote of Balthazar DAO, not a management committe.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amitoj Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USTC Eyes Resurgence To $1 As Community Begins Voting On Groundbreaking Proposal]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748cedacde</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ustc-resurgence-to-1-proposal/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T14:35:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Terra Classic community led by the L1 Task Force (L1TF) and network validators have continued to devise ways to restore USTC to its dollar peg. As part of their endeavors, they recently introduced a new proposal, which is currently undergoing voting.
 
Latest Proposal Involves Plan To Burn 800 Million USTC
 
The latest proposal (Proposal 11927) involves plans by the community to burn 800 million USTC tokens in a “legally absolved route.” The proposed funds to be burned happen to come from the Luna Classic treasury, held in the Risk Harbor Multisig Wallet. 
 
 
The idea to burn these funds arose from the fact that Risk Harbour admitted that they had lost the keys to the Multisig wallet. As a result of this, they had agreed to blacklist the wallet. However, the community opined that burn…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Circle Informs Clients of IRS Inquiry Into $20K Annual Transactions]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748cedc45d</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/circle-informs-clients-of-irs-inquiry-into-20k-annual-transactions/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T14:34:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Numerous advocates of digital currencies report that Circle Internet Financial has been reaching out to its clients about a summons received from the Internal Revenue Service (IRS). Circle has stated that it is obliged to submit records concerning U.S. taxpayers who have engaged in transactions amounting to at least $20,000 annually during the years 2016 to 2020.
 
Crypto Firm Circle Addresses IRS Summons on User Transactions Exceeding $20,000
 
Circle, a crypto company and stablecoin issuer has been informing its U.S. clientele via email about its intention to adhere to a summons from the IRS. This summons, issued on April 9, 2021, targets Circle and its associated subsidiaries. According to the email from Circle, the IRS is seeking data on clients who transacted $20,000 or more in any ye…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>