<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-04-10T04:17:55.449Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-04-10T04:17:55.449Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Right time’ for Hong Kong’s Web3 push despite market flux — Financial Secretary]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18073469/Right-time-for-Hong-Kongs-Web3-push-despite-market-flux-Financial-Secretary</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18073469/Right-time-for-Hong-Kongs-Web3-push-despite-market-flux-Financial-Secretary"/>
        <updated>2023-04-10T03:58:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong has already taken serious steps to develop the Web3 industry and its Financial Secretary says now is the right time to keep moving forward.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sushiswap Smart Contract Bug Results in Over $3M in Losses; Head Chef Says Hundreds of ETH Recovered]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75275fb198</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/sushiswap-smart-contract-bug-results-in-over-3m-in-losses-head-chef-says-hundreds-of-eth-recovered/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-10T03:39:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to several reports, a bug introduced to the decentralized exchange (dex) protocol Sushiswap’s smart contract has resulted in more than $3 million in losses. The blockchain and smart contract security firm Peckshield explained the exploited contract was “deployed in multiple blockchains.”
 
Dex Platform Sushiswap Suffers From Smart Contract Exploit
 
Over the weekend, the dex platform Sushiswap saw its RouteProcess02 contract exploited and then distributed across various blockchain networks. Blockchain security firm Certik published an alert after discovering the exploit. The company Peckshield also updated the crypto community via Twitter, noting that Sushiswap’s “RouterProcessor2 contract has an approve-related bug.” It has also been reported that the victim was a well-known cry…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tron outperforms Ethereum in this category, how will it affect TRX’s growth]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18073460/Tron-outperforms-Ethereum-in-this-category-how-will-it-affect-TRXs-growth</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18073460/Tron-outperforms-Ethereum-in-this-category-how-will-it-affect-TRXs-growth"/>
        <updated>2023-04-10T03:30:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Social interest in Tron increased as it outperformed Ethereum in some areas. TVL declined as dApps started to underperform. According to Google Trends’ data, the Tron [TRX] protocol had out-competed Ethereum [ETH] in terms of social interest. While comparing the keywords TRC20 to ERC20, it was...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Jumps 5% After Burger King Hints At Mysterious ‘BiteCoin’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75275a1ab6</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-up-5-after-burger-king-tweet/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-10T03:07:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin (DOGE) has seemingly responded favorably to Burger King UK’s recent tweet referencing an unknown coin that nobody in the community seems to be aware of.
 
The UK branch of the popular fastfood chain caused a stir last week when it tweeted about wanting an “office doge,” following an unusual request by a cryptocurrency user for “We need doge.”
 
The Dogecoin community immediately reacted to the tweet, resulting in a surge in the price of this memecoin.
 
 
Dogecoin Community Reacts To ‘BiteCoin’
 
Over the weekend, Burger King UK again set the crypto community abuzz on Twitter with a tweet that read, “brb I’m making BiteCoin.”
 
As per the latest update on Coingecko, DOGE’s price has risen nearly 1.0% in the past 24 hours and 4.5% in the past seven days. The tweet from the fastfood…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Jumps 5% After Burger King Hints At Mysterious ‘BiteCoin’]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18073446/Dogecoin-Jumps-5-After-Burger-King-Hints-At-Mysterious-BiteCoin</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18073446/Dogecoin-Jumps-5-After-Burger-King-Hints-At-Mysterious-BiteCoin"/>
        <updated>2023-04-10T03:06:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin (DOGE) has seemingly responded favorably to Burger King UK’s recent tweet referencing an unknown coin that nobody in the community seems to be aware of. The UK branch of the popular fastfood chain caused a stir last week when it tweeted about wanting an “office doge,” following an...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Revolutionizing Brand Performance in Web3 w/Filippo Chisari – eakTV]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18073448/Revolutionizing-Brand-Performance-in-Web3-wFilippo-Chisari-eakTV</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18073448/Revolutionizing-Brand-Performance-in-Web3-wFilippo-Chisari-eakTV"/>
        <updated>2023-04-10T03:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an exclusive interview from Paris Blockchain Week, go-to-market specialist Filippo Kazari discusses the unique challenges and successes faced by top brands entering the Web3 space. Find out which Layer 1 and Layer 2 chains have attracted major brands like Nike, Adidas, and Tiffany, and how...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX financial controls were a ‘hodgepodge’ of apps, says court filings]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18073435/FTX-financial-controls-were-a-hodgepodge-of-apps-says-court-filings</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18073435/FTX-financial-controls-were-a-hodgepodge-of-apps-says-court-filings"/>
        <updated>2023-04-10T02:50:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A court filing alleged apps such as Excel spreadsheets and Slack messages were used to manage the assets and liabilities of FTX and its entities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin resumes rise, Ether gains ahead of upgrade, Dogecoin makes up some lost ground]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18073434/Bitcoin-resumes-rise-Ether-gains-ahead-of-upgrade-Dogecoin-makes-up-some-lost-ground</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18073434/Bitcoin-resumes-rise-Ether-gains-ahead-of-upgrade-Dogecoin-makes-up-some-lost-ground"/>
        <updated>2023-04-10T02:47:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin resumed its rise above US$28,000 in Monday morning trading in Asia, a support level it has fluctuated around for most of April.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase CEO says Bitcoin Lightning is 'something we’ll integrate']]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18073431/Coinbase-CEO-says-Bitcoin-Lightning-is-something-well-integrate</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18073431/Coinbase-CEO-says-Bitcoin-Lightning-is-something-well-integrate"/>
        <updated>2023-04-10T02:30:35.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thai Man Says ChatGPT Gave Him The Numbers To Win Lottery]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7527451dca</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/chatgpt-helps-man-win-lottery/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-10T02:26:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Patthawikorn Boonrin, a man from Thailand, recently went viral on social media after claiming he used ChatGPT, an AI chatbot developed by OpenAI, to formulate the winning lottery numbers.
 
According to reports, the strategy Boonrin used entails inputting hypothetical queries and previous winning numbers on the chatbot. The generated numbers for his victorious draw were 57, 27, 29, and 99. Although the prize was not that big, Boonrin claimed to have generated lottery numbers using this method in the past.
 
Boonrin shared his experience using ChatGPT to generate lottery numbers on TikTok, where he has acquired a following and intends to disclose additional details.
 
 

 
 
According to the local news source CatDumb, the AI chatbot also advised Boonrin to “not be obsessed” with his newly d…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Economy at Risk of Crash Landing, Allianz Warns]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7527403cb4</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/us-economy-at-risk-of-crash-landing-allianz-warns/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-10T01:45:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Allianz, one of the world’s largest insurers, has warned that the U.S. economy is headed toward a crash landing. “We expect the economic momentum to deteriorate during the second half of the year on the back of rapidly tightening credit conditions, exacerbated by the banking crisis,” said the insurance giant’s analysts.
 
Crash Landing Ahead, Warned Allianz
 
Allianz’s research and analysis division published a report last week stating that the U.S. economy is “headed towards a crash landing.” Allianz is one of the world’s largest insurers with over 122 million private and corporate customers worldwide and more than 159,000 employees. It is headquartered in Munich, Germany.
 
“Negative confidence effects from the near-death experience in the U.S. banking sector and the unresolved energy si…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried declared Alameda ‘unauditable,’ new report shows]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18073395/Sam-Bankman-Fried-declared-Alameda-unauditable-new-report-shows</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18073395/Sam-Bankman-Fried-declared-Alameda-unauditable-new-report-shows"/>
        <updated>2023-04-10T01:40:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new management of FTX, headed by CEO John Ray III, today released its first interim report on control failures at the collapsed crypto exchange.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Mover Asia: Is a ‘Sharp Move’ Around the Corner for Bitcoin and Ether?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e752743ae97</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/04/10/first-mover-asia-is-a-sharp-move-around-the-corner-for-bitcoin-and-ether/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-04-10T00:56:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC Edges Up. ALSO: CoinDesk Chief Content Officer ties the recent political and regulatory backlash toward the crypto industry to the alleged misdeeds of disgraced FTX CEO Sam Bankman-Fried. Will the current climate drive digital asset innovation and leadership away from the U.S.?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds, Michael J. Casey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Mover Asia: Is a ‘Sharp Move’ Around the Corner for Bitcoin and Ether?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18073372/First-Mover-Asia-Is-a-Sharp-Move-Around-the-Corner-for-Bitcoin-and-Ether</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18073372/First-Mover-Asia-Is-a-Sharp-Move-Around-the-Corner-for-Bitcoin-and-Ether"/>
        <updated>2023-04-10T00:50:18.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All eyes on Bitcoin [BTC] as Coinbase CEO reveals…]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18073368/All-eyes-on-Bitcoin-BTC-as-Coinbase-CEO-reveals</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18073368/All-eyes-on-Bitcoin-BTC-as-Coinbase-CEO-reveals"/>
        <updated>2023-04-10T00:30:52.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Dollar Could Lose Most of Its Value in 5 Years, Investment Manager Warns]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e752748da8b</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/us-dollar-could-lose-most-of-its-value-in-5-years-investment-manager-warns/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-09T23:42:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Investment manager Larry Lepard has warned that the U.S. dollar could lose most of its value within five to 10 years. Following the onset of the Russia-Ukraine war, “the U.S. did something which I perceived to be very stupid, which is it seized $600 billion of Russian currency reserves, and that sent the message to every other country in the world that ‘Hey if the U.S. doesn’t like what you’re doing, they can grab your money,'” the executive described.
 
Investment Manager Expects U.S. Dollar to Lose Most of Its Value in 5-10 Years
 
Larry Lepard, investment manager and founder of Equity Management Associates (EMA), shared his prediction about the demise of the U.S. dollar in an interview with Kitco News, published Wednesday. He said:
 

I’m very comfortable saying the dollar will effectiv…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former FTX US President Reportedly Quit After ‘Protracted Disagreement’ With Bankman-Fried]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e752749e12b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/04/09/former-ftx-us-president-reportedly-quit-after-protracted-disagreement-with-bankman-fried/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-04-09T23:25:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new report from the failed crypto exchange FTX’s current leadership says that former FTX US President Brett Harrison resigned last September partly because of a “protracted disagreement” with CEO Sam Bankman-Fried and members of his inner circle.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cheyenne Ligon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former FTX US President Reportedly Quit After ‘Protracted Disagreement’ With Bankman-Fried]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18073328/Former-FTX-US-President-Reportedly-Quit-After-Protracted-Disagreement-With-Bankman-Fried</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18073328/Former-FTX-US-President-Reportedly-Quit-After-Protracted-Disagreement-With-Bankman-Fried"/>
        <updated>2023-04-09T23:19:31.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Traders Shifting to Tether and BTC Are Voting Against the U.S.]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18073331/Traders-Shifting-to-Tether-and-BTC-Are-Voting-Against-the-US</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18073331/Traders-Shifting-to-Tether-and-BTC-Are-Voting-Against-the-US"/>
        <updated>2023-04-09T23:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Europe Must Reduce Reliance on US Dollar, Says French President Emmanuel Macron]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18073327/Europe-Must-Reduce-Reliance-on-US-Dollar-Says-French-President-Emmanuel-Macron</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18073327/Europe-Must-Reduce-Reliance-on-US-Dollar-Says-French-President-Emmanuel-Macron"/>
        <updated>2023-04-09T23:13:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[French President Emmanuel Macron says all of Europe should focus on lowering its dependence on the US dollar. In a new interview with Politico, President Macron says European leaders should soften ties to America and focus on staying out of a potential conflict between China and the US over...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Luck Strikes Again: Player Wins 6 BTC Jackpot on Book of the Fallen at Bitcoin.com Games]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e752734ced3</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/luck-strikes-again-player-wins-6-btc-jackpot-on-book-of-the-fallen-at-bitcoin-com-games/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-09T22:42:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A thrilling adventure in Book of the Fallen by Pragmatic leads to a huge win of 6 BTC!
 
Another Massive Win on Bitcoin.com Games
 
It seems like the lucky streak on Bitcoin.com Games crypto casino continues with yet another player hitting the jackpot of 1,214 times their initial bet amount, and winning a life-changing amount of BTC. The latest big win came from a player who took a chance on the thrilling game Book of the Fallen by Pragmatic and ended up with a massive $170,000 payout in Bitcoin.
 
Book of the Fallen by Pragmatic
 
Book of the Fallen is an action-packed slot game with an adventurous theme that takes players on a quest to discover the hidden treasures of an ancient civilization. With its impressive graphics and unique features, this game offers players an unforgettable gami…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Less Than 1% of Crypto Investors Declared Their Taxes to Authorities (Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18073310/Less-Than-1-of-Crypto-Investors-Declared-Their-Taxes-to-Authorities-Study</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18073310/Less-Than-1-of-Crypto-Investors-Declared-Their-Taxes-to-Authorities-Study"/>
        <updated>2023-04-09T22:32:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[4.09% of the cryptocurrency investors in Finland have paid taxes last year, while only 0.03% of the Filipino traders have done so.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Having doubts about Bitcoin’s [BTC] short-term gains? Consider this]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18073308/Having-doubts-about-Bitcoins-BTC-short-term-gains-Consider-this</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18073308/Having-doubts-about-Bitcoins-BTC-short-term-gains-Consider-this"/>
        <updated>2023-04-09T22:30:50.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Exchange SushiSwap Exploited – Here’s How to Ensure Your Funds Are Safe]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18073298/Crypto-Exchange-SushiSwap-Exploited-Heres-How-to-Ensure-Your-Funds-Are-Safe</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18073298/Crypto-Exchange-SushiSwap-Exploited-Heres-How-to-Ensure-Your-Funds-Are-Safe"/>
        <updated>2023-04-09T22:08:38.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ordinal Inscriptions Surpass 1 Million Mark, Miners Collect $4.7M in Fees as Bitcoin NFT Trend Continues]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e752732af45</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ordinal-inscriptions-surpass-1-million-mark-miners-collect-4-7m-in-fees-as-bitcoin-nft-trend-continues/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-09T21:12:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On April 8, 2023, the number of Ordinal inscriptions surpassed the million mark as the non-fungible token (NFT) trend has seemingly become a mainstay. Presently, on Sunday, April 9, the total number of Ordinal inscriptions is 1,049,263, and so far, 169.85 bitcoins worth $4.7 million have been collected in fees.
 
Ordinal Inscriptions Reach 1 Million
 
This weekend, Ordinal inscriptions reached a milestone by surpassing the 1 million mark on Saturday, April 8, 2023. Ordinal inscriptions started to see significant demand after the mining pool Luxor mined Bitcoin block No. 774,628, which was not only close to 4 megabytes in size but also contained Ordinal inscription No. 652. Ordinal inscriptions is an idea that sprang from the mind of Casey Rodarmor, which allows users to inscribe satoshis (…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s Energy Transparency is a Double-Edged Sword: Hut 8 CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125805</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125805/bitcoin-energy-use-transparency-feature-not-bug"/>
        <updated>2023-04-09T20:10:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Although it gets a lot of negative attention, Bitcoin’s power usage also creates accountability, says Jamie Leverto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s Energy Transparency is a Double-Edged Sword: Hut 8 CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18073252/Bitcoins-Energy-Transparency-is-a-Double-Edged-Sword-Hut-8-CEO</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18073252/Bitcoins-Energy-Transparency-is-a-Double-Edged-Sword-Hut-8-CEO"/>
        <updated>2023-04-09T20:10:12.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DCG’s Foundry Shutters Free Mining Service (Report)]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18073250/DCGs-Foundry-Shutters-Free-Mining-Service-Report</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18073250/DCGs-Foundry-Shutters-Free-Mining-Service-Report"/>
        <updated>2023-04-09T20:05:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The free model used by Foundry, which propelled the service to the top, will become a paid service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s What Could Trigger a New Altseason, According to Macro Economist Henrik Zeberg]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18073240/Heres-What-Could-Trigger-a-New-Altseason-According-to-Macro-Economist-Henrik-Zeberg</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18073240/Heres-What-Could-Trigger-a-New-Altseason-According-to-Macro-Economist-Henrik-Zeberg"/>
        <updated>2023-04-09T20:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SushiSwap Smart Contract Bug Exploited in $3.3 Million Theft]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125799</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125799/sushiswap-smart-contract-bug-exploited-in-3-3-million-theft"/>
        <updated>2023-04-09T19:51:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The decentralized exchange says it's "all hands on deck" and that some of the funds have been recovered.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SushiSwap Smart Contract Bug Exploited in $3.3 Million Theft]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18073237/SushiSwap-Smart-Contract-Bug-Exploited-in-33-Million-Theft</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18073237/SushiSwap-Smart-Contract-Bug-Exploited-in-33-Million-Theft"/>
        <updated>2023-04-09T19:51:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The decentralized exchange says it's "all hands on deck" and that some of the funds have been recovered.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russian Law Enforcement Prepares to Seize Crypto Assets, Seeks Permission to Set Up Wallets]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7527392a5a</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/russian-law-enforcement-prepares-to-seize-crypto-assets-seeks-permission-to-set-up-wallets/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-09T19:38:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Russian investigators are pressing the parliament and government in Moscow for permission to open their own cryptocurrency wallets. This would allow law enforcement agencies to seize digital assets during criminal cases and eventually sell them, something that authorities in the United States and Europe already do.
 
Russian Prosecutors Lobby for Powers to Confiscate and Auction Cryptocurrencies
 
The Prosecutor General’s Office of the Russian Federation is proposing to allow investigative bodies to set up crypto accounts and wallets under their control for storing seized digital coins that can later be sold for the benefit of the state.
 
Speaking in the Federation Council, the upper house of Russian parliament, a representative of the Office’s Main Criminal Procedural Department, Madina …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lubomir Tassev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Economist Jim Rickards Says US Dollar’s Greatest Enemy as Reserve Currency Is the Treasury]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e752721ec50</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/economist-jim-rickards-says-us-dollars-greatest-enemy-as-reserve-currency-is-the-treasury/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-09T17:45:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jim Rickards, an economist and the author of “Currency Wars,” says the U.S. Treasury is actually the biggest threat to the U.S. dollar’s status as a reserve currency. However, he cautioned that an increasing number of countries seeking alternatives to the dollar as a payment currency is also “a big deal,” emphasizing: “The dollar is being attacked from all sides.”
 
Jim Rickards on U.S. Dollar Losing Reserve Currency Status
 
Economist and “Currency Wars” author Jim Rickards has warned that despite China and other nations intensifying their efforts to reduce their dependency on the U.S. dollar, the USD’s biggest threat comes from the Treasury. He stressed on “Fox & Friends Weekend” Saturday:
 

The greatest enemy of the dollar as a reserve currency is not all those other countries. It’s th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week on Crypto Twitter: Musk Goes Full Dogecoin, Pumping the Memecoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125783</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125783/this-week-on-crypto-twitter-elon-musk-logo-change-doge-dogecoin"/>
        <updated>2023-04-09T16:08:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CoinFLEX co-founder Mark Lamb tweeted a bizarre letter to his alleged debtors and a candidate for U.S. president 2024 spread serious misinformation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Bank Lending Drops by Record $105 Billion in Two Weeks, Trillions Moving to Money Market Accounts, Elon Musk Warns ‘Trend Will Accelerate’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7527151125</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/us-bank-lending-drops-by-record-105-billion-in-two-weeks-trillions-moving-to-money-market-accounts-elon-musk-warns-trend-will-accelerate/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-09T15:41:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The banking industry in the United States is still struggling after the collapse of three major banks. According to statistics, bank lending in the U.S. has dropped by close to $105 billion in the last two weeks of March, which is the largest decline on record. Additionally, Elon Musk, a Tesla executive and owner of Twitter, recently commented on trillions of dollars being withdrawn from banks into money market funds, and he insists that the “trend will accelerate.”
 
Statistics Still Show Glaring Signs of U.S. Bank Weaknesses; Musk Issues Warning
 
There are still plenty of signs showing that the U.S. banking system is feeling the aftermath of several high-profile bank collapses. During the first week of March, Silvergate Bank, Silicon Valley Bank (SVB), and Signature Bank (SBNY) closed d…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Not Related to a Digital Currency’ — US Central Bank Addresses Concerns Over Fednow Payment Network]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75271ff1c6</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/not-related-to-a-digital-currency-us-central-bank-addresses-concerns-over-fednow-payment-network/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-09T13:40:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Central Bank has issued an update regarding the Federal Reserve’s Fednow project, which is scheduled to commence in July. The Fed has responded to recent criticism of the Fednow service and asserts that the Fednow payment network is “neither a form of currency nor a step toward eliminating any form of payment, including cash.”
 
Fednow Won’t Replace Cash, the U.S. Central Bank Insists
 
When the U.S. Federal Reserve announced the launch of the Fednow service in July, it sparked immediate opposition and led many to believe it is one of the initial stages of an American central bank digital currency (CBDC). Several prominent economists and politicians have cautioned that a CBDC would bring about greater surveillance of Americans’ financial transactions.
 
In order to quell fears, th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking Dollar Hegemony, BRICS Nations Are Leading The World To Hyperbitcoinization]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75271a5602</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/brics-nations-drive-bitcoin-adoption"/>
        <updated>2023-04-09T13:13:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How the emergence of BRICS as an alternative to the U.S. dollar’s global dominance will usher in worldwide bitcoin adoption.
This is an opinion editorial by Milan Stanojevic, an elementary school teacher and filmmaker.
Since the end of the second world war, the United States has consistently been the dominant global superpower. The Soviet Union vied for superiority during the Cold War but ultimately failed as it lost control of its satellite states. This was evident when the Berlin Wall came down in 1989. 
In recent years, American hegemony has been challenged by China, a nation which has accumulated tremendous wealth since opening up its economy to the world. China now seems poised to usurp global power as it continues to engage in a form of financial imperialism across the globe (for mor…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Milan Stanojevic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bank of England Targets 30-Strong Team for Digital Currency: Report]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7527046537</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/04/09/bank-of-england-targets-30-strong-team-for-digital-currency-report/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-04-09T12:49:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Among the positions available: Digital Pound Security Architect and Digital Pound Solutions Architect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sheldon Reback</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Retraces 15% After Reaching 10-Month High Of $0.58 In The Past Week]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7527018d7b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/xrp-retraces-15-after-reaching-10-month-high-of-0-58-in-the-past-week/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-09T11:50:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XRP has experienced over 15% price retracement after initially hitting a whooping 10-month high over the last week. The past week has seen the sixth-largest cryptocurrency in the world by market capitalization rise to over $0.58. The last time this digital asset touched this mark was May 2022. However, the coin has since entered a retracement losing over 14% in 7 days. 
 
According to a chart by TradingView, the coin currently plateaus at around $0.51, where it has been for the past two days. 
 
 
Is This A Mere Correction Or Downtrend?
 
With such a significant downturn, Ripple has left many investors wondering if the coin is still in an uptrend or a complete trend reversal. However, recent happenings in the XRP ecosystem suggest that this is nothing to be worried about. 
 
Recent trends …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olowoporoku Adeniyi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mounting Trend of Challenges to USD Hegemony Reported: Saudi Arabia, BRICS; Ron Paul Weighs in on Potential Fall of Dollar as Reserve — Week in Review]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e752701a548</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/mounting-trend-of-challenges-to-usd-hegemony-reported-saudi-arabia-brics-ron-paul-weighs-in-on-potential-fall-of-dollar-as-reserve-week-in-review/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-09T11:48:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The United States dollar has been a hot topic in recent weeks, with multiple reported developments occurring globally which could signal significant moves toward de-dollarization in large economies. Former U.S. congressman Ron Paul also noted this week that if the USD’s influence as a reserve currency is undermined, it might happen later than some expect. All this and more, just below, in the latest Bitcoin.com News Week in Review.
 

 
US-Saudi Tensions Escalate as Report Says Crown Prince Is No Longer Interested in Pleasing the United States
 
After Saudi Arabia and members of the Organization of the Petroleum Exporting Countries (OPEC) surprised the world by announcing cuts to oil production, a spokesperson for U.S. president Biden’s National Security Council stated that reducing produc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Hallucinating’ ChatGPT Wrongly Claims Law Professor Sexually Assaulted A Student]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75270f81f9</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/chatgpt-wrongly-claims-professor-groped-student/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-09T10:39:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT, an OpenAI-trained artificial intelligence chatbot, falsely accused prominent criminal defense attorney and law professor Jonathan Turley of sexual harassment.
 
The chatbot made up a Washington Post article about a law school trip to Alaska in which Turley was accused of making sexually provocative statements and attempting to touch a student, even though Turley had never been on such a trip.
 
Turley’s reputation took a major hit after these damaging claims quickly became viral on social media.
 

“It was a surprise to me since I have never gone to Alaska with students, The Post never published such an article, and I have never been accused of sexual harassment or assault by anyone,” he said.
 
After receiving an email from a fellow law professor who had utilized ChatGPT to resea…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sushi’s Head Chef Releases Statement Over SEC Subpoena]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75270aebd5</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/sushis-head-chef-statement-over-sec-subpoena/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-09T09:59:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sushi DAO’s head chef, Jared Grey, has released a statement addressing the subpoena served against himself and the protocol by the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). 
 
In a Friday blog post on the Sushi Forum, Grey decided to address the growing concerns of the Sushi community using an FAQ format which he claims answers the most frequently asked questions he has received since the news about the SEC’s subpoena broke out. 
 
As part of its ongoing regulatory crackdown on the crypto space, the SEC served the Sushi DAO and its head chef a subpoena on Tuesday, March 21, indicating the commission was investigating both parties for violating U.S securities laws, presumably over SushiSwap’s native token – SUSHI. 
 
In response to the subpoena, Grey stated the protocol was co…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Semilore Faleti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russia Takes Second Place Rank by Power Capacity in Crypto Mining, Reports]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7520f46835</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/russia-takes-second-place-rank-by-power-capacity-in-crypto-mining-reports/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-09T09:40:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Russia is now ranking second in terms of energy capacities engaged in the extraction of cryptocurrencies, new data suggests. Despite persisting regulatory uncertainty and the negative effects of sanctions, the amount of power devoted to the sector has been growing, reaching record highs this year. 
 
1 GW of Electrical Power Involved in Crypto Mining in Russia During Q1 of 2023
 
Russia has for the first time climbed to second place in the world in terms of total power capacity of the facilities devoted to the production of digital currencies. According to data provided by the country’s largest mining operator, Bitriver, the amount of power involved in coin minting has reached 1 gigawatt (GW) in the first three months of the year.
 
The United States remains the clear leader with 3 to 4 GW…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lubomir Tassev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Midjourney Uses Photo Uploads To Help You Craft Prompts]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125746</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125746/midjourney-uses-photo-uploads-to-help-you-craft-prompts"/>
        <updated>2023-04-08T15:14:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new upload feature takes the guesswork out of the creative art process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[And the Winner of Metaverse Fashion Week 2023 Is...]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125737</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125737/winner-decentraland-metaverse-fashion-week-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-04-08T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week’s event plummeted in attendance from 2022. But it may have offered clues towards a path forward for brands in the virtual realm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized Pictures Plots Its Next Web3 Grant for Filmmakers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/WlVsgaOs/decentralized-pictures-plots-its-next-web3-grant-for-filmmakers</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/WlVsgaOs/decentralized-pictures-plots-its-next-web3-grant-for-filmmakers"/>
        <updated>2023-04-08T13:15:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leo Matchett from Web3 film funding platform Decentralized Pictures tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson at Outer Edge LA about DCP's just announced iPhone Filmmaking Initiative, which will support aspiring filmmakers who create a short film on their iPhones, and will be determined via DCP's crypto-native on-chain voting system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thai Man Uses AI To Win Lottery]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125765</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125765/thai-man-uses-ai-to-win-lottery"/>
        <updated>2023-04-08T13:15:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It only earned him $60, but he still gets his five minutes of fame. Was it good luck or science?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 Ways DAO Treasuries Will Hit $100B in Balances]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125709</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125709/dao-treasuries-hit-25-billion-what-comes-next"/>
        <updated>2023-04-08T12:15:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With DAO treasuries hitting a cumulative $25 billion recently, the next question is: How long until they reach $100 billion?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Bitcoin and Ethereum Unmoved, Musk Makes Dogecoin Noise]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125762</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125762/bitcoin-ethereum-shanghai-dogecoin-makes-noise"/>
        <updated>2023-04-08T11:48:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite a relatively uneventful week in coin markets, several big crypto adoption stories hit the press.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Give Your Bitcoin to the Poor, Salvadoran Economist Urges Nayib Bukele]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125739</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125739/give-bitcoin-poor-economist-nayib-bukele"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T22:49:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[El Salvador President Nayib Bukele’s Bitcoin bet is not popular with everyone in the country.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Craig Wright Hints Apple May Be Violating Copyright by Storing Bitcoin White Paper]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125718</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125718/craig-wright-apple-copyright-bitcoin-white-paper"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T21:03:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Australian computer scientist who claims to have created Bitcoin suggests he might get litigious with one of the biggest tech companies on the planet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Staked Ethereum Withdrawals Could Take Weeks After Shanghai Upgrade: Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125731</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125731/staked-ethereum-withdrawals-could-take-weeks-after-shanghai-upgrade-analyst"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T21:01:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum's next big upgrade will enable withdrawals of staked ETH, but heavy demand could drag out the process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Farren</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT Wrongly Accuses Law Professor of Sexual Assault]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125712</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125712/chatgpt-wrongly-accuses-law-professor-sexual-assault"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T18:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The chatbot says a prominent law professor committed sexual assault during a trip he never took.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Push Protocol Launches Privacy-Focused ChatGPT Clone]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125671</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125671/push-protocol-launches-privacy-focused-chatgpt-clone"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T14:39:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Web3 project uses Metamask and other wallets to create an encrypted chatbot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SBI Crypto Sues Riot Blockchain-Owned Data Center for Fraud, Negligence]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125685</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125685/sbi-crypto-sues-riot-blockchain-owned-data-center-fraud-negligence"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T13:45:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SBI Crypto alleges that Riot-owned data center Whinstone fraudulently misrepresented its capacity to host large-scale mining operations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korea's ‘Malicious Cyber Activities’ Deeply Concerning, Say US, Japan, South Korea: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125683</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125683/north-koreas-malicious-cyber-activities-deeply-concerning-say-us-japan-south-korea-report"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T11:26:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[High-level diplomats have urged the global community to ensure the repatriation of all North Korean nationals working abroad.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Which Crypto Transactions Are NOT Taxable? How To Minimize Your Crypto Taxes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125680</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/dont-overpay-your-crypto-taxes-decrypt-learn-article"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T10:07:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Doing your crypto taxes can be a lot less stressful if you know how to minimize your tax burden.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kade Garrett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 YouTuber CryptoStache: Gaming Will Be the Catalyst That Takes NFTs Mainstream]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Exb7eWKj/web3-youtuber-cryptostache-gaming-will-be-the-catalyst-that-takes-nfts-mainstream</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Exb7eWKj/web3-youtuber-cryptostache-gaming-will-be-the-catalyst-that-takes-nfts-mainstream"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T02:51:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 gaming YouTuber CryptoStache talks to Decrypt's Jason Nelson at Outer Edge LA about why Web3 gaming will bring NFTs mainstream, the partnerships that prove it's already happening, how gamers will change their tune on NFTs, and how the terminology is likely to change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fordefi Aims to Dramatically Simplify the Institutional Crypto Wallet]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/LGxyFJP5/fordefi-aims-to-dramatically-simplify-the-institutional-crypto-wallet</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/LGxyFJP5/fordefi-aims-to-dramatically-simplify-the-institutional-crypto-wallet"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T02:39:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Steve H., VP of sales from Fordefi, which raised $18 million in funding last year, tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson at Outer Edge LA how Fordefi uses multi-party computation to make signing transactions on an institutional crypto wallet much simpler—no seed phrase needed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unreleased David Bowie Recording to Debut as Music NFT]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125653</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125653/unreleased-david-bowie-recording-debut-music-nft"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T23:28:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The never-before-heard version of Bowie's hit "Let’s Dance" will be sold via pay-what-you-want NFTs from Gala Music and benefit charity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Launches AI Tool That Can Identify, Separate Items in Pictures]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125660</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125660/meta-ai-artificial-intelligence-image-segmentation-segment-anything"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T23:09:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meta unveils "Segment Anything" AI image identification tool, but the scale of the dataset used by the social giant raises privacy concerns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Drops Sharply After Twitter Blue Bird Returns]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125649</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125649/dogecoin-drop-twitter-bird-returns"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T22:11:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Doge had a very short run as Twitter's new mascot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: Canadian Bitcoin Miner Hut 8 Is Heading West]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5AGD2ifd/gm-canadian-bitcoin-miner-hut-8-is-heading-west</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5AGD2ifd/gm-canadian-bitcoin-miner-hut-8-is-heading-west"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T21:40:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Toronto-based Bitcoin mining company Hut 8 recently announced a merger with U.S. Bitcoin Corp that will take it into Texas, Nebraska, and New York. Hut 8 CEO Jaime Leverton joined Dan Roberts and Stacy Elliott to talk expanding into the U.S., dealing with regulatory pushback post-FTX, why Texas is such a hotspot, and where she'd like to expand globally down the road (the climates may surprise you). Watch and make sure to subscribe to the gm podcast on Apple or Spotify.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT Picks Gold Over Bitcoin, Says Crypto Critic Peter Schiff]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125646</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125646/chatgpt-picks-gold-over-bitcoin-says-crypto-critic-peter-schiff"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T21:30:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT chooses to include gold, not Bitcoin, as part of its "recession-proof" portfolio.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lawyer Says He’s Called the FBI on Bitboy Over Threatening Emails, Calls and Tweets]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125630</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125630/lawyer-adam-moskowitz-fbi-bitboy-threatening-emails-calls"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T20:25:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After weeks of threatening messages, lawyer Adam Moskowitz says he fears that one of Bitboy’s followers might try to harm him and his family.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Treasury Says Crooks Prefer Fiat to Crypto in DeFi Risk Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125623</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125623/crooks-defi-crypto-fiat-treasury"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T18:50:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Treasury Department said in a Thursday report that criminals do indeed use DeFi tools and apps, but most criminal activity still opts for fiat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lawyers Claim Shaq Is Hiding From FTX Lawsuit, Seek Alternative Method to Serve Him]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125616</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125616/shaq-hiding-ftx-lawsuit-seek-alternative-method-serve"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T18:41:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shaquille O'Neal is a defendant in a lawsuit for promoting FTX, including Tom Brady and Larry David.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple's Hidden Bitcoin White Paper the Latest in a Long List of Easter Eggs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125612</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125612/apples-hidden-bitcoin-whitepaper-the-latest-in-a-long-list-of-easter-eggs"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T17:31:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The seminal document behind Bitcoin has been lurking in an innocuous file on Apple computers for years. Here's how to find it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Magic Eden Bitcoin NFT Launchpad Debuts as Ordinals Total Nears 1 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125599</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125599/magic-eden-bitcoin-nft-launchpad-ordinals"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T16:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Interest in Ordinals is going strong, and now NFT marketplace Magic Eden looks to further capitalize on the latest Bitcoin craze.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aragon’s New DAO Toolkit on Polygon Takes Aim at Voter Apathy]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125577</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125577/aragons-new-dao-toolkit-polygon-takes-aim-voter-apathy"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T14:10:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aragon’s recently launched tech stack is now live on Polygon, dropping costs for spinning up DAOs and taking aim at voter apathy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mutant Apes Take the Lead in Serum City, an ApeCoin-Powered Ethereum NFT Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125548</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125548/mutant-apes-take-lead-serum-city-apecoin-powered-ethereum-nft-game"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Novel Labs and Faraway are developing an independent city-building game that gives new life to Yuga Labs’ Mutant Ape Yacht Club NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Down 8% as Musk’s Twitter Hype Fades]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125588</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125588/dogecoin-down-twitter-hype-fades"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T13:27:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin has posted an intraday loss of roughly 8%, but it still has most of its Elon Musk-assisted gains over the last seven days.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Carolina County Mulls 1-Year Bitcoin Mining Moratorium]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125575</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125575/north-carolina-county-mulls-1-year-bitcoin-mining-moratorium"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T09:53:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 1-year moratorium on mining would give county officials more time to better establish clearer standards for the activity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Australia Financial Regulator Cancels Binance Derivatives Business License]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125572</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125572/financial-regulator-cancels-license-binances-derivatives-business-australia"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T08:57:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance requested the cancellation a day before Australia's securities regulator announced that it would end the license.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report Blasts Bitcoin Mining for Pollution—But Bitcoiners Aren’t Buying It]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125566</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125566/bitcoin-environmental-harm-report"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T01:08:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Environmental Working Group continues to rail against proof-of-work blockchains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Has Amazon Lost The AI Race?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125558</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125558/amazon-ai-artificial-intelligence-aws-accelerator"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T00:25:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite flagging demand for Alexa, experts say Amazon could still pull ahead of the pack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Bitcoin Stamps’ NFTs Are Gaining On Ordinals]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125556</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125556/bitcoin-stamps-nfts-are-gaining-on-ordinals"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T22:51:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The creator of the new protocol claims it is the “most permanent” means of inscribing data on the Bitcoin blockchain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Fears Grow as Germany, France, Sweden, and Canada Voice Concerns]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125540</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125540/ai-artificial-intelligence-national-bans-laws"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T22:33:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the wake of an outright ban of ChatGPT in Italy, governments are trying to balance innovation with protecting user privacy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Texas Still 'Very Open for Business' for Bitcoin Mining?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125545</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125545/is-texas-still-open-for-business-for-bitcoin-mining"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T22:11:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The state is a mining hot-spot, but a new bill limiting benefits got unanimous approval by a state Senate committee. Mining advocates are concerned.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Future of Paxful Bitcoin Exchange in Flux As Co-Founders Fight]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125527</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125527/founders-fight-paxful-bitcoin-exchange-future-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T21:54:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One wants to resume operation of the marketplace, the other is directing users to an alternative service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MobileCoin Exec Bob Lee Fatally Stabbed in San Francisco]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125516</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125516/bob-lee-mobilecoin-cash-app-death"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T18:44:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Cash App creator also led Google's Android team and helped combat the COVID-19 pandemic.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Reveals AI Tool to Help Brands Target Facebook, Instagram Users]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125512</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125512/meta-reveals-ai-tool-help-brands-target-facebook-instagram-users"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T18:28:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meta’s recent embrace of AI is only growing, with new plans for generative ads—and Meta’s CTO thinks AI will help power the metaverse, too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Cohen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy Buys More Bitcoin as Asset Nears Company’s Break Even Price]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125511</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125511/microstrategy-buys-more-bitcoin-break-even-price"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T18:20:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The software company is still buying up the cryptocurrency—which has soared in value since January.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Lollipop' NFT Racing Game From Filmmaker David Ayer Coming to Polygon]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=125440</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/125440/lollipop-nft-racing-game-from-filmmaker-david-ayer-coming-to-polygon"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T16:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feature.io tapped “The Fast and Furious” co-writer Ayer to write and produce the project, which is billed as an interactive media experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: Kevin Owocki Wants to Regenerate DeFi]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/knbMLd17/gm-kevin-owocki-wants-to-regenerate-defi</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/knbMLd17/gm-kevin-owocki-wants-to-regenerate-defi"/>
        <updated>2023-04-01T14:23:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Move over, DeFi—ReFi is coming? Gitcoin founder Kevin Owocki has stepped away from DeFi grant-giving machine Gitcoin as it fully decentralizes and is now focused on regenerative finance (huh?) and ReFi incubator Supermodular. He aims to "regenerate the regenerators." He explained it all to Dan Roberts and Liam Kelly, and also talks DAO structure, crypto factions, NFT use cases, his book "Greenpilled," and much more. Watch and make sure to subscribe to the gm podcast on Apple or Spotify.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Aurory's Head of Production Left Ubisoft for Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PqJHF0N9/why-aurorys-head-of-production-left-ubisoft-for-web3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PqJHF0N9/why-aurorys-head-of-production-left-ubisoft-for-web3"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T21:24:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aurory executive producer and head of production Jonathan Campeau tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin at GDC about how the first-generation of Web3 games came out of DeFi and are now evolving.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['We Don't Really Do the Corporate Thing Very Well' Says Jason Brink on Gala Games Approach]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/EDzHoKrt/we-dont-really-do-the-corporate-thing-very-well-says-jason-brink-on-gala-games-approach</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/EDzHoKrt/we-dont-really-do-the-corporate-thing-very-well-says-jason-brink-on-gala-games-approach"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T21:14:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With roughly 50 video games in its pipeline, Gala Games is all-in on Web3. Gala's President of Blockchain Jason Brink told Decrypt's Kate Irwin at GDC about the studio's ethos and weighs in on the different approaches to Web3 gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: Coinbase's Top Lawyer Gets Real on SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mB7DMx7l/gm-coinbases-top-lawyer-gets-real-on-sec</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mB7DMx7l/gm-coinbases-top-lawyer-gets-real-on-sec"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T16:36:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paul Grewal is the Chief Legal Officer at Coinbase and a former U.S. magistrate judge in Northern California. He gave Dan Roberts and Stacy Elliott his candid takes on Sam Bankman-Fried and FTX, the SEC's crackdown on staking, the sanctioning of Tornado Cash, and more alpha on how Coinbase is approaching the current unfriendly US regulatory environment. Watch and make sure to subscribe to the gm podcast on Apple or Spotify.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Founder of Rotten Tomatoes Says Web3 Entertainment Isn’t Nearly Entertaining Enough Yet]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/ri2LLifZ/the-founder-of-rotten-tomatoes-says-web3-entertainment-isnt-nearly-entertaining-enough-yet</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/ri2LLifZ/the-founder-of-rotten-tomatoes-says-web3-entertainment-isnt-nearly-entertaining-enough-yet"/>
        <updated>2023-03-25T02:44:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rotten Tomatoes founder Patrick Lee, who has led companies at the intersection of technology and entertainment from Web1 to Web3, spoke to Decrypt's Sander Lutz at Outer Edge LA about the current state of decentralized gaming, film and television.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: How Gnosis Has Endured and Evolved]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Kxfs2Dmd/gm-how-gnosis-has-endured-and-evolved</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Kxfs2Dmd/gm-how-gnosis-has-endured-and-evolved"/>
        <updated>2023-03-24T20:58:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gnosis first launched in 2015 as a decentralized prediction market built on Ethereum. Now it's a DAO, a multi-sig wallet, a staking chain, and a vibrant community with its own GNO governance token. Co-founder and COO Friederike Ernst talked to Dan Roberts and Stacy Elliott about the careful evolution of Gnosis, decentralization impostors, account abstraction, DeFi UX failures, why Ethereum is the "Manhattan of crypto," and much more. Watch and make sure to subscribe to the gm podcast on Apple or Spotify.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Justin Aversano's Inspiration for Tarot-Themed NFT Photo Series 'Smoke and Mirrors']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/dkWNFMPb/justin-aversanos-inspiration-for-tarot-themed-nft-photo-series-smoke-and-mirrors</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/dkWNFMPb/justin-aversanos-inspiration-for-tarot-themed-nft-photo-series-smoke-and-mirrors"/>
        <updated>2023-03-24T20:03:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Justin Aversano, best known for his high-selling "Twin Flames" NFT photo series, joined Decrypt’s Andrew Hayward ahead of the upcoming L.A. exhibition for his new Ethereum NFT project "Smoke and Mirrors." He shared the wild inspiration behind the tarot-themed collection, and why—despite his growing profile—he opted not to exhibit at a major brand-name gallery.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Midnight Society’s Rob Bowling Talks Deadrop Launch and Working With Dr. Disrespect]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/yIc3fKH2/midnight-societys-rob-bowling-talks-deadrop-launch-and-working-with-dr-disrespect</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/yIc3fKH2/midnight-societys-rob-bowling-talks-deadrop-launch-and-working-with-dr-disrespect"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T21:28:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former "Call of Duty" developer Rob Bowling, now head of Midnight Society Studio, checked in with Decrypt's Kate Irwin at GDC and shared some behind-the-scenes statistics on how players are enjoying "Deadrop." The game saw 90,000 player hours over the weekend, with 97 minutes average play time per player, and their community size tripled in just a few days.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big Brands Get Serious About NFTs: Salesforce, VW, Panerai, Absolute Labs at NFT Paris]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/BHN8nxxH/big-brands-get-serious-about-nfts-salesforce-vw-panerai-absolute-labs-at-nft-paris</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/BHN8nxxH/big-brands-get-serious-about-nfts-salesforce-vw-panerai-absolute-labs-at-nft-paris"/>
        <updated>2023-03-16T14:57:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this panel from NFT Paris 2023 moderated by Decrypt's Dan Roberts, Web3 leads from some of the largest consumer and tech brands discuss their NFT strategies. Marc Mathieu of Salesforce, Tim Walther of VW Group, Eva Assayag of Panerai, and Samir Addamine of Absolute Labs joined the panel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFT Entertainment Revolution: Warner Bros, Orange Comet, CyberBrokers and NFT Now at NFT Paris]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/ZWr09Uou/nft-entertainment-revolution-warner-bros-orange-comet-cyberbrokers-and-nft-now-at-nft-paris</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/ZWr09Uou/nft-entertainment-revolution-warner-bros-orange-comet-cyberbrokers-and-nft-now-at-nft-paris"/>
        <updated>2023-03-16T14:49:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At NFT Paris 2023, Decrypt’s Stephen Graves moderated a discussion about NFTs and the entertainment industry with Warner Bros’ NFT head Josh Hackbarth, CyberBrokers founder Josie Bellini, NFT Now founder Matt Medved and Dave Broome, CEO of Orange Comet, which has produced NFTs for Anthony Hopkins and The Walking Dead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Step Inside the Armory of the NFT Collective 'Knights Who Say Nah']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/V6NGpw3i/step-inside-the-armory-of-the-nft-collective-knights-who-say-nah</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/V6NGpw3i/step-inside-the-armory-of-the-nft-collective-knights-who-say-nah"/>
        <updated>2023-03-15T20:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Knights Who Say Nah co-founder and project lead Nick Richey chats with Decrypt's Jason Nelson inside the group's armory of artifacts, shows off a historic Japanese tanto sword, and discusses why the preservation of historical artifacts is the best use case for NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>