<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-12-17T18:17:44.715Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-12-17T18:17:44.715Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unveiling the Top 24 Security Predictions for 2024 (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19115276/Unveiling-the-Top-24-Security-Predictions-for-2024-Part-1</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19115276/Unveiling-the-Top-24-Security-Predictions-for-2024-Part-1"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T18:08:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the ever-evolving landscape of cybersecurity, experts predict a myriad of challenges and advancements for the upcoming year. As 2024 approaches, global attention is drawn to crucial topics such as elections, regional conflicts, space exploration, and the pervasive influence of artificial...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BONK’s Meteoric Rise: Outpaces PEPE with 621% Surge, Secures Third Place in Meme Coin Market]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748e556442</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bonks-meteoric-rise-outpaces-pepe-with-621-surge-secures-third-place-in-meme-coin-market/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T18:05:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In recent weeks, the meme-inspired cryptocurrency bonk (BONK) has experienced substantial growth against the U.S. dollar and has now overtaken pepe (PEPE) to become the third largest meme coin in terms of market capitalization. In the past month alone, the Solana-based BONK surged over 621% in value when measured against the greenback.
 
BONK’s Astonishing Climb; Solana-Based Meme Coin Overtakes PEPE
 
The meme coin bonk (BONK) has emerged as a leader in the cryptocurrency market regarding 30-day gains. Upon its introduction on Dec. 25, 2022, it was valued at $1.21 million in market terms. As of today, BONK’s market capitalization has reached a striking $1.23 billion, marking a thousandfold increase in its value over the past year. Currently, BONK is the third-largest meme coin after displ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 Altcoins Poised for Growth Amid Binance and SEC Resolution]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19115275/4-Altcoins-Poised-for-Growth-Amid-Binance-and-SEC-Resolution</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19115275/4-Altcoins-Poised-for-Growth-Amid-Binance-and-SEC-Resolution"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T18:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amid a potential Binance-SEC settlement, certain altcoins seek reprieve, prompting questions about an impending 'Altseason' in the crypto market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano Founder Denounces XRP Community's "Harassment"]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19115278/Cardano-Founder-Denounces-XRP-Communitys-Harassment</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19115278/Cardano-Founder-Denounces-XRP-Communitys-Harassment"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T17:55:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Charles Hoskinson stands firm on his critique of the XRP community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP could move up 1,500% if this condition is met]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19115262/XRP-could-move-up-1500-if-this-condition-is-met</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19115262/XRP-could-move-up-1500-if-this-condition-is-met"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T17:49:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price of XRP has struggled to make a significant move, remaining largely consolidated despite Ripple, the parent company, entering … Continued]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Franklin Templeton Senior Vice President Foresees Global Adoption of Bitcoin in National Treasuries]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19115265/Franklin-Templeton-Senior-Vice-President-Foresees-Global-Adoption-of-Bitcoin-in-National-Treasuries</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19115265/Franklin-Templeton-Senior-Vice-President-Foresees-Global-Adoption-of-Bitcoin-in-National-Treasuries"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T17:48:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On 14 December 2023, Sandy Kaul, the head of digital asset and industry advisory services at Franklin Templeton, shared her vision of Bitcoin’s role in future global economics in an interview with crypto influencer Natalie Brunell. Franklin Templeton is a global investment management...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s Everything That Happened in Bitcoin and Crypto in 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19115273/Heres-Everything-That-Happened-in-Bitcoin-and-Crypto-in-2023</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19115273/Heres-Everything-That-Happened-in-Bitcoin-and-Crypto-in-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T17:47:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2023 was a rollercoaster for Bitcoin, altcoins, and the overall cryptocurrency market, marked by regulatory upheavals, institutional advancements, and significant price movements. Indeed, the industry faced challenges and opportunities, reflecting the nature of this emerging financial sector....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harvard Lecturer Matt Welsh Explores the Future of Computer Science in the Age of AI]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19115250/Harvard-Lecturer-Matt-Welsh-Explores-the-Future-of-Computer-Science-in-the-Age-of-AI</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19115250/Harvard-Lecturer-Matt-Welsh-Explores-the-Future-of-Computer-Science-in-the-Age-of-AI"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T17:25:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a thought-provoking lecture at Harvard University’s introductory computer science course CS50, Matt Welsh, co-founder of AI application-building platform Fixie and former engineer at Google and Apple, stirred excitement and contemplation among students and professionals alike.  With a bold...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Demand for Transparency in AI Grows as Howso Tackles “Black Box” AI]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19115241/Demand-for-Transparency-in-AI-Grows-as-Howso-Tackles-Black-Box-AI</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19115241/Demand-for-Transparency-in-AI-Grows-as-Howso-Tackles-Black-Box-AI"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T17:18:05.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nanjing University Unveils Digital Twin System for Human-Robot Collaboration]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19115233/Nanjing-University-Unveils-Digital-Twin-System-for-Human-Robot-Collaboration</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19115233/Nanjing-University-Unveils-Digital-Twin-System-for-Human-Robot-Collaboration"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T17:09:26.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Funding Wrap: Investors bet on NFT turnaround]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19115219/Funding-Wrap-Investors-bet-on-NFT-turnaround</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19115219/Funding-Wrap-Investors-bet-on-NFT-turnaround"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Price Set for Tailwinds in 2024 as Ripple Predicts Massive Crypto Adoption]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19115226/XRP-Price-Set-for-Tailwinds-in-2024-as-Ripple-Predicts-Massive-Crypto-Adoption</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19115226/XRP-Price-Set-for-Tailwinds-in-2024-as-Ripple-Predicts-Massive-Crypto-Adoption"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T16:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XRP might benefit from Ripple's crypto adoption outlook for 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Whales Aim To Keep Price Afloat – Will The Latest 100,000 ETH Accumulation Suffice?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748e5e46d6</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-whale-to-keep-price-afloat-et-accumulation/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T16:33:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ethereum (ETH) token has been under a considerable amount of downward pressure, with its price struggling to build on recent momentum. If there is a group of investors that could turn around this situation for the altcoin, it is the large ETH whales.
 
In a rather interesting turn of events, the latest on-chain data has revealed that this set of large investors has been on a buying spree, purchasing massive amounts of the Ethereum token. 
 
Whales Purchase $230 Million Worth Of ETH – Impact On Price?
 
Prominent crypto analyst Ali Martinez revealed – via a post on the X platform – that some of the largest whales have been accumulating significant amounts of Ethereum over the past week. This report is based on on-chain data provided by blockchain analytics platform Santiment.
 
Accordin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Opeyemi Sule</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Whales Aim To Keep Price Afloat – Will The Latest 100,000 ETH Accumulation Suffice?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19115214/Ethereum-Whales-Aim-To-Keep-Price-Afloat-Will-The-Latest-100000-ETH-Accumulation-Suffice</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19115214/Ethereum-Whales-Aim-To-Keep-Price-Afloat-Will-The-Latest-100000-ETH-Accumulation-Suffice"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T16:30:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ethereum (ETH) token has been under a considerable amount of downward pressure, with its price struggling to build on recent momentum. If there is a group of investors that could turn around this situation for the altcoin, it is the large ETH whales. In a rather interesting turn of events,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is BNB Chain’s new proposal good news for BNB?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19115206/Is-BNB-Chains-new-proposal-good-news-for-BNB</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19115206/Is-BNB-Chains-new-proposal-good-news-for-BNB"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T16:30:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BNB Chain submitted a new proposal on the Venus forum. Will this help BNB's chart finally see green?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin L2 Solutions Witness Decline, Lackluster Demand Despite Surging Transaction Fees]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748e594d83</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-l2-solutions-witness-decline-lackluster-demand-despite-surging-transaction-fees/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T16:03:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Saturday, December 16, the cost of transacting in bitcoin eclipsed its previous peak from May 8, 2023, surging past $40 per transaction. The trend of escalating onchain fees began on the final day of October, steadily increasing thereafter. Numerous crypto proponents foresaw this spike, suggesting a potential shift to Layer two (L2) platforms as a prudent measure. Despite an initial increase in the quantity of BTC on the Lightning Network from late October to November’s conclusion, approximately 350 bitcoin have been withdrawn in the subsequent one and a half months.
 
The Rush to L2s Remains Underwhelming
 
After a brief pause in September 2023, Ordinal inscriptions surged towards October’s end, currently accounting for 40-50% of Bitcoin’s transactions. In November, BTC miners hit reco…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto faces uncertain future in U.S. senate as support for De Facto ban grows]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19115194/Crypto-faces-uncertain-future-in-US-senate-as-support-for-De-Facto-ban-grows</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19115194/Crypto-faces-uncertain-future-in-US-senate-as-support-for-De-Facto-ban-grows"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T16:01:32.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum whale sells Off ETH holdings after year-long dormancy]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19115174/Ethereum-whale-sells-Off-ETH-holdings-after-year-long-dormancy</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19115174/Ethereum-whale-sells-Off-ETH-holdings-after-year-long-dormancy"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T15:50:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent development in the cryptocurrency market, a significant Ethereum (ETH) whale investor, who had remained dormant for a year, has re-emerged to start selling off their ETH holdings. This comes as the leading altcoin, Ethereum, experiences a loss in momentum. Ethereum Whale Activity...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin NFTs: Analyst warns of network stress and hash war]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19115165/Bitcoin-NFTs-Analyst-warns-of-network-stress-and-hash-war</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19115165/Bitcoin-NFTs-Analyst-warns-of-network-stress-and-hash-war"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T15:38:31.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Transaction Fees Soar Above $37: What’s Going On?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19115167/Bitcoin-BTC-Transaction-Fees-Soar-Above-37-Whats-Going-On</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19115167/Bitcoin-BTC-Transaction-Fees-Soar-Above-37-Whats-Going-On"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T15:37:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Transaction fees on the Bitcoin network have started to peak again after a long time. So what's behind the increase? Continue Reading: Bitcoin (BTC) Transaction Fees Soar Above $37: What’s Going On?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Franklin Templeton Strategist Sees Every National Treasury Holding Bitcoin, Says BTC Will Be Base Unit of Trade]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19115161/Franklin-Templeton-Strategist-Sees-Every-National-Treasury-Holding-Bitcoin-Says-BTC-Will-Be-Base-Unit-of-Trade</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19115161/Franklin-Templeton-Strategist-Sees-Every-National-Treasury-Holding-Bitcoin-Says-BTC-Will-Be-Base-Unit-of-Trade"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T15:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX debtors’ bold move: Crypto claims tied to 2022 market prices stirs debate]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19115158/FTX-debtors-bold-move-Crypto-claims-tied-to-2022-market-prices-stirs-debate</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19115158/FTX-debtors-bold-move-Crypto-claims-tied-to-2022-market-prices-stirs-debate"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T15:29:15.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Buy Metaverse Land And Property | Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19115136/How-To-Buy-Metaverse-Land-And-Property-Guide</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19115136/How-To-Buy-Metaverse-Land-And-Property-Guide"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T15:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the world of Metaverse land and property investment! This guide provides essential insights into buying and owning digital real estate. From understanding metaverse land value to navigating legalities, we cover all you need to start your journey in the virtual property market. What Is...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether Teams Up With FBI And Secret Service In Crime-Busting Alliance]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748e42a095</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/tether-teams-up-with-fbi-and-secret-service/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T14:30:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tether, the company that created the popular stablecoin USDT, has taken the initiative to publicly reveal letters it sent to the US House Financial Services Committee and the US Senate Committee on Banking, Housing, and Urban Affairs in an attempt to reaffirm its commitment to openness and legal compliance.
 
Tether, which has taken a proactive approach to maintaining the integrity of the cryptocurrency ecosystem, has increased its commitment to fighting the exploitation of its stablecoins in unlawful operations under the direction of Paolo Ardoino, its newly appointed CEO.
 
Tether Freezes 200 Wallets: Compliance Triumph
 
As part of a calculated move, the organization implemented a novel wallet-freezing policy that targeted persons on the Specially Designated Nationals list.
 
 
As a res…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kiyosaki on Deadly Economic Gamble, Vaneck’s Crypto Predictions — Week in Review]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748e4c849e</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/kiyosaki-on-deadly-economic-gamble-vanecks-crypto-predictions-week-in-review/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T14:11:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robert Kiyosaki has said that the biggest crash is coming and warned people against playing “Russian Roulette” with their lives. Even still, asset management firm Vaneck has done some safe gambling of its own, revealing 15 crypto predictions for 2024. All this and more just below, in the latest Bitcoin.com News Week in Review.
 

 
Robert Kiyosaki Doubles Down on Biggest Crash Prediction — ‘No Time to Play Russian Roulette With Your Life’
 
Rich Dad Poor Dad author Robert Kiyosaki has warned that the biggest crash in history may be starting. Emphasizing that the U.S. banking system is bankrupt, he warned that the S&P 500 will be next to collapse, which will “toast millions” of U.S. retirement plans. There’s “no time to play Russian Roulette with your life,” he stressed.
 
Read More
 

 
Va…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Restructuring Plan Leaves Creditors And Users Dumbfounded – Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748e345aef</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ftx-restruct-plan-leaves-creditors-dumbfounded/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T12:50:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The FTX Debtors estate has filed an amended Chapter 11 to its reorganization plan today, leaving investors its creditors dumbfounded on the defunct exchange’s next steps. According to the proposed plan, under the leadership of CEO John Ray III and the legal team from Sullivan & Cromwell, the estate is looking to value crypto claims at the time the company filed for bankruptcy last year, not current market values. 
 
FTX Debtors’ Reorganization Plan
 
 
FTX’s collapse in November 2022 sent ripples across the crypto industry that are still being felt today, one year later. The collapse led to a further cascade in already struggling crypto prices, leading to some wondering if that’s what might be the end of a flourishing crypto industry. 
 
At the time of the FTX bankruptcy, Bitcoin was value…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Complaints From Crypto Users Can Be ‘a Goldmine for Improvement’ Says Tom Blok]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748e3558dd</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/complaints-from-crypto-users-can-be-a-goldmine-for-improvement-says-tom-blok/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T12:40:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The number of user complaints received by crypto and blockchain entities has been on a decline since August, the latest Complains.Biz data has shown. The data shows that in just 28 days, Complains.Biz’s sentiment meter detected a 29% decline in the number of complaints. According to company founder Tom Blok, platforms that deliberately ignore user complaints are often shady platforms or outright scams.
 
Shady Crypto Businesses Do Not Prioritize Customer Complaints
 
According to Complains.Biz’s Dec. 15 data, user complaints and queries related to crypto have declined by 29% in just 28 days. The data indicates that complaints against decentralized finance, crypto, and blockchain platforms in 2023 have generally trended downwards since their August peak.
 
Explaining why the complaints sent…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Team Carries Out Massive SHIB Burn, Triggers 779,000% Spike]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748e3f53e3</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-team-carries-out-massive-shib-burn-triggers-779000-spike/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T10:50:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data from Shibburn, the burn tracker on Shiba Inu’s ecosystem, has shown a massive 779,000% spike in the number of SHIB tokens burnt in the past 24 hours. A new record for the most 24-hour burn may have just been set, as data shows more than 8 billion SHIB tokens recently made their way into inactive wallets. 
 
Over 8.6 Billion Tokens Burned In 24 Hours
 
 
SHIB burns have been an integral part of the Shiba Inu ecosystem, as investors believe burns are a catalyst for price spikes. SHIB tokens can be burnt by any investor. Once these tokens are burned, they are removed from circulation permanently, thereby decreasing the supply of SHIB. 
 
Data from Shibburn shows that 8.62 billion SHIB were burned in the past 24 hours. Surprisingly, the majority of the tokens were burned in a single trans…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[P2P Platform NFT Trader Falls Victim to Security Flaw, $3 Million in Blue-Chip NFTs Lifted]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748e38ab6e</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/p2p-platform-nft-trader-falls-victim-to-security-flaw-3-million-in-blue-chip-nfts-lifted/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T10:36:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reports indicate, and the peer-to-peer non-fungible token (NFT) market platform has confirmed, that the NFT platform NFT Trader experienced a security breach. An assailant exploited an outdated smart contract, resulting in the theft of nearly $3 million worth of esteemed digital collectibles, including those from the Mutant Ape Yacht Club (MAYC) and Bored Ape Yacht Club (BAYC) NFT collections.
 
High-Value Bored and Mutant Ape NFTs Snatched in NFT Trader Security Breach
 
The NFT trading platform NFT Trader has been compromised, resulting in a loss estimated at approximately $2.85 million in high-value NFTs. On Saturday, NFT Trader issued a public statement on X, warning, “We’ve suffered an attack on old smart contracts, please remove the delegation using revoke cash to the following addre…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week on Crypto Twitter: BONK Simply Won’t Quit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210073</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210073/this-week-on-crypto-twitter-bonk-simply-wont-quit"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T10:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ever-ascendant Solana meme coin dominated Twitter discourse for yet another week, as inscriptions hobbled traffic on multiple layer 2 networks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CFTC Chairman: Many Crypto Tokens Are Considered Commodities Under Existing Laws]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748e20dc77</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/cftc-chairman-many-crypto-tokens-are-considered-commodities-under-existing-laws/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T09:06:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The chairman of the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC), Rostin Behnam, has stated that many digital assets are considered commodities under existing law. Behnam urged the U.S. Congress to hasten the process of establishing a regulatory regime for cryptocurrency. He also emphasized that he and Gary Gensler, the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission chairperson, “get along quite well.” 
 
Gap in Regulation
 
Rostin Behnam, the chairman of the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC), has stated that many digital assets or tokens are considered commodities under existing law. However, Behnam lamented the emergence of a gap in regulation and urged the U.S. Congress to step in.
 
 
"It is figuring out how existing, decades-old law, fits into this new technology that seems to be ch…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFT Trader Suffers $3 Million Loss In Multiple Attacks – Details]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748e21abd5</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/nft-trader-3-million-loss-in-multiple-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T08:56:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NFT Trader, a peer-to-peer non-fungible token trading platform, has suffered a set of multiple exploits leading to multi-million dollar losses in users’ assets. The incident occurred on December 16, with the bad actors carting away $3 million worth of tokens, including 13 Mutant Ape Yacht Club, 37 Bored Ape, some VeeFriends, and World of Women NFTs.
 
NFT Trader has since confirmed the attack via an X post advising users to revoke access to some of its old smart contracts, which it claims to have been compromised. According to a post by X user foobar, the attacks are now over after NFT Trader implemented a smart contract update to eliminate a reentrancy vulnerability on its platform. 
 
 
We've suffered an attack on old smart contracts,  please remove the delegation using https://t.co/zEMg…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Semilore Faleti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Lawmakers Slam SEC and Chair Gensler for Refusing to Provide Clear Regulation for Crypto Industry]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748e2ad769</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/us-lawmakers-slam-sec-and-chair-gensler-for-refusing-to-provide-clear-regulation-for-crypto-industry/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T07:04:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. lawmakers have slammed the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and its chairman Gary Gensler for refusing to provide clear crypto regulation. “SEC Chair Gary Gensler’s continued refusal to provide clarity for the digital asset ecosystem is shameful,” one congressman said. “The SEC’s policy to provide less clarity to the marketplace instead of more is designed to create chaos and it will corrupt our great capital markets,” another opined.
 
Lawmakers Concerned About SEC’s Refusal to Provide Clarity for Crypto Ecosystem
 
U.S. Representatives Patrick McHenry (R-NC) and Tom Emmer criticized the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and its Chairman Gary Gensler on Friday after the SEC denied Coinbase’s petition for clear crypto regulation.
 
Following Gensler’s statement in …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Goldman Sachs: Don’t Expect Immediate BTC Spike After Spot Bitcoin ETF Approvals]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748e13b24c</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/goldman-sachs-dont-expect-immediate-btc-spike-after-spot-bitcoin-etf-approvals/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T05:05:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Global investment bank Goldman Sachs has advised investors against anticipating a sudden and immediate surge in the price of bitcoin upon the approval of spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). Nonetheless, Goldman Sachs highlighted that the “ability to actually transact a product that people are familiar with and can provide scale” is “very positive.”
 
Goldman on Spot Bitcoin ETF Hype
 
Global investment bank Goldman Sachs does not anticipate an immediate surge in BTC prices following the approval of spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), Mathew McDermott, head of the digital asset unit at Goldman Sachs, told Reuters this week.
 
While emphasizing that he does not expect the a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Denies Coinbase’s Petition for Clear Crypto Regulation — Exchange Responds by Taking the Regulator to Court]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748e1b6c0c</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/sec-denies-coinbases-petition-for-clear-crypto-regulation-exchange-responds-by-taking-the-regulator-to-court/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T03:08:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has rejected cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase’s petition for regulatory clarity in the crypto industry. SEC Chairman Gary Gensler backs his agency’s decision to deny Coinbase’s petition. In response, Coinbase has pursued legal action against the securities regulator to challenge this decision.
 
Coinbase Challenging SEC’s Decision in Court
 
The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has denied Coinbase Global’s Petition for Rulemaking. The crypto exchange filed the petition in July last year, seeking regulatory clarity, including “potential rules to identify which digital assets are securities.” With no response from the SEC for 18 months, the crypto exchange escalated the matter to court, prompting the agency to respond with the de…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blackrock Meets With SEC 4 Times to Discuss Spot Bitcoin ETF Application]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748e036825</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/blackrock-meets-with-sec-4-times-to-discuss-spot-bitcoin-etf-application/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T01:06:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blackrock, the world’s largest asset manager, has met with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) for the fourth time recently to discuss its spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) application. SEC Chairman Gary Gensler said this week that the securities regulator is “taking a new look” at spot bitcoin ETF filings.
 
Blackrock Holds Another Meeting With SEC
 
The expectation of the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) approving spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) has intensified this week as several spot bitcoin ETF issuers engage in discussions with the securities regulator regarding their applications. Notably, Blackrock, the world’s largest asset manager, has held its fourth recent meeting with the SEC concerning its spot bitcoin ETF proposal.
 
According to a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Safemoon Files for Chapter 7 Bankruptcy Protection Amid Securities and Wire Fraud Charges]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748e0996c0</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/safemoon-files-for-chapter-7-bankruptcy-protection-amid-securities-and-wire-fraud-charges/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T23:37:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the latest development, Safemoon, a crypto company, voluntarily initiated Chapter 7 bankruptcy proceedings in the District of Utah, as stated in their bankruptcy documentation. This action comes on the heels of the company’s founders facing indictment for securities fraud, wire fraud, and money laundering by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission and Department of Justice last month.
 
Safemoon US Files Chapter 7; SFM Token Plummets
 
On December 14, 2023, Safemoon US, LLC, the entity behind the safemoon.com website, lodged a Chapter 7 bankruptcy petition in Utah. This type of bankruptcy, often referred to as “liquidation,” necessitates selling the debtor’s nonexempt assets to settle debts with creditors.
 
For a business such as Safemoon, Chapter 7 bankruptcy signifies halting all…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto App Shakepay Reveals Data Breach Affecting a ‘Small Number’ of Customers]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748ff02c80</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/crypto-app-shakepay-reveals-data-breach-affecting-a-small-number-of-customers/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T22:06:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent announcement, Shakepay, the Canadian crypto app, disclosed a data breach involving unauthorized access to personal information of a select group of its customers. The breach, detected on Dec. 13, 2023, compromised data but did not affect any bank accounts, crypto wallets, or customer credentials.
 
Shakepay Addresses Data Breach Concerns, Offers Free Credit Monitoring to Impacted Users
 
The breach at Shakepay, which offers commission-free services for trading bitcoin (BTC) and ethereum (ETH), was identified following unusual activity on an employee’s work device. Shakepay’s security team quickly responded, deauthenticating and removing the compromised device from their network. This action was part of the company’s incident response protocol, aimed at minimizing the impact of …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Team Member Addresses Questions Of When Massive $1.2 Million In SHIB Will Be Burned]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748ff042cd</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-team-1-2-million-burned/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T22:05:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A member of the Shiba Inu (SHIB) team has come out to provide an update to the community following a ‘failed promise’. This comes as the team has come under fire for failing to carry out certain transactions that could have been bullish for SHIB’s price.
 
Shiba Inu Team Addresses Burns Delay
 
In a post on his X (formerly Twitter) platform, Digarch shared an update on the SHIB burns from the Shibarium development team. The post contained a screenshotted Telegram message from DaVinci, who highlighted the fact that the burn didn’t take place as scheduled. He further mentioned that there was no exact timing for when these burns will now take place. 
 
 
Many in the Shiba Inu community, however, seemed displeased with the update. One X user alluded to the poor communication from the team. The…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Transaction Fees Soar to $40, Sparking Debate and Push for L2 Solutions Amid Mempool Backlog]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748fff1d71</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-transaction-fees-soar-to-40-sparking-debate-and-push-for-l2-solutions-amid-mempool-backlog/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T20:36:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Saturday, Dec. 16, 2023, Bitcoin’s transaction fees spike to a high of $40 per transaction at 1:48 p.m. Eastern Time. The jump in onchain fees surpassed the high reached on May 8, 2023, when the average transfer cost topped $31 per transfer.
 
Skyrocketing Bitcoin Fees Surpass $40
 
Bitcoin transaction fees are climbing and at the time of writing, a high-priority transaction tapped $40 just before 2 p.m. on Saturday, Dec. 16. Miners have been raking in the fees and an example of this is the fact that block height 821,485 came with 7.314 BTC in fees, which is over the size of the 6.25 BTC block subsidy. Presently, the hash price per petahash per second (PH/s) is coasting along at $108 per PH/s per day.
 
The recent spike in Bitcoin’s transaction fees to $40 each significantly surpasses t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Spot ETF: Why SEC Boss Gary Gensler Is Taking A ‘New Look’ At Applications]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748fe6d08e</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-spot-etf-sec-new-look/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T19:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent interview with CNBC, the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Chair Gary Gensler mentioned that the Commission is taking a “new look” at the pending Spot Bitcoin ETF applications. His comment suggests that the SEC may be looking to do things the right way now despite any reservations Gensler or the Commission might have about the crypto industry. 
 
Gensler’s Comment Suggests That SEC’s Hands Are Tied
 
Gensler stated that the SEC was taking a “new look” at these Spot Bitcoin ETF applications because of the court’s decision in the Grayscale case. He alluded to the fact that the Commission had, in the past, rejected similar applications but has had to reconsider its stance following the court’s intervention. 
 
 
The Court in the Grayscale case had adopted the asset manager’…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Biggest Games Coming Out in 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210052</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210052/biggest-games-coming-out-nintendo-playstation-xbox-pc"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From Final Fantasy VII Rebirth to Star Wars Outlaws and plenty in between, these are our most anticipated games of 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Bonk Continues Surge With Solana Hype, Bitcoin Dips]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210009</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210009/this-week-in-coins-bonk-continues-surge-with-solana-hype-bitcoin-dips"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T10:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin and other major coins and tokens are down. But new meme coin BONK is still rallying.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Voice Generating Startup Resemble AI Promises to Restore Old Audio]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210063</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210063/resemble-ai-voice-enhance-recordings"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T01:34:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An AI startup has built a tool that it says can make low-fidelity speech recordings sound like new.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not That Grok: Musician Grimes and OpenAI Launch Plush Toy with AI Inside]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210024</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210024/grok-ai-twitter-toy-elon-musk-grimes-trademark"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T22:36:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk’s ex partners with Curio to launch a line of AI-powered toys designed to cut back on screen time and enhance interaction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jupiter Airdrop Set for January With a Billion JUP for Solana DeFi Users]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210017</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210017/jupiter-airdrop-set-january-billion-jup-solana-defi-users"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T22:10:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Half of the 10 billion JUP supply will ultimately go to the Jupiter community, with 10% landing in Solana wallets during the first airdrop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Weighs Demand for Saga Phones After Sellout Amid BONK Boom]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210036</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210036/solana-weighs-demand-saga-phones-after-sellout-amid-bonk-boom"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T21:51:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Saga is sold out in the U.S. and EU supplies are nearly tapped out. Solana Labs told Decrypt how it’s assessing next moves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Tech Giant Alibaba Unveils New AI Video Tool]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210018</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210018/alibaba-ai-text-to-video-generative-cloud"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T21:07:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alibaba says its I2VGen-XL model can handle “visualization, sampling, training, inference, join training using images and videos, acceleration, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitch Walks Back Changes After Surge in Nudity: 'We Went Too Far']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209998</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209998/twitch-walks-back-changes-after-surge-nudity-went-too-far"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T19:37:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, Twitch announced it would allow artistic nudity. Now, it’s blocked again, in part because of concerns around AI realism.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Plans to Challenge SEC Denial of Crypto Rulemaking Petition]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209997</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209997/coinbase-plans-challenge-sec-denial-crypto-rulemaking"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T18:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC today denied crypto exchange Coinbase's petition to clarify new crypto rules for the digital assets industry. Coinbase isn't taking "no" for an answer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Scaler Arbitrum Suffers Outage—And Inscriptions Are to Blame]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209996</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209996/ethereum-scaler-arbitrum-suffers-outage-inscriptions-blame"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T18:12:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arbitrum and other chains have recently been bombarded by users making "inscriptions" as on Bitcoin, even though such networks support NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gary Gensler: SEC 'Taking a New Look' at Bitcoin ETF Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209964</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209964/gary-gensler-sec-taking-new-look-bitcoin-etf-applications"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T16:06:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC chair stated that the regulator is reviewing spot Bitcoin ETF applications in light of a recent court ruling.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BONK Spikes 101% Amid Solana Saga Sales Frenzy to Claim Airdrop]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209966</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209966/bonk-spikes-101-amid-solana-saga-sales-frenzy-to-claim-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T15:40:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana-based meme coin BONK has continued to soar in value and hit new all-time highs—and the Saga smartphone is an unexpected beneficiary.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SocialFi Startup Reach Aims to Improve Crypto Twitter With Anti-Bot Protocol]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209903</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209903/socialfi-reach-crypto-twitter-anti-bot-protocol-token"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T15:01:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest addition to the "point" meta seeks to address the challenges of Crypto Twitter with the support of Seedphrase, Pranksy, Gmoney, and Zeneca.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SafeMoon Files for Bankruptcy, SFM Token Crashes 50% to All-Time Low]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209951</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209951/safemoon-files-for-bankruptcy-sfm-token-crashes-50-to-all-time-low"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T10:08:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Chapter 7 bankruptcy filing comes after SafeMoon's founders were indicted by the DOJ for a "multi-million dollar international fraud scheme."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Casio Drops Virtual G-Shock Watches as Ethereum NFTs—With Exclusive Perks]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209939</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209939/casio-drops-virtual-g-shock-watches-ethereum-nfts-exclusive-perks"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T03:02:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The G-Shock watch brand debuts a pair of fantastical digital designs on Ethereum, with a variety of special benefits for holders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vatican Says AI Is the ‘Highest-Stakes Gamble of Our Future’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209925</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209925/pope-declares-ai-the-highest-stakes-gamble-of-our-future"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T00:46:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pope Francis urged global leaders to work together to adopt a binding international treaty that regulates AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grindr Dating App Adds an AI ‘Wingman’ to Help Users Find Love]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209919</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209919/grindr-dating-app-adds-an-ai-wingman-to-help-users-find-love"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T00:18:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“If you’re not first to market with something in AI, you’re going to miss out," says Grindr CEO George Arison.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Devs Got a BONK Airdrop Worth $300 Last Christmas—It's Now Worth $500,000]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209906</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209906/solana-devs-bonk-airdrop-worth-300-last-christmas-now-worth-500000"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T23:01:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers in LamportDAO received a gift of billions of BONK last year. It helped some pay rent—and others get crypto-rich (maybe).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Instagram Adds Generative AI That Swaps Image Backgrounds]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209868</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209868/instagram-adds-generative-ai-that-swaps-image-backgrounds"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T21:59:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The green screen-like Backdrop feature lets users replace their messy kitchens with lush tropical forests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Native Bitcoin Staking on Ethereum and Solana Could Soon Be a Reality]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209867</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209867/native-bitcoin-staking-ethereum-solana-soon-reality-babylon"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T21:24:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto startup Babylon says it's developed a way to stake Bitcoin on any proof-of-stake blockchain. Here's how it works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana DeFi Hacker Pleads Guilty in First-Ever Smart Contract Fraud Conviction]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209859</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209859/solana-defi-hacker-pleads-guilty-smart-contract-fraud-conviction"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T21:01:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's the "first ever conviction for such a hack,” according to the DOJ. The hacker will be sentenced in March.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Did Michael Cohen Let AI Write His Legal Briefs?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209869</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209869/did-michael-cohen-let-ai-write-his-legal-briefs"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T20:53:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cohen's attorneys must prove the existence of cases they cited as speculation swirls around potential AI-generated content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emerge 2023 Project of the Year: OpenAI ChatGPT 3.5]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209784</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209784/emerge-2023-project-of-the-year-openai-chatgpt"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T19:37:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In barely over a year, ChatGPT rocketed from obscure, largely academic roots to the embodiment of a global revolution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Kawailani Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana's BONK Becomes 69th Largest Coin as Market Cap Tops $1 Billion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209850</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209850/solanas-bonk-69th-largest-coin-market-cap-tops-1-billion"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T18:55:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BONK continues its recent boom with a 64% surge on the day, landing in the meme-friendly #69 spot on CoinGecko’s market ranking.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Farcana Raises $10 Million for NFT Esports Shooter That Pays Out Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209817</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209817/farcana-raiases-10-million-nft-esports-shooter-pays-out-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T18:36:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Exclusive: The sci-fi, team-based hero shooter Farcana is still in early development. Now, it has a fresh round of capital to tap into.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a Single Phishing Link Unleashed Chaos on Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209838</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209838/single-phishing-link-unleashed-chaos-on-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T18:14:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ledger has confirmed the attack began because “a former Ledger employee fell victim to a phishing attack.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin and Ethereum Rebound From Wallet Hack Wobble]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209814</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209814/bitcoin-ethereum-rebound-after-wallet-hack-wobble"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T17:40:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin had briefly dipped, but it and the rest of the market has bounced back.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nintendo Switch 2 Preview: Everything You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197793</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197793/nintendo-switch-2-rumors-leaks-latest-news"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T16:46:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATE: Will the Nintendo Switch 2 get Grand Theft Auto 6? Technical experts weigh in on whether the hardware can even handle GTA 6.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fetch AI, SingularityNET Team Up to Squash AI Hallucinations]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209790</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209790/fetch-ai-singularitynet-team-up-to-squash-ai-hallucinations"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The two companies aim to use decentralized technology to make AI more dependable and intelligent, reducing inaccurate or irrelevant outputs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Stop Using Dapps': Ledger Library 'Compromised' With Wallet Drainer]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209804</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209804/ledger-library-compromised-with-wallet-drainer"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T13:47:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ledger has warned users not to connect to any dapps after a malicious version of its Connect Kit was identified.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JP Morgan: Ethereum to Outperform Bitcoin in 2024, Halving ‘Priced In’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209786</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209786/jp-morgan-ethereum-to-outperform-bitcoin-in-2024-halving-priced-in"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T11:53:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bank’s 2024 crypto outlook is cautious, with Bitcoin overbought amid “excessive optimism” over a spot Bitcoin ETF approval.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Axie Infinity NFTs Can Soon Evolve Like Pokémon—Here's How]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209166</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209166/axie-infinity-nfts-can-soon-evolve-like-pokemon-heres-how"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T07:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Exclusive: You can finally power-up your Axies and give them a new look with upgraded parts, but it'll take money, materials, and time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2023 Will Be the ‘Last Year You’ll Know A Song Was Written by a Human’: Queen Guitarist]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209761</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209761/2023-will-be-the-last-year-youll-know-a-song-was-written-by-a-human-queen-guitarist"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T01:16:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Legendary guitarist and astrophysicist Brian May reflects on AI's current and future impact on the music industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI Joins Rolling Stone Publisher to Merge AI With Journalism]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209754</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209754/openai-joins-rolling-stone-publisher-to-merge-ai-with-journalism"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T00:08:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Readers get better summaries, and LLMs get more training data—could AI enhance journalism while disrupting it?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Lords of Light' NFT Game Studio Raini Reveals New Owners, RST Token on Beam]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=209730</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/209730/lords-light-nft-game-studio-raini-reveals-new-owners-launches-rst-token-beam"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T23:29:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Raini Studios is now part of a joint venture, and the firms have already begun development on a new unannounced combat game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating peaceful money & taking over your local government w/ Joseph Schiarizzi]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zb0VG27G/creating-peaceful-money-taking-over-your-local-government-w-joseph-schiarizzi</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zb0VG27G/creating-peaceful-money-taking-over-your-local-government-w-joseph-schiarizzi"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T23:23:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week our host Reza Jafery is joined by Joseph Schiarizzi, founder of OpenDollar and prolific solidity developer. 


We discuss: 
- Onchain beer
- Taking over your local government
- His Emmy and 3 patents?!?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INTERVIEW: Ember Sword CEO Says NFT Games Are More 'Transparent']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/M9OHCVpA/interview-ember-sword-ceo-says-nft-games-are-more-transparent</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/M9OHCVpA/interview-ember-sword-ceo-says-nft-games-are-more-transparent"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T21:58:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ember Sword CEO Mark Laursen shares why some big game studios "irk" him—and why he got into game development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Director Jordan Bayne on the State of Film3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZLoEDkL9/director-jordan-bayne-on-the-state-of-film3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZLoEDkL9/director-jordan-bayne-on-the-state-of-film3"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T00:11:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the 2023 Film3 Summit, Jordan Bayne—director and founder of The Squad—spoke with Decrypt's Sander Lutz about how the Film3 world has progressed over the last year and what decentralized technologies can offer to creators that want to buck the Hollywood system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Questions With SCENE: Phil Mohun]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TwOjXfOR/5-questions-with-scene-phil-mohun</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TwOjXfOR/5-questions-with-scene-phil-mohun"/>
        <updated>2023-12-01T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bright Moments co-founder Phil Mohun joins 5 Questions With SCENE to recount some favorite moments from the road, including negotiating with Patagonian gauchos, falling in love with Tokyo, and gaining a newfound appreciation for shrooms chocolate bars.

Shot and edited by Vincent Roazzi Jr.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are NFTs Ever Coming Back?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qLmFpNKE/are-nfts-ever-coming-back</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qLmFpNKE/are-nfts-ever-coming-back"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T18:38:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this weeks episode we sit down with Cashtro from Arcade.xyz to discuss NFTs, shitcoins, what collections have held onto their floor prices, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Summit: Will Web3 Gaming Ever be Mainstream?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OvVWhGbW/web-summit-will-web3-gaming-ever-be-mainstream</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OvVWhGbW/web-summit-will-web3-gaming-ever-be-mainstream"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T19:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animoca Brands CEO Robby Yung, EndeavorXR CEO Amy Peck and Gamee co-founder CEO Bozena Rezab joined Decrypt's Stephen Graves on stage at Web Summit to talk about the future of Web3 gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Allie Eve Knox on Spankchain and the life of a Crypto Financial Dominatrix]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/16rVeg6o/allie-eve-knox-on-spankchain-and-the-life-of-a-crypto-financial-dominatrix</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/16rVeg6o/allie-eve-knox-on-spankchain-and-the-life-of-a-crypto-financial-dominatrix"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T21:20:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the first IRL episode of This Time Will Be Different!

In this week's episode, our host, Reza Jafery, is joined by Allie Eve Knox, the Spankchain Chief of Staff and FinDomme. 

They discuss
- How to sell feet pics
- If crypto is really as permissionless as it seems
- the intersections between crypto and sex work]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>