<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-07-27T08:17:49.042Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-07-27T08:17:49.042Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance to Restore Full Services in Japan in August, CZ Unveils]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7566e46d00</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/binance-to-restore-full-services-in-japan-in-august-cz-unveils/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T08:14:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency exchange Binance will start offering full services in Japan next month, founder Changpeng Zhao (CZ) announced. The leading trading venue for digital assets reenters the Japanese market with a domestic exchange after announcing earlier it was discontinuing services through its global platform.
 
Binance Returns to Japan, Praises Its Web3 Regulatory Framework
 
The world’s largest crypto exchange by daily trading volume, Binance, will provide full services on its new platform in Japan starting from August, its founder and CEO Changpeng Zhao revealed in a virtual address to the participants in the Webx conference in Tokyo on Tuesday.
 
 
CZ: Japan is a flagship leader for Web3 regulatory environments.
 
Earlier today, @cz_binance virtually addressed the WebX conference in Japan…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lubomir Tassev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does Crypto Have Further to Fall?  Crypto Chart TA with DOC today! ReadySetCryto ONE 7/26/2023]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18798502/Does-Crypto-Have-Further-to-Fall-Crypto-Chart-TA-with-DOC-today-ReadySetCryto-ONE-7262023</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18798502/Does-Crypto-Have-Further-to-Fall-Crypto-Chart-TA-with-DOC-today-ReadySetCryto-ONE-7262023"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T08:09:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[🟢 Sign up for one week of free trial and get our crypto trading signals at readysetcrypto.ONE👉10X Your Trades w/ Our Strategies: https://elite.readyset.trade/🟡 Beat The Market w/ On-Chain Analysis: readyset.vision/👉 See Doc's latest Market Minute here!: https://youtu.be/UxezIBaaQRo🚀 Sign up for...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Announces Launching Mining Service In This Altcoin!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799537/Binance-Announces-Launching-Mining-Service-In-This-Altcoin</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799537/Binance-Announces-Launching-Mining-Service-In-This-Altcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T08:03:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance's mining arm, Binance Pool, announced to its users that it will launch its mining service in this altcoin. Continue Reading: Binance Announces Launching Mining Service In This Altcoin!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reversal of SBF’s Bail Requested Over Caroline Ellison Diary Leak]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799532/Reversal-of-SBFs-Bail-Requested-Over-Caroline-Ellison-Diary-Leak</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799532/Reversal-of-SBFs-Bail-Requested-Over-Caroline-Ellison-Diary-Leak"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T08:01:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New evidence has been presented to the court, leaving little doubt as to SBF being the leaker.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I Feel God in This Crypto Scam Tonight:’ CFTC Charges Couple for $6M Scam]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799509/I-Feel-God-in-This-Crypto-Scam-Tonight-CFTC-Charges-Couple-for-6M-Scam</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799509/I-Feel-God-in-This-Crypto-Scam-Tonight-CFTC-Charges-Couple-for-6M-Scam"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T07:52:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Commodity Futures Trading Commission on July 25 accused Michael and Amanda Griffis of Clarksville, Tennesse, of allegedly defrauding more than 100 individuals through a cryptocurrency scheme, netting over $6 million, according to the file.The Griffises, real estate entrepreneurs,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Move: Robert F. Kennedy Jr. Buys 14 Bitcoin For His Children]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799505/Crypto-Move-Robert-F-Kennedy-Jr-Buys-14-Bitcoin-For-His-Children</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799505/Crypto-Move-Robert-F-Kennedy-Jr-Buys-14-Bitcoin-For-His-Children"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T07:52:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robert F. Kennedy Jr. has recently divulged his venture into the world of crypto, confirming his acquisition of a substantial amount of Bitcoin (BTC) earlier this year. Surprising many, Kennedy revealed that he purchased two BTC for each of his seven beloved children. During an insightful...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US House Financial Services Committee Approves First Crypto Regulatory Framework Bill]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799508/US-House-Financial-Services-Committee-Approves-First-Crypto-Regulatory-Framework-Bill</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799508/US-House-Financial-Services-Committee-Approves-First-Crypto-Regulatory-Framework-Bill"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T07:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Prediction: BTC Dips Nearly 3% in Response to Federal Reserve's 25 Basis Point Rate Hike]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799494/Bitcoin-Price-Prediction-BTC-Dips-Nearly-3-in-Response-to-Federal-Reserves-25-Basis-Point-Rate-Hike</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799494/Bitcoin-Price-Prediction-BTC-Dips-Nearly-3-in-Response-to-Federal-Reserves-25-Basis-Point-Rate-Hike"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T07:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin's current trading price is 29,464, indicating a slight 0.50% increase on Thursday.  However, the cryptocurrency faced a notable dip of nearly 3% in the last seven days in response to the Federal Reserve's decision to raise the federal funds rate by 25 basis points.  Despite the economy...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EthStorage reaches $100 million valuation in seed token round]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799480/EthStorage-reaches-100-million-valuation-in-seed-token-round</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799480/EthStorage-reaches-100-million-valuation-in-seed-token-round"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T07:36:01.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Senate Overwhelmingly Passes Legislation Related to Investments in Chinese Technologies]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799485/US-Senate-Overwhelmingly-Passes-Legislation-Related-to-Investments-in-Chinese-Technologies</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799485/US-Senate-Overwhelmingly-Passes-Legislation-Related-to-Investments-in-Chinese-Technologies"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T07:35:02.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. DoJ to drop campaign finance charge against FTX’s SBF]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799478/US-DoJ-to-drop-campaign-finance-charge-against-FTXs-SBF</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799478/US-DoJ-to-drop-campaign-finance-charge-against-FTXs-SBF"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T07:30:21.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[One Catalyst Could Trigger Bitcoin To Explode by Over 350% Within the Next Nine Months, Says Fundstrat’s Tom Lee]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799447/One-Catalyst-Could-Trigger-Bitcoin-To-Explode-by-Over-350-Within-the-Next-Nine-Months-Says-Fundstrats-Tom-Lee</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799447/One-Catalyst-Could-Trigger-Bitcoin-To-Explode-by-Over-350-Within-the-Next-Nine-Months-Says-Fundstrats-Tom-Lee"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T07:04:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fundstrat Global Advisors’ managing partner Tom Lee is predicting that Bitcoin (BTC) could hit six figures before the halvening scheduled for 2024. Lee says in a research note that the approval of a spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) could trigger BTC to rally to between $140,000 and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock Looks to India in Jio Partnership for Digital Asset Services: FT]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799424/BlackRock-Looks-to-India-in-Jio-Partnership-for-Digital-Asset-Services-FT</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799424/BlackRock-Looks-to-India-in-Jio-Partnership-for-Digital-Asset-Services-FT"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T06:54:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The world’s largest asset manager BlackRock is eyeing the burgeoning Indian market with its latest partnership to offer digital asset services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcement of TRY Parity for This Altcoin From Bitcoin Exchange Binance!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799412/Announcement-of-TRY-Parity-for-This-Altcoin-From-Bitcoin-Exchange-Binance</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799412/Announcement-of-TRY-Parity-for-This-Altcoin-From-Bitcoin-Exchange-Binance"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T06:48:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance, the world's largest cryptocurrency exchange, announced that it has listed three new altcoin parities, one of which is the TRY parity. Continue Reading: Announcement of TRY Parity for This Altcoin From Bitcoin Exchange Binance!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analysts predict end of the hiking cycle as Chancer token sale continues]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799409/Analysts-predict-end-of-the-hiking-cycle-as-Chancer-token-sale-continues</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799409/Analysts-predict-end-of-the-hiking-cycle-as-Chancer-token-sale-continues"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T06:45:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Federal Reserve delivered another interest rate hike on Wednesday. Chancer token sale continued this week as it raised over $1 million. Cryptocurrency prices reacted mildly to the latest interest rate decision by the Fed. Bitcoin remained stuck slightly below the important level at $30,000...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Landmark Victory: US Congress Committee Passes Historic Crypto Bill]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7566ef55fe</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/us-congress-committee-passes-historic-crypto-bill/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T06:39:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a landmark victory for the crypto industry, the US House Financial Services Committee has achieved a landmark victory by advancing a bipartisan bill aimed at establishing a regulatory framework for Bitcoin and cryptocurrencies yesterday. The bill’s passage marks Capitol Hill’s efforts to codify federal oversight for the digital asset industry, providing much-needed clarity and regulation for investors and the industry alike.
 
Landmark Regulation For The US Crypto Industry
 
The crypto industry has been under intense scrutiny since investors faced substantial losses last year due to sudden collapses of prominent companies like Celsius, Voyager and FTX. The bill passed by the House Financial Services Committee sets out to define whether a cryptocurrency should be classified as a security…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Remains Committed to the Metaverse, Mark Zuckerberg Says]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7566efd893</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/07/27/meta-remains-committed-to-the-metaverse-mark-zuckerberg-says/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T06:35:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The pivot to the metaverse has cost Meta billions of dollars, but the company’s founder and CEO Mark Zuckerberg says the social media isn't looking to give up anytime soon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon Warning Signs Point To Slide In MATIC Price On Support Breakdown]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799388/Polygon-Warning-Signs-Point-To-Slide-In-MATIC-Price-On-Support-Breakdown</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799388/Polygon-Warning-Signs-Point-To-Slide-In-MATIC-Price-On-Support-Breakdown"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T06:27:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon (MATIC) has been experiencing a mix of price action, with a 24-hour rally of 3.5% that hints at potential positive movement. However, the coin has suffered a 4.4% slump over the past seven days, indicating underlying bearish sentiments in the market.  Despite the short-term surge, the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Over 10,000 South African Retail Outlets Now Accept Momint Crypto Vouchers]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7566ea08d2</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/over-10000-south-african-retail-outlets-now-accept-momint-crypto-vouchers/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T06:14:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Momint, a Web3 marketplace app, has said South African residents can now use cryptocurrency to purchase shopping vouchers which are accepted by over 10,000 retailers. The Momint app can also be used to send cross-border remittances at a fraction of the fees charged by regular money transfer companies. 
 
Vouchers Accepted by Popular Businesses
 
Momint, a Web3 marketplace, has launched a blockchain wallet which allows South African residents to purchase a shopping voucher with cryptocurrency, a report has said. Holders of the voucher can make payments at over 10,000 retail outlets across the African country.
 
According to a Mybroadband report, South Africa’s retail giants such as Checkers, Woolworths, Engen, and Takealot are some of the outlets that accept the Momint vouchers. The report added that the voucher is also accepted at some 5,000 international retailers.
 

 
In comments following the announcement, Momint CEO Ahren Posthumus also revealed that South Africans outside the formal economy can use the Web3 app to make everyday payments. Posthumus further explained why Momint proceeded to make it possible for South Africans to use crypto for regular payments.
 
“The new South African crypto asset digital regulation is laying the groundwork to protect investors and consumers to make sure businesses are acting ethically in this space. And that is also unlocking this potential for us to use the technology for much cheaper transaction costs, transacting with one another without going through a bank,” the Momint CEO said.
 
In addition to payments, the Momint app can be used to send cross-border remittances at a fraction of the fees charged by regular money transfer companies.
 
Register your email here to get a weekly update on African news sent to your inbox:
 
 
What are your thoughts on this story? Let us know what you think in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Remains Committed to the Metaverse, Mark Zuckerberg Says]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799378/Meta-Remains-Committed-to-the-Metaverse-Mark-Zuckerberg-Says</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799378/Meta-Remains-Committed-to-the-Metaverse-Mark-Zuckerberg-Says"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T06:07:13.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pepe Coin Is Up 6% Today: How Many Tokes Can Make You A PEPE Millionaire?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799386/Pepe-Coin-Is-Up-6-Today-How-Many-Tokes-Can-Make-You-A-PEPE-Millionaire</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799386/Pepe-Coin-Is-Up-6-Today-How-Many-Tokes-Can-Make-You-A-PEPE-Millionaire"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T06:06:38.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UFO hearing: Crypto degens spare no time crafting 50 alien shitcoins]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799366/UFO-hearing-Crypto-degens-spare-no-time-crafting-50-alien-shitcoins</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799366/UFO-hearing-Crypto-degens-spare-no-time-crafting-50-alien-shitcoins"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T06:01:54.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Landmark Victory: US Congress Committee Passes Historic Crypto Bill]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799364/Landmark-Victory-US-Congress-Committee-Passes-Historic-Crypto-Bill</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799364/Landmark-Victory-US-Congress-Committee-Passes-Historic-Crypto-Bill"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T06:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russian Regions Welcome Digital Ruble Developments – But When Will CBDC Debut?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799368/Russian-Regions-Welcome-Digital-Ruble-Developments-But-When-Will-CBDC-Debut</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18799368/Russian-Regions-Welcome-Digital-Ruble-Developments-But-When-Will-CBDC-Debut"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Russian regions are welcoming news that the nation’s digital ruble pilot is set to officially launch on August 1, but banks and officials claim that a full CBDC rollout may not come until 2027. Ludmila Panina, the head of the payment systems and settlements department at the Chelyabinsk Branch...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ether CME Futures Saw Record Participation From Large Traders in Q2]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7566eba46d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/07/27/bitcoin-ether-cme-futures-saw-record-participation-from-large-traders-in-q2/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T05:58:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The standard bitcoin futures contract on CME is equivalent to 5 BTC, while the micro contract is sized at one-tenth of 1 BTC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried Won't Face Campaign Finance Charge, U.S. DOJ Says]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7566d73708</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/07/27/sam-bankman-fried-wont-face-campaign-finance-charge-us-doj-says/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T05:22:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Department of Justice informed a federal judge that it did "not intend to proceed" with a campaign finance charge against FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried after consulting with The Bahamas over whether it was included in an extradition document last year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Forces Quantstamp To Refund Investors In $28 Million ICO Settlement]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7566d36eac</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/sec-forces-quantstamp-to-refund-investors/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T04:38:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain security firm Quantstamp has settled with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) over charges related to an unauthorized initial coin offering (ICO) that raised $28 million in 2017.
 
The SEC filed charges against the San Francisco-based firm for allegedly conducting an unregistered ICO of crypto asset securities, resulting in a settlement that requires Quantstamp to refund the ICO proceeds. 
 
As a result, the company has agreed to pay a disgorgement of $1,979,201, prejudgment interest of $494,314, and a civil penalty of $1 million.
 
Quantstamp Settles With SEC Over Regulatory Violations
 
According to the SEC’s complaint, Quantstamp raised over $28 million by selling “QSP” tokens to around 5,000 investors, including investors in the United States, in October and No…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robert Kennedy Jr Reveals BTC Investment for His Children, Insists Bitcoin ‘Threatens the Monopoly on Money’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7566ddb7a6</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/robert-kennedy-jr-reveals-btc-investment-for-his-children-insists-bitcoin-threatens-the-monopoly-on-money/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T04:13:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During a Twitter Spaces event on Wednesday, Robert F. Kennedy Jr., a Democratic U.S. presidential contender, revealed that he acquired 14 bitcoin for his children. This announcement comes on the heels of financial documents filed on June 30, 2023, which indicated his ownership of the leading cryptocurrency.
 
Bitcoin Supporter Robert Kennedy Jr Purchases 14 Bitcoin for His Kids
 
On July 26, 2023, Robert F. Kennedy Jr. joined Scott Melker, also known as the Wolf of All Streets, in a Twitter Spaces gathering. An avid bitcoin (BTC) supporter, Kennedy recently revealed a proposal to back the U.S. dollar with bitcoin while speaking at a Heal-the-Divide event if elected president.
 
Kennedy confirmed his bitcoin ownership during Wednesday’s Twitter Spaces discussion with Melker, following repor…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Terminates German Crypto License Application As European Troubles Continue]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7566d8d73b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/binance-terminates-german-cryptolicense-application/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T03:37:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prominent cryptocurrency exchange Binance has canceled its application for a crypto license in Germany as regulatory scrutiny on the exchange intensifies across the continent.
 
According to a report by Reuters, Binance withdrew its crypto custody license application only after the German Federal Financial Supervisory Authority (BaFin) reportedly informed the exchange it would not approve the request. 
 
However, in explaining the reasons behind this recent move, a Binance spokesman highlighted a shift in the worldwide market and regulatory conditions to Reuters.
 
In addition, the representative also laid out the exchange’s plans to still reapply for a crypto license in Germany. 
 
The spokesperson said: 
 

Binance confirms it has proactively withdrawn its BaFin (Germany’s financial regu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Semilore Faleti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are Chainalysis’ Tools Scientifically Sound? Executive’s Statement Casts Doubt]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7566c5f231</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/chainalysis-scientifically-sound-executives-doubt/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T02:37:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An executive for on-chain analytics firm Chainalysis was the source of controversy following a recent statement. According to a court filing, the company’s Director of Investigation Solutions for government applications, Elizabeth Bisbee, provided testimony in the case against Roman Sterlingov. 
 
 
The alleged leading operator of Bitcoin Fog, a platform accused of enabling money laundering services via the cryptocurrency. Sterlingov is accused of money laundering, fraud, and other alleged criminal activities, and the crypto analytic platform is playing a pivotal role in supporting the case against the defender.
 
Chainalysis Methodology Under The Spotlight
 
Bisbee was a former agent of the Drug Enforcement Administration (DEA) and their department for cryptocurrency investigations. The e…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reynaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lawyer Outlines 4 Options SEC Could Proceed in Ripple Case Over XRP]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7566c04dcb</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/lawyer-outlines-4-options-sec-could-proceed-in-ripple-case-over-xrp/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T02:09:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lawyer has outlined four potential next steps that the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) could take following the ruling on the Ripple case regarding XRP. “I expect the SEC to file a request for interlocutory appeal within the next 2 weeks,” he opined, asserting that it would be in the best interests of Ripple and the XRP community for the SEC to start the appeal process now.
 
4 Options SEC Could Take Next in Ripple Case
 
Lawyer James Murphy outlined in a series of tweets on Tuesday four options the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) could take in the Ripple case following the ruling by District Judge Analisa Torres regarding XRP. The SEC has indicated that it will appeal the court decision.
 
“There’s a lot of debate about what the SEC will do next in the Ripple…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[House Financial Services Committee Votes in Favor of Crypto, Blockchain Bills]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7566c3f6fb</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/07/27/house-financial-services-committee-votes-in-favor-of-crypto-blockchain-bills/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T01:24:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The House Financial Services Committee advanced a set of crypto bills after a landmark markup on Wednesday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De, Elizabeth Napolitano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robert F. Kennedy Jr. Says He Bought 14 Bitcoin for His Kids]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150273</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150273/robert-kennedy-jr-bought-14-bitcoin-in-may"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T01:19:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Democratic candidate for U.S. President also blasted banks for succumbing to political pressure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC’s Crossroads On Ripple Case Appeal: Here’s What This Crypto Lawyer Says]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7566cfb0aa</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/secs-crossroads-on-ripple-case-appeal-crypto-lawyer/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T00:37:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto lawyer and XRP advocate John Deaton has put forward a viewpoint, underlining that either of the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission’s (SEC) probable routes of action in its case against payment company Ripple could significantly influence the future of the crypto landscape.
 
Deaton’s assertions shed light on the situation’s complexity and the potential impact of the SEC’s final decision.
 
Potential SEC Paths: Unique Case Argument Or Acceptance Of Verdict?
 
According to Deaton, the SEC might opt for one of two directions in the aftermath of the SEC vs. Ripple case. One potential route could involve arguing “facts and circumstances” to present XRP’s case as unique.
 
 
I believe this is he biggest and hottest debate at the SEC and I believe there are Senior SEC officials who ar…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Mover Asia: Bitcoin Post-Fed Rate Hike Fizzles. Will BTC's Recent Low Volatility Last Much Longer?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7566c9aab8</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/07/26/first-mover-asia-bitcoin-post-fed-rate-hike-fizzles-will-btcs-recent-low-volatility-last-much-longer/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T00:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[zkSync Era launched only in March but has more daily active addresses than Arbitrum and Optimism, the two largest scaling solutions by total value locked, underscoring the rising interest in its potential airdrop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Rubin, Sage D. Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[White House Says US Policy Allows Partners to Seek BRICS Membership]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7566ca4074</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/white-house-says-us-policy-allows-partners-to-seek-brics-membership/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T00:06:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The White House has affirmed that U.S. policy does not ask partners to choose between the U.S. and other countries, including the BRICS nations. “The U.S. does not want to limit countries’ partnership with other countries,” said Press Secretary Karine Jean-Pierre. More than 40 countries have expressed interest in joining the BRICS group, and around 70 leaders have been invited to the economic bloc’s summit in August.
 
White House on US Partners’ Interest in Joining BRICS
 
While House Press Secretary Karine Jean-Pierre was asked in a press briefing on Monday about U.S. partners seeking membership in the BRICS economic bloc. The BRICS group comprises Brazil, Russia, India, China, and South Africa.
 
“Algeria and Egypt, which are two partners of the U.S. … have applied to join BRICS … and r…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bearish Signal? Litecoin’s Daily Trading Volume Plunges 28% Ahead Of Halving]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7566b4a9b2</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/litecoin-daily-trading-volume-plunges/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T23:37:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Litecoin has been one of investors’ favorites over the last couple of months due to its consistent uptrend coming out of the month of June. However, recent data suggests that the interest in the digital asset may be waning even as its halving event draws closer than ever, a development that could deeply impact the altcoin’s ability to recover.
 
Litecoin Daily Trading Volume Falls By 28%
 
Litecoin’s volume was on the rise especially with its price surging above the $100 level just a few weeks ago. But with the drawdown that the altcoin has seen during this time, its trading volume has also nosedived with significant daily declines.
 
 
In the early hours of Wednesday, data from Coinmarketcap shows that the Litecoin trading volume had fallen by 28% compared to its previous day’s volumes. L…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Best Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Surpasses $29.6K After Fed's Rate Hike; CoinDesk Market Index Jumps 1.2%]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7566b126dc</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/07/26/crypto-markets-today-btc-eth-doge-ogn-comp-xlm-sol-price-analysis/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T22:46:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few more Fed rate hikes are likely, but "the hardest work is done," one expert said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Rubin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Alchemy: Battle for Ankhos' RPG Mashes Up Discord, Generative AI, and Solana NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149871</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149871/alchemy-battle-ankhos-rpg-mashes-up-discord-generative-ai-solana-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T22:40:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shown at Solana's PlayGG event, Alchemy: Battle for Ankhos taps into AI and blockchain alike for a decidedly unique concoction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FDUSD: Is Binance’s Latest Addition Another Stablecoin By Tron’s Justin Sun?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7566b1e0e3</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/binance-stablecoin-fdusd-linked-tron-justin-sun/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T22:37:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance, the leading crypto exchange, has added a new stablecoin to its platform – First Digital USD (FDUSD) today. The stablecoin, issued by First Digital Trust, a Hong Kong-based digital asset custodian, has attracted attention and sparked controversy within the crypto community. With allegations linking FDUSD to Justin Sun who is also allegedly behind TrueUSD (TUSD), the launch has left traders and investors questioning its credibility.
 
On June 1, First Digital Group announced the launch of FDUSD, a stablecoin pegged to the U.S. dollar. Initially issued on the Ethereum and Binance Smart Chain (BNB) networks, the stablecoin aims to provide users with a reliable and efficient means of conducting transactions. Data shows that the current total circulation of FDUSD is only about 10.11 mil…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uncensored and ‘Insane’: A Look at OpenAI’s Secret Image Generator]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150259</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150259/openai-image-generator-preview-uncensored-mattvidpro"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T22:31:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The unreleased generative imaging tool doesn’t shy away from nudity and gore, and puts MidJourney on notice.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[For Crypto Investors Down Bad in Hector, the DAO Can’t Die Fast Enough]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7566b3aca4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/07/26/for-crypto-investors-down-bad-in-hector-the-dao-cant-die-fast-enough/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T22:18:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hector Network will take six to 12 months to hold a liquidation. Token holders want their money back sooner.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Auradine Unveils Teraflux, New Line of US-Crafted Bitcoin Mining Rigs Providing Up to 270 TH/s]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7566bcb08e</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/auradine-unveils-teraflux-new-line-of-us-crafted-bitcoin-mining-rigs-providing-up-to-270-th-s/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T22:07:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to a press release published July 25, 2023, Auradine, a new competitor in the blockchain infrastructure sector, is entering the application-specific integrated circuit (ASIC) bitcoin mining industry with a line of bitcoin mining rigs known as the Teraflux series. Auradine’s new machines boast hashrates between 185 terahash per second (TH/s) and 270 TH/s.
 
Auradine Introduces Teraflux Bitcoin Miners
 
Auradine, a firm launched in 2022, recently emerged from stealth mode, revealing it raised $81 million in a Series A funding round in mid-May 2023. Celesta Capital and Mayfield led the funding round, with other participants including Marathon Digital Holdings, Cota Capital, DCVC and Stanford University. On Tuesday, the company announced a new line of miners, the Teraflux line, which…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Discord Game with AI and Blockchain: 'Alchemy: Battle for Ankhos' Creative Lead Alex Finden]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mF18GHGo/building-a-discord-game-with-ai-and-blockchain-alchemy-battle-for-ankhos-creative-lead-alex-finden</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mF18GHGo/building-a-discord-game-with-ai-and-blockchain-alchemy-battle-for-ankhos-creative-lead-alex-finden"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T21:55:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Jason Nelson interviews Alchemy: Battle for Ankhos Creative Director Alex Finden at the Solana PlayGG event in San Diego, California.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t Like Twitter’s ‘Ugly’ X Brand? Get the Bird Back With This Extension]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150237</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150237/twitter-x-brand-replace-restore-blue-bird-browser-extension"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T21:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A crypto developer has built a browser tool for Twitter aficionado to restore the classic logo.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accusations of a Government Cover-Up Dominate Congressional UFO Hearing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150243</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150243/ufo-hearing-evidence-cover-up-whistleblower-crypto-tokens"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T21:01:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Witnesses claim there is first-hand evidence of the existence—and possession—of alien spacecraft.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reddit Launches More Polygon NFTs—After Already Minting 18 Million Avatars]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150229</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150229/reddit-polygon-nft-collectible-avatars-gen-4-18-million"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T19:50:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cool Cats and Aku are in the mix for the new Collectible Avatars NFT drop, with prices ranging from a couple bucks to $200 apiece.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feds Want Sam Bankman-Fried Jailed Until Trial Over Alleged Witness Tampering]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150191</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150191/sam-bankman-fried-jailed-trial-witness-tampering"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T19:38:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Federal prosecutors accused Bankman-Fried of trying to discredit a witness in talking to the New York Times.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Democrats Attack New Crypto Bill for Weak Consumer Protections]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150217</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150217/democrats-republicans-financial-innovation-technology-bill-debate"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T19:11:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Democratic lawmakers claim Republicans are catering to large crypto companies and undermining the SEC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Pitch ‘Immunizing’ Images Against Deepfake Manipulation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150216</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150216/deepfake-image-protection-mit-immunization"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T19:05:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A team at MIT says injecting tiny disruptive bits of code can cause distorted deepfake images.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix Pushes Ahead with AI Hiring Despite Industry-Wide Strike]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150210</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150210/netflix-pushes-ahead-with-ai-hiring-despite-industry-wide-strike"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T18:39:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The streaming giant is offering up to $900,000 for roles in R&D and machine learning.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Holds Steady After Federal Reserve Raises Rates to 22-Year High]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150203</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150203/bitcoin-holds-steady-after-federal-reserve-raises-rates-to-22-year-high"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T18:16:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Federal Reserve today said it would continue to hike interest rates—but Bitcoin and Ethereum did not immediately move.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Tokenization?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=9571</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-tokenization"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T17:18:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We explore what tokenization is, how it works, and how it's revolutionizing the way assets can be issued, managed, and traded.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ki Chong Tran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Star Atlas' CEO After Massive Layoffs: 'Nothing About Our Vision Has Changed']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150077</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150077/star-atlas-ceo-after-massive-layoffs-nothing-about-our-vision-changed"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T17:01:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After laying off 73% of its team, Star Atlas developer ATMTA says it remains focused on building out the Solana-based NFT space game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Is the Real Winner in the Bitcoin ETF Race—Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149608</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149608/coinbase-winner-bitcoin-etf-race"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T17:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase has been tapped by BlackRock and others to help launch a Bitcoin ETF, and its stock price has felt the bump. But the company still faces significant risks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Legends at War' Mobile Game Launching on Avalanche Subnet]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150156</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150156/legends-war-creator-solert-games-launch-avalanche-subnet"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T15:15:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Android and iOS game Legends at War, endorsed by "Game of Thrones" star Hafthor Bjornsson, will get an NFT-powered version on Avalanche.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Withdraws Crypto License Application with German Regulator BaFin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150170</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150170/binance-withdraws-crypto-license-application-with-german-regulator-bafin"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T14:21:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance's issues in Europe continue to escalate as the crypto exchange faces another regulatory setback in Germany.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Italian Central Bank-Backed Hub Taps Polygon, Others to Bring TradFi Deeper Into DeFi]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150169</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150169/italian-central-bank-backed-hub-partners-polygon-others-bring-tradfi-deeper-defi"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The aim is to create an environment where more TradFi institutions can get involved in DeFi minus the risks facing retail investors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Early Computers to NFTs: Vera Molnàr's Pioneering Art Journey at Sotheby's]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150142</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150142/from-early-computers-nft-vera-molnar-pioneering-art-journey-sothebys"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T12:43:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vera Molnár's new generative art series reimagines typography with algorithms, marking the kickoff of Sotheby's Gen-Art Program.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Generative Art Challenger Highlight Takes on Art Blocks]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150089</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150089/ethereum-generative-art-challenger-highlight-takes-on-art-blocks"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T12:24:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Haun Ventures-backed Highlight, which debuts today, claims to be the first "open access" generative art NFT platform on Ethereum.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance’s New General Counsel On the Cutting Edge of Crypto Regulation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149578</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149578/binances-new-general-counsel-on-the-cutting-edge-of-crypto-regulation"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T12:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Each day brings “a legal question which there’s no precedent for,” says top lawyer Eleanor Hughes, as Binance works to build trust in the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alys Key</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Korea Rolls Out Interagency Investigation Unit to Tackle Crypto Crime]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150127</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150127/south-korea-announces-interagency-investigation-unit-tackle-crypto-crime"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T11:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[South Korea is ramping up fight against crypto crime with the launch of multi-agency virtual asset crime investigation unit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lido Finance DAO Mulls Introducing New Dual Governance Model]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150113</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150113/lido-finance-dao-mulls-introducing-new-dual-governance-model"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T10:50:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LDO holders currently hold the keys to the bank, which could put the Lido Finance’s staking community at a disadvantage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi,Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Gaming Startup Ultra Launches Esports Platform With Token, NFT Prizes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150076</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150076/crypto-gaming-startup-ultra-launches-esports-platform-token-nft-prizes"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T10:01:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ultra Arena features on-chain digital identities and reputation, with an aim to help amateur players rise up the ranks—and maybe even go pro.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ransomware May Be Dying Out, But Cryptojacking Is Up 399%: Cybersecurity Firm]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150112</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150112/ransomware-may-be-dying-but-cryptojacking-is-399-cybersecurity-firm"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T10:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The education sector saw 320 times more cryptojackings in the first half of 2023 than last year—and weirdly, market downturns spark more attacks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Connor Sephton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lacoste's New Virtual Store Has Exclusive Perks for Ethereum NFT Holders]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150014</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150014/lacoste-new-virtual-store-exclusive-perks-ethereum-nft-holders"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T09:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apparel brand Lacoste's new digital storefront provides an immersive shopping experience—and NFT holders get full access.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephanie Hirschmiller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitter’s Original ‘Blue Bird’ Logo Creator Martin Grasser Says ‘It Had a Great 11-Year Run’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150097</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150097/twitters-original-blue-bird-logo-creator-martin-grasser-says-had-great-11-year-run"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T08:31:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite a tinge of sadness, the designer behind the iconic blue bird is nonetheless optimistic about Musk’s new direction for Twitter–or, X.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Rich Are Splurging on Biohacking Clubs to Cheat Death]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150047</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150047/biohacking-trend-longevity-life-extension-gyms-clubs"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T01:51:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ultra rich want to live forever and are shelling out big bucks to do so. But biohacking is starting to seep into the mainstream.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Earn Bitcoin for Walking Around Major Cities—Here's How]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150026</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150026/you-can-earn-bitcoin-walking-around-major-cities-heres-how"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T22:41:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The sMiles app's new location-based "Bitcoinverse" game offers another way to earn Bitcoin rewards beyond racking up steps and shopping.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Whales Moved Nearly $60 Million In Five Days]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150027</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150027/bitcoin-whales-moved-nearly-60-million-in-five-days"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T21:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More than 2,000 BTC are on the move after years of inactivity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EDX Markets Crypto Exchange Taps Talos to Broaden Reach]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=150025</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/150025/edx-markets-talos-trading-wall-street-banks-crypto-trading"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T21:28:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The exchange, which began trading last month, seeks to bring more liquidity to market for its clients.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Dogecoin?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=5678</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/dogecoin-crypto-cryptocurrency-guide-how-to-buy-doge"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T19:28:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin is a peer-to-peer cryptocurrency based on a popular Internet meme. The token started off as a joke, but it's become a serious proposition.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward,Stephen Graves,Wendy Clack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Surges 9% After Cryptic Elon Musk Tweets Link DOGE and X]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149992</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149992/dogecoin-surges-on-elon-musk-tweet-will-it-be-integrated-into-x-com"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T18:45:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum, and other digital assets aren't moving much today. But Dogecoin is after Musk tweeted about it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KuCoin Denies Layoffs, Says Cuts Are Result of 'Biannual Appraisal']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149991</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149991/kucoin-denies-layoffs-says-cuts-are-result-of-biannual-appraisal"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T18:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KuCoin’s clarification follows a claim that its new KYC policy is cutting into its profits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Gaming Franchise Aurory Expands to Ethereum Layer-2 Arbitrum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149830</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149830/solana-gaming-franchise-aurory-expands-ethereum-layer-2-arbitrum"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T16:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The blockchain world of Aurory just got a little bigger. The studio behind two upcoming NFT games is going cross-chain to Arbitrum.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche Foundation Launches $50M Asset Tokenization Initiative]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149978</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149978/avalanche-foundation-launches-50m-asset-tokenization-initiative"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T14:51:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Avalanche Foundation is looking to cash in on tokenization, launching a new $50 million initiative to bring activity to the network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Traders Are Turning From Bitcoin to Altcoins Amid Favorable Ripple Ruling]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149969</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149969/traders-are-turning-from-bitcoin-to-altcoins-amid-favorable-ripple-ruling"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T14:04:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alt season? Among the 25 largest exchanges, Bitcoin’s market dominance has dropped to levels not seen since April this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Big Respect Between Ethereum and Cosmos Developer Communities': dYdX Foundation CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/XU5MbCGE/big-respect-between-ethereum-and-cosmos-developer-communities-dydx-foundation-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/XU5MbCGE/big-respect-between-ethereum-and-cosmos-developer-communities-dydx-foundation-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T13:24:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CEO of the dYdX Foundation Charles d'Haussy unpacks the decision behind moving one of the largest decentralized exchange protocol's over to its very own chain built on Cosmos. A key driver, he told Decrypt at this year's EthCC event, was that instead of launching on a rollup or another layer-1, launching a fully customized chain will allow dYdX to fine tune the network for its product's needs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CyberKongz to Mint Genkai NFTs on Ronin, Migrate Game to 'Axie' Chain]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149925</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149925/cyberkongz-mint-genkai-nfts-ronin-migrate-game-axie-infinity-chain"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T13:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CyberKongz is moving its Play and Kollect NFT game from Polygon to Ronin, with plans for a second Ronin game in the works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK Privacy Regulator 'Making Enquiries' Into Sam Altman’s Worldcoin Amid Token Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149943</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149943/uk-privacy-regulator-making-enquiries-sam-altmans-worldcoin-token-launch"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T12:58:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This isn't stopping Worldcoin from rolling out in Britain—with iris-scanning orbs now available in three locations throughout London.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Connor Sephton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Staking Solution Lido 'Had Perfect Product Market Fit' at Launch, Says DAO's Biz Dev Contributor]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/fUHhelhV/ethereum-staking-solution-lido-had-perfect-product-market-fit-at-launch-says-daos-biz-dev-contributor</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/fUHhelhV/ethereum-staking-solution-lido-had-perfect-product-market-fit-at-launch-says-daos-biz-dev-contributor"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T08:43:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marin Tvrdić, a business development contributor to the Lido DAO, sat down with Decrypt during this year's EthCC to break down how the liquid staking protocol has managed such a massive lead, how it plans to keep that lead, and the protocol's new dual-governance tokenomics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Ev.io' Game Review: Earn Solana While Blasting Enemies]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/2ZmkuhL2/evio-game-review-earn-solana-while-blasting-enemies</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/2ZmkuhL2/evio-game-review-earn-solana-while-blasting-enemies"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T22:21:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ev.io is a web-based first-person shooter that's free to play, but lets NFT holders earn in-game currency that can be redeemed for Solana (SOL). Decrypt contributor Ryan Gladwin shares his review of the fun throwback to Quake-style blasting, albeit with a modern crypto twist.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Moving Fast and Breaking Things Isn't the Web3 Ethos': MetaMask Product Lead]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/l1EbLgl3/moving-fast-and-breaking-things-isnt-the-web3-ethos-metamask-product-lead</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/l1EbLgl3/moving-fast-and-breaking-things-isnt-the-web3-ethos-metamask-product-lead"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T15:45:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Account abstraction this, smart wallets that. Discussions at EthCC Paris about improving user experience have pointed at industry leader MetaMask as an example of what not to do. But that may soon change, with a host of updates and optimizations coming to crypto's number one wallet, said its product lead Alex Jupiter. It still may take some time, though, before these changes take effect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling Smart Wallets on Starknet 'Was The Winning Combination', Says Argent Co-Founder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/gnBsxw4D/scaling-smart-wallets-on-starknet-was-the-winning-combination-says-argent-co-founder</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/gnBsxw4D/scaling-smart-wallets-on-starknet-was-the-winning-combination-says-argent-co-founder"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T07:35:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Argent co-founder Julien Niset told Decrypt at EthCC Paris that he wants to make crypto wallets disappear. Or at least how they're currently conceived. From clunky seed phrases to a stiff user experience, Argent hopes to make using crypto a little less intimidating and a whole lot more fun.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Mighty Action Heroes' Open Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/litL6kKs/inside-mighty-action-heroes-open-beta</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/litL6kKs/inside-mighty-action-heroes-open-beta"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T18:23:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mighty Action Heroes is the flagship blockchain title from Mighty Bear Games. But is the browser-based battle royale shooter worth checking out? Decrypt's Kate Irwin offers her thoughts and a first look at the upcoming game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dr. Disrespect's 'Deadrop': Early Access Gameplay From Snapshot VI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/8l21EHoa/dr-disrespects-deadrop-early-access-gameplay-from-snapshot-vi</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/8l21EHoa/dr-disrespects-deadrop-early-access-gameplay-from-snapshot-vi"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T18:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin playtests Dr. Disrespect and Midnight Society's first-person shooter Deadrop and shares the latest game updates, as well as her opinions on the game in development. Currently, Deadrop offers Polygon Founders Pass NFTs with no other crypto plans revealed just yet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['More and More' Game Publishers Will Embrace NFTs: Mythical Games CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/wBWogSkl/more-and-more-game-publishers-will-embrace-nfts-mythical-games-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/wBWogSkl/more-and-more-game-publishers-will-embrace-nfts-mythical-games-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T22:28:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the wake of EA Sports and Fortnite creator Epic Games embracing Nike's NFT platform, Mythical Games CEO John Linden tells Decrypt's Andrew Hayward how quickly he expects to see more major traditional game publishers enter the blockchain space and how quickly the industry will scale.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gran Saga Unlimited Early Access: Inside the Anime MMORPG on Aptos]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JeFWMVwo/gran-saga-unlimited-early-access-inside-the-anime-mmorpg-on-aptos</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JeFWMVwo/gran-saga-unlimited-early-access-inside-the-anime-mmorpg-on-aptos"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T21:46:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin plays Gran Saga: Unlimited's second community playtest, reports her findings, and offers her opinion and insights on the upcoming game, which will offer optional Aptos NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[100 Thieves' Moe Says Blockchain Games Will 'Eventually' Be Accepted by Livestreamers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/xHhh62ID/100-thieves-moe-says-blockchain-games-will-eventually-be-accepted-by-livestreamers</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/xHhh62ID/100-thieves-moe-says-blockchain-games-will-eventually-be-accepted-by-livestreamers"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T16:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[100 Thieves content creator and gamer Moe also goes by "Yassuo" online after his favorite League of Legends character. Decrypt's Kate Irwin asks him about 100 Thieves' future crypto plans and whether Moe thinks creators like xQc and Pokimane might ever come around to blockchain games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Games of the Future Are Going to Be Different," Says Splinterlands Cofounder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/sQv6zcil/games-of-the-future-are-going-to-be-different-says-splinterlands-cofounder</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/sQv6zcil/games-of-the-future-are-going-to-be-different-says-splinterlands-cofounder"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T20:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Splinterlands Cofounder Matt Rosen tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about how the game has evolved over its five-year history and why he doesn't listen to the FUD around crypto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Champions Ascension: Like 'For Honor' with NFTs?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/gvM9ajww/inside-champions-ascension-like-for-honor-with-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/gvM9ajww/inside-champions-ascension-like-for-honor-with-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T22:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plai Labs Marketing Director Payton Kaleiwahea tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about player response to the combat game Champions Ascension in development, which offers arena combat, raid bosses, AI landscape features, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Activision VP Michael Lee: Gaming Is Crypto's 'Killer App']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/M9ulXrb3/ex-activision-vp-michael-lee-gaming-is-cryptos-killer-app</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/M9ulXrb3/ex-activision-vp-michael-lee-gaming-is-cryptos-killer-app"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Activision Vice President Michael Lee is now the SVP of Growth at Matter Labs. At the 3XP gaming conference, Lee sat down with Decrypt's Kate Irwin to discuss crypto gaming and give his predictions for the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Behind the Scenes with AMGI Studios and My Pet Hooligan]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/eQ71oapI/behind-the-scenes-with-amgi-studios-and-my-pet-hooligan</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/eQ71oapI/behind-the-scenes-with-amgi-studios-and-my-pet-hooligan"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T21:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin goes to Burbank, California for a behind-the-scenes tour of AMGI Studios, the developers of upcoming game My Pet Hooligan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Legend of Arcadia Chose Sui Over EVM Chains]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/H6JSRJIk/why-legend-of-arcadia-chose-sui-over-evm-chains</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/H6JSRJIk/why-legend-of-arcadia-chose-sui-over-evm-chains"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T21:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Legend of Arcadia Executive Producer Andy Lee tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the game and why they switched from EVM to new protocol Sui.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rumble Racing Star Game Preview: Is This Mario Kart With NFTs?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/lXVkuaeq/rumble-racing-star-game-preview-is-this-mario-kart-with-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/lXVkuaeq/rumble-racing-star-game-preview-is-this-mario-kart-with-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T16:47:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin shares a first look at Delabs' upcoming lawn mower racing game Rumble Racing Star, which offers a large cast of quirky characters pulled from the worlds of Bored Ape Yacht Club, Pudgy Penguins, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Laguna Games Turned Down 'Game of Thrones' for Crypto Unicorns]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/IqET3GYs/why-laguna-games-turned-down-game-of-thrones-for-crypto-unicorns</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/IqET3GYs/why-laguna-games-turned-down-game-of-thrones-for-crypto-unicorns"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T21:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin chats with Laguna Games about why the team chose to move away from an offer with WB Games to develop a Game of Thrones licensed title—and made Crypto Unicorns instead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>