<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-10-24T17:13:19.295Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-10-24T17:13:19.295Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Sees Over 2,000% Rise In Whale Appetite Amid Crypto Market Price Boom]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18991184/Shiba-Inu-Sees-Over-2000-Rise-In-Whale-Appetite-Amid-Crypto-Market-Price-Boom</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18991184/Shiba-Inu-Sees-Over-2000-Rise-In-Whale-Appetite-Amid-Crypto-Market-Price-Boom"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T17:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB) has recently attracted considerable attention in the crypto market, thanks to a sudden surge in whale movements over the past weekend. Crypto whales, a term used to describe individuals or entities that hold large amounts of cryptocurrencies, have notably contributed to a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Is Not Gold – Why Spot ETF May Not Be 'Sell the News' Event: EY's Brody]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a9d65670</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/10/24/bitcoin-is-not-gold-why-spot-etf-may-not-be-sell-the-news-event-eys-brody/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T16:58:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The consulting firm's global blockchain leader discussed his bullish outlook in a CNBC appearance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen  Alpher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Co-Founder of Paradigm, a Top Crypto Investor,  Steps Down as Managing Partner to Focus on Science]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18991185/Co-Founder-of-Paradigm-a-Top-Crypto-Investor-Steps-Down-as-Managing-Partner-to-Focus-on-Science</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18991185/Co-Founder-of-Paradigm-a-Top-Crypto-Investor-Steps-Down-as-Managing-Partner-to-Focus-on-Science"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T16:56:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fred Ehrsam, co-founder of large crypto investment firm Paradigm, has stepped down as managing partner at the company and will act as a general partner going forward, he announced in a Tuesday post on X (formerly Twitter).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cosmos Developer Releases New Proposal To Cut ATOM Inflation in Half to 10% – Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18991169/Cosmos-Developer-Releases-New-Proposal-To-Cut-ATOM-Inflation-in-Half-to-10-Heres-Why</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18991169/Cosmos-Developer-Releases-New-Proposal-To-Cut-ATOM-Inflation-in-Half-to-10-Heres-Why"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T16:55:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Cosmos (ATOM) developer has unveiled a proposal that will cut the maximum inflation of the project’s native asset in half. Zaki Manian, the co-founder of decentralized asset management protocol Sommelier, has proposed changing the max inflation parameter on Cosmos from 20% to 10%, which would...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Comprehensive Review of CryptoLeo Casino]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18991150/A-Comprehensive-Review-of-CryptoLeo-Casino</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18991150/A-Comprehensive-Review-of-CryptoLeo-Casino"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T16:53:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Official website www.cryptoleo.com Year established 2021 Owner Uno Digital Media B.V. Address Johan Van Walbeeckplein 24, Willemstad, Curaçao Licence Curaçao Casino bonus Welcome Bonus: 150% up to 3,000 USDT Languages English, Czech, French, German, Greek, Italian, Norwegian, Polish, Portuguese,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale Partners With FTSE Russell for New Crypto Indexes Business]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a9d05996</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/10/24/grayscale-partners-with-ftse-russell-for-new-crypto-indexes-business/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T16:45:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. crypto asset manager Grayscale Investments has entered into a partnership with FTSE Russell – the index division of London Stock Exchange parent LSE Group – to create a new crypto indexes business.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leaked Proof! Blackrock Bitcoin ETF Coming Soon]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18991168/Leaked-Proof-Blackrock-Bitcoin-ETF-Coming-Soon</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18991168/Leaked-Proof-Blackrock-Bitcoin-ETF-Coming-Soon"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T16:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blackrock Bitcoin ETF coming soon according to leaked info! Bybit Lucky Draw https://www.bybit.com/en-US/promo/affiliates-campaign/iphone15-pro-lucky-draw/?affiliate_id=1378 🔥 GET MY FREE NEWSLETTER 👉 https://cryptolark.co/WEALTHMASTERY💸 BYBIT $30,030 BONUS & FEE DISCOUNT 👉...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Schiff Calls Bitcoin Buyers 'Dumb']]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18991148/Schiff-Calls-Bitcoin-Buyers-Dumb</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18991148/Schiff-Calls-Bitcoin-Buyers-Dumb"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T16:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gold bug Peter Schiff believes that recent rally is based on naive anticipation rather than genuine market confidence]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC To Review Grayscale's Spot Ether ETF: Will Ethereum Prices Breakout Above $2,000?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18991151/SEC-To-Review-Grayscales-Spot-Ether-ETF-Will-Ethereum-Prices-Breakout-Above-2000</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18991151/SEC-To-Review-Grayscales-Spot-Ether-ETF-Will-Ethereum-Prices-Breakout-Above-2000"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T16:44:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) will review Grayscale’s Bitcoin Trust ETF filing once more. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Is Not Gold – Why Spot ETF May Not Be 'Sell the News' Event: EY's Brody]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18991152/Bitcoin-Is-Not-Gold-Why-Spot-ETF-May-Not-Be-Sell-the-News-Event-EYs-Brody</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18991152/Bitcoin-Is-Not-Gold-Why-Spot-ETF-May-Not-Be-Sell-the-News-Event-EYs-Brody"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T16:43:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The consulting firm's global blockchain leader discussed his bullish outlook in a CNBC appearance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CME says Q3 open interest for bitcoin, ether derivatives hit all time highs]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18991134/CME-says-Q3-open-interest-for-bitcoin-ether-derivatives-hit-all-time-highs</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18991134/CME-says-Q3-open-interest-for-bitcoin-ether-derivatives-hit-all-time-highs"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T16:40:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Futures and options contracts for bitcoin and ethereum are soared in Q3 as institutions continue to grow more interested]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mexican Billionaire Says 'Buy Bitcoin, Sell Bonds, Reject Inflation']]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a9d1a7a9</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/markets/ricardo-salinas-mexican-billionaire-buy-bitcoin-sell-bonds-reject-inflation"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T16:37:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Store your wealth in Bitcoin."
That was the message give by Ricardo Salinas, a prominent billionaire and the honorary chairman of TV Azteca, in an exclusive interview with Bitcoin Magazine reporter Isabella Santos last week. The rare sit-down interview, which marked the Mexican billionaire's first Spanish-language interview on the topic.
The Ricardo Salinas Interview: Mexican Billionaire Says Sell Bonds, Buy Bitcoin, & Reject Inflation (; 19:49) 
In the 20-minute interview, he discussed how the cryptocurrency can act as a safeguard against inflation and the pitfalls of traditional financial systems, the conversation taking place on the occasion of Salinas' recognition by the Atlas Society, an organization known for promoting individualism and free-market philosophies.
Salinas began by add…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reed Macdonald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond Bukele: Sustaining El Salvador’s Orange Wave of Freedom]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a9d1a7a0</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/el-salvador-bitcoin-news/beyond-bukele-sustaining-el-salvadors-orange-wave-of-freedom"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T16:37:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is El Salvador’s Orange Enlightenment Only One Leader Deep?
The world is witnessing a miracle unfold in the beautiful country of El Salvador. In just the first four years of president Nayib Bukele’s presidency, the smallest Central American country and recurring murder capital of the world, plagued by civil war, endemic corruption, and generational poverty, not only reformed its justice system and neutered its terrorizing gangs resulting in unprecedented public safety, a surge in tourism, and foreign investment, but began casting off its neocolonial yoke, paying its latest bond debt on schedule and declining further IMF assistance. Equally impactful for its future: President Bukele defied the U.S.-dominated IMF and declared bitcoin legal tender—the world’s first nation to do so. But he wil…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>William E. Stebbins Jr.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Up 1.6 Million Percent Since Infamous Nick Allen 'Mess Tweet']]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a9d1a78c</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/markets/bitcoin-price-up-1-6-million-percent-since-infamous-allen-tweet"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T16:37:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[They say time heals all wounds – not in Bitcoin.
As documented by Bitcoin Historian Pete Rizzo, tomorrow marks the 12th anniversary of a now-infamous tweet by Nick Allen back in 2011, one that demonstrates the remarkable growth and resilience of the cryptocurrency over the past decade.
The tweet in question, posted on October 25, 2011, by technologist Nick Allen, expressed disbelief at Bitcoin's value, which was "down to $2.70 a pop." Allen went on to say he was "so glad I didn't buy in on that mess."
At the time of the tweet, Bitcoin was trading at $2, and it's up some 1,600,000 percent since that date.
Fast forward to today, and Bitcoin's price has soared to nearly $35,000 per coin, marking a phenomenal increase from the days when it was valued in the single digits. Allen's tweet has since become a symbol of how the cryptocurrency has defied expectations and evolved into a mainstream asset class.
 
         
         
         
        Allen's responded to the post in 2021, at a time when Bitcoin was down from $60,000 all-time highs. 
    
Nick Allen, who has an extensive background in the gaming and esports industry, may not have anticipated the extraordinary growth of Bitcoin when he posted his tweet, but the incredible price increase highlights the digital currency's journey and the increasing interest in cryptocurrencies as a legitimate investment vehicle.
Still, as recent news stories show, Allen is not alone when it comes to believing Bitcoin is a fad whose best days are behind it. While some are excited about the potential approval of a Bitcoin spot ETF, there has been a continued barrage of news stories in the wake of the FTX trial that take a similar tone.
In this way, Allen's tweet may serve as a reminder that Bitcoin has a history of defying its doubters – and rewarding its investors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reed Macdonald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP’s Price Surges to Two-Month High as Bitcoin ETF Hopes Boost Crypto Market]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18991138/XRPs-Price-Surges-to-Two-Month-High-as-Bitcoin-ETF-Hopes-Boost-Crypto-Market</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18991138/XRPs-Price-Surges-to-Two-Month-High-as-Bitcoin-ETF-Hopes-Boost-Crypto-Market"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T16:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price of the native token of the XRP Ledger, $XRP, has surged to a two-month high amid a wider cryptocurrency market rally that saw the price of the flagship cryptocurrency Bitcoin ($BTC) reach a 16-month high. The crypto market rally, which saw XRP’s price rise over 15% over the past week...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$300 Million Investment Fuels Nym Technologies’ Privacy Focus]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18991119/300-Million-Investment-Fuels-Nym-Technologies-Privacy-Focus</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18991119/300-Million-Investment-Fuels-Nym-Technologies-Privacy-Focus"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T16:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A group of crypto venture firms are investing over $300 million in Nym Technologies through its Innovation Fund, aimed at enhancing user privacy in the crypto landscape. Investors include Polychain Capital, Huobi Incubator, Eden Block, and KR1, among others. The Nym Innovation Fund, an...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paradigm co-founder Ehrsam steps down as managing partner]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18991116/Paradigm-co-founder-Ehrsam-steps-down-as-managing-partner</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18991116/Paradigm-co-founder-Ehrsam-steps-down-as-managing-partner"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T16:33:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paradigm co-founder Fred Ehrsam is stepping down as managing partner as the venture capital firm eyes a new fund.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s Meteoric Rise to $35,000 Erases $232M in Short Positions in Just 24 Hours]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a9d2e6a0</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoins-meteoric-rise-to-35000-erases-232m-in-short-positions-in-just-24-hours/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T16:30:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On October 24, 2023, bitcoin (BTC) experienced a robust 13% surge during the early morning trading hours, Eastern Time (ET). This rise catapulted bitcoin’s value to $35,108 per unit, propelling the entire cryptocurrency market upwards by over 10%. As the market soared, traders who had placed their bets against crypto assets like bitcoin and ethereum found themselves in a tight spot. In a mere 24 hours, a staggering $323 million in crypto short positions evaporated.
 
24-Hour Rally: Crypto Economy’s Ascent Liquidates $427M in Short and Long Stakes
 
Currently, the cryptocurrency market’s value hovers around a whopping $1.3 trillion, marking a 10% increase. Within the past day, BTC’s value ascended by 13%. Other major players also saw notable gains: ETH leaped by 9%, BNB ascended by 5%, and …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Postmortem On The Lightning Replacement Cycling Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18991068/Postmortem-On-The-Lightning-Replacement-Cycling-Attack</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18991068/Postmortem-On-The-Lightning-Replacement-Cycling-Attack"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a legitimate vulnerability in the Lightning protocol, but the sky is not falling.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is bitcoin’s ETF-fueled rally to $35K premature? Well, maybe]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18991069/Is-bitcoins-ETF-fueled-rally-to-35K-premature-Well-maybe</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18991069/Is-bitcoins-ETF-fueled-rally-to-35K-premature-Well-maybe"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T16:29:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Rumors are generating a buying signal, but the news might be a different story,” industry exec says amid apparent bullish signals for such proposals]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Euroclear Unveils RWA Tokenization Service With World Bank's 100M Euros Digital Bond Issuance]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a9d3a2da</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/10/24/euroclear-unveils-rwa-tokenization-service-with-world-banks-100m-euros-digital-bond-issuance/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T16:26:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The digital bond was issued on R3's Corda blockchain, while global bank Citi and investment manager TD Securities assisted in the issuance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Regulatory uncertainty in North America impends DeFi adoption: Chainalysis reports]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18991080/Regulatory-uncertainty-in-North-America-impends-DeFi-adoption-Chainalysis-reports</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18991080/Regulatory-uncertainty-in-North-America-impends-DeFi-adoption-Chainalysis-reports"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T16:23:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized finance (DeFi) is among the new innovations brought about by the realization of digital currencies. They have become a force to reckon with as they offer financial services through blockchain technology. DeFi growth has been hindered in the region of North America due to regulatory...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Bitcoin-Related Greenidge Generation Holdings Stock Is Growing Greener]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18991107/Why-Bitcoin-Related-Greenidge-Generation-Holdings-Stock-Is-Growing-Greener</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18991107/Why-Bitcoin-Related-Greenidge-Generation-Holdings-Stock-Is-Growing-Greener"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T16:20:43.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Invesco MD Anna Paglia: 'I Always Looked At ETFs As A Game-Changer']]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18991108/Invesco-MD-Anna-Paglia-I-Always-Looked-At-ETFs-As-A-Game-Changer</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18991108/Invesco-MD-Anna-Paglia-I-Always-Looked-At-ETFs-As-A-Game-Changer"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T16:20:22.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DCG says it ‘cooperated for months’ with NYAG prior to lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18991053/DCG-says-it-cooperated-for-months-with-NYAG-prior-to-lawsuit</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18991053/DCG-says-it-cooperated-for-months-with-NYAG-prior-to-lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T16:19:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In its third quarter shareholder letter, DCG gave updates on Grayscale, the NYAG suit and the Genesis creditor plan]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Wallet Maker Ledger Officially Rolls Out 'Recover,' Unleashing Fresh Round of Snark]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a9dce552</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/10/24/crypto-wallet-maker-ledger-officially-rolls-out-recover-unleashing-fresh-round-of-snark/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T16:18:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recover involves users' private keys being encrypted, duplicated and divided into three pieces which are held with three different parties.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralization on a Spectrum: How Fully On-chain Games Are the Future of Web3 Gaming]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a9dce522</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/10/24/decentralization-on-a-spectrum-how-fully-on-chain-games-are-the-future-of-web3-gaming/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T16:18:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Game developers should stop worrying about Web3’s friction and think more about many true benefits that blockchain can bring, says Leah Callon-Butler.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leah Callon-Butler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chainalysis blames US banks for the drop in institutional crypto adoption]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18991081/Chainalysis-blames-US-banks-for-the-drop-in-institutional-crypto-adoption</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18991081/Chainalysis-blames-US-banks-for-the-drop-in-institutional-crypto-adoption"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T16:18:48.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Euroclear Unveils RWA Tokenization Service With World Bank's 100M Euros Digital Bond Issuance]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18991070/Euroclear-Unveils-RWA-Tokenization-Service-With-World-Banks-100M-Euros-Digital-Bond-Issuance</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18991070/Euroclear-Unveils-RWA-Tokenization-Service-With-World-Banks-100M-Euros-Digital-Bond-Issuance"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T16:16:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The digital bond was issued on R3's Corda blockchain, while global bank Citi and investment manager TD Securities assisted in the issuance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Tumbles 3% as BlackRock Spot ETF Ticker Pulled From DTCC Website]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a9de80b0</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/10/24/bitcoin-tumbles-3-as-blackrock-spot-etf-ticker-pulled-from-dtcc-website/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T16:08:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin fell by more than 3% from $34,500 to $33,400 on Tuesday afternoon after the ticker for BlackRock's spot bitcoin ETF was removed from the Depository Trust & Clearing Corporation's website.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Regulatory Clarity Won’t Bring an End to Crypto Risk]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a9de8098</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/10/24/regulatory-clarity-wont-bring-an-end-to-crypto-risk/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T16:08:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even comprehensive crypto legislation won’t stop people from making bad investment decisions, says EY's blockchain leader.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Brody</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase, Bitcoin Miners Extend Gains as BTC Surges on BlackRock ETF Hopes]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a9d86f4f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/10/24/coinbase-bitcoin-miners-extend-gains-as-btc-surges-on-blackrock-etf-hopes/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T15:56:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shares of Coinbase (COIN), MicroStrategy (MSTR) and Marathon Digital (MARA) surged more than 13% as Bitcoin (BTC) tops $34,000.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aoyon Ashraf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastercard Plans Web3 Collaborations With Self-Custody Wallet Firms]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a9d9ba5f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/10/24/mastercard-plans-web3-collaborations-with-self-custody-wallet-firms/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T15:48:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The payments processor is working with MetaMask and Ledger among others, according to a Web3 Workshop presentation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biggest Movers: XRP Extends Recent Gains, Rising to 8-Week High]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a9db9210</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/biggest-movers-xrp-extends-recent-gains-rising-to-8-week-high/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T15:37:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XRP rose for a fourth straight day on Tuesday, as overall sentiment in the market was mostly bullish. The global crypto market cap is nearly 10% higher at the time of writing, with the likes of bitcoin trading at a 17-month high. Cardano also surged, recording a 2-month peak.
 
XRP
 
XRP, formerly ripple, was one of Tuesday’s biggest movers, as the token rose by as much as 10% today.
 
After trading at a low of $0.5267 on Monday, XRP/USD climbed to a peak of $0.581 earlier in the day.
 
This surge resulted in XRP rising to its highest point since August 18, when price was on the cusp of breaking into the $0.60 region.
 
 
From the chart, it appears that the move came after the 10-day (red) moving average crossed over its 25-day (blue) counterpart.
 
Should bulls intend to maintain this recent round of momentum, they will first need to break a ceiling on the relative strength index (RSI) of 72.00.
 
At the time of writing, the index is tracking at a reading of 71.70.
 
 
Cardano (ADA )
 
Additionally, cardano (ADA) rallied to a multi-month high during today’s session, breaking a key resistance level in the process.
 
ADA/USD jumped to an intraday peak of $0.2911 on Tuesday, after starting the week trading at a low of $0.2626.
 
Today’s surge in price has sent the cryptocurrency to its strongest level since August 13, and comes after six days of consecutive gains.
 
 
This has resulted in price strength now residing in overbought territory, with a current reading of 75.70.
 
Looking back at the chart, this is the highest the index has hit since January, and was the catalyst for bulls to break a price ceiling of $0.280.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
Is the $0.30 level attainable in the coming days? Let us know your thoughts in the comments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can a FanDuel Co-Founder's 'Fantasy Music' Game Help Discover the Next Taylor Swift?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202927</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202927/fanduel-cofounder-fantasy-music-game-help-discover-next-taylor-swift"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T15:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vault’s Solana NFT music platform is spinning up a fantasy sports-like experience around emerging artists. Can it push them to prominence?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ali Shutler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Price Breakout: SOL Rally To $55 Already Programmed?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a9c60cc7</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/solana-price-breakout-to-55/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T15:22:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana (SOL) has undoubtedly been one of the major winners of the recent crypto rally after notching over 60% gains on the weekly chart. Since it has grown so much, expectations of a downside are common. However, one crypto analyst is bucking this trend as they see a continued breakout for the altcoin.
 
Solana To Breakout To $55
 
In the post shared by crypto analyst Babenski on TradingView, we can see where the analyst expects the price of Solana to end up. The chart which already shows Solana’s price surge above $30 suggests an almost 100% leg-up from this high level.
 
 
Babenski uses the Solana weekly chart in which they see the price breaking out. This comes as no surprise given that Solana has performed better on the weekly chart compared to the daily chart with a 60.89% increase fo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacker Denis Katana Helped Russian Crime Boss Launder Money With Bitcoin, Says Spanish Judge]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202807</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202807/hacker-denis-katana-bitcoin-money-laundering"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T15:16:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 'Bitcoin czar' is accused of advising a crime ring to launder their money with Bitcoin because of its “lack of state control.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cathie Wood's ARK Invest Sells 2% of Grayscale Bitcoin Trust Holdings as BTC Rallies]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a9c2a82d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/10/24/cathie-woods-ark-invest-sells-2-of-grayscale-bitcoin-trust-holdings-as-btc-tops-34k/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T14:52:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin's momentum is attributed to anticipation of the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) finally approving a spot bitcoin ETF.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Archax to Launch Regulated Exchange for Tokenized Assets This Year]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a9c2a823</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/10/24/archax-to-launch-regulated-exchange-for-tokenized-assets-this-year/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T14:52:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company also said it tokenized an abrdn market fund in euros, pounds and dollars and has a pipeline of several hundred million dollars to be held in the fund.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camomile Shumba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NASD Raises $3.3M Seed Round for Asset Issuer Chain Noble]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a9c2a81d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/10/24/nasd-raises-33m-seed-round-for-asset-issuer-chain-noble/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T14:52:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Noble is an appchain built for native asset issuance in Cosmos and the boundless Inter-Blockchain Communication (IBC) ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lyllah Ledesma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Again Seeks to Nix ‘Incendiary’ CFTC Suit]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a9c2a811</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/10/24/binance-again-seeks-to-nix-incendiary-cftc-suit/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T14:52:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. law “does not control the world,” said the filing by the world’s biggest crypto exchange as it feels increasing regulatory pressure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack Schickler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will The Spot Bitcoin ETF Approval Be A ‘Sell The News’-Event?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a9cf41be</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/spot-bitcoin-etf-approval-sell-the-news-event/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T14:21:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The anticipated approval of a spot Bitcoin Exchange Traded Fund (ETF) has dominated discussions among traders, analysts, and market observers over the past few days. With many speculating on the potential impact, the age-old strategy of “buy the rumor, sell the news” has been at the forefront of many conversations. Will the strategy push the Bitcoin price down once BlackRock, Fidelity, Invesco, Bitwise and other financial giants list their spot ETFs on the market?
 
Spot Bitcoin ETF Approval: A ‘Sell The News’-Event?
 
Notorious financial expert and Bitcoin skeptic, Peter Schiff, questioned the prolonged excitement surrounding ETF prospects, suggesting its approval could mark a peak in optimism. He tweeted, “How many times can Bitcoin rally on the same ETF rumor? Once a US Bitcoin ETF is a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[dYdX Releases Cosmos-Based Chain Source Code Ahead of Mainnet Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202941</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202941/dydx-releases-cosmos-based-chain-source-code-ahead-mainnet-launch"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T12:07:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The release of the open source code marks the initial phase of dYdX Chain’s mainnet launch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Soar Double Digits as Crypto Markets Add $100 Billion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202944</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202944/bitcoin-ethereum-soar-crypto-markets-add-100-billion"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T12:03:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin and Ethereum soared nearly double digits early on Tuesday, as the wider crypto market added nearly 10% to its market cap overnight.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Andreessen Horowitz Backs Nym's $300M Privacy-Centric 'Innovation Fund']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202861</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202861/andreessen-horowitz-backs-nym-300m-privacy-centric-innovation-fund"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T11:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Applications for the innovation fund, which is not strictly limited to Nym’s privacy-preserving tech, will be accepted starting in November.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cathie Wood's Ark Invest Sells $5.8M in Coinbase, Grayscale Bitcoin Trust Shares as Crypto Market Surges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202938</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202938/cathie-woods-ark-invest-sells-5-8m-in-coinbase-grayscale-bitcoin-trust-shares-as-crypto-market-surges"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T09:29:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Bitcoin jumped over 10% amid renewed hopes of a spot ETF approval, Ark Invest opted to sell some of its Bitcoin-related assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deepfakes Made Simple With AI: An In-Depth Look at FaceFusion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201688</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201688/how-to-ai-deepfake-video-facefusion-face-swap-ai-tool"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T08:07:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The open-source FaceFusion tool is described as a next-generation face swapper and enhancer, and an accessible entry into the world of deepfake creation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Next Snapdragon Chip Leaks: The Upcoming Mobile CPU Is Packed with AI Power]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202905</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202905/snapdragon-8-generation-3-artificial-intelligence-smartphone-chip"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T01:20:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From enhanced performance to groundbreaking AI capabilities, the Qualcomm Snapdragon 8 Gen 3 is set to redefine what you can do with your smartphone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Touches $34K as $114 Million in Shorts Liquidated]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202894</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202894/bitcoin-price-34000-35000-liquidiations-2023-record"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T23:41:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A second rally for the day triggered $145 million in overall crypto market liquidations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Film3 Summit Returns to L.A. Alongside Streaming Festival With Theta]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202668</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202668/film3-summit-returns-la-alongside-streaming-festival-theta"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T23:15:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The live Film3 Summit will run alongside MetaFilm3 Fest, an on-chain festival powered by Theta that includes multiple film premieres.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ghost in the Machine: OpenAI CEO Sees ChatGPT on Track From AI to AGI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202877</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202877/openai-ai-agi-sam-altman-wall-street-journal"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T22:54:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI CEO Sam Altman delved into the transformative potential of AI, hinting at a future where data takes a backseat to reasoning.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Are the Odds Sam Bankman-Fried Testifies in His Trial?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202863</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202863/what-are-the-odds-sam-bankman-fried-testifies-in-his-trial"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T21:18:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The formal crypto mogul has remained silent in court so far. But that could change as his trial progresses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Ordered to Review Grayscale’s Bitcoin ETF Application]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202874</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202874/sec-must-again-review-grayscale-bitcoin-etf-application"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T20:39:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Will the SEC find another reason to reject Grayscale, or will it finally approve a spot Bitcoin ETF?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These Crypto Stocks Are Still Outperforming Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202865</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202865/crypto-stocks-beating-bitcoin-grayscale-microstrategy-coinbase"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T20:10:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While Bitcoin has been a great buy, many companies built around it are flying even higher this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock Preps for Bitcoin ETF Launch, Lines Up Seed Investor and Reveals Ticker]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202862</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202862/blackrock-preps-for-bitcoin-etf-launch-with-amendment-showing-seed-fund-investor"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T19:59:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock's iShares Bitcoin Trust has a ticker and seed funding lined up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Blasts Past $31,000 as Optimism for BTC Spot ETF Surges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202840</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202840/bitcoin-31000-spot-btc-etf-optimism"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T17:19:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The last time the asset was this high was back in July.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF Coming Soon? Delays Have SEC’s Hester Peirce ‘Mystified’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202826</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202826/bitcoin-etf-coming-soon-delays-have-secs-hester-peirce-mystified"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T16:56:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After Grayscale's court victory, Hester Peirce doesn't know what her agency is waiting for.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microstrategy’s Bitcoin Billions Back in Profit as ‘Digital Gold’ Nears $31K]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202813</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202813/microstrategys-bitcoin-in-the-green-digital-gold-rallies"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T16:37:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC is fast closing in on $31,000 per coin—which means the largest public owner of the asset is making a return on its investment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is the Lightning Network? Bitcoin's Scalability Solution.]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=5684</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/bitcoin-lightning-network"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T14:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lightning Network is a scaling solution that attempts to address Bitcoin's slow transaction speeds and high transaction costs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Hussey,Tim Copeland,Daniel Phillips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Banking Crisis Destroyed Institutional Crypto Trading: Chainalysis]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202791</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202791/us-banking-crisis-destroyed-institutional-crypto-trading-chainalysis"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T13:10:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto activity saw a sharp drop following Silicon Valley Bank and crypto-friendly banks Signature and Silvergate shutting down.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Almost All Mining Stocks Have Outpaced Bitcoin This Year]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202776</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202776/almost-all-mining-stocks-have-outpaced-bitcoin-this-year"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T11:01:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most mining stocks, except two, have outperformed Bitcoin by more than double this year despite the ongoing bear market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 Security Firm Blockaid Lands $33 Million in Latest Funding]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202523</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202523/web3-security-firm-blockaid-lands-33-million-latest-funding"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T11:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By offering an enhanced level of security for Web3 wallets, Blockaid aims to make the space safer for average users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Sees Lion’s Share of Investment Amid Spot ETF Hype: CoinShares]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202775</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202775/bitcoin-sees-lions-share-investment-amid-spot-etf-hype-coinshares"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T10:19:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As hype around a spot Bitcoin ETF reaches a pitch, investors are looking for more exposure to the leading cryptocurrency, reports CoinShares.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chainlink Leads Crypto Market Rally, Soaring 8% Overnight]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202771</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202771/chainlink-leads-crypto-market-rally-soaring-overnight"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T09:50:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price of Chainlink’s LINK rose about $10, bringing the oracle token to a high not seen in the last 17 months.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robot Hands Can Match Humans' Dexterity With New AI Smarts, Claims Nvidia]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202659</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202659/nvidia-eureka-ai-agent-allegedly-makes-robot-hands-dextrous-human-ones"/>
        <updated>2023-10-22T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia is all-in when it comes to AI. Eureka helps robots learn intricate skills faster than an aspiring surgeon, and its new SteerLM wants to make human annotation in AI training a thing of the past.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[God Mode: 9 Can't-Miss 'Starfield' Quests With the Best Stories and Rewards]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202444</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202444/9-cant-miss-starfield-quests-best-stories-rewards"/>
        <updated>2023-10-22T14:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to make the most of your time in Bethesda's epic sci-fi odyssey? Here are the Starfield quests that you must seek out and complete.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Frederiksen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Huawei Unveils OceanStor A310—A Speedy Storage Solution for AI Model Trainers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202568</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202568/huawei-unveils-oceanstor-a310-speedy-storage-solution-ai-model-trainers"/>
        <updated>2023-10-22T12:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Huawei steps into the AI storage arena with its OceanStor A310, showcasing potential solutions to industry-wide data processing hurdles.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dr. Disrespect's 'Deadrop' Shooter Unveils Cars, Racing Battles at Vegas Event]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202701</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202701/dr-disrespect-deadrop-shooter-unveils-cars-racing-battles-vegas-event"/>
        <updated>2023-10-22T02:04:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Midnight Society showed off the latest Deadrop update, Snapshot VII, at a lavish Las Vegas event that showcased newly-added cars and modes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Midnight Society's Rob Bowling on Deadrop's New Cars and User-Generated Modes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/A0auyZzn/midnight-societys-rob-bowling-on-deadrops-new-cars-and-user-generated-modes</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/A0auyZzn/midnight-societys-rob-bowling-on-deadrops-new-cars-and-user-generated-modes"/>
        <updated>2023-10-22T01:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt reporter and GG producer Kate Irwin interviews Midnight Society Studio Head Rob Bowling about Deadrop's development and Snapshot VII.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NASA Prepares Deep Space Mission—Why AI Will Play Important Role]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202611</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202611/nasa-prepares-deep-space-mission-why-ai-play-important-role"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T15:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NASA's Nancy Grace Roman Telescope, launching May 2027, aims to unravel dark matter mysteries and honor Roman's legacy in astronomy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week on Crypto Twitter: Fake ETF News Pumps Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202616</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202616/this-week-crypto-twitter-fake-etf-news-pumps-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T12:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One mistaken tweet on Monday pumped the price of Bitcoin by 10% in 24 hours—but it's not the only buzz from a busy week on Crypto Twitter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Is Like a Grocery Store Selling Oranges and SEC Should Leave It Alone, Says Crypto Lobby Group]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202626</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202626/binance-grocery-store-oranges-sec-crypto-lobby-group"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T22:10:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In its fight against Binance, "the SEC is suing the equivalent of a grocery store selling oranges and other fruit," says US Chamber of Digital Commerce in an amicus brief.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitch Will Let Users Stream Across Platforms—But They Better Act Right]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202617</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202617/twitch-let-users-stream-across-platforms-they-better-act-right"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T22:04:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Popular video game streaming site Twitch introduces big changes at TwitchCon 2023 as rivals new and old start to pose serious competition.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google and BlackRock Considered Investing in FTX as It Crumbled]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202583</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202583/google-blackrock-considered-investing-ftx-before-bankruptcy"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T20:12:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The exchange wanted to tap big names for its C1 funding, but FTX buckled before it closed the round.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI and Bitcoin Mining Meet in New Texas Data Center]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202590</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202590/ai-and-bitcoin-mining-meet-in-new-texas-data-center"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T20:09:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite the expansion, APLD shares fell 5.3% on Friday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Raini: The Lords of Light Review—SBF, CZ, and Satoshi Battle in This Crypto Card Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202585</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202585/raini-lords-light-review-sbf-cz-satoshi-battle-crypto-card-game"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T19:36:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[REVIEW: Putting an NFT spin on the Hearthstone formula, Raini: The Lords of Light goes even further with crypto memes and compelling card mechanics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Game Review: 'Raini: The Lords of Light' Brands Itself With Memes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/32YyJHCJ/game-review-raini-the-lords-of-light-brands-itself-with-memes</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/32YyJHCJ/game-review-raini-the-lords-of-light-brands-itself-with-memes"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T19:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Raini: Lords of Light is an NFT-optional card game bursting with crypto memes. From SBF to CZ and Elon, this free-to-play game has some truly wild animations. Decrypt contributor Ryan S. Gladwin shares his honest thoughts on the game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s Going On With Crypto Behemoth Digital Currency Group?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202551</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202551/whats-going-on-with-crypto-behemoth-digital-currency-group"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T18:31:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most important companies in the space has been steeped in legal woes. Here’s how it got to this point.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Model Transparency Is Getting Worse, Researchers Warn]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202555</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202555/ai-model-transparency-getting-worse-stanford-researchers"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T17:58:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Foundation models promise a new era in AI, but Stanford University researchers have flagged that they're becoming less transparent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Solana Explodes 25%, Bitcoin Reclaims $30K on ETF Hopes and Ripple Wins]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202554</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202554/week-in-coins-solana-bitcoin-xrp-ripple"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T16:59:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, usually the market pace-setter, was far outpaced by Solana, Bitcoin Cash and XRP.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Art Blocks Marfa Weekend Recap]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/QaTBP6eO/art-blocks-marfa-weekend-recap</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/QaTBP6eO/art-blocks-marfa-weekend-recap"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T19:19:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Relive the Art Blocks Marfa Weekend 2023 event with this highlights video, produced by Vincent Roazzi Jr. for Decrypt Studios in partnership with Art Blocks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Phantom Galaxies: A Look Inside the Mech Shooter NFT Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QI1uDwQv/phantom-galaxies-a-look-inside-the-mech-shooter-nft-game</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QI1uDwQv/phantom-galaxies-a-look-inside-the-mech-shooter-nft-game"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T21:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animoca Brands and game studio Blowfish are developing Phantom Galaxies, an upcoming sci-fi mech shooter game inspired by mech battlers like Transformers. Decrypt's Kate Irwin asks Blowfish Studios Cofounder and Managing Director Ben Lee about what it's like to play the game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Clip: DeepMedia's DeepID Deepfake Detection Tool at Work]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/m4Vy4vhC/clip-deepmedias-deepid-deepfake-detection-tool-at-work</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/m4Vy4vhC/clip-deepmedias-deepid-deepfake-detection-tool-at-work"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T16:48:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A clip showcasing how DeepMedia's DeepID deepfake detection tool works. Courtesy: DeepMedia]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentraland AI World Fair Trailer]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/3tUb56Fv/decentraland-ai-world-fair-trailer</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/3tUb56Fv/decentraland-ai-world-fair-trailer"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A trailer for the AI World Fair event in metaverse game Decentraland, taking place from October 25-27. Courtesy: Decentraland.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BackTheBunny - Money, Conspiracy, Milady]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BRoKZzer/backthebunny-money-conspiracy-milady</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BRoKZzer/backthebunny-money-conspiracy-milady"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T19:48:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our host Reza Jafery sits down with BackTheBunny to dive deep into money, the fight against crypto that we're witnessing in real-time, and milady culture. 

Our Host: https://twitter.com/rezajafery
Our Guest: https://twitter.com/BackTheBunny

Our Sponsors
https://decrypt.co/1000x]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['A Grand Experiment': Shrapnel Studio Head Don Norbury Talks Game Economics]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Z2OMMsC5/a-grand-experiment-shrapnel-studio-head-don-norbury-talks-game-economics</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Z2OMMsC5/a-grand-experiment-shrapnel-studio-head-don-norbury-talks-game-economics"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T17:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How much of Shrapnel's in-game items are tradeable NFTs? Don Norbury, Studio Head at Shrapnel and CTO at game studio NEON, tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about Shrapnel's approach to game economics, including different game pricing models and how NFT game economies create different challenges for developers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trezor Safe 3 and Trezor Keep Metal Unboxing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/IjqnO9pR/trezor-safe-3-and-trezor-keep-metal-unboxing</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/IjqnO9pR/trezor-safe-3-and-trezor-keep-metal-unboxing"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T14:45:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trezor has launched the Safe 3, a hardware wallet aimed at "new entrants to crypto," alongside the new Keep Metal recovery seed storage device. We take a first look at what comes in the box.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why AI Arena is Building on Arbitrum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Gl80TQOm/why-ai-arena-is-building-on-arbitrum</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Gl80TQOm/why-ai-arena-is-building-on-arbitrum"/>
        <updated>2023-10-12T14:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI Arena CEO Brandon Da Silva and COO Wei Xie discuss the challenges that come with building on Ethereum, ETH sidechains, and layer-two blockchains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pet3rPan_ on venture DAOs and blockchain games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DawNLI3O/pet3rpan-on-venture-daos-and-blockchain-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DawNLI3O/pet3rpan-on-venture-daos-and-blockchain-games"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T18:24:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the 4th episode of this time will be different.

Our guest for today's episode is Pet3rpan_ from Metacartel, 1kx, HydraVentures, and more!

https://twitter.com/pet3rpan_

This Time Will Be Different is sponsored by 1000x
https://decrypt.co/1000x]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Shrapnel's Marketplace, New Map, and 'AI Director' Feature]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/F5RQCmvH/inside-shrapnels-marketplace-new-map-and-ai-director-feature</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/F5RQCmvH/inside-shrapnels-marketplace-new-map-and-ai-director-feature"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T16:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin chats with Shrapnel's Head of Studio Don Norbury to get the latest updates on how the NFT-powered first-person sci-fi extraction shooter's development is progressing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Art of the Times': Art Blocks Founder Erick Calderon on the State of Generative Art]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zSjfRrl5/art-of-the-times-art-blocks-founder-erick-calderon-on-the-state-of-generative-art</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zSjfRrl5/art-of-the-times-art-blocks-founder-erick-calderon-on-the-state-of-generative-art"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T18:10:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Art Blocks founder and CEO Erick Calderon sat down with Sander Lutz, lead culture reporter at Decrypt's SCENE, at Art Blocks Marfa Weekend 2023. They discuss the evolution of the company and the generative art world, along with what draws art enthusiasts to be an active part of the community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt Learn: Digital Ownership Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/6udZCotB/decrypt-learn-digital-ownership-explained</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/6udZCotB/decrypt-learn-digital-ownership-explained"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T10:57:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most powerful aspects of blockchain technology is its ability to provide us genuine ownership of our digital assets. This is called digital ownership. In this video, we’ll deep dive into digital ownership, why it matters, and how web3 makes owning digital assets like our social networks, music libraries, personal data, and beyond possible. Author: Clarissa Watson, Senior Writer at Consensys.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Martin Shkreli on E/ACC and SBF in Prison]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QONaWXKZ/martin-shkreli-on-e-acc-and-sbf-in-prison</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QONaWXKZ/martin-shkreli-on-e-acc-and-sbf-in-prison"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T22:03:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reza Jafery and Martin Shkreli sit down for a casual conversation about the growing movement that is E/ACC, what songs they could recite at gunpoint, and whether or not SBF will thrive or just survive during his time in prison.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Can AI Do in Gaming?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JKuqCMao/what-can-ai-do-in-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JKuqCMao/what-can-ai-do-in-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T17:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI Arena CEO Brandon Da Silva and COO Wei Xie discuss how artificial intelligence can shape the video game experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['There Are No Real Standards': Ready Player Me CEO Timmu Tõke on Building for an Open Gaming Ecosystem]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TH3KEAI0/there-are-no-real-standards-ready-player-me-ceo-timmu-tke-on-building-for-an-open-gaming-ecosystem</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TH3KEAI0/there-are-no-real-standards-ready-player-me-ceo-timmu-tke-on-building-for-an-open-gaming-ecosystem"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T17:29:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Timmu Tõke, co-founder and CEO of Ready Player Me, joins Decrypt contributor Ryan Gladwin to discuss the startup's approach to powering avatars that are interoperable across games and metaverse platforms—and what's needed to convince the industry to adopt standards and open up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain Is 'Only Way' Forward for Gaming, Says Shrapnel Studio Head]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/fhoy7Z8f/blockchain-is-only-way-forward-for-gaming-says-shrapnel-studio-head</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/fhoy7Z8f/blockchain-is-only-way-forward-for-gaming-says-shrapnel-studio-head"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T21:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shrapnel Studio Head Don Norbury tells Kate Irwin the reasons why the upcoming first-person shooter game will offer a wide range of NFTs. He also reveals team-based gameplay plans and shares how game maps have already changed this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Social Media Sentiment Is Key to Crypto Price Discovery]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/981TBppa/social-media-sentiment-is-key-to-crypto-price-discovery</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/981TBppa/social-media-sentiment-is-key-to-crypto-price-discovery"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T23:47:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sacha Ghebali, Director of Strategy and Business Development at The TIE, says social media sentiment remains a key factor in price movements for major cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin and Ethereum. However, he notes that sentiment has turned more negative lately amid regulatory uncertainty. Ghebali believes events like the Ripple lawsuit ruling significantly impacted sentiment and prices. André Beganski interviewed him at Messari Mainnet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[500Altcoins discusses DeFi Summer and the Dubai Crypto Scene - This Time Will Be Different - Episode 2]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cI7p8AK3/500altcoins-discusses-defi-summer-and-the-dubai-crypto-scene-this-time-will-be-different-episode-2</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cI7p8AK3/500altcoins-discusses-defi-summer-and-the-dubai-crypto-scene-this-time-will-be-different-episode-2"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our host Reza Jafery is joined by Gareth Fenney aka 500Altcoins. They discuss the glory days of DeFi Summer and whether or not its a smart move for builders in the crypto space to relocate to Dubai.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>