<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-04-25T22:14:03.672Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-04-25T22:14:03.672Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morgan Stanley to Broaden Availability of Spot Bitcoin ETFs: Report]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74378e0aed</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/morgan-stanley-to-broaden-availability-of-spot-bitcoin-etfs-report/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T22:11:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Morgan Stanley, a leading global investment bank, is reportedly considering expanding access to bitcoin spot exchange-traded funds (ETFs). The firm may soon authorize its approximately 15,000 brokers to actively solicit customer purchases. Morgan Stanley to Widen Access to Spot Bitcoin ETFs Global investment bank Morgan Stanley is contemplating broadening access to spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anti-crypto SEC commissioner’s term is up in 41 days — Will she be replaced?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19437332/Anti-crypto-SEC-commissioners-term-is-up-in-41-days-Will-she-be-replaced</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19437332/Anti-crypto-SEC-commissioners-term-is-up-in-41-days-Will-she-be-replaced"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T22:07:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Caroline Crenshaw may continue to serve at the SEC for an additional 18 months after her term ends in June if the White House doesn't nominate a replacement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PEPE, FLOKI Backtrack 7% As Whales Keep Topping Up Billions]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19437330/PEPE-FLOKI-Backtrack-7-As-Whales-Keep-Topping-Up-Billions</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19437330/PEPE-FLOKI-Backtrack-7-As-Whales-Keep-Topping-Up-Billions"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T22:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whales splash millions on PEPE and FLOKI, expecting these meme tokens to continue showcasing exponential growth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Dogecoin Top Holder Profitability Ahead Of Cardano & Ethereum: Details]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74378ed7c9</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-dogecoin-top-holder-cardano-ethereum/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T22:04:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data shows that Bitcoin and Dogecoin have managed to top the charts regarding holder profitability. Here’s what the ranking looks like.
 
Bitcoin & Dogecoin Are Among Coins With Highest Investor Profitability Ratio
 
In a new post on X, the market intelligence platform IntoTheBlock talked about how holder profitability compares between some of the top layer-1 networks in the sector.
 
Here, holder profitability refers to the total percentage of investors or addresses on a given cryptocurrency network that are currently carrying some net unrealized gains.
 
 
This metric works by going through the transaction history of each address on the blockchain to find the average price at which it acquired its coins. If this average cost basis for any holder is less than the current spot pri…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spot Crypto ETFs Set To Begin Trading in Hong Kong Next Week: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19437326/Spot-Crypto-ETFs-Set-To-Begin-Trading-in-Hong-Kong-Next-Week-Report</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19437326/Spot-Crypto-ETFs-Set-To-Begin-Trading-in-Hong-Kong-Next-Week-Report"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T22:01:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spot market crypto exchange-traded funds (ETFs) are reportedly set to launch in Hong Kong as soon as next week. According to a new report by Reuters, the three asset managers who are providing the products say that Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) ETFs should start trading by April 30th as they...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Dogecoin Top Holder Profitability Ahead Of Cardano & Ethereum: Details]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19437324/Bitcoin-Dogecoin-Top-Holder-Profitability-Ahead-Of-Cardano-Ethereum-Details</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19437324/Bitcoin-Dogecoin-Top-Holder-Profitability-Ahead-Of-Cardano-Ethereum-Details"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T22:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data shows that Bitcoin and Dogecoin have managed to top the charts regarding holder profitability. Here’s what the ranking looks like. Bitcoin & Dogecoin Are Among Coins With Highest Investor Profitability Ratio In a new post on X, the market intelligence platform IntoTheBlock talked...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BONK, POPCAT and Solana memecoins stay green even as Bitcoin price drops]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19437325/BONK-POPCAT-and-Solana-memecoins-stay-green-even-as-Bitcoin-price-drops</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19437325/BONK-POPCAT-and-Solana-memecoins-stay-green-even-as-Bitcoin-price-drops"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Memecoins in the Solana ecosystem defy the recent bearish downtrend in the crypto market by managing to generate double-digit gains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SHIB and DOGE Rival Memecoin Cyborg Shiba (CYSHIB)Will Rally 4,700% After Solana Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19437313/SHIB-and-DOGE-Rival-Memecoin-Cyborg-Shiba-CYSHIBWill-Rally-4700-After-Solana-Launch</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19437313/SHIB-and-DOGE-Rival-Memecoin-Cyborg-Shiba-CYSHIBWill-Rally-4700-After-Solana-Launch"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T21:55:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cyborg Shiba (CYSHIB) could become a viral memecoin, like Shiba Inu (SHIB) and Dogecoin (DOGE)....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bonk Price Prediction as BONK Gains 130% From Recent Lows – Dip-Buying Opportunity Over?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19437329/Bonk-Price-Prediction-as-BONK-Gains-130-From-Recent-Lows-Dip-Buying-Opportunity-Over</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19437329/Bonk-Price-Prediction-as-BONK-Gains-130-From-Recent-Lows-Dip-Buying-Opportunity-Over"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T21:54:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bonk (BONK) price has been moving aggressively higher over the past week, despite a subdued tone to recent trade in the blue-chip cryptocurrency market, with BONK now up more than 130% from the lows it set earlier in the month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Immutable zkEVM Offering Up to $50 Million in Token Rewards to Ethereum Gamers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228155</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228155/immutable-zkevm-50-million-token-rewards-ethereum-gamers"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T21:51:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum users can earn IMX rewards for playing games, using exchanges, trading NFTs, and more on Immutable zkEVM.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Immutable zkEVM Offering Up to $50 Million in Token Rewards to Ethereum Gamers]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19437310/Immutable-zkEVM-Offering-Up-to-50-Million-in-Token-Rewards-to-Ethereum-Gamers</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19437310/Immutable-zkEVM-Offering-Up-to-50-Million-in-Token-Rewards-to-Ethereum-Gamers"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T21:51:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum users can earn IMX rewards for playing games, using exchanges, trading NFTs, and more on Immutable zkEVM.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Bitcoin Mining Stock Marathon Digital Is Moving Higher After Hours]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19437327/Why-Bitcoin-Mining-Stock-Marathon-Digital-Is-Moving-Higher-After-Hours</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19437327/Why-Bitcoin-Mining-Stock-Marathon-Digital-Is-Moving-Higher-After-Hours"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T21:45:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marathon Digital Holdings Inc (NASDAQ:MARA) shares are moving higher after the bell on Thursday after the Bitcoin (CRYPTO: BTC) miner announced an read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Franklin Templeton tokenizes $380 million US government money fund on Polygon, Stellar]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19437272/Franklin-Templeton-tokenizes-380-million-US-government-money-fund-on-Polygon-Stellar</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19437272/Franklin-Templeton-tokenizes-380-million-US-government-money-fund-on-Polygon-Stellar"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T21:36:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Franklin Templeton has tokenized a $380 million treasuries fund on the Polygon and Stellar blockchains to enable peer-to-peer (P2P) transfers without intermediaries. The company has launched the Franklin OnChain United States Government Money Fund (FOBXX), offering shares as BENJI tokens. Each...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP to Reach $4, Analysts Believe: Will It Overcome SEC First?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19437270/XRP-to-Reach-4-Analysts-Believe-Will-It-Overcome-SEC-First</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19437270/XRP-to-Reach-4-Analysts-Believe-Will-It-Overcome-SEC-First"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T21:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XRP price struggles despite analyst predictions for a surge, with the ongoing SEC lawsuit a potential turning point.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google's stock surged on reports of soaring profits]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19437264/Googles-stock-surged-on-reports-of-soaring-profits</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19437264/Googles-stock-surged-on-reports-of-soaring-profits"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T21:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google parent Alphabet reported a surge in profits of nearly 60% in the first quarter of this year versus the same period a prior year.Read more...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Giant Cryptocurrency Warning from the FBI – They Used a Very Strong Language]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19437255/Giant-Cryptocurrency-Warning-from-the-FBI-They-Used-a-Very-Strong-Language</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19437255/Giant-Cryptocurrency-Warning-from-the-FBI-They-Used-a-Very-Strong-Language"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T21:23:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) used very harsh language in its article regarding cryptocurrencies and their transfer. Continue Reading: Giant Cryptocurrency Warning from the FBI – They Used a Very Strong Language]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘No ETF Has Ever Done Anything Close’ — Analyst Highlights Record GBTC Outflows, Surpassing All ETFs]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7437741864</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/no-etf-has-ever-done-anything-close-analyst-highlights-record-gbtc-outflows-surpassing-all-etfs/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T21:19:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While Blackrock’s spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF), IBIT, experienced a continuous influx for 71 days before halting this week, Grayscale’s Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) holds the record with 72 consecutive days of outflows, surpassing all other ETFs on record. “No ETF has ever done anything close to that,” observed Eric Balchunas, Bloomberg’s senior ETF analyst, on […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Was CZ’s Biggest Mistake, According to Binance Co-Founder He Yi]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19437240/This-Was-CZs-Biggest-Mistake-According-to-Binance-Co-Founder-He-Yi</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19437240/This-Was-CZs-Biggest-Mistake-According-to-Binance-Co-Founder-He-Yi"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T21:16:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[He Yi, Binance co-founder and mother of CZ’s three children, pointed out his ignorance as a key mistake, considering the team's startup roots and legal constraints.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stripe Brings Back Crypto Payments Via USDC Stablecoin]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7437755739</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2024/04/25/stripe-brings-back-crypto-payments-via-usdc-stablecoin/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T21:09:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Six years after dropping support for bitcoin and, thus, crypto payments altogether, Stripe is bringing back the service later this summer, though initially only for Circle’s USDC stablecoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The BTC Halving's Grave Warning]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19437231/The-BTC-Halvings-Grave-Warning</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19437231/The-BTC-Halvings-Grave-Warning"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T21:07:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin likely can't keep on with business as usual.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Government Declares "Bitcoin Is Money"]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19437241/Government-Declares-Bitcoin-Is-Money</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19437241/Government-Declares-Bitcoin-Is-Money"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T21:06:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US Government stated that "Bitcoin is Money!" See why the latest attack against BTC is incredibly bullish! Is a $1,000,000 Bitcoin Price still in play? Strike CEO Jack Mallers thinks so! The Bitcoin Halving isn't priced in yet! Could the Supreme Court send BTC to $1 Billion? You don't want...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FBI Warns Americans Against Using Non-KYC Crypto Money Transmitting Services]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e743775eb39</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/markets/fbi-warns-americans-against-using-non-kyc-crypto-money-transmitting-services"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T21:05:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The FBI has issued a public service announcement today, warning Americans against using unregistered and non-Know Your Customer (KYC) cryptocurrency money transmitting services.

JUST IN: 🇺🇸 FBI warns Americans against using non-KYC #Bitcoin and crypto money transmitting services. pic.twitter.com/BkSuG6MiCE
— Bitcoin Magazine (@BitcoinMagazine) April 25, 2024
  
  
  
This announcement, identified as Alert Number I-042524-PSA, urged Americans to only engage with registered Money Services Businesses (MSBs) that comply with anti-money laundering (AML) regulations.
According to United States federal law, cryptocurrency money transmitting services must be registered as MSBs and adhere to AML requirements (31 U.S.C. § 5330; 31 CFR §§ 1010; 1022). The FBI says failure to comply may result in financial disruptions during law enforcement actions, particularly if funds are mixed with illegally obtained money.
The warning clarified that services that knowingly facilitate illegal transactions or violate federal laws are subject to investigation by law enforcement agencies, and that individuals using such services may lose access to their funds during enforcement operations.
Just yesterday, the US Department of Justice (DOJ) arrested the founders and CEO of popular privacy focused Bitcoin wallet and mixer, Samourai Wallet, and charged them with laundering “more than $100 million in criminal proceeds.” The DOJ then worked with law enforcement in Portugal and Iceland to arrest one of the founders, and seized Samourai's web servers and domain, in addition to serving a seizure warrant on the Google Play Store for its mobile app.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nik Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Apps Become Easier to Build With Subsquid and Neon EVM]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19437222/Solana-Apps-Become-Easier-to-Build-With-Subsquid-and-Neon-EVM</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19437222/Solana-Apps-Become-Easier-to-Build-With-Subsquid-and-Neon-EVM"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T21:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This strategic alliance between Subsquid and Neon EVM brings Ethereum's versatility and Solana's efficiency together, improving blockchain development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ready, Set, Grow: Why It Might Be Time To Invest In Altcoins Now – Santiment]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e743775ff14</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/why-time-to-invest-in-altcoins-now-santiment/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T21:04:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recent data from Santiment, a prominent market intelligence firm, indicate that the altcoins may enter a “prime buying” phase. According to Santiment, more than 85% of the altcoins they track are currently positioned in what is historically considered a “buying opportunity zone.”
 
Sentiment And Technical Indicators Favor Altcoins
 
This assessment is based on the Market Value to Realized Value (MVRV) ratio, which measures the profitability of held assets over one-month, three-month, and six-month periods. Such data suggest that despite recent market volatility, the potential for a significant bullish rally in the altcoin sector remains high.
 
 
 According to our model, the mid-term gains and losses by average wallets indicate heavy realized losses across most #altcoins. Over 85% of asset…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano Founder Charles Hoskinson Reiterates Core Purpose of Cryptocurrency – Here’s What You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19437230/Cardano-Founder-Charles-Hoskinson-Reiterates-Core-Purpose-of-Cryptocurrency-Heres-What-You-Need-to-Know</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19437230/Cardano-Founder-Charles-Hoskinson-Reiterates-Core-Purpose-of-Cryptocurrency-Heres-What-You-Need-to-Know"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T21:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a heartfelt article shared on X on April 25, Charles Hoskinson, the founder and CEO of Cardano Blockchain, reminded the cryptocurrency world of the real motivation and ideology of digital currencies. He made it clear that their application goes well beyond trade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Forms Death Cross & TD-9 Sell Signal: Brace For Impact?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19437218/Bitcoin-Forms-Death-Cross-TD-9-Sell-Signal-Brace-For-Impact</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19437218/Bitcoin-Forms-Death-Cross-TD-9-Sell-Signal-Brace-For-Impact"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T21:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An analyst has explained how Bitcoin is forming both a death cross and TD sell signal, which may lead to potential dips in these targets. Bitcoin Looking In Trouble As 12-Hour Chart Forms Two Bearish Signals In a new post on X, analyst Ali discussed two signals that have recently formed in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ready, Set, Grow: Why It Might Be Time To Invest In Altcoins Now – Santiment]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19437215/Ready-Set-Grow-Why-It-Might-Be-Time-To-Invest-In-Altcoins-Now-Santiment</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19437215/Ready-Set-Grow-Why-It-Might-Be-Time-To-Invest-In-Altcoins-Now-Santiment"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T21:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recent data from Santiment, a prominent market intelligence firm, indicate that the altcoins may enter a “prime buying” phase. According to Santiment, more than 85% of the altcoins they track are currently positioned in what is historically considered a “buying opportunity zone.” Sentiment And...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rabbit R1 Reviews Herald ‘Standout’ AI Assistant After Disastrous Humane Pin Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228146</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228146/rabbit-r1-ai-reviews-gadget-hardware"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T20:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Affordability, user-friendly design, and impressive capabilities help the latest AI gadget hop ahead of its scant competition.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘ETH Should Not Be Treated as a Security’ — Consensys Sues SEC Over Ethereum Regulations]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e743773e698</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/eth-should-not-be-treated-as-a-security-consensys-sues-sec-over-ethereum-regulations/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T20:18:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a significant legal move, Consensys has initiated a lawsuit against the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to protect the Ethereum blockchain from what it deems overreaching regulations. A report further alleges that the SEC issued a Wells Notice to Consensys, asserting that Metamask functions as an “unlicensed broker-dealer.” Consensys Confronts SEC Following Receipt […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Burn Rate Sees Massive 2,076% Spike In 24 Hours]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74377de288</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-burn-2076-spike/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T20:02:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an interesting turn of events, the Shiba Inu burn rate has received a massive boost in the last day. This is a welcome change to the slow momentum which the burn initiative had recorded over the last week, proving that the SHIB community is coming back to the table to burn more tokens.
 
Shiba Inu Burn Rate Picks Up
 
The Shiba Inu burn was an initiative that begun over a year ago as community members worked to reduce the supply of the meme coin. With a large supply of over 500 trillion, it has posed an hindrance to the coin’s growth, making a rally to $1 an impossible feat at this point. So, in an effort to increase its value, SHIB community members began sending tokens to a burn address.
 
 
Since the burn began, there have been steady burns carried out almost daily. Sometimes the bur…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Franklin Templeton Enables Peer-to-Peer Trades of Blockchain Fund]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228135</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228135/franklin-templeton-enables-peer-to-peer-trades-of-blockchain-fund"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T19:46:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Participants in the OnChain U.S. Government Money Fund can now swap shares directly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blackrock’s Bitcoin ETF Wallets Hold Over $20,000 in Runes Tokens, Arkham Data Shows]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74377adbc0</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/blackrocks-bitcoin-etf-wallets-hold-over-20000-in-runes-tokens-arkham-data-shows/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T19:25:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amid the excitement of Bitcoin’s new Runes protocol, Blackrock’s exchange-traded fund (ETF) wallets now contain over $20,000 worth of RSIC•GENESIS•RUNE tokens. Blackrock’s IBIT Benefits From Airdropped Runes Tokens On Thursday, Arkham, an onchain intelligence firm, revealed on social media platform X that two of Blackrock‘s IBIT bitcoin addresses possess tokens based on the Runes protocol. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consensys Sues SEC Over Attempts to Regulate Ethereum as a Security]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228134</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228134/consensys-sues-sec-attempts-regulate-ethereum-security"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T19:25:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum giant Consensys filed a preemptive suit against the SEC, revealing that it received a Wells Notice over MetaMask.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consensys Sues SEC Over ‘Unlawful Seizure Of Authority’ Over Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e743766dadc</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/04/25/consensys-sues-sec-over-unlawful-seizure-of-authority-over-ethereum/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T18:56:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum developer Consensys has filed a lawsuit against the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission, striking back against what the company calls an “unlawful seizure of authority” over Ethereum by the federal regulator.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cheyenne Ligon, Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Privacy Is Not a Crime’ — Samourai Indictment Provokes Strong Reactions From Crypto Advocates]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e743762012c</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/privacy-is-not-a-crime-samourai-indictment-provokes-strong-reactions-from-crypto-advocates/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T18:34:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Wednesday, the U.S. Department of Justice from the Southern District of New York brought charges against the creators of Samourai Wallet for running an unlicensed money transmission service and for engaging in money laundering activities. This development has left the cryptocurrency community in dismay, with many expressing their displeasure over the aggressive measures employed […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ohio Mulls Law to Protect Bitcoin Rights, Scrap Capital Gains Taxes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228124</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228124/ohio-mulls-law-to-protect-bitcoin-rights-scrap-capital-gains-taxes"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T18:33:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bill would also require state pension funds to consider investing in Bitcoin spot ETFs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Influencer ‘Jay Mazini’ Receives Seven-Year Jail Sentence And $10M Asset Seizure]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e743762a543</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-influencer-jay-mazini-7-year-jail-sentence/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T18:30:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a Brooklyn federal court, a crypto-influencer on social media sites such as Instagram, Jebara Igbara, also known as “Jay Mazini,” was sentenced to 84 months for wire fraud, wire fraud conspiracy, and money laundering. 
 
According to the United States Attorney’s Office for the Eastern District of New York, Igbara’s schemes resulted in substantial financial losses to unsuspecting investors, amounting to millions of dollars. 
 
Social Media Deception
 
According to the investigation, operating under the popular Instagram account name “Jay Mazini,” Igbara utilized his social media presence to portray a false image of wealth. 
 
Igbara posted videos in which he appeared to distribute large sums of cash to various individuals as gifts. However, it was revealed that behind this “facade,” Igba…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Dip as Inflation Figures Hamstring Rate Cut Hopes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228113</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228113/bitcoin-ethereum-gdp-fed-rate-cuts-inflation"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T18:17:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Fed’s preferred inflation gauge showed personal expenditures grew 3.7% in the first quarter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Franklin Templeton Upgrades $380M Tokenized Treasury Fund to Enable Peer-to-Peer Transfers]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74376c8f22</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2024/04/25/franklin-templeton-upgrades-380m-tokenized-treasury-fund-to-enable-peer-to-peer-transfers/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T18:16:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The feature helps to expand the utility of the Franklin OnChain U.S. Government Money Fund's BENJI token and make it more interconnected with the digital asset ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor, Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beck & Bulow Adopts Bitcoin as a Treasury Reserve Asset]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74376e325d</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/meat-and-seafood-company-beck-bulow-adopts-bitcoin-as-a-treasury-reserve-asset"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T18:05:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Beck & Bulow, a nationally acclaimed meat and seafood company based in Santa Fe, New Mexico, has announced its decision to accept Bitcoin as payment online and in-store, as well as include it in their employee 401k program. The company has also committed to holding Bitcoin and revenue generated in Bitcoin in its reserves indefinitely.
Founded in humble beginnings, working farmers markets and selling meat door-to-door, Beck & Bulow has grown to play a much bigger role in the meat supply chain in New Mexico. The company now serves over 1,000 restaurants and retailers across the United States, including luxury hotels and high-end markets, and has recently begun exporting bison to Mexico.
The decision to adopt Bitcoin aligned with Beck & Bulow's philosophy of financial sovereignty and food sov…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vivek Sen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Further Crackdown On Bitcoin Mixing Services Will Hurt Human Rights Activists]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74376e3251</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/legal/a-further-crackdown-on-bitcoin-mixing-services-will-hurt-human-rights-activists"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T18:05:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday, the US Department of Justice (DOJ) charged Keonne Rodriguez and William Lonergan Hill, co-founders of Samourai Wallet, a privacy-focused bitcoin wallet that also serves as a mixer, with money laundering and operating an unlicensed money transmitting business.
Many, including activists and human rights defenders, spoke out about the significance of this legal action soon after the news broke.

A monumentally bad day for privacy on the internet
The implications of this are so dire
A real “before and after” moment https://t.co/ou6CgT9E0T
— Alex Gladstein 🌋 ⚡ (@gladstein) April 24, 2024
  
  
  
Lyudmyla Kozlovska, President of the Open Dialogue Foundation, who educates policymakers and regulators about how bitcoin mixing services are tools for pro-democracy activists living under …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Frank Corva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[One of Only Four Bitcoin "Epic Sats" Just Auctioned Off For Over $2.1 Million]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74376e324f</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/markets/one-of-only-four-bitcoin-epic-sats-just-auctioned-off-for-over-2-1-million"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T18:05:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, Bitcoin mining pool ViaBTC auctioned off its “epic sat” for a sum of 33.3 BTC, equivalent to over $2.1 million. The auction, conducted on the CoinEx exchange platform, witnessed fervent bidding as collectors and enthusiasts competed for this satoshi.

JUST IN: The first satoshi of #Bitcoin's fourth halving block just auctioned off for 33.3 #BTC worth over $2.1 million 🤯 pic.twitter.com/Sw1tHxWVyR
— Bitcoin Magazine (@BitcoinMagazine) April 25, 2024
  
  
  
The term "epic sat" refers to the first satoshi (the smallest unit of Bitcoin) of each halving epoch. A halving epoch occurs approximately every four years, coinciding with a reduction in the block reward for Bitcoin miners. These "epic sats" are part of the Ordinals numbering system, which categorizes satoshis based on rarity a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nik Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CyberKongz Reveal Bitcoin Runes Airdrop Details, 'Mad Rush' Behind Etching]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228112</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228112/cyberkongz-reveal-bitcoin-runes-airdrop-details"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T17:51:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The "DECENTRALIZED" airdrop of Bitcoin Runes tokens is nearing. The CyberKongz team shared exclusive details with Decrypt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erika Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptopunk #635 Achieves $12.41M Sale, Joins Ranks of Top Priciest NFTs]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e743754c0fb</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/cryptopunk-635-achieves-12-41m-sale-joins-ranks-of-top-priciest-nfts/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T17:22:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Thursday, a Cryptopunk NFT with an alien theme changed hands for 4,000 ether, equivalent to $12.41 million. This particular Cryptopunk, #635, ranks as the sixth priciest in the Cryptopunks collection. Cryptopunks Collection Sees Another Major Sale With $12.41M Transaction In 2024, another significant transaction involving Cryptopunk #635 took place on Apr. 25, fetching 4,000 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI-Powered Discovery Network for NFTs Launches $PULSR Token]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e743757fed0</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ai-powered-discovery-network-for-nfts-launches-pulsr-token/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T17:02:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. GEORGE TOWN, CAYMAN ISLANDS — APRIL 25, 2024 Pulsr, an AI-powered search engine for NFTs, is launching a new token. The genesis of $PULSR is taking place on Thursday, April 25 at 11.30am EST — and will fuel the project’s ambition to make on-chain assets across the Web3 ecosystem more visible. Established in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BONK Sees Bullish Prospects As Community Votes Yes To Massive Burn]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7437505eef</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bonk-bullish-massive-burn/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T17:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BONK, a Solana meme token, recently went on a surge that saw it pushing weekly gains above 70% after community members voted in favor of a burn proposal. Recent market dynamics have seen the value of BONK, along with the majority of meme coins falling in April. BONK, in particular, witnessed a 70% plunge in trading volume earlier in the month, a direct consequence of the waning interest at the time.
 
However, the recent conclusion of the Bitcoin halving event has seen BONK surging in the past week. Interestingly, this surge was intensified after a recent announcement of BONK burns and a listing on Revolut.
 
BONK Rallies After Burn Votes
 
According to a social media post by the BONK Decentralized Autonomous Organization (DAO), members of the BONK communities voted in favor of burning 278…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kara Swisher Downplays Crypto's Significance: 'It's Not the Center of Everything']]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7437509a17</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/04/25/kara-swisher-says-crypto-will-change-a-little-corner-of-the-world/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T16:59:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The author of "Burn Book" says while crypto is important, it's not the center of everything.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meme Coins Are Causing 'Damage' to Crypto, Says Andreessen Horowitz Exec]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228099</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228099/meme-coins-causing-damage-crypto-andreessen-horowitz-exec"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T16:58:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CTO of VC firm Andreessen Horowitz, Eddy Lazzarin, argued that meme coins are "undermining the long-term vision of crypto."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin 'Epic Sat' From the Halving Sells for $2.1 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228084</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228084/bitcoin-epic-sat-halving-sells-over-2-1-million"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T16:13:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first satoshi mined on Bitcoin after the halving, one of just four "epic sats" to date, fetched 33.3 BTC at auction. Here's why.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CryptoPunk Sells for $12.4 Million in Ethereum—One of the Biggest NFT Sales Ever]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228076</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228076/cryptopunk-sells-12-4-million-ethereum-one-biggest-nft-sales"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T15:56:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CryptoPunks NFT was the third ultra-rare Alien Punk to sell for over $10 million worth of Ethereum in the last two months alone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Gaming Tokens Battered as Bitcoin Price Sinks to $63,000]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228073</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228073/ethereum-gaming-tokens-battered-bitcoin-price-sinks"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T15:34:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some of the biggest Ethereum tokens tied to gaming projects, such as Immutable and Parallel, have plunged over the past 24 hours.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kokodi’s New NFT Collection 'The Masks' Is Set for Mint on Xterio Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228057</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228057/kokodis-new-nft-collection-the-masks-is-set-for-mint-on-xterio-games"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T13:51:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kokodi Inc, a modern video game company, is the mastermind behind the Mask NFT Mint. It’s the project’s second collection for an upcoming extraction shooter game built by the developer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>gamingwire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Started With Bitcoin Runes: A Guide to Etching, Minting and Trading]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=227968</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/how-get-started-bitcoin-runes-guide-etching-minting-trading"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Runes tokens are taking over the network, but they can be tricky to handle. Here's a guide on how to get started with Runes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erika Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Buy Bitcoin’ Notepad Held Behind Janet Yellen Sells for $1M]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228037</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228037/buy-bitcoin-notepad-held-behind-janet-yellen-sells-for-1m"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T12:08:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The iconic sign was held before cameras during a televised House Financial Services Committee hearing in 2017.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Slips Below $64,000 as $209 Million in Crypto Longs Liquidated]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228029</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228029/bitcoin-price-slips-below-64000-as-209-million-in-crypto-longs-liquidated"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T11:17:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The market slump saw over $209 million in crypto long positions liquidated, with over $52 million in Bitcoin longs liquidated.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETFs See $120 Million Outflows, BlackRock's IBIT Ends 71-Day Inflow Streak]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228027</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228027/bitcoin-etfs-see-120-million-outflows-blackrocks-ibit-ends-71-day-inflow-streak"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T10:45:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock's iShares Bitcoin Trust saw zero inflows yesterday, after scraping into the top 10 ETFs with the longest daily inflow streaks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Runes Transactions Are Taking Over the Network—And Dominating BRC-20]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228012</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228012/bitcoin-runes-transactions-dominate-btc-network-brc-20-dog"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T23:30:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The popular DOG collection helped Runes claim 81% of all transactions on the Bitcoin network Tuesday, Dune reports.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Ultra Light AI Model Fits on Your Phone and Can Beat ChatGPT]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=227974</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/227974/microsoft-phi-3-mini-small-ai-language-model"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T22:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft's latest “small language model” is well-suited to specific needs, offering cost-effective performance in a compact package.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Wallets Holding At Least $1K Are Growing in 'Positive Trend': Fidelity]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=227971</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/227971/bitcoin-wallets-with-over-1000-growing-fidelity"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T21:36:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The amount of Bitcoin held on exchanges, meanwhile, fell 30% in the first quarter to 2.3 million BTC]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's Next for Notcoin? Becoming the 'Netflix of Social, Viral Games']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=227970</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/227970/notcoin-next-move-netflix-social-viral-games-interview"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T21:06:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The team behind viral Telegram-based game Notcoin is racing to create a sustainable ecosystem of similar, interconnected experiences from third-party developers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interview: Hot 'Notcoin' Will Evolve After the NOT Token Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PprnGP14/interview-hot-notcoin-will-evolve-after-the-not-token-launch</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PprnGP14/interview-hot-notcoin-will-evolve-after-the-not-token-launch"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Open Builders founder Sasha Plotvinov speaks with Decrypt's Sander Lutz at Token 2049 Dubai about how he envisions Notcoin's expansion and evolution after the token drop—into something akin to the "Netflix of social, viral games."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Meme Coin DOG Hits $336 Million Market Cap After Runes Airdrop]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=227953</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/227953/bitcoin-meme-coin-dog-336-million-market-cap-runes-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T20:17:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DOG•GO•TO•THE•MOON (aka DOG) was airdropped to Ordinals holders Wednesday, immediately becoming the most widely-held Bitcoin Runes token.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feds Arrest Founders of Bitcoin Mixer Samourai Wallet]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=227949</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/227949/feds-arrest-founders-bitcoin-mixer-samourai-wallet"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T19:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The DOJ has “once again criminalized the developers of an app that restores financial privacy,” protested Edward Snowden.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF Hype Cooling, But BTC Will Still Hit $150,000: Standard Chartered]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=227946</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/227946/bitcoin-price-prediction-150000-in-2024-standard-chartered"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T19:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The leading UK-based bank says it is still bullish on Bitcoin, holding firm on its bold price prediction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s Inflation Rate Is Now Lower Than Gold: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=227940</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/227940/bitcoins-inflation-rate-is-now-lower-than-gold-report"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T17:46:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meanwhile, analysts say the latest halving is symbolically significant but unlikely to have a noticeable price impact.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jack Dorsey's Square Will Convert Shops' Revenue to Bitcoin via Cash App]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=227903</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/227903/jack-dorseys-square-will-convert-shops-revenue-to-bitcoin-via-cash-app"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T17:26:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jack Dorsey's Square platform is allowing businesses to automatically convert a portion of their sales into Bitcoin with a new feature.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Play-to-Earn 'Puffverse' Migrating to Ethereum Gaming Network Ronin From BNB Chain]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=227910</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/227910/puffverse-migrating-ethereum-gaming-network-ronin-bnb-chain"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T17:08:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Puffverse has raised $3 million in a round led by Animoca Brands, with plans to shift to Ronin and launch a party game, token, and new NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Dog Coins Have Their Day as BONK and WIF Post Big Price Gains]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=227911</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/227911/solana-dog-coins-bonk-wif-big-gains"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T16:52:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Major Solana meme coins BONK and WIF are on fire, posting considerable jumps in the last 24 hours despite the broader market correction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terra Founder Do Kwon Files Extradition Appeal, Calls Out 'Bizarre' Legal Readings From Court]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=227906</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/227906/terra-founder-do-kwon-files-extradition-appeal-bizarre-legal-readings-court"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T16:39:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Labs co-founder Do Kwon filed a fresh appeal in his Montenegrin legal saga, accusing a court of "bizarre" legal interpretations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Card Game 'The Lost Glitches' Coming to Layer-3 Network Xai]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=227888</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/227888/ethereum-card-game-lost-glitches-layer-3-network-xai"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T16:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Xai Foundation is teaming up with and investing with Ethereum NFT card battler The Lost Glitches to bring it to the Arbitrum-based network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hedera Jumps 113% Amid BlackRock Confusion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=227877</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/227877/hedera-jumps-113-amid-blackrock-confusion"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T15:02:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HBAR skyrocketed after an announcement that name-dropped BlackRock, but the price is now falling as the investment giant says it's not directly involved.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Magic Runes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IGWg0R64/magic-runes</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IGWg0R64/magic-runes"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T13:59:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC stables at $66k, liquidations in narrow range. BTC funding again turns negative in bullish sign. ETFs net inflow after Grayscale moves to lower fees. BTC demand 5x vs supply post-halving: Bitfinex. SOL congestion issue now largely solved. Two SEC lawyers resign after ‘gross abuse of power’. Ripple fights to lower $2bn SEC fine. SAFE trades at $2.8bn FDV after OKX lists. MANEKI hits $150m on first day, China memes pump. Memecoins are ‘black hole you can’t ignore’. DeGods up 20%, may switch back to SOL. Magic Eden launches Runes platform ahead of time.  Louis Vuitton gifts Pharrell jacket to NFT holders. Melania Trump launches necklace with SOL NFTs. Hoodie Punk trades for $620K.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Luxury Watches, Designer Shoes Will Soon Trade Like NFTs: Arianee CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/CSNQG2md/luxury-watches-designer-shoes-will-soon-trade-like-nfts-arianee-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/CSNQG2md/luxury-watches-designer-shoes-will-soon-trade-like-nfts-arianee-ceo"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arianee CEO Pierre-Nicolas Hurstel sat down with Rug Radio founder Farokh and Decrypt’s Sander Lutz at NFT Paris to discuss everything from the future of on-chain luxury to the secret hack to finding the best restaurants in France.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notcoin's Co-Creator Explains the Game's Token Delay—And When to Expect NOT Now]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/7Zx33xo5/notcoins-co-creator-explains-the-games-token-delayand-when-to-expect-not-now</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/7Zx33xo5/notcoins-co-creator-explains-the-games-token-delayand-when-to-expect-not-now"/>
        <updated>2024-04-22T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Notcoin co-creator Sasha Plotvinov spoke with Decrypt's Sander Lutz at Token 2049 Dubai to discuss why the NOT token launch was pushed back from the original 4/20 target, when to expect the listing, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TON’s Justin Hyun Breaks Down The Importance of USDT Coming to Telegram]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ODQI6ACA/tons-justin-hyun-breaks-down-the-importance-of-usdt-coming-to-telegram</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ODQI6ACA/tons-justin-hyun-breaks-down-the-importance-of-usdt-coming-to-telegram"/>
        <updated>2024-04-19T10:14:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Token 2049 in Dubai, The Open Network’s director of investments sat down with Decrypt’s Sander Lutz to discuss what he sees as the game-changing integration of USDT onto TON, and his plans for getting Telegram’s 900 million users to start using crypto in the immediate future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Influencer Ansem Explains His Meme Coin Thesis and Why He’s Bullish on Bitcoin Runes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/u9DHFoK0/crypto-influencer-ansem-explains-his-meme-coin-thesis-and-why-hes-bullish-on-bitcoin-runes</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/u9DHFoK0/crypto-influencer-ansem-explains-his-meme-coin-thesis-and-why-hes-bullish-on-bitcoin-runes"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T21:56:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ansem, the crypto trader who's amassed a sizable following on the back of meme coin Dogwifhat (WIF) and other calls, chats with Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz at Token 2049 Dubai about his meme coin thesis, why he's bullish on Bitcoin Runes, and what he sees ahead for the crypto markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Sander Lutz Braves the Dubai Floods for a Crypto Conference]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/mtjVHGa3/decrypts-sander-lutz-braves-the-dubai-floods-for-a-crypto-conference</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/mtjVHGa3/decrypts-sander-lutz-braves-the-dubai-floods-for-a-crypto-conference"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T21:33:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz reports from Dubai amid a historic storm that flooded the famed city, trudging through the streets to complete his essential task: Attending the Token 2049 crypto conference.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gold Beats Its All Time High]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/6ULgUKVk/gold-beats-its-all-time-high</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/6ULgUKVk/gold-beats-its-all-time-high"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T09:53:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) maintains its trend of reaching higher lows amidst choppy market conditions. Exchange-traded funds (ETFs) witness another influx of $125 million. There's anticipation of Hong Kong approving ETFs for both Bitcoin and Ethereum (ETH) come Monday. Notable institutional investor BlackRock shows interest in Bitcoin. Recent filings reveal increased Bitcoin purchases by banks. A Bitcoin-friendly political party secures victory in the South Korean election. Analyst Kang predicts Bitcoin could surge to $80-100k by May. Meanwhile, Ethereum sees accumulation by stablecoin whales on the rise. A new Ethereum Improvement Proposal (EIP) aims to streamline signing requests. Solana (SOL) experiences a resurgence in activity, reaching yearly highs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NASA’s Next Deep Space Mission Won’t Use Artificial Intelligence]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/0WGP33Rp/nasas-next-deep-space-mission-wont-use-artificial-intelligence</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/0WGP33Rp/nasas-next-deep-space-mission-wont-use-artificial-intelligence"/>
        <updated>2024-04-13T18:42:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Thursday, Decrypt Media visited NASA's Jet Propulsion Laboratory in Pasadena, CA to meet with the Engineering team behind the Europa Clipper before its launch to Jupiter's Europa moon in October.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Do A Little with Weesh]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LnaOT9bF/we-do-a-little-with-weesh</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LnaOT9bF/we-do-a-little-with-weesh"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T07:46:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week’s episode, we did a little something different. We took the man who is usually behind the camera and put him in front of it. We sat down with our producer Weesh to dive into how in fell in love with art and became a collector, how he met Andy and fun childhood memories together, his biggest wins in crypto, and so much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside VanEck’s Crypto Takeover of the New York Stock Exchange]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9YAY4wGD/inside-vanecks-crypto-takeover-of-the-new-york-stock-exchange</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9YAY4wGD/inside-vanecks-crypto-takeover-of-the-new-york-stock-exchange"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T14:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worlds collide as Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz heads to the floor of the NYSE to witness a special closing bell ceremony hosted by VanEck in honor of Web3. Featuring Choose Rich Nick, VanEck Head of Web3 Matt Bartlett, and more!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wormhole Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9SNiIVfU/wormhole-wednesday</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9SNiIVfU/wormhole-wednesday"/>
        <updated>2024-04-07T17:42:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC hits $64.5K then rebounds, SOL outperforms. Government sends $2B BTC to Coinbase to sell. Funding rates stay low after sweep lower. ETFs see small inflow, Ark outflow more than GBTC. Wormhole W launches at $15B FDV. BTC ‘inflection point’ if it follows rates or gold. Gold & BTC very correlated for the last year. Expect slower ETF volume this month: Bloomberg. BTC 2x and 3x levered ETFs launch yesterday. BTC ETFs now half the size of gold.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Dogs, Now Cats]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/2KrbCFNp/first-dogs-now-cats</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/2KrbCFNp/first-dogs-now-cats"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T14:06:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC falls another 6% amid $400m liquidations. ETF outflows and dollar strength blamed for move. Funding completely reset to lows in move. BTC lower high leaves market in ‘no trade zone’. This cycle acting ‘nothing like previous cycle’. ETH unlikely to be classed a security: Coinbase CFO. Crypto VC funding up 53% in MarchAnsem’s cat coin sees more volume than NFT market. Most memecoins down 10-20% given move in majors. MEW up 10% after HTX lists, airdrop to Saga phones. MEME to launch memecoin chain, NFTs rise. Pixelmon releases trailer for Anime series.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Do A Little With Spencer Gordon-Sand]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/jSsgl6SQ/we-do-a-little-with-spencer-gordon-sand</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/jSsgl6SQ/we-do-a-little-with-spencer-gordon-sand"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T17:11:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week’s episode, we sit down with Spencer Gordon Sand, the mastermind behind Spencer Ventures. Before launching Spencer Ventures, Spencer was a competitive fencer, Magic the gathering player, and startup enjoyooor. 

We dive into Spencer’s investment thesis behind NFTs and how his fund invests, finding and buying distressed assets in a bear market , point farming optimization, a peak behind the 3AC liquidation and dickbutt buys, and so much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Get Your Foot In Ihe Door And Building During Bear Markets]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/d8FYP5tO/how-to-get-your-foot-in-ihe-door-and-building-during-bear-markets</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/d8FYP5tO/how-to-get-your-foot-in-ihe-door-and-building-during-bear-markets"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T11:37:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week’s episode, we sit down with Intern and Tunez from the Monad team. Prior to Monad, Tunez was working with Delphi Digital and Intern was working at CMS Holdings. They’re two of my oldest friends from crypto twitter.

We get into why they joined the Monad team, alpha for finding jobs in the space, biggest lessons from previous cycles, and so much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SBF Sentencing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZmRslhIl/sbf-sentencing</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZmRslhIl/sbf-sentencing"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T11:29:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC: 70.7k (+1%), ETH: 3585 (0%), SOL: 186 (-1%). Top 100 gainers: DOGE, GT, BCH, RBN. Crypto mixed, BTC-beta & memes outperform. SEC case vs Coinbase set to go to trial. DeFi win as case dismissed vs Coinbase wallet. ETFs see $244m inflows led by Ark. BlackRock ETF fastest growing in history: Fink. ETH ETF possible even if its a security: Fink. ETH spot ETF by May chances only 20%: GSR. SBF sentencing today, faces 50 years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The $63 Million Exploit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/l2sy2ZQY/the-63-million-exploit</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/l2sy2ZQY/the-63-million-exploit"/>
        <updated>2024-03-28T16:42:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC consolidates around $70k, funding still low. ETFs see $418m inflow as GBTC outflow tiny. BTC set to have record 7th-straight green month. AI coins soar, FET hits ATH amid merger rumour. FET, OCEAN, AGIX token proposed at $7.5bn FDV. DoJ charges KuCoin over money laundering. KuCoin sees $800m outflows after charges. CFTC names ETH & LTC commodities in charges. HK set to allow ‘in-kind’ style ETFs. HSBC launches tokenised gold fund. Fidelity files S1 form for ETH ETF. Short sellers bet $11bn crypto rally won’t last. More customer USDC balances to be stored on Base.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BTC Is Back On Top]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/1t8j4uWb/btc-is-back-on-top</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/1t8j4uWb/btc-is-back-on-top"/>
        <updated>2024-03-28T16:16:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC breaks $70K as $175M of shorts liquidated. ETFs see net inflow despite high GBTC outflows. Gold miner set to buy $1.7B BTC. UK to list crypto ETNs in May. ETH ETF may still be approved: Grayscale. Grayscale ETH discount falls to 22%. ETH ETF has no positive signs: Bloomberg. Coinbase pumps 10%, Ark continue to sell shares. Coinbase Int. record trading volumes in March. FTX to sell majority of Anthropic stake for $884M. Trader makes $20m profit in MEW rally. Puppets hit ATH, lead move higher in Ordinals. Azuki flips MAYC market cap in bounce. Magic Eden makes $15m in 30d trading revenue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Base On Top]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OGLEeanX/base-on-top</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OGLEeanX/base-on-top"/>
        <updated>2024-03-28T15:05:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Majors continue to rally as ETF sentiment improves. Genesis have likely sold half their GBTC position. BlackRock could flip GBTC holdings in 3 weeks. BTC short squeeze would liquidate $6.6bn by $75k. Lack of on-chain activity indicates ‘limited selling’. BTC crucial to the financial system: BlackRock. Resurging interest in crypto assets: Goldman Sachs. Crypto summer has started: Raoul Pal. Base outpaces SOL & ETH for trading volumes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>