<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-08-13T11:10:39.740Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-08-13T11:10:39.740Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shibarium Release Countdown: Top Exchange Teases Shiba Inu Tokens Listing]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18834424/Shibarium-Release-Countdown-Top-Exchange-Teases-Shiba-Inu-Tokens-Listing</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18834424/Shibarium-Release-Countdown-Top-Exchange-Teases-Shiba-Inu-Tokens-Listing"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T10:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Major exchange KuCoin teases Shiba Inu tokens listing as Shibarium set to launch]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2 technical reasons to buy Bitcoin (or sell the US dollar)]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18834406/2-technical-reasons-to-buy-Bitcoin-or-sell-the-US-dollar</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18834406/2-technical-reasons-to-buy-Bitcoin-or-sell-the-US-dollar"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T10:36:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RSI stays above 50 in 2023 The weekly chart points out an ascending triangle pattern $45k is the next target, providing the Bitcoin price holds above $25k Bitcoin bulls must be frustrated by the slow price action in the last few months. After all, ever since it met resistance at the $30k level,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptosphere: Your Place of Knowledge]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18834419/Cryptosphere-Your-Place-of-Knowledge</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18834419/Cryptosphere-Your-Place-of-Knowledge"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On September 2, 2023, an event dedicated to digital assets will take place in Wrocław, where you will learn how and whether it is worth investing in modern technologies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korea Hackers Continue to Target Crypto Platforms: UN Report]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755c561106</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/north-korea-hackers-continue-to-target-crypto-platforms-un-report/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T09:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers working for North Korea have continued to attack companies in the crypto space this year, according to independent sanctions monitors. Their findings, which reveal that Pyongyang proceeds with the development of its nuclear and weapons programs, will be included in a U.N. report which is to be released in the coming weeks. 
 
North Korea Still Trying to Steal Cryptocurrency, Sanctions Experts Say
 
North Korea continued to produce nuclear fissile material and develop nuclear weapons in 2023, a new report prepared for a U.N. Security Council committee unveils. The document, which is yet to be officially published, has been seen by Reuters.
 
Its authors, independent sanctions monitors who report to the U.N. twice a year, have also established that the Democratic People’s Republic of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lubomir Tassev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Non-Zero Addresses Have Reached An All-Time High]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18834364/Bitcoin-BTC-Non-Zero-Addresses-Have-Reached-An-All-Time-High</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18834364/Bitcoin-BTC-Non-Zero-Addresses-Have-Reached-An-All-Time-High"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T09:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The market analytics platform, Glassnode Alerts, shared on Twitter earlier today that various on-chain metrics for the cryptocurrency market leader, Bitcoin (BTC), have reached new all-time highs (ATH). According to the post, BTC’s number of non-zero addresses has reached a new ATH for...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Honeypot Scam Alert: Token that Linked Itself to SHIB Ecosystem Went Zero]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18834358/Honeypot-Scam-Alert-Token-that-Linked-Itself-to-SHIB-Ecosystem-Went-Zero</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18834358/Honeypot-Scam-Alert-Token-that-Linked-Itself-to-SHIB-Ecosystem-Went-Zero"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T09:19:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The token, which was created by its developer to be associated with the SHIB ecosystem, turned out to be a fraud. Continue Reading: Honeypot Scam Alert: Token that Linked Itself to SHIB Ecosystem Went Zero]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PayPal Executive Says PYUSD Will Be Made Available for DeFi in the Future]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18834356/PayPal-Executive-Says-PYUSD-Will-Be-Made-Available-for-DeFi-in-the-Future</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18834356/PayPal-Executive-Says-PYUSD-Will-Be-Made-Available-for-DeFi-in-the-Future"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T09:15:16.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Steadefi Hacker Sent 100 ETH Worth $185K into TornadoCash]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18834340/Steadefi-Hacker-Sent-100-ETH-Worth-185K-into-TornadoCash</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18834340/Steadefi-Hacker-Sent-100-ETH-Worth-185K-into-TornadoCash"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T08:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uniswap employee fired after memecoin liquidity pull: ‘Not behavior we support or condone’]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18834327/Uniswap-employee-fired-after-memecoin-liquidity-pull-Not-behavior-we-support-or-condone</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18834327/Uniswap-employee-fired-after-memecoin-liquidity-pull-Not-behavior-we-support-or-condone"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T08:30:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Uniswap founder Hayden Adams shared that the team removed an employee after what some call a rug pull of memecoin FrensTech.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Assessing Hedera post Calaxy’s launch – Here’s what you should know]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18834332/Assessing-Hedera-post-Calaxys-launch-Heres-what-you-should-know</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18834332/Assessing-Hedera-post-Calaxys-launch-Heres-what-you-should-know"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T08:30:37.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AltSignals price forecast 2023: How attractive is $ASI in the presale?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18834326/AltSignals-price-forecast-2023-How-attractive-is-ASI-in-the-presale</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18834326/AltSignals-price-forecast-2023-How-attractive-is-ASI-in-the-presale"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T08:29:38.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chamber of Digital Commerce Joins Coinbase in Legal Battle Against SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18834320/Chamber-of-Digital-Commerce-Joins-Coinbase-in-Legal-Battle-Against-SEC</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18834320/Chamber-of-Digital-Commerce-Joins-Coinbase-in-Legal-Battle-Against-SEC"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T08:12:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leading blockchain trade association Chamber of Digital Commerce (CDC) recently made a significant move in the ongoing legal battle between the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and Coinbase. The association took to X on Friday to announce that it has filed an amicus curiae brief in the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Voyager’s token transfer to Coinbase sparks sell-off suspicions]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18834312/Voyagers-token-transfer-to-Coinbase-sparks-sell-off-suspicions</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18834312/Voyagers-token-transfer-to-Coinbase-sparks-sell-off-suspicions"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T08:04:37.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Japan to Use KYC Services From Liquid]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755c5f467a</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/binance-japan-to-use-kyc-services-from-liquid/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T07:39:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The world’s leading cryptocurrency exchange, Binance, has selected Liquid as an identity verification partner for its Japanese platform. The services of the Tokyo-headquartered biometrics firm will allow Binance Japan to ensure its know-your-customer (KYC) procedures comply with Japan’s strict regulations.
 
Liquid to Provide Binance Japan With AI-Based KYC Solution
 
Binance, the largest crypto exchange in terms of trading volume and users, will employ Japanese company Liquid for identity verification of customers on its new domestic platform in Japan. As a first step in this partnership, Liquid said it will provide Binance with its eKYC service.
 
“Liquid eKYC offers top-in-class facial authentication through its unique AI-based image processing capability, enabling smooth identity verif…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lubomir Tassev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uniswap Fires Developer Accused of Siphoning $25k in Memecoin Rugpull]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18834293/Uniswap-Fires-Developer-Accused-of-Siphoning-25k-in-Memecoin-Rugpull</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18834293/Uniswap-Fires-Developer-Accused-of-Siphoning-25k-in-Memecoin-Rugpull"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T07:32:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A prominent employee of Uniswap, the most popular decentralized exchange, has come under damning allegations of a crypto scam. In a recent tweet, pseudonymous UniswapVillain notified the crypto community that AzFlin, a Uniswap developer, rugged a meme coin project a few hours after creating it....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC Aims at Defining All Crypto Under Securities Law: Lawyer]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18834283/The-SEC-Aims-at-Defining-All-Crypto-Under-Securities-Law-Lawyer</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18834283/The-SEC-Aims-at-Defining-All-Crypto-Under-Securities-Law-Lawyer"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T07:18:08.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin a Ticking Time Bomb Set for ‘Historic Expansion’ As Rare Indicator Sends Signal: Crypto Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18834278/Bitcoin-a-Ticking-Time-Bomb-Set-for-Historic-Expansion-As-Rare-Indicator-Sends-Signal-Crypto-Analyst</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18834278/Bitcoin-a-Ticking-Time-Bomb-Set-for-Historic-Expansion-As-Rare-Indicator-Sends-Signal-Crypto-Analyst"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T07:04:28.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Legal scholars file amicus brief in support of Coinbase]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18834269/Legal-scholars-file-amicus-brief-in-support-of-Coinbase</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18834269/Legal-scholars-file-amicus-brief-in-support-of-Coinbase"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T06:57:27.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SIMPLY SESSION  BTC HUGE News! FED Oversight, Rogan's Stance, Bitfinex Justice & $100K Bet!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18834266/SIMPLY-SESSION-BTC-HUGE-News-FED-Oversight-Rogans-Stance-Bitfinex-Justice-100K-Bet</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18834266/SIMPLY-SESSION-BTC-HUGE-News-FED-Oversight-Rogans-Stance-Bitfinex-Justice-100K-Bet"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T06:36:15.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin bought by corporate giants should not be feared — Michael Saylor]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18834256/Bitcoin-bought-by-corporate-giants-should-not-be-feared-Michael-Saylor</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18834256/Bitcoin-bought-by-corporate-giants-should-not-be-feared-Michael-Saylor"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T06:13:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During a recent podcast interview, Michael Saylor explained that Bitcoin being bought and custodied by corporations should not be feared, outlining three main reasons driving the need for custodians.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Graph: interview with the crypto project to talk about Dapps and DeFi]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18834264/The-Graph-interview-with-the-crypto-project-to-talk-about-Dapps-and-DeFi</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18834264/The-Graph-interview-with-the-crypto-project-to-talk-about-Dapps-and-DeFi"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[STEPN: interview with the NFT company that pays you to walk]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18834263/STEPN-interview-with-the-NFT-company-that-pays-you-to-walk</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18834263/STEPN-interview-with-the-NFT-company-that-pays-you-to-walk"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During ETHCC, an important event for the Ethereum community that was held in Paris in July 2023, The Cryptonomist interviewed Shiti Rastogi Manghani]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zimbabwe Central Bank Says Gold-Backed Tokens Set to Be Used for ‘Transactional Purposes’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755c47b0ad</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/zimbabwe-central-bank-says-gold-backed-tokens-set-to-be-used-for-transactional-purposes/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T05:37:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Zimbabwean central bank recently said it is close to rolling out gold-backed digital tokens “for transactional purposes.” According to the bank’s governor, the gold-backed digital tokens have already proven to be an effective monetary policy instrument. Central bank governor John Mangudya also said the results of a consumer survey had shown that residents had limited knowledge about an envisaged central bank digital currency (CBDC).
 
An ‘Effective Monetary Policy Instrument’
 
The Reserve Bank of Zimbabwe (RBZ) has said it is now “at an advanced stage in preparations for the rolling out of GBDT [gold-backed digital tokens] for transactional purposes.” The bank said the rollout would see the gold tokens complement the U.S. dollar “in domestic transactions as retailers will be offered a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[French Regulator Revises Crypto Rules to Align With EU’s MiCA Law]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755c4f463f</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/french-regulator-revises-crypto-rules-to-align-with-eus-mica-law/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T03:34:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[France’s financial market regulator said it’s adjusting the rules for crypto companies in line with Europe’s new regulatory framework. The changes, which will enter into force next year, seek to enhance registration requirements for businesses offering certain services for digital assets like custody and trading. 
 
AMF Revamps Crypto Regulations to Enforce Stricter Registration Rules for DASPs
 
Autorité des Marchés Financiers (AMF), the French financial regulator, announced Thursday it’s amending its regulations and policies regarding digital asset service providers (DASPs) to implement “enhanced” registration for some of these entities.
 
The new requirements for crypto companies were introduced with a law known by the French abbreviation DDADUE, allowing the government in Paris to tran…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lubomir Tassev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former SEC Official Warns ‘Crypto Regulatory Onslaught Will Never End’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755c363361</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/former-sec-official-warns-crypto-regulatory-onslaught-will-never-end/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T01:34:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission’s former head of internet enforcement has warned that “crypto regulatory onslaught will never end.” He claimed that cryptocurrency trading platforms, like Binance and Coinbase, are simply playing “a short game of regulatory arbitrage, all carried out in an effort to make as much fiat as possible before their inevitable demise.”
 
Former SEC Official’s Warning of Ongoing Crypto Regulatory Sweep
 
Former U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) official John Reed Stark warned in a lengthy tweet on Saturday that “the SEC’s crypto-regulatory onslaught will never end (ever).” Stark is currently president of cybersecurity firm John Reed Stark Consulting. He founded and served as chief of the SEC Office of Internet Enforcement for 11 years. He was …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Schiff Warns Investors of 2 ‘Huge Surprises’ — Foresees Inflation Too High for Fed Rate Cuts to Stimulate Economy]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755c3cbbc7</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/peter-schiff-warns-investors-of-2-huge-surprises-foresees-inflation-too-high-for-fed-rate-cuts-to-stimulate-economy/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-12T23:36:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Economist Peter Schiff says investors are in for “two huge surprises.” Noting that the Federal Reserve has already lost its fight against inflation, he explained that by the time the U.S. economy officially enters a recession, inflation will be too high for the Fed to “stimulate” with interest rate cuts.
 
Peter Schiff Sounds Alarm on U.S. Economy
 
Economist and gold bug Peter Schiff issued multiple warnings about the U.S. economy in a series of tweets this week. He wrote on Wednesday:
 

Investors are in for two huge surprises. The first is that future inflation rates will be much higher than they think. The second is that the Fed won’t be willing or able to do what it takes to fight it.
 
Following the U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics report, released Thursday, that the consumer price in…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bankrupt Celsius Network Reveals Plan To Shut Down App, Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755c3f3ddf</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/celsius-to-shut-down-app/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-12T22:53:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Celsius launched back in 2017, many saw the company as one that had the potential to disrupt the industry with its crypto lending platform. Six years on, Celsius’ chapter in the crypto world seems to be ending, as recent developments will suggest.
 
App To Shut Down In 90 Days
 
The Celsius app will shut down within 90 days, according to the company’s revised disclosure statement in its ongoing bankruptcy proceedings. This comes as the company prepares for a new chapter that will see the company operate under a new entity, “NewCo,” which will be managed by Fahrenheit Group and owned by Celsius’ creditors.
 
 
As revealed in the statement, Celsius chose 90 days based on past experiences in enabling crypto withdrawals from the app “for custody and withhold account holders pursuant to th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unidentified Miners, F2pool Lead All-Time Bitcoin Mining Rankings: A Comprehensive Review of Bitcoin’s Historic Block Discovery]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755c3be519</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/unidentified-miners-f2pool-lead-all-time-bitcoin-mining-rankings-a-comprehensive-review-of-bitcoins-historic-block-discovery/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-12T21:35:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since the inception of the Bitcoin blockchain by Satoshi Nakamoto, the network has diligently processed in excess of 800,000 blocks. An examination of data from 99 distinct mining pools, spanning the previous 14 years, reveals that unidentified mining participants discovered 28.37% of the network’s total blocks. Trailing not far behind, F2pool secures the second position, having found just slightly more than 10% of all the blocks since 2009.
 
Unknown, F2pool, and Antpool Lead the Pack in Terms of Number of Bitcoin Blocks Mined
 
Over the last year, Foundry USA has emerged as the prevailing bitcoin (BTC) mining pool, uncovering 15,767 blocks from a total of 53,703 block rewards since August 12, 2022. Although Foundry has consistently led among large mining pools in recent periods, it ranks…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[California Says Political Campaigns Can Accept Crypto, But There’s A Caveat]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755c2292e3</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/california-political-campaigns-can-accept-crypto/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-12T19:53:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the world continues to adapt to the growing rise and mass adoption of crypto, governments and regulators worldwide are moving to create updated frameworks that govern and regulate the use and impact of digital currencies in certain sectors. Likewise, the California Fair Political Practices Commission (FPPC) is the latest to make such a move.
 
Crypto In Politics
 
The FPPC recognizes cryptocurrencies’ role in the political sphere, especially regarding campaign donations. So as part of its agenda for its August meeting, the agency will discuss the updated campaign disclosure manuals, which now include cryptocurrency contributions.
 
 
In a move reiterating the agency’s commitment to transparent campaign financing, these updated guidelines provide a more comprehensive framework for politi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IEA Report: Oil Prices on the Brink of Soaring as Supply Narrows and Demand Shatters Records]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755c23926c</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/iea-report-oil-prices-on-the-brink-of-soaring-as-supply-narrows-and-demand-shatters-records/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-12T19:38:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The stage is set for a potentially striking upswing in global oil prices, as supply constricts and demand ascends to unprecedented levels. With oil reserves dwindling at a breakneck pace, OPEC’s spare capacity restrained, and powerhouse consumers like China and India snapping up record quantities of Russian crude at discounted rates, a confluence of these factors is signaling the likelihood of an enduring escalation in oil prices, the International Energy Agency (IEA) warns in its August report.
 
IEA Report Sheds Light on Skyrocketing Oil Demand in the Face of Production Slump
 
According to the IEA’s projections, the world’s thirst for oil is set to swell by 2.2 million barrels per day (mb/d), reaching a new peak of 102.2 mb/d in 2023. In stark contrast, OPEC+ saw its supply contract by …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Bring Wall Street Into Crypto? Build Better ‘Piping,’ Says Talos CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152315</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152315/wall-street-crypto-institutional-investors-talos-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-08-12T17:47:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anton Katz says Wall Street firms need tools that better connect them to trading opportunities similar to the ones they use on capital markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFT Sales Jump 6.59%: A Week of Growth, Dominance of Ethereum, and Record-Breaking Collections]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755c148483</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/nft-sales-jump-6-59-a-week-of-growth-dominance-of-ethereum-and-record-breaking-collections/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-12T17:39:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the past seven days, the non-fungible token (NFT) market has seen a slight rise, recording sales of $106.87 million — an increase of 6.59% from the previous week. Ethereum-based NFTs made a significant contribution, accounting for 56.35% of the total weekly sales, or roughly $60.23 million, a modest 0.98% climb from the week before.
 
From Ethereum to Draftkings: Unpacking a Week of NFT Sales
 
The past week marked a small uptick in NFT sales, rising 6.59% higher than the preceding week, with the total reaching $106.87 million according to metrics provided by cryptoslam.io. Ethereum-based NFTs led the market, capturing $60.23 million, while Polygon-based NFTs took second place in weekly sales, commanding $13 million — an increase of 92.07% over the previous week.
 
Solana’s NFT sales se…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aragon Aims to Accelerate DAO Launches With Base]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152299</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152299/aragon-osx-dao-launching-platform-coinbase-base"/>
        <updated>2023-08-12T17:10:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aragon is launching its namesake app and OSx protocol on the new Coinbase blockchain, which can help DAOs get off the ground without developer expertise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Senator Cynthia Lummis Backs Coinbase Against SEC]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755c104071</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/cynthia-lummis-backs-coinbase/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-12T16:53:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a new development, Senator Cynthia Lummis,  a prominent advocate for cryptocurrency, filed an amicus brief on August 11 to support the Coinbase exchange against the SEC’s lawsuit. 
 
Lummis maintains that the responsibility to formulate crypto regulations lies with Congress, not the SEC. This standpoint emphasizes the importance of a clear separation of powers in shaping the landscape of cryptocurrencies.
 
The Current Conflict And Its Wide-Ranging Implications
 
In the lawsuit, SEC claims Coinbase operates as an unregistered broker, exchange, and clearing agency. This has resulted in a national issue and has attracted responses from all corners. 
 
 
Coinbase fired back and filed for a dismissal of the case against the crypto exchange on Friday, August 4 alleging the Security and Excha…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paris Hilton Won't Stop Trying to Make 'Sliving' Happen]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152264</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152264/paris-hilton-wont-stop-trying-make-sliving-happen"/>
        <updated>2023-08-12T16:25:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The influencer has launched Slivingland, a Roblox game inspired by a word she's been trying to get off the ground for almost four years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why the MET Is Expanding Into the Metaverse With Roblox]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152282</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152282/the-met-metropolitan-museum-roblox-replica-quest"/>
        <updated>2023-08-12T16:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Metropolitan Museum has launched a quest based app and installed a virtual doppelgänger on the Roblox gaming platform to meet young visitors where they are.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephanie Hirschmiller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chatbot Makers Respond to Accusations That AI Promotes Eating Disorders]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152276</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152276/chatbot-makers-respond-to-accusations-that-ai-promotes-eating-disorders"/>
        <updated>2023-08-12T15:43:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Center for Countering Digital Hate tested the safety guardrails of popular chatbots and found them lacking.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rebase Tokens: A Stunning Collapse From $8 Billion to $351 Million in 20 Months]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755c1edc65</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/rebase-tokens-a-stunning-collapse-from-8-billion-to-351-million-in-20-months/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-12T15:40:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto winter inflicted a brutal toll on the digital currency landscape, leaving numerous coins with values utterly obliterated. Within this ravaged financial terrain, one specific category — rebase tokens — suffered a tremendous deflation in worth over the previous 20 months. In a stark illustration of this downturn, the total value of the leading rebase tokens, once exceeding $8 billion in November 2021, has now plummeted to a mere $351 million.
 
Crypto Winter Chills Rebase Tokens: A $7.68 Billion Loss in Value
 
In 2021, the rebase token economy soared to an impressive $8.03 billion, concurrent with the crypto economy’s monumental valuation of $2.78 trillion. Fast forward to the present, and the crypto economy has contracted to $1.21 trillion, with a significant portion of value ha…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Bitcoin and Ethereum Prices Inch Upwards After PayPal Pitches Stablecoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152271</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152271/this-week-in-coins-bitcoin-and-ethereum-prices-inch-upwards-after-paypal-pitches-stablecoin"/>
        <updated>2023-08-12T15:07:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC this week did a lot of playing for time, but a new note on stablecoins by the Federal Reserve signaled a possible softening on crypto in Washington.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Binance.US CEO Weighs In On Stablecoin Regulation, Claims A Boost For Dollar Adoption]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755c1b4446</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ex-binance-us-ceo-weigh-in-on-stablecoin-regulation/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-12T14:53:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Binance.US CEO and an ex-acting US Comptroller of the Currency Brian Brooks has commented on the ongoing discourse regarding stablecoin regulation in the US. 
 
In an interview with CNBC on Friday, August 11, Brooks, now a partner at Valor Capital Group, took a stance against stablecoins opposition in the US government, saying that a proper regulatory framework for these assets could boost the relevance of the US dollar worldwide. 
 
 
US Dollar Can Benefit From High Stablecoin Demand, Brooks Says
 
Stablecoins are a type of cryptocurrency with values pegged to a fiat currency, mostly the US dollar, or a commodity such as gold, oil, etc.
 
According to Brooks, nations with high inflation rates have a buoyant demand for dollar-backed assets such as stablecoins as citizens look to pre…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Semilore Faleti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brazil Reports Record 3.3 Million Crypto Users In June As Bitcoin Adoption Surges]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755c0054ca</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/brazil-reports-record-3-3m-crypto-users/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-12T13:53:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brazil, the South American juggernaut, has solidified its position as a global leader in cryptocurrency adoption during June, with an impressive surge in both individual and corporate usage of bitcoin (BTC) and other digital assets. Recent data released by the Brazilian government highlights the nation’s robust adoption of cryptocurrencies, boosting its reputation as a thriving hub for crypto enthusiasts and companies alike.
 
Latest Data Shows Rise In Crypto Adoption 
 
According to the latest report compiled by the Federal Revenue Service (FRB), June witnessed a remarkable engagement with cryptocurrencies in Brazil, as more than 3.2 million individuals and over 89,000 registered Brazilian businesses actively participated in crypto-related operations. The data demonstrates a staggering in…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olowoporoku Adeniyi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Base Is Here, But Some of Its Projects Raise Red Flags]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755c00d552</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/web3/2023/08/12/base-is-here-but-some-of-its-projects-raise-red-flags/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-12T13:47:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, Coinbase launched its new Base blockchain while DeGods NFTs are way up after the project announced its upcoming Season III series. Plus, Microsoft and Aptos are teaming up to launch new blockchain AI tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rosie Perper</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biggest Movers: SHIB Climbs to 4-Month High, as Meme Coins Rally on Saturday]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755c01a769</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/biggest-movers-shib-climbs-to-4-month-high-as-meme-coins-rally-on-saturday/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-12T13:38:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba inu surged to a multi-month high on Saturday, as the meme coin extended its recent run of bullish momentum. The rally began as a result of the hopes surrounding its upcoming layer 2 launch. Dogecoin also extended recent gains to start the weekend.
 
Shiba Inu (SHIB)
 
Shiba inu (SHIB) was one of the notable gainers during Saturday’s session, as price surged to a multi-month high.
 
Following a low of $0.00001001 on Friday, SHIB/USD rallied to a peak of $0.00001127 earlier in the day.
 
The move came as SHIB surged for a fifth straight day, climbing to its strongest point since April in the process.
 
 
Looking at the chart, the latest rally occurred as the relative strength index (RSI) moved past a ceiling of 65.00.
 
Currently, price strength is at a reading of 74.27, with the next visible resistance zone at the 76.00 mark.
 
Should bulls hit this target, SHIB could possibly hit $0.00001200.
 
 
Dogecoin (DOGE)
 
Dogecoin (DOGE) also raced higher during the weekend, as it too remained in the green for a fifth consecutive session.
 
DOGE/USD jumped to an intraday high of $0.07715 on Saturday, which came after a low of $0.07517 the day prior.
 
This resulted in the cryptocurrency climbing to its strongest level since August 2, when price peaked at $0.0786.
 
 
Similar to shiba inu, the dogecoin move came as price strength broke out of a resistance level of 55.00.
 
A ceiling of 60.00 now awaits bulls, in the event they are able to maintain this week’s momentum.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
Do you expect meme coins to maintain bullish sentiment this weekend? Let us know your thoughts in the comments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CFTC Files Fraud Charge Against ‘Blockchain’ Entity That Claims To Grow Customer Funds]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755c0da08a</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/cftc-fraud-charge-on-entity-that-grow-customer-fund/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-12T12:53:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Commodity Futures Trading Commission has filed a complaint in the US District Court for the Middle District of Florida against four individuals and their unincorporated entity, Fundsz. This complaint accuses them of fraudulent solicitation from customers to supposedly trade in cryptocurrencies and precious metals.
 
According to its website, Fundsz claims to be a decentralized platform that utilizes “revolutionary” blockchain technology that empowers individuals, charities, and institutions to raise recurring and sustainable income. 
 
Fundsz Makes Up Fictional Weekly Returns For Clients, CFTC Says
 
In a press release published on August 11, 2023, the CFTC announced that it has charged Rene Larralde of Melbourne, Florida; Juan Pablo Valcarce of West Melbourne, Florida; Brian Early of …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Opeyemi Sule</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Technical Analysis: BTC, ETH Rebound on Saturday, as Markets Consolidate Following Recent Decline]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755c0f0e7d</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-ethereum-technical-analysis-btc-eth-rebound-on-saturday-as-markets-consolidate-following-recent-decline/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-12T12:36:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin was back in the green to start the weekend, after bulls rejected a breakout below $29,000 during Friday’s session. The cryptocurrency continues to hover around a key support level, without either bulls or bears taking control. Ethereum was also marginally higher.
 
Bitcoin
 
Bitcoin (BTC) returned to the green on Saturday, as traders of the cryptocurrency rejected a breakout of a key price level.
 
Following a low of $29,253.52 on Friday, BTC/USD rose to an intraday peak of $29,517.77 earlier in today’s session.
 
The move comes as the world’s largest cryptocurrency by market cap began to consolidate, following a recent move above $30,000.
 
 
Bitcoin surged earlier this week, as markets reacted to Moody’s downgrading the credit rating of several U.S. banks.
 
Today’s consolidation occurred just as the relative strength index (RSI) flatlined around a support point near 49.00.
 
As of writing, the index is now tracking at a reading of 48.70, with earlier gains in BTC somewhat fading.
 
 
Ethereum
 
Additionally, ethereum (ETH) was also marginally higher to start the weekend, snapping a three-day losing streak in the process.
 
ETH/USD peaked at $1,855.07 so far during Saturday’s session, following Friday’s low at the $1,839.57 level.
 
This is the first time since Tuesday that ethereum has climbed higher, and comes as profit taking from this week’s high seems to have ended.
 
 
In order for momentum to once again shift, ethereum will need to break out of a ceiling at 50.00 on the RSI.
 
Price strength is currently tracking at 47.45.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
Could ethereum move above $1,900 next week? Leave your thoughts in the comments below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitter Scam Infestation: How AI Tracked 95,000 Crypto ‘Free Giveaway’ Schemes]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e755c0ad527</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/twitter-scam-ai-tracks-9k-crypto-schemes/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-12T11:52:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto and Twitter scams have met their digital match as a team of researchers hailing from San Diego State University in California unveils an ingenious artificial intelligence (AI) tool. 
 
Crafted with precision, this innovative system, which they call GiveawayScamHunter, is capable of ferreting out, monitoring, and laying bare the intricate web of free cryptocurrency giveaway scams sprawling across the social media platform X (formerly Twitter). 
 
Over the course of a year – spanning from June 2022 to June 2023 – this automated sentinel unearthed a staggering 95,111 scam lists, all meticulously concocted from the network of 87,617 accounts nestled within the folds of the social network.
 
 
Twitter Scam: Unearthing The Trove Of Deception
 
With a pioneering approach, the team harnesse…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Loan Is Still a Loan Even in DeFi]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152189</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152189/loan-is-still-loan-even-defi"/>
        <updated>2023-08-12T10:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What happens when you mix microfinancing, a motorbike company in Kenya, and decentralized lending? Lots of risk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Hope You Enjoy Prison': Crypto Twitter Reacts as Sam Bankman-Fried's Bail Is Revoked]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152259</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152259/crypto-twitter-reacts-sam-bankman-fried-bail-revoked-ftx"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T23:55:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Disgraced FTX founder and former CEO Sam Bankman-Fried was sent to jail for witness tampering—and crypto personalities didn't hold back.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Degens Allegedly Launched Lil Tay Token Amid Teen Rapper's Death Hoax]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152248</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152248/degens-allegedly-launched-lil-tay-token-amid-teen-rapper-death-hoax"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T23:13:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The internet-famous rapper is apparently alive, but now there’s crypto confusion in the mix thanks to multiple Lil Tay-themed tokens.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Custodia Bank Now Accepting US Dollar Deposits, Adding Bitcoin Custody]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152245</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152245/custodia-bank-now-accepting-us-dollar-deposits-adding-bitcoin-custody"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T20:50:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“The bar is very high for banks to launch, and we cleared it," Custodia Bank CEO Caitlin Long told Decrypt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Seeks to 'Usurp Congress's Authority' in Coinbase Lawsuit: Blockchain Association]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152239</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152239/sec-seeks-to-usurp-congresss-authority-in-coinbase-lawsuit-blockchain-association"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T20:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["The SEC is trying to short-circuit the legislative process" the consortium of crypto associations argued in its court brief.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Scammy Dumpster Fire'—Overwatch 2 Steam Debut Review Bombed Into Oblivion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152231</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152231/scammy-dumpster-fire-overwatch-2-steam-debut-review-bombed-oblivion"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T20:37:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over 47,000 negative player reviews have taken Blizzard to task for various complaints, from the free-to-play model to the missing PvE mode.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried Is Going to Jail, Judge Revokes Bail Over Witness Tampering]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152210</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152210/sam-bankman-fried-going-to-jail-judge-revokes-bail"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T19:28:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Disgraced FTX CEO Sam Bankman-Fried's bail has been revoked. He will be detained in jail until the start of his criminal trial in October.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Grand Theft Auto 5 Mod Lets AI NPCs Insult You]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152196</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152196/grand-theft-auto-5-mod-lets-ai-npcs-insult-you"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T19:06:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rockstar's open-world smash gains new life via AI—and the NPCs really have a mind of their own, with one ranting about a "divine AI god."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are You Not Entertained? Elon Musk Says Fight With Zuck Will Be Livestreamed via Twitter, Meta]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152212</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152212/are-you-not-entertained-elon-musk-says-fight-zuck-livestreamed-twitter-meta"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T18:48:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk suggests the clash of the tech titans will happen in "an epic location" in Italy—though he may need surgery first.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There’s More Evidence ChatGPT Is a Good Doctor But a Bad Coder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152107</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152107/chatgpt-good-doctor-bad-coder"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T17:13:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two research papers evaluating ChatGPT's accuracy conclude that the AI chatbot seems to be better at writing prescriptions than writing code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum DeFi Dashboard DeBank Launches Layer-2 on Optimism’s OP Stack]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152202</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152202/ethereum-defi-dashboard-debank-launches-layer-2-on-optimisms-op-stack"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T16:19:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DeBank plans to launch a social media platform, DeBank Stream, by leveraging the 200,000-plus users on its chat app DeBank Hi.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Parallel' Puts an Epic Sci-Fi Spin on Complex NFT Card Battles]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152075</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152075/parallel-puts-epic-sci-fi-spin-complex-nft-card-battles-preview"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T16:02:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PREVIEW: Parallel is a competitive trading card game with NFTs—for fans of the genre and space operas alike. We go hands-on with the beta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Musician Nick Cave Rails Against AI: ChatGPT Is the 'Commodification of the Human Spirit']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152185</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152185/musician-nick-cave-rails-against-ai-chatgpt-is-the-commodification-of-the-human-spirit"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T15:57:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cave asserts AI overlooks the struggles in creativity and mechanizes the artistic process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Pumps Brakes on ARK 21Shares Bitcoin ETF]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152184</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152184/sec-pumps-brakes-on-ark-21shares-bitcoin-etf"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T15:37:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With more attention than ever on Bitcoin ETFs, the SEC has again delayed its decision on the ARK 21Shares Bitcoin ETF application.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Parallel TCG: Inside the Sci-Fi Card Game’s Closed Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/q8YVWJh4/parallel-tcg-inside-the-sci-fi-card-games-closed-beta</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/q8YVWJh4/parallel-tcg-inside-the-sci-fi-card-games-closed-beta"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T15:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin goes hands-on with Parallel’s closed beta on Windows PC to find out what sets it apart from other crypto card-battlers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visa Trials Ethereum Gas Fee Payments Using Cards]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152178</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152178/visa-trials-ethereum-gas-fee-payments-using-cards"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T15:13:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Global payment technology giant Visa has successfully completed a test that enables users to pay Ethereum gas fees using credit or debit cards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining Could Help Decarbonize Energy Grids, Researchers Say]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152088</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152088/bitcoin-mining-carbon-footprint-decarbonization"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T14:54:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin mining can indeed help achieve decarbonization, but faces some stiff practical challenges along the way, researchers find.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fool Me Once: Ethereum Traders Make More Money After Being Scammed]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152179</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152179/ethereum-traders-make-more-money-after-being-scammed"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T14:36:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the researchers said "burning your fingers is good for you," to an extent, because traders diversify and de-risk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generative AI a Top Emerging Risk for Organizations: Gartner Survey]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152161</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152161/generative-ai-a-top-emerging-risk-for-organizations-gartner-survey"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T12:22:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intellectual property, data privacy and cybersecurity are three areas that need to be addressed quickly, according to Gartner.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$170M Bridged to Coinbase Layer-2 Base as Daily Active Users Hit 136,000]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152164</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152164/170m-bridged-to-coinbase-layer-2-base-as-daily-active-users-hit-136000"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T11:38:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new chain has entered the top five layer-2 networks by total amount bridged, while daily active users hit 136,000.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These Are the High-Profile Ethereum Futures ETF Applications Currently in Play]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151012</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151012/these-are-the-high-profile-ethereum-futures-etf-applications-currently-in-play"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T10:10:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first Ethereum futures ETF could be launched as soon as October 2023—that is, if the SEC approves it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Labs Invests $10M to Accelerate Helio Protocol's Liquid Staking Pivot]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151990</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151990/binance-labs-invests-10m-accelerate-helio-protocols-liquid-staking-pivot"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T01:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LSDfi is a fast growing space within DeFi. Now Binance is throwing capital into it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Post Malone Disses CBDCs on Joe Rogan Podcast—And Bitcoiners Love It]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152126</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152126/post-malone-disses-cbdcs-joe-rogan-podcast-bitcoiners-love"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T00:03:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin supporters back the celebs’ take on CBDCs as the “digital dollar” discussion reaches mainstream audiences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[As Coach Swallows Versace, A Crypto Divide Grows in Luxury Fashion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152121</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152121/as-coach-swallows-versace-crypto-divide-grows-luxury-fashion"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T23:29:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An $8.5 billion merger between luxury giants could have major implications for the future of blockchain in fashion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Gaming Investments Surged in July as Metaverse NFTs Fizzled Out]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152091</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152091/crypto-gaming-investments-surged-july-metaverse-nfts-fizzled-out"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T22:24:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Investors pumped $297 million into the fledging crypto video game industry in July, but metaverse NFT sales have slowed significantly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Godfather of Generative Art Goes Global]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=151933</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/151933/godfather-generative-art-goes-global-casey-reas"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T21:50:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pioneering generative artist Casey Reas will release "923 Empty Rooms" with Bright Moments and Art Blocks at live events spanning six cities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alameda Hits a Snag in Lawsuit Over $9 Billion Locked in Grayscale Bitcoin Trust]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152089</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152089/alameda-lawsuit-grayscale-bitcoin-trust"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T21:41:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The FTX affiliate first sued Grayscale in March. Now it says it needs more time to find a co-plaintiff.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Exchange Bittrex Agrees to Pay $24 Million to Settle SEC Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152090</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152090/crypto-exchange-bittrex-agrees-pay-24-million-settle-sec-lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T21:33:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Four months after the SEC sued, bankrupt exchange Bittrex has agreed to a settlement without admitting to or denying the allegations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Is Literally Trying to Kill You With This Grocery Store App]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152060</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152060/ai-is-literally-trying-to-kill-you-with-this-grocery-store-app"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T19:31:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trying to use up leftovers? An AI-powered app produced ghastly results when users input things like "turpentine" and "ant-poison."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roblox Is Tapping AI to Generate 'More Rich and Dynamic' Games: CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152058</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152058/roblox-tapping-ai-generate-more-rich-dynamic-games-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T18:59:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the biggest games on the planet wants to let creators design games by typing prompts. Here’s how Roblox is approaching AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Digital Currency Group Wants 'Hodgepodge' Gemini Lawsuit Tossed Out]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152059</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152059/digital-currency-group-wants-hodgepodge-gemini-lawsuit-tossed-out"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T18:46:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A letter supporting the motion accused Cameron and Tyler Winklevoss of a “Twitter-based character assassination campaign.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gemini Opens XRP Deposits and Trading Following Ripple Labs Partial Victory]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152045</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152045/gemini-announces-xrp-deposits-following-ripple-labs-partial-victory"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T18:23:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Users will soon be able to trade the cryptocurrency on the platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Trade Sideways as Inflation Jumps to 3.2% in July]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152013</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152013/bitcoin-ethereum-trade-sideways-inflation-jumps-3-2-july"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T12:52:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Inflation has trended downward since it hit 9.1% last June, but the Fed’s target of 2% is the ultimate goal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jump Crypto Leads $5 Million Seed Round in Bitcoin Wallet Xverse]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152012</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152012/jump-crypto-leads-5m-fundingbitcoin-based-web-wallet-xverse"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T12:26:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Xverse wallet supports projects like Ordinals, Stacks, and the blockchain’s speedy Lightning Network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 Games Need to Compete with All Games, Says Solana Foundation GM]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ud9wTd4s/web3-games-need-to-compete-with-all-games-says-solana-foundation-gm</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ud9wTd4s/web3-games-need-to-compete-with-all-games-says-solana-foundation-gm"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T19:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Foundation's General Manager of Games Johnny Lee tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about Solana's PlayGG conference and shares his take on crypto gaming and the "play-to-earn" concept.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Many Early Blockchain Games Were 'Cash Grabs,' Says Twitch Streamer Alliestrasza]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BA4yE45A/many-early-blockchain-games-were-cash-grabs-says-twitch-streamer-alliestrasza</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BA4yE45A/many-early-blockchain-games-were-cash-grabs-says-twitch-streamer-alliestrasza"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T16:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["I wrote them off," Twitch streamer Alliestrasza said of her initial thoughts on many early blockchain games. She tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how her perspective on Web3 games has evolved over time and now sees blockchain games getting significantly better.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['MetalCore' Game Preview: Hands-on With the 'Titanfall' Meets 'Destiny' NFT Mashup]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/tjK6i7lv/metalcore-game-preview-hands-on-with-the-titanfall-meets-destiny-nft-mashup</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/tjK6i7lv/metalcore-game-preview-hands-on-with-the-titanfall-meets-destiny-nft-mashup"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T19:46:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MetalCore is an upcoming mech shooter developed by Studio 369, and it's being developed on Ethereum scaling network Immutable zkEVM. Decrypt contributor Ryan Gladwin played through the prologue and tested out the recent Alpha 3 online experience to get a sense of the NFT-infused mashup of Titanfall and Destiny.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Give Projects a Chance,' Says Aurory's Michael Natoli on NFT Game Challenges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/nBNKKZdK/give-projects-a-chance-says-aurorys-michael-natoli-on-nft-game-challenges</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/nBNKKZdK/give-projects-a-chance-says-aurorys-michael-natoli-on-nft-game-challenges"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aurory is an NFT-driven game franchise that started life on Solana and is expanding to other chains. Decrypt's Jason Nelson spoke with Aurory Head of Marketing Michael Natoli at Solana's PlayGG event, where Natoli shared his thoughts on the challenges that blockchain games face in reaching players.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Is Only Network Ready for Gaming: Solana Foundation's Johnny Lee]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5OvV3ZXn/solana-is-only-network-ready-for-gaming-solana-foundations-johnny-lee</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5OvV3ZXn/solana-is-only-network-ready-for-gaming-solana-foundations-johnny-lee"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T17:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Foundation General Manager Johnny Lee tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how the Solana network will tackle the scaling problem that blockchain games pose for the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Com2uS Is Going "Full Speed" on Crypto Gaming: Kyu Lee]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pYMZRoYy/com2us-is-going-full-speed-on-crypto-gaming-kyu-lee</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pYMZRoYy/com2us-is-going-full-speed-on-crypto-gaming-kyu-lee"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kyu Lee is the President of game studio Com2uS USA. In an interview, he shares the studio's approach to Web3 and crypto gaming with Decrypt GG's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Discord Game with AI and Blockchain: 'Alchemy: Battle for Ankhos' Creative Lead Alex Finden]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mF18GHGo/building-a-discord-game-with-ai-and-blockchain-alchemy-battle-for-ankhos-creative-lead-alex-finden</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mF18GHGo/building-a-discord-game-with-ai-and-blockchain-alchemy-battle-for-ankhos-creative-lead-alex-finden"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T21:55:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Jason Nelson interviews Alchemy: Battle for Ankhos Creative Director Alex Finden at the Solana PlayGG event in San Diego, California.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Big Respect Between Ethereum and Cosmos Developer Communities': dYdX Foundation CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/XU5MbCGE/big-respect-between-ethereum-and-cosmos-developer-communities-dydx-foundation-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/XU5MbCGE/big-respect-between-ethereum-and-cosmos-developer-communities-dydx-foundation-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T13:24:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CEO of the dYdX Foundation Charles d'Haussy unpacks the decision behind moving one of the largest decentralized exchange protocol's over to its very own chain built on Cosmos. A key driver, he told Decrypt at this year's EthCC event, was that instead of launching on a rollup or another layer-1, launching a fully customized chain will allow dYdX to fine tune the network for its product's needs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Staking Solution Lido 'Had Perfect Product Market Fit' at Launch, Says DAO's Biz Dev Contributor]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/fUHhelhV/ethereum-staking-solution-lido-had-perfect-product-market-fit-at-launch-says-daos-biz-dev-contributor</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/fUHhelhV/ethereum-staking-solution-lido-had-perfect-product-market-fit-at-launch-says-daos-biz-dev-contributor"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T08:43:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marin Tvrdić, a business development contributor to the Lido DAO, sat down with Decrypt during this year's EthCC to break down how the liquid staking protocol has managed such a massive lead, how it plans to keep that lead, and the protocol's new dual-governance tokenomics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's Going to Stop All the DeFi Hacks? 'Standards,' Says OpenZepplin Security Architect]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/aYNuFdAi/whats-going-to-stop-all-the-defi-hacks-standards-says-openzepplin-security-architect</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/aYNuFdAi/whats-going-to-stop-all-the-defi-hacks-standards-says-openzepplin-security-architect"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T08:04:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenZeppelin's security solutions architect Michael Lewellen sat down with Decrypt to discuss how the industry can become a little safer for users at this year's EthCC Paris. The key? Introducing security standards across the industry so folks know what an audit actually means and where risks lie, be it bad faith actors or poor implementation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Ev.io' Game Review: Earn Solana While Blasting Enemies]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/2ZmkuhL2/evio-game-review-earn-solana-while-blasting-enemies</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/2ZmkuhL2/evio-game-review-earn-solana-while-blasting-enemies"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T22:21:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ev.io is a web-based first-person shooter that's free to play, but lets NFT holders earn in-game currency that can be redeemed for Solana (SOL). Decrypt contributor Ryan Gladwin shares his review of the fun throwback to Quake-style blasting, albeit with a modern crypto twist.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Moving Fast and Breaking Things Isn't the Web3 Ethos': MetaMask Product Lead]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/l1EbLgl3/moving-fast-and-breaking-things-isnt-the-web3-ethos-metamask-product-lead</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/l1EbLgl3/moving-fast-and-breaking-things-isnt-the-web3-ethos-metamask-product-lead"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T15:45:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Account abstraction this, smart wallets that. Discussions at EthCC Paris about improving user experience have pointed at industry leader MetaMask as an example of what not to do. But that may soon change, with a host of updates and optimizations coming to crypto's number one wallet, said its product lead Alex Jupiter. It still may take some time, though, before these changes take effect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling Smart Wallets on Starknet 'Was The Winning Combination', Says Argent Co-Founder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/gnBsxw4D/scaling-smart-wallets-on-starknet-was-the-winning-combination-says-argent-co-founder</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/gnBsxw4D/scaling-smart-wallets-on-starknet-was-the-winning-combination-says-argent-co-founder"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T07:35:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Argent co-founder Julien Niset told Decrypt at EthCC Paris that he wants to make crypto wallets disappear. Or at least how they're currently conceived. From clunky seed phrases to a stiff user experience, Argent hopes to make using crypto a little less intimidating and a whole lot more fun.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Mighty Action Heroes' Open Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/litL6kKs/inside-mighty-action-heroes-open-beta</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/litL6kKs/inside-mighty-action-heroes-open-beta"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T18:23:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mighty Action Heroes is the flagship blockchain title from Mighty Bear Games. But is the browser-based battle royale shooter worth checking out? Decrypt's Kate Irwin offers her thoughts and a first look at the upcoming game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>