<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-04-30T02:24:25.127Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-04-30T02:24:25.127Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Whales, Not Retailers, Are Safe If The United States Government Begins Confiscating Coins: Analyst]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74342fc7b2</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-whales-retailers-safe-united-states-coins/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T02:04:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Willy Woo, an on-chain analyst, took to X on April 29, raising concerns about the fate of retail Bitcoin investors if the world, especially the United States, plunges into a recession. 
 
Woo, referencing historical events, argues that while large Bitcoin holders, or “whales,” are likely to weather the storm since they control private keys of their coins, retailers or everyday BTC investors might face a different reality.
 
Who Will Be Safe If The United States Government Began Confiscating Bitcoin?
 
The analyst compares the current market and the economic downturn of the Great Depression of 1930. During that time, the United States government, Woo warned, seized gold from the public to replenish national reserves. 
 
 
Woo now raises the question of whether a similar scenario could unfol…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dalmas Ngetich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s Profit Crunch: Hash Price Hits Record Low Post-Halving—What’s Next For Miners?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19446266/Bitcoins-Profit-Crunch-Hash-Price-Hits-Record-Low-Post-HalvingWhats-Next-For-Miners</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19446266/Bitcoins-Profit-Crunch-Hash-Price-Hits-Record-Low-Post-HalvingWhats-Next-For-Miners"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T02:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Bitcoin mining, the activity’s profitability is significantly influenced by a metric known as the ‘hash price.’ This metric has recently plummeted to unprecedented levels, causing concerns within the mining community. Bitcoin’s Latest Halving Sends Hash Price Into Freefall As Bitcoin...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Whales, Not Retailers, Are Safe If The United States Government Begins Confiscating Coins: Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19446264/Bitcoin-Whales-Not-Retailers-Are-Safe-If-The-United-States-Government-Begins-Confiscating-Coins-Analyst</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19446264/Bitcoin-Whales-Not-Retailers-Are-Safe-If-The-United-States-Government-Begins-Confiscating-Coins-Analyst"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T02:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Willy Woo, an on-chain analyst, took to X on April 29, raising concerns about the fate of retail Bitcoin investors if the world, especially the United States, plunges into a recession. Woo, referencing historical events, argues that while large Bitcoin holders, or “whales,” are likely to weather...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mollars token creator sends animated ‘warning’ about Shiba Inu & Bitcoin founders]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19446255/Mollars-token-creator-sends-animated-warning-about-Shiba-Inu-Bitcoin-founders</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19446255/Mollars-token-creator-sends-animated-warning-about-Shiba-Inu-Bitcoin-founders"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T01:59:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mollars initial coin offering is surging in presales while on it’s way to the event’s closeout. The new store-of-value asset, deemed  the ‘Bitcoin for Ethereum blockchain,’  will complete its ICO stage on May 1st.  But before the deadline,  the founder is now stirring up controversy over the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China Asset Management Exec Anticipates Hong Kong Spot Bitcoin ETFs to ‘Exceed’ US Debut]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e743429f0bc</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/china-asset-management-exec-anticipates-hong-kong-spot-bitcoin-etfs-to-exceed-us-debut/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T01:40:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the debut of spot bitcoin and ethereum exchange-traded funds (ETFs) in Hong Kong trading on Tuesday, market observers are speculating about the potential demand for these ETFs in the region, reminiscent of the enthusiasm seen in the U.S. following the approval of 11 spot bitcoin ETFs on Jan. 10. Zhu Haokang, head of digital […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin's Short-Term Holder Realized Price At $59,800; Analyst Says Falling Below This Could Trigger Notable 'Price Corrections']]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19446244/Bitcoins-Short-Term-Holder-Realized-Price-At-59800-Analyst-Says-Falling-Below-This-Could-Trigger-Notable-Price-Corrections</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19446244/Bitcoins-Short-Term-Holder-Realized-Price-At-59800-Analyst-Says-Falling-Below-This-Could-Trigger-Notable-Price-Corrections"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T01:26:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (CRYPTO: BTC) has seen its short-term holder realized price at $59,800, which could potentially lead to a significant correction in its price, according to a prominent crypto analyst. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum spot ETFs start trading in Hong Kong with high expectations]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19446217/Bitcoin-Ethereum-spot-ETFs-start-trading-in-Hong-Kong-with-high-expectations</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19446217/Bitcoin-Ethereum-spot-ETFs-start-trading-in-Hong-Kong-with-high-expectations"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T01:21:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong-listed spot Bitcoin and Ethereum exchange-traded funds (ETFs) are set to debut in a few minutes. In anticipation of the launch, Zhu Haokang, Digital Asset Management Director and Family Wealth Director at China Asset Management, is confident that the launch scale of Hong Kong's virtual...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Huge Day For Bitcoin!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19446215/HUGE-DAY-FOR-BITCOIN</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19446215/HUGE-DAY-FOR-BITCOIN"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T01:04:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETFs new round, altcoin updates, airdrops, and more! ITRUST https://itrust.capital/LarkDavis AARK https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSf_5N7OCCvDhZe16vXUea8ckDuKxg3s141oAkgWe3_NngiXjQ/viewform 🔥 GET MY FREE NEWSLETTER 👉 https://cryptolark.co/WEALTH_MASTERY💎 BITGET 👉 $30,000 IN...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Regulatory Saga: Court Filings Expose SEC Chair Gensler’s Stand]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7434159628</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/sec-chair-genslers-stance-on-ethereum/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T01:02:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Newly disclosed court filings have shed light on the belief of the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and its chairman, Gary Gensler, that Ethereum (ETH) is an “unregistered security” under the Howey Test, which is considered by the vast majority of crypto advocates to be an outdated legal framework for regulating crypto assets.  
 
According to a recent Fox Business report, the details emerged following Ethereum software company ConsenSys’s filing of an unredacted complaint against the SEC.
 
Is Ethereum An ‘Unregistered Security’? 
 
According to the court filings, SEC Chair Gensler and the agency seem to have held the belief for at least a year that Ethereum was operating as an unregistered security, thereby violating federal regulations. 
 
The SEC’s Division of Enforcement, l…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Regulatory Saga: Court Filings Expose SEC Chair Gensler’s Stand]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19446192/Ethereum-Regulatory-Saga-Court-Filings-Expose-SEC-Chair-Genslers-Stand</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19446192/Ethereum-Regulatory-Saga-Court-Filings-Expose-SEC-Chair-Genslers-Stand"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T01:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Newly disclosed court filings have shed light on the belief of the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and its chairman, Gary Gensler, that Ethereum (ETH) is an “unregistered security” under the Howey Test, which is considered by the vast majority of crypto advocates to be an outdated...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Operation Chokepoint 2.0 (2.0)]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19446181/Operation-Chokepoint-20-20</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19446181/Operation-Chokepoint-20-20"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T00:54:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is the US government coordinated crackdown back? This time it seems focused on self-custody. ﻿Today's Show Brought To You ByLedger - 5% to Bitcoin Developers When You Buy https://shop.ledger.com/pages/bitcoin-hardware-walletConsensus 2024 is happening May 29-31 in Austin, Texas. This year marks...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hidden Dogecoin (DOGE) Growth Signal, XRP Loses Its Floor, Solana (SOL) Is Safer Than You Think]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19446170/Hidden-Dogecoin-DOGE-Growth-Signal-XRP-Loses-Its-Floor-Solana-SOL-Is-Safer-Than-You-Think</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19446170/Hidden-Dogecoin-DOGE-Growth-Signal-XRP-Loses-Its-Floor-Solana-SOL-Is-Safer-Than-You-Think"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T00:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cryptocurrency market's state raises some dangerous questions]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cyber Heist Alert: North Korea Hackers Lazarus Group Use LinkedIn To Prey on Crypto Firms]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7434135e79</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/north-korea-hackers-lazarus-linkedin-crypto-firms/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T00:02:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The notorious Lazarus Group, a cyber-hacker entity backed by North Korea, appears to have escalated its fraudulent activities to attack crypto by exploiting LinkedIn’s professional networking platform. This cyber threat has been detailed in a report by SlowMist, a leading information security firm.
 
The Lazarus Group, known for its elaborate cyber offenses, has now impersonated high-profile figures within the crypto industry to orchestrate phishing attacks that jeopardize personal and organizational security.
 
 
Deceptive Identities And Phishing Ploys
 
SlowMist’s chief information security officer findings posted on X expose how the Lazarus Group masquerades as reputable figures from institutions such as Fenbushi Capital. By assuming the identity of executives, the hackers gain unwarran…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cyber Heist Alert: North Korea Hackers Lazarus Group Use LinkedIn To Prey on Crypto Firms]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19446113/Cyber-Heist-Alert-North-Korea-Hackers-Lazarus-Group-Use-LinkedIn-To-Prey-on-Crypto-Firms</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19446113/Cyber-Heist-Alert-North-Korea-Hackers-Lazarus-Group-Use-LinkedIn-To-Prey-on-Crypto-Firms"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T00:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The notorious Lazarus Group, a cyber-hacker entity backed by North Korea, appears to have escalated its fraudulent activities to attack crypto by exploiting LinkedIn’s professional networking platform. This cyber threat has been detailed in a report by SlowMist, a leading information security...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Dominance: Traders Preferring The OG To Dogecoin & Other Altcoins]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19446100/Bitcoin-Dominance-Traders-Preferring-The-OG-To-Dogecoin-Other-Altcoins</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19446100/Bitcoin-Dominance-Traders-Preferring-The-OG-To-Dogecoin-Other-Altcoins"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T00:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data suggests Bitcoin has recently experienced an influx of investors while Dogecoin, Cardano, and other altcoins have seen a slowdown. Bitcoin Total Amount Of Holders Rise While Altcoins See Flat Movement According to data from the on-chain analytics firm Santiment, the number of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Showing Serious Strength as One Low-Cap Altcoin Flashes Bullish Signal for First Time Since 2022: Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19446102/Ethereum-Showing-Serious-Strength-as-One-Low-Cap-Altcoin-Flashes-Bullish-Signal-for-First-Time-Since-2022-Analyst</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19446102/Ethereum-Showing-Serious-Strength-as-One-Low-Cap-Altcoin-Flashes-Bullish-Signal-for-First-Time-Since-2022-Analyst"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T00:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A widely followed crypto strategist says that Ethereum (ETH) is likely gearing up for a big upside move as the leading smart contract platform shows “serious strength” in the charts. Pseudonymous analyst and trader Bluntz tells his 257,000 followers on the social media platform X that ETH is...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy Q1 net loss hits $53.1M but Bitcoin buying spree continues]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19446099/MicroStrategy-Q1-net-loss-hits-531M-but-Bitcoin-buying-spree-continues</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19446099/MicroStrategy-Q1-net-loss-hits-531M-but-Bitcoin-buying-spree-continues"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T23:52:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy has yet to adopt the new accounting standard that would have taken the billions of dollars in paper gains from Bitcoin’s 65% price rally into account.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samourai Wallet developer Keonne Rodriguez under home incarceration after securing $1 million bail]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19446096/Samourai-Wallet-developer-Keonne-Rodriguez-under-home-incarceration-after-securing-1-million-bail</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19446096/Samourai-Wallet-developer-Keonne-Rodriguez-under-home-incarceration-after-securing-1-million-bail"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T23:44:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samourai Wallet developer Keonne Rodriguez has pleaded not guilty to criminal charges and will stay under home incarceration until trial. Rodriguez’s bail conditions, as outlined in an April 26 docket entry, include a $1 million personal recognizance bond to be secured before May 14. Two others...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In a Sea of Mining Giants, One Solo Miner Strikes Digital Gold by Finding Bitcoin Block 841,286]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74341d9820</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/in-a-sea-of-mining-giants-one-solo-miner-strikes-digital-gold-by-finding-bitcoin-block-841286/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T23:39:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While bitcoin mining has become increasingly difficult and block rewards have dropped from 6.25 bitcoins to 3.125 bitcoins, a solo miner discovered block 841,286. Bitcoin’s Harsh Mining Climate Yields Treasure for One Solo Entity Mining bitcoin (BTC) has become significantly challenging, with the network’s difficulty reaching an all-time high of 88.10 trillion. This complexity, coupled […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin and Shiba Inu Rival Homo Dogecoin (HODOGE) to Explode Over 8,000% Amid MEXC Listing]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19446084/Dogecoin-and-Shiba-Inu-Rival-Homo-Dogecoin-HODOGE-to-Explode-Over-8000-Amid-MEXC-Listing</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19446084/Dogecoin-and-Shiba-Inu-Rival-Homo-Dogecoin-HODOGE-to-Explode-Over-8000-Amid-MEXC-Listing"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T23:36:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Homo Dogecoin (HODOGE) could turn early investors into multi-millionaires if it becomes a mainstream coin,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Meets With DeSantis, Noem Stirs Up Controversy: How Will Republican Vice President Betting Odds Be Impacted?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19446098/Trump-Meets-With-DeSantis-Noem-Stirs-Up-Controversy-How-Will-Republican-Vice-President-Betting-Odds-Be-Impacted</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19446098/Trump-Meets-With-DeSantis-Noem-Stirs-Up-Controversy-How-Will-Republican-Vice-President-Betting-Odds-Be-Impacted"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T23:36:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The relationship between Donald Trump and Ron DeSantis was heated at times during the Republican primary season, before the Florida governor dropped out of the 2024 presidential election and threw his support behind the read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Russian Law Will Legalize Industrial Crypto Miners, Limit Private Mining]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19446122/New-Russian-Law-Will-Legalize-Industrial-Crypto-Miners-Limit-Private-Mining</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19446122/New-Russian-Law-Will-Legalize-Industrial-Crypto-Miners-Limit-Private-Mining"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T23:30:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Russian lawmakers are set to legalize the nation’s industrial crypto mining sector, but could impose limits on home-based “private” miners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Isn't Gambling #bitcoin #bitcoinnews #shorts]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19446075/Bitcoin-Isnt-Gambling-bitcoin-bitcoinnews-shorts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19446075/Bitcoin-Isnt-Gambling-bitcoin-bitcoinnews-shorts"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T23:27:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin is savings!! START SAVING TODAY!!Follow Adam O'Brien - Founder of Bitcoin Well - @adamobrien_ Brought to you by Bitcoinwell.com a bitcoin-only platform on a mission to enable independence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Bitcoin Bear Market May Have Already Started, Signal Shows]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19446066/The-Bitcoin-Bear-Market-May-Have-Already-Started-Signal-Shows</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19446066/The-Bitcoin-Bear-Market-May-Have-Already-Started-Signal-Shows"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T23:16:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Between persistent weekly drawdowns and stagnant ETF flows, some think the Bitcoin bull market top is already in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s Where The Shiba Inu Price Is Headed In May According To Historical Data]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74341898b9</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-price-in-may/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T23:09:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Shiba Inu price, along with the rest of the crypto market, has suffered uncertain headwinds as a result of massive sell-offs suppressing the price. However, with the month of April drawing to an end, crypto investors are expecting the price direction. One way of getting an idea of where the price might be headed next is using historical data, so here is how Shiba Inu has performed in May, historically.
 
How Shiba Inu Performs In May
 
Historical data shows that the month of May her not been particularly bullish for the Shiba Inu price. According to data from CryptoRank, the meme coin has seen more red months in May than green months, suggesting that the trend could continue.
 
 
The last time that the Shiba Inu price finished in the green in the month of May was back in 2021, which wa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CasinoBello.com – Revolutionizing Online Gaming With Crypto Innovations]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7434189a2c</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/casinobello-com-revolutionizing-online-gaming-with-crypto-innovations/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T23:09:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. Casinobello.com, a Curacao-licensed online casino, is thrilled to gain the biggest popularity in its history and become one of the leading destinations for crypto-savvy iGaming users. With a strong presence in Germany, Austria, Switzerland, Italy, New Zealand, Canada, and Australia, Casinobello is pioneering the integration of cryptocurrency into the online gaming world to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s Where The Shiba Inu Price Is Headed In May According To Historical Data]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19446059/Heres-Where-The-Shiba-Inu-Price-Is-Headed-In-May-According-To-Historical-Data</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19446059/Heres-Where-The-Shiba-Inu-Price-Is-Headed-In-May-According-To-Historical-Data"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T23:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Shiba Inu price, along with the rest of the crypto market, has suffered uncertain headwinds as a result of massive sell-offs suppressing the price. However, with the month of April drawing to an end, crypto investors are expecting the price direction. One way of getting an idea of where the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microstrategy Boosts Bitcoin Holdings to 214,400 BTC With Latest Purchase]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7434071c1d</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/microstrategy-boosts-bitcoin-holdings-to-214400-btc-with-latest-purchase/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T22:09:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microstrategy, the Nasdaq-listed software intelligence firm and “the world’s first bitcoin development company,” has disclosed that it now holds 214,400 bitcoins after the latest purchase. “We acquired 25,250 additional bitcoins since the end of the fourth quarter, our 14th consecutive quarter of adding more bitcoin to our balance sheet,” said the company’s chief financial officer. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Expert Flags Dangers Of Spot Bitcoin ETFs: Labels Them ‘Orange FOMO Poker Chips’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e743407452f</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/expert-flags-dangers-of-spot-bitcoin-etfs/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T22:08:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Market expert and researcher Jim Bianco recently voiced cautionary remarks regarding the alleged risks of spot Bitcoin ETFs. Bianco’s insights shed light on these ETFs’ implications for the market and address specific concerns related to investor behavior.
 
Minimal Involvement In New Bitcoin ETFs?
 
In a thought-provoking social media post on X (formerly Twitter), Bianco emphasized his increasing worries as more data becomes available. Notably, he expressed concerns about the potential risks that spot Bitcoin ETFs pose to the market. 
 
Bianco highlighted that investment advisors (IAs) hold a substantial portion, approximately 35%, of all ETFs. Surprisingly, their holdings account for less than 1% of spot BTC ETFs. For Bianco, this revelation challenges the popular belief that “boomers ar…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Wavers Around $63K, Awaiting Hong Kong Spot Crypto ETF Debut]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7434003e37</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/04/29/bitcoin-wavers-around-63k-awaiting-hong-kong-spot-crypto-etf-debut/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T21:59:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite muted anticipation for the new products, an executive of one of the issuers reportedly expects that the first-day issuance of the Hong Kong offerings will exceed the U.S. debut in January.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nintendo Switch 2 Preview: Everything You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197793</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197793/nintendo-switch-2-rumors-leaks-latest-news"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T21:55:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATED: Magnetically attached Joy-Con controllers? Backwards compatibility? A huge 1080p screen? Here's the latest on the Nintendo Switch 2.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche Hoops Game ‘Rumble Kong League’ Nets Gatorade Deal]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228663</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228663/avalanche-hoops-game-rumble-kong-league-gatorade-deal"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T21:46:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Upcoming mobile basketball game Rumble Kong League will feature Gatorade-branded items.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy Bought 122 Bitcoin In April, Now Holds 214,400 BTC]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74340d26db</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/markets/microstrategy-bought-122-bitcoin-in-april-now-holds-214400-btc"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T21:17:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy, a leading business intelligence and software company, has continued its steadfast commitment to Bitcoin by purchasing an additional 122 BTC in April at a total cost of $7.8 million, Founder & Chairman Michael Saylor announced today.

BREAKING: MicroStrategy bought 122 more #Bitcoin for $7.8 million. pic.twitter.com/IZWUNj0kHY
— Bitcoin Magazine (@BitcoinMagazine) April 29, 2024
 
 
 
“As the world’s first Bitcoin Development Company, MicroStrategy is committed to the continued development of the bitcoin network through our activities in the financial markets, advocacy and technology innovation,” said Phong Le, President and Chief Executive Officer at MicroStrategy. “It is through our unique bitcoin strategy and solid track record as an operating company that we now hold 214,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nik Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Network Now Cheapest In 6 Months: What It Means]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74340e862c</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-network-now-cheapest-6-months-what-means/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T21:05:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data shows the Ethereum transaction fees is now at its lowest since October 2023. Here’s what it could mean for the cryptocurrency.
 
Ethereum Transfer Fees Has Recently Plunged To A Low Of $1.12
 
According to data from the on-chain analytics firm Santiment, the average fee on the Ethereum network has dropped to low levels recently. The fee here naturally refers to the amount that every sender has to attach to their transactions as compensation for the blockchain to process their move.
 
What fee an investor may have to attach in order for the transfer to swiftly go through depends on the network conditions at the time. During times of high activity, there can be high competition to get transactions through fast, so users who are in a rush may have to pay fees high enough to beat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy Q1 Operating Loss of $53.1M After Bitcoin Holdings Impairment Charge of $191.6M]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74340874d5</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2024/04/29/microstrategy-q1-operating-loss-of-531m-after-bitcoin-holdings-impairment-charge-of-1916m/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T20:50:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To this point, the company has not adopted fair value accounting for its bitcoin stack, resulting in the first quarter write-down despite a major rally in prices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen  Alpher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy Buys Even More Bitcoin, Pushing Stash to $13.5 Billion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228660</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228660/microstrategy-buys-even-more-bitcoin-13-5-billion"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T20:50:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Saylor’s software firm MicroStrategy bought the dip, expanding its enormous pile of Bitcoin with more than 1% of the total supply in hand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Launched Formal Investigation Into Ethereum’s Security Status Over a Year Ago, New Court Filing Shows]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74340a44f8</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/sec-launched-formal-investigation-into-ethereums-security-status-over-a-year-ago-new-court-filing-shows/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T20:35:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new court filing claims that the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), led by Chair Gary Gensler, initiated a formal investigation into ethereum’s potential classification as a security more than a year ago. SEC Enforcement Division Director Gurbir Grewal approved a formal investigative order in March last year to scrutinize potential securities transactions involving […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New AI Model Reka Rises to Challenge ChatGPT, Claude and Llama-3—And It's Free]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228507</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228507/reka-ai-core-free-competition-chatgpt-claude-llama-3"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T20:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lesser-known startup has produced a top-performing AI model, Reka Core. We put it to the test against its high-powered competition.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Restaking Protocol EigenLayer Reveals Token and Airdrop Plans]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228642</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228642/eigen-token-airdrop-plan-ethereum-restaking-protocol-eigenlayer"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T20:16:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Eigen Foundation will begin distributing EIGEN tokens on May 10, but US and VPN users will be blocked.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samourai Wallet Co-Founder Keonne Rodriguez Pleads Not Guilty, Released on $1M Bond]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7435f4e8c4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/04/29/samourai-wallet-co-founder-keonne-rodriguez-pleads-not-guilty-released-on-1m-bond/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T20:13:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NEW YORK — Samourai Wallet co-founder Keonne Rodriguez pleaded not guilty to two criminal charges tied to creating and marketing the privacy-focused bitcoin wallet application and mixing service in a Manhattan courtroom on Monday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cheyenne Ligon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[As Wasabi Wallet and Phoenix Leave the U.S., What’s Next for Non-Custodial Crypto?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7435f5af2c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2024/04/29/as-wasabi-wallet-and-phoenix-leave-the-us-whats-next-for-non-custodial-crypto/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T20:07:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following DOJ action against Samourai Wallet and a possible Metamask investigation, Wasabi Wallet and Phoenix are closing their U.S. offerings. Is non-custodial crypto under threat?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Kuhn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why This Crypto Analyst Believes PEPE Could Flip Dogecoin And Shiba Inu]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7435f5d7d3</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/pepe-flip-dogecoin-shiba-inu/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T20:06:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pepe (PEPE) has been one of the best-performing crypto assets since the beginning of the year, with a year-to-date (YTD) gain of over 400%. This crypto analyst predicts that PEPE can continue this impressive run and become the largest meme coin by market cap, ahead of Dogecoin and Shiba Inu.
 
PEPE To Flip Dogecoin (DOGE) And Shiba Inu (SHIB)
 
Crypto analyst and trader Murad mentioned in an X (formerly Twitter) post that it is “possible that PEPE flips SHIB and possibly even DOGE.” PEPE flipping these two meme coins will make it the largest meme coin by market cap, as they occupy the second and first positions, respectively. 
 
 
Murad further explained why he holds this belief, noting that PEPE is a “cult community with 10,000,000+ unique memes that is [sic] perpetually relevant to moder…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solo Bitcoin Miner Hits the Jackpot with $218,000 Block Reward]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228584</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228584/solo-bitcoin-miner-wins-block-reward-218000"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T20:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One miner's perseverance in the face of the dominance of centralized mining firms and major mining pools has paid off.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Clash of Clans' Maker Supercell Invests in Crypto Gaming Startup]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228607</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228607/clash-of-clans-maker-supercell-invests-games-living"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T19:36:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain startup Games for a Living has raised $3.2 million, with mobile gaming giant Supercell in the mix.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Press Briefing With ChinaAMC Executive Ahead of Tuesday Launch of Hong Kong Spot Bitcoin and Ether ETFs]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7435fd8cd1</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/04/29/press-briefing-with-chinaamc-executive-ahead-of-tuesday-launch-of-hong-kong-spot-bitcoin-and-ether-etfs/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T19:06:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zhu Haokang is head of digital asset management and family wealth at one of the ETF providers, ChinaAMC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen  Alpher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korea's Lazarus Group Laundered $200M in Crypto, Says Blockchain Sleuth—Here's How]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228606</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228606/north-koreas-lazarus-group-laundered-200m-in-crypto-says-blockchain-sleuth-heres-how"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T18:58:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain analyst ZachXBT has broken down exactly how North Korea’s notorious hacking group Lazarus laundered over $200 million into fiat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Rollups Could Boost Transaction Speeds 10X, Devs Claim]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228630</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228630/bitcoin-rollups-bitcoinos-whitepaper-10x-transaction-speed"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T18:45:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new BitcoinOS whitepaper says its scaling system is resistant to government attackers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu’s Decentralized Exchange ShibaSwap Expands To Shibarium]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7435f9db48</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-shibaswap-expands-to-shibarium/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T18:34:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu has announced the expansion of its decentralized exchange (DEX), ShibaSwap, to include support for Shibarium, its related Ethereum Layer 2 (L2) blockchain. This development introduces multi-chain functionality to ShibaSwap, allowing it to operate across both the Ethereum and Shibarium platforms, a move set to significantly enhance its operational flexibility and efficiency.
 
Shiba Inu Team Introduces Of Multi-Chain Capabilities
 
Lucie, Shiba Inu’s marketing lead, made the expansion announcement on X (formerly Twitter), stating, “ShibaSwap is going multi-chain, operating on both #Shibarium and Ethereum. Who knows what the future holds? We’re expanding our horizons. Don’t forget, Bone is the Shibarium gas fee token. IYKYK.” This strategic move underscores ShibaSwap’s shift toward…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EigenLayer, After Touching Off Restaking Frenzy, Plans Own EIGEN token]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7435fa2f29</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2024/04/29/eigenlayer-after-touching-off-restaking-frenzy-plans-own-eigen-token/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T18:32:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some 45% of the EIGEN token supply will go towards the EigenLayer community, while investors will be allocated 29.5% of the token supply, and 25.5% will go towards early contributors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Margaux Nijkerk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Funds Bleed Investor Cash for Third Straight Week]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228620</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228620/digital-asset-investment-funds-lose-cash-three-weeks"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T18:10:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Persistent outflows from Grayscale’s Bitcoin Trust overshadowed the modest gains of its peers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETFs Expected to Launch on Australia's ASX Exchange in 2024: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228563</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228563/bitcoin-etfs-expected-launch-australia-asx-exchange-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T17:11:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Approval of spot Bitcoin ETFs on the ASX exchange, which accounts for the bulk of Australia's equity trading, is reportedly near.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Holograph Expands 'Omnichain' Gaming NFT Push With New Funding]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228602</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228602/holographomnichain-gaming-nfts-new-funding"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T17:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With $3 million in fresh funding led by Mechanism Capital and Selini Capital, Holograph is pushing deeper into gaming with tokens that can be used across Ethereum-compatible chains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Token Runecoin Hits All-Time High Price Ahead of OKX Listing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228573</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228573/bitcoin-token-runecoin-all-time-high-price-okx-listing"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T16:28:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Centralized exchange OKX is the latest to embrace Bitcoin Runes, running a Runecoin rewards drive ahead of the listing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More Than $3 Billion in Tokens Unlock in May—Here’s What to Watch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228564</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228564/3-billion-token-unlocks-may-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T15:26:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some of the biggest unlocks are coming from DeFi oracle provider Pyth and decentralized crypto derivatives platform Aevo.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Has Secretly Considered Ethereum a Security Since 2023, Says Consensys in Unredacted Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228504</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228504/sec-declared-ethereum-security-last-year-consensys-lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T14:20:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unredacted portions of a lawsuit filed by Consensys reveal that the agency classified ETH as a security last April.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Payments Giant Stripe Expands Crypto Return With Avalanche Integration]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228359</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228359/payments-giant-stripe-expands-crypto-return-with-avalanche-support"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T13:01:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stripe's new Avalanche integration means that users can buy AVAX directly through the mobile app—without having to go through an exchange.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Primitives Protocol’s Decentralized Social Graph Has Facebook In its Sights]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=227044</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/227044/primitives-protocols-decentralized-social-graph-has-facebook-in-its-sights"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T13:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Built with Solana’s State Compression Technology, Primitives Protocol’s "non-fungible graphs" enable friends to migrate between social networks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Apeiron' Open Beta: Should You Play This Clever Mashup of Strategy Genres?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228218</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228218/apeiron-open-beta-should-you-play-clever-strategy-mashup"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T12:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's more than just airdrop hype behind Ronin game Apeiron, which smartly blends genres for a satisfying strategy affair.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friend.tech V2 Goes Live as Hype Builds for 100% Airdrop of FRIEND Token]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228473</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228473/friend-tech-v2-goes-live-as-hype-builds-for-100-airdrop-of-friend-token"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T11:11:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Friend.tech launches its version 2, hype builds among the community for its new points system and FRIEND token airdrop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Priest Fired by Catholic Group After Pitching Gatorade Baptisms]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228360</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228360/ai-priest-catholic-answers-father-justin"/>
        <updated>2024-04-28T19:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Pope Francis prepares to address AI at the G7 summit, a virtual priest loses his collar.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It's an Incredible Time for RPGs—Don't Miss These 11 Recent Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228395</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228395/11-must-play-role-playing-games-rpgs"/>
        <updated>2024-04-28T17:56:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Love role-playing games? RPG fans have been spoiled over the last year with huge sequels and clever originals. Here are 11 must-play games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Frederiksen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Crypto Games: Notcoin Token Launch Nears, Immutable's $50 Million Giveaway]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228386</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228386/this-week-crypto-games-notcoin-token-launch-immutable-50-million-giveaway"/>
        <updated>2024-04-28T13:31:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Notcoin launch is only days away, while Immutable is giving out rewards and Charles Hoskinson's studio released a game—not on Cardano.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week on Crypto Twitter: Bitcoin Runes Mania and More Ethereum Legal Drama]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228373</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228373/crypto-twitter-bitcoin-runes-cryptopunk-bored-ape-consensys-ethereum-lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2024-04-28T10:01:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As new Runes tokens dominated crypto, a proactive suit from Consensys against the SEC fostered a wartime mood among industry leaders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Cold Wallet' Review: The First Real Crypto Film]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228289</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228289/cold-wallet-review-first-real-crypto-film"/>
        <updated>2024-04-27T12:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a crypto exchange collapses, a group of Redditors set out to recover their funds from the CEO—by whatever means necessary.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Bitcoin Stumbles but Meme Coins Come Out Winning—Again]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228355</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228355/this-week-in-coins-bitcoin-meme-coins-bonk-pepe-floki"/>
        <updated>2024-04-27T10:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bonk, Pepe, and Floki are among the biggest gainers of the past seven days.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Altman, Satya Nadella Join High-Powered AI Safety Board for Homeland Security]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228348</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228348/openai-sam-altman-microsoft-satya-nadella-homeland-security-ai-safety-board"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T21:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twenty leading AI developers—including OpenAI, Microsoft, NVIDIA, and Google—pledge to help the US Department of Homeland Security protect critical infrastructure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Notcoin’ Game Token Is Launching Soon—Here's How the Claim Works]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228345</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228345/notcoin-game-token-launch-how-to-claim"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T19:56:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NOT token is dropping in a matter of days, Notcoin’s co-creator told Decrypt’s GG. Here’s what to expect from the claim process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Releases 8 Small AI Language Models To Compete With Microsoft’s Phi-3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228325</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228325/apple-small-ai-models-openelm-microsoft-phi-mini"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T19:46:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Competition in the AI space has started to shift from building the largest models to the smallest, most capable tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yuga Labs ‘Lost Its Way’ Says CEO as Bored Ape NFT Maker Reveals Layoffs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228336</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228336/yuga-labs-lost-way-says-ceo-bored-ape-nft-layoffs"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T19:19:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bored Ape Yacht Club creator Yuga Labs is restructuring with an aim to get back to its smaller, scrappier early days.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Allies: Arbitrum Team Helps Optimism Avoid ‘High Risk’ Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228318</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228318/arbitrum-offchain-labs-optimism-vulnerability"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T18:54:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reaching out to combat potential fraud, from one layer-2 to another.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elizabeth Warren Claims Crypto Is the ‘Payment of Choice’ for Child Abuse Material]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228317</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228317/elizabeth-warren-claims-crypto-is-the-payment-of-choice-for-child-abuse-material"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T18:21:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The top senator wants to help the Justice Department and Homeland Security clamp down on the use of cryptocurrency in child exploitation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Game On: The Hottest Upcoming Gaming Token Airdrops]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211029</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211029/game-on-hottest-upcoming-gaming-token-airdrops"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T17:45:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATED: Here's what you need to know about gaming airdrops and rewards around Notcoin, Immutable zkEVM, Saga, Illuvium, Apeiron, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETFs Bleed Badly as Skittish Investors Cash Out $218 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228300</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228300/bitcoin-etf-outflows-end-71-day-run"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T17:25:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nearly $218 million exited the formerly red-hot investment vehicles in the wake of a weak U.S. economic report.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase, Uniswap Execs Praise Ethereum Giant Consensys for Taking On SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=228274</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/228274/coinbase-uniswap-ethereum-consensys-sec"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T17:07:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The heads of crypto industry titans like Coinbase and Uniswap are rallying behind Consensys in its fight to get the SEC to concede Ethereum is not a security.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Sasha Stiles’ Experiential, AI-Infused NFT Drop with Bang & Olufsen]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/6Vi2IgYj/inside-sasha-stiles-experiential-ai-infused-nft-drop-with-bang-olufsen</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/6Vi2IgYj/inside-sasha-stiles-experiential-ai-infused-nft-drop-with-bang-olufsen"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T22:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At a launch party for the collection in New York’s SoHo neighborhood, the artist broke down her latest art experiment, “Four Core Texts,” with Decrypt’s Sander Lutz.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interview: How 'Notcoin' Will Evolve After the NOT Token Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PprnGP14/interview-how-notcoin-will-evolve-after-the-not-token-launch</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PprnGP14/interview-how-notcoin-will-evolve-after-the-not-token-launch"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Open Builders founder Sasha Plotvinov speaks with Decrypt's Sander Lutz at Token 2049 Dubai about how he envisions Notcoin's expansion and evolution after the token drop—into something akin to the "Netflix of social, viral games."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Magic Runes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IGWg0R64/magic-runes</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IGWg0R64/magic-runes"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T13:59:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC stables at $66k, liquidations in narrow range. BTC funding again turns negative in bullish sign. ETFs net inflow after Grayscale moves to lower fees. BTC demand 5x vs supply post-halving: Bitfinex. SOL congestion issue now largely solved. Two SEC lawyers resign after ‘gross abuse of power’. Ripple fights to lower $2bn SEC fine. SAFE trades at $2.8bn FDV after OKX lists. MANEKI hits $150m on first day, China memes pump. Memecoins are ‘black hole you can’t ignore’. DeGods up 20%, may switch back to SOL. Magic Eden launches Runes platform ahead of time.  Louis Vuitton gifts Pharrell jacket to NFT holders. Melania Trump launches necklace with SOL NFTs. Hoodie Punk trades for $620K.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Luxury Watches, Designer Shoes Will Soon Trade Like NFTs: Arianee CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/CSNQG2md/luxury-watches-designer-shoes-will-soon-trade-like-nfts-arianee-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/CSNQG2md/luxury-watches-designer-shoes-will-soon-trade-like-nfts-arianee-ceo"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arianee CEO Pierre-Nicolas Hurstel sat down with Rug Radio founder Farokh and Decrypt’s Sander Lutz at NFT Paris to discuss everything from the future of on-chain luxury to the secret hack to finding the best restaurants in France.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notcoin's Co-Creator Explains the Game's Token Delay—And When to Expect NOT Now]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/7Zx33xo5/notcoins-co-creator-explains-the-games-token-delayand-when-to-expect-not-now</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/7Zx33xo5/notcoins-co-creator-explains-the-games-token-delayand-when-to-expect-not-now"/>
        <updated>2024-04-22T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Notcoin co-creator Sasha Plotvinov spoke with Decrypt's Sander Lutz at Token 2049 Dubai to discuss why the NOT token launch was pushed back from the original 4/20 target, when to expect the listing, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TON’s Justin Hyun Breaks Down The Importance of USDT Coming to Telegram]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ODQI6ACA/tons-justin-hyun-breaks-down-the-importance-of-usdt-coming-to-telegram</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ODQI6ACA/tons-justin-hyun-breaks-down-the-importance-of-usdt-coming-to-telegram"/>
        <updated>2024-04-19T10:14:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Token 2049 in Dubai, The Open Network’s director of investments sat down with Decrypt’s Sander Lutz to discuss what he sees as the game-changing integration of USDT onto TON, and his plans for getting Telegram’s 900 million users to start using crypto in the immediate future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Influencer Ansem Explains His Meme Coin Thesis and Why He’s Bullish on Bitcoin Runes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/u9DHFoK0/crypto-influencer-ansem-explains-his-meme-coin-thesis-and-why-hes-bullish-on-bitcoin-runes</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/u9DHFoK0/crypto-influencer-ansem-explains-his-meme-coin-thesis-and-why-hes-bullish-on-bitcoin-runes"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T21:56:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ansem, the crypto trader who's amassed a sizable following on the back of meme coin Dogwifhat (WIF) and other calls, chats with Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz at Token 2049 Dubai about his meme coin thesis, why he's bullish on Bitcoin Runes, and what he sees ahead for the crypto markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Sander Lutz Braves the Dubai Floods for a Crypto Conference]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/mtjVHGa3/decrypts-sander-lutz-braves-the-dubai-floods-for-a-crypto-conference</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/mtjVHGa3/decrypts-sander-lutz-braves-the-dubai-floods-for-a-crypto-conference"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T21:33:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz reports from Dubai amid a historic storm that flooded the famed city, trudging through the streets to complete his essential task: Attending the Token 2049 crypto conference.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gold Beats Its All Time High]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/6ULgUKVk/gold-beats-its-all-time-high</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/6ULgUKVk/gold-beats-its-all-time-high"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T09:53:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) maintains its trend of reaching higher lows amidst choppy market conditions. Exchange-traded funds (ETFs) witness another influx of $125 million. There's anticipation of Hong Kong approving ETFs for both Bitcoin and Ethereum (ETH) come Monday. Notable institutional investor BlackRock shows interest in Bitcoin. Recent filings reveal increased Bitcoin purchases by banks. A Bitcoin-friendly political party secures victory in the South Korean election. Analyst Kang predicts Bitcoin could surge to $80-100k by May. Meanwhile, Ethereum sees accumulation by stablecoin whales on the rise. A new Ethereum Improvement Proposal (EIP) aims to streamline signing requests. Solana (SOL) experiences a resurgence in activity, reaching yearly highs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NASA’s Next Deep Space Mission Won’t Use Artificial Intelligence]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/0WGP33Rp/nasas-next-deep-space-mission-wont-use-artificial-intelligence</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/0WGP33Rp/nasas-next-deep-space-mission-wont-use-artificial-intelligence"/>
        <updated>2024-04-13T18:42:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Thursday, Decrypt Media visited NASA's Jet Propulsion Laboratory in Pasadena, CA to meet with the Engineering team behind the Europa Clipper before its launch to Jupiter's Europa moon in October.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Do A Little with Weesh]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LnaOT9bF/we-do-a-little-with-weesh</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LnaOT9bF/we-do-a-little-with-weesh"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T07:46:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week’s episode, we did a little something different. We took the man who is usually behind the camera and put him in front of it. We sat down with our producer Weesh to dive into how in fell in love with art and became a collector, how he met Andy and fun childhood memories together, his biggest wins in crypto, and so much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside VanEck’s Crypto Takeover of the New York Stock Exchange]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9YAY4wGD/inside-vanecks-crypto-takeover-of-the-new-york-stock-exchange</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9YAY4wGD/inside-vanecks-crypto-takeover-of-the-new-york-stock-exchange"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T14:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worlds collide as Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz heads to the floor of the NYSE to witness a special closing bell ceremony hosted by VanEck in honor of Web3. Featuring Choose Rich Nick, VanEck Head of Web3 Matt Bartlett, and more!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wormhole Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9SNiIVfU/wormhole-wednesday</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9SNiIVfU/wormhole-wednesday"/>
        <updated>2024-04-07T17:42:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC hits $64.5K then rebounds, SOL outperforms. Government sends $2B BTC to Coinbase to sell. Funding rates stay low after sweep lower. ETFs see small inflow, Ark outflow more than GBTC. Wormhole W launches at $15B FDV. BTC ‘inflection point’ if it follows rates or gold. Gold & BTC very correlated for the last year. Expect slower ETF volume this month: Bloomberg. BTC 2x and 3x levered ETFs launch yesterday. BTC ETFs now half the size of gold.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Dogs, Now Cats]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/2KrbCFNp/first-dogs-now-cats</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/2KrbCFNp/first-dogs-now-cats"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T14:06:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC falls another 6% amid $400m liquidations. ETF outflows and dollar strength blamed for move. Funding completely reset to lows in move. BTC lower high leaves market in ‘no trade zone’. This cycle acting ‘nothing like previous cycle’. ETH unlikely to be classed a security: Coinbase CFO. Crypto VC funding up 53% in MarchAnsem’s cat coin sees more volume than NFT market. Most memecoins down 10-20% given move in majors. MEW up 10% after HTX lists, airdrop to Saga phones. MEME to launch memecoin chain, NFTs rise. Pixelmon releases trailer for Anime series.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>