<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-09-12T04:16:46.845Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-09-12T04:16:46.845Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Cloud and Kiln ‘Unlock’ Native Ethereum Staking: No More 32 ETH Minimum]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7543092786</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/coinbase-cloud-and-kiln-unlock-native-ethereum-staking-no-more-32-eth-minimum/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T04:12:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Cloud and blockchain infrastructure company Kiln are now allowing ethereum (ETH) users to stake any amount of ether natively. The new offering removes the previous 32 ETH minimum staking requirement.
 
Staking for All: Coinbase Cloud and Kiln Break Down Minimum Barriers
 
With the integration of Kiln’s onchain staking platform, Coinbase Cloud and its clients can enable partial ETH staking. This allows wallet providers like Coinbase Wallet to give users the ability to earn staking rewards without needing to meet minimums. The press announcement notes that over 99 percent of ether wallets hold less than the 32 ETH previously required to stake on the network.
 
“We are thrilled to have worked with Coinbase Cloud and to welcome them as the first (non-Kiln) node operator leveraging the Kiln Onchain Staking Platform,” said Kiln CEO Laszlo Szabo. The Kiln CEO added:
 
 
This integration with Coinbase Cloud is unique because it allows them to enable other wallets and services, including [decentralized exchanges], with the same limitless [ether] staking solution that will be offered by Coinbase Wallet.
 
 
 
Partial ETH staking builds on Coinbase Cloud’s existing staking infrastructure. The company said its multi-cloud, multi-region setup ensures reliability alongside trusted security standards. Coinbase further discloses that staking operations occur transparently onchain through audited smart contracts.
 
Coinbase posits that by removing staking minimums, more individual users can participate in securing the Ethereum network while earning rewards. The move comes as staked ETH ratios continue rising after Ethereum’s recent upgrade. Coinbase Cloud is currently offering this new open staking access starting with integration in Coinbase Wallet.
 
What do you think about Coinbase and Kiln’s announcement? Share your thoughts and opinions about this subject in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin reveals X account hack was caused by SIM-swap attack]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18895886/Vitalik-Buterin-reveals-X-account-hack-was-caused-by-SIM-swap-attack</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18895886/Vitalik-Buterin-reveals-X-account-hack-was-caused-by-SIM-swap-attack"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T03:51:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ethereum co-founder has regained control of his T-Mobile account, confirming that a SIM-swap attack resulted in the hack of his X account.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOJ 'Overreaching' in Trying to Block Sam Bankman-Fried's Proposed Witnesses, Defense Says]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75430bdab7</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/09/12/doj-overreaching-in-trying-to-block-sam-bankman-frieds-proposed-witnesses-defense-says/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T03:43:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prosecutors with the U.S. Department of Justice are trying to limit FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried's right to a fair trial by moving to block all of his proposed expert witnesses, defense attorneys said. The DOJ, for its part, said the defense mischaracterized a proposed prosecution witness's planned testimony.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOJ 'Overreaching' in Trying to Block Sam Bankman-Fried's Proposed Witnesses, Defense Says]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18895883/DOJ-Overreaching-in-Trying-to-Block-Sam-Bankman-Frieds-Proposed-Witnesses-Defense-Says</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18895883/DOJ-Overreaching-in-Trying-to-Block-Sam-Bankman-Frieds-Proposed-Witnesses-Defense-Says"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T03:41:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prosecutors with the U.S. Department of Justice are trying to limit FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried's right to a fair trial by moving to block all of his proposed expert witnesses, defense attorneys said. The DOJ, for its part, said the defense mischaracterized a proposed prosecution witness's...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Odds of Pepe bidding farewell to the top 100 crypto club]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18895868/Odds-of-Pepe-bidding-farewell-to-the-top-100-crypto-club</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18895868/Odds-of-Pepe-bidding-farewell-to-the-top-100-crypto-club"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T03:30:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PEPE is witnessing a massive increase in selling pressure, which has resulted in a double-digit drop in the memecoin’s price over the last week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SOL Drops Ahead Of Court Verdict On FTX Asset Sales]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18895859/SOL-Drops-Ahead-Of-Court-Verdict-On-FTX-Asset-Sales</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18895859/SOL-Drops-Ahead-Of-Court-Verdict-On-FTX-Asset-Sales"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T03:25:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If Approved On Wednesday, FTX Plans To Offload Between $100M and $200M Worth Of Crypto Per Week Through Galaxy Digital]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Standard Chartered’s crypto custody arm Zodia launches in Singapore]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18895861/Standard-Chartereds-crypto-custody-arm-Zodia-launches-in-Singapore</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18895861/Standard-Chartereds-crypto-custody-arm-Zodia-launches-in-Singapore"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T03:21:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zodia Custody owned by Standard Chartered, announced Tuesday that it is launching its services in Singapore for financial institutions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why DAOs are choking on majority rule and failing their democratic ideals]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18895843/Why-DAOs-are-choking-on-majority-rule-and-failing-their-democratic-ideals</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18895843/Why-DAOs-are-choking-on-majority-rule-and-failing-their-democratic-ideals"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T03:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To solve DAOs’ people problems with mismanagement and bad actors, they need to lean into automation — and take more matters out of human hands.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum, Dogecoin Drop As Beleaguered FTX Looks To Offload Billions In Tokens: Analyst Foresees Extreme Ethereum Crash, Predicts ETH Dropping More Than 70%]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18895852/Bitcoin-Ethereum-Dogecoin-Drop-As-Beleaguered-FTX-Looks-To-Offload-Billions-In-Tokens-Analyst-Foresees-Extreme-Ethereum-Crash-Predicts-ETH-Dropping-More-Than-70</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18895852/Bitcoin-Ethereum-Dogecoin-Drop-As-Beleaguered-FTX-Looks-To-Offload-Billions-In-Tokens-Analyst-Foresees-Extreme-Ethereum-Crash-Predicts-ETH-Dropping-More-Than-70"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T02:59:58.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Enforcement Funds Under Scrutiny: Congressman Emmer Calls For Restrictions On SEC]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754cf14037</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/congressman-emmer-for-restricting-secs-crypto-funds/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T02:43:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent statement, Congressman Tom Emmer, a prominent figure in the GOP and a staunch advocate for crypto, expressed his concerns regarding the actions of Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Chair Gary Gensler. 
 
Emmer accused Gensler of abusing his authority, leading to the expansion of the Administrative State while “disregarding the interests of the American people”. 
 
To address these concerns, Emmer plans to sponsor an appropriations amendment aimed at restricting the SEC’s use of funds for crypto enforcement until clear rules and regulations are established.
 
 
Emmer Advocates For Clear Rules In The Crypto Industry
 
Emmer’s criticism of Chair Gensler centers on what he perceives as the weaponization of taxpayer dollars. Emmer argues that Gensler has utilized his position…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX sues LayerZero over alleged illicit fund withdrawals. Details inside…]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18895818/FTX-sues-LayerZero-over-alleged-illicit-fund-withdrawals-Details-inside</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18895818/FTX-sues-LayerZero-over-alleged-illicit-fund-withdrawals-Details-inside"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T02:30:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The troubled cryptocurrency exchange FTX has taken legal action against the cross-chain protocol LayerZero Labs, aiming to recover $21 million in allegedly illicitly withdrawn funds prior to FTX's closure in November.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Exchange Bitget Establishes $100M Pot to Fund Ecosystem Growth]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754cf31166</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/09/12/crypto-exchange-bitget-establishes-100m-pot-to-fund-ecosystem-growth/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T02:23:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitget anticipates tightened regulations and growth of layer-2 blockchain networks and DeFi technologies bringing about an evolution in how centralized exchanges operate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[test]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18895860/test</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18895860/test"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T02:09:44.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SBF Lawyers Challenge Claims of Sufficient Internet Access]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18895828/SBF-Lawyers-Challenge-Claims-of-Sufficient-Internet-Access</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18895828/SBF-Lawyers-Challenge-Claims-of-Sufficient-Internet-Access"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T02:08:53.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[India to Finalize Crypto Stance in Coming Months, Economic Affairs Secretary Says]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754cfc746f</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/india-to-finalize-crypto-stance-in-coming-months-economic-affairs-secretary-says/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T02:07:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[India’s economic affairs secretary says the Indian government will decide on the country’s crypto position “in the coming months.” He explained that the government will consider all the recommendations presented at the G20 summit regarding crypto regulation “very carefully and decide our own policies and thereafter take further action.”
 
Officials Discuss Indian Crypto Regulation
 
India’s Economic Affairs Secretary Ajay Seth talked about how the Indian government will proceed with establishing a crypto framework for India in an interview with CNBC-TV18 on Sunday.
 
India recently hosted the G20 leaders’ summit where crypto regulation was among the key topics of discussion. At the conclusion of the summit, the G20 leaders endorsed high-level recommendations proposed by the Financial Stabi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Enforcement Funds Under Scrutiny: Congressman Emmer Calls For Restrictions On SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18895795/Crypto-Enforcement-Funds-Under-Scrutiny-Congressman-Emmer-Calls-For-Restrictions-On-SEC</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18895795/Crypto-Enforcement-Funds-Under-Scrutiny-Congressman-Emmer-Calls-For-Restrictions-On-SEC"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T02:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gaming blockchain Oasys partners Japan telco KDDI’s αU Wallet, αU Market in Web3 push]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18895788/Gaming-blockchain-Oasys-partners-Japan-telco-KDDIs-U-Wallet-U-Market-in-Web3-push</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18895788/Gaming-blockchain-Oasys-partners-Japan-telco-KDDIs-U-Wallet-U-Market-in-Web3-push"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T02:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oasys reveals integration of KDDI’s aU Wallet and aU Market into its ecosystem]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18895786/Oasys-reveals-integration-of-KDDIs-aU-Wallet-and-aU-Market-into-its-ecosystem</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18895786/Oasys-reveals-integration-of-KDDIs-aU-Wallet-and-aU-Market-into-its-ecosystem"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T02:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oasys is a blockchain-based game development platform that offers a highly scalable Layer 1 hub and specialized Layer 2 using … Continued]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitget Makes a $100 Million Move to Diversify Crypto Exchange Business]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754cfe21cb</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/bitget-makes-a-100-million-move-to-diversify-crypto-exchange-business/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T01:48:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After  
launching two funds in April aimed at supporting the development of Web3 and  
decentralized applications (DApps) with a total value of $300 million, the  
cryptocurrency exchange, Bitget has introduced another fund called EmpowerX with  
a capital base of $100 million. The fund is designed to accelerate the  
platform's ecosystem by investing in various sectors, including regional  
exchanges, data analytics firms, and media organizations. 
Bitget Launches $100  
Million EmpowerX Fund to Expand Ecosystem
The  
EmpowerX Fund aims to strategically allocate its $100 million capital to  
maximize Bitget's presence in the digital asset space. The company wants to offer  
a variety of services that cater to the diverse demands of users worldwide. As  
a result, the exchange no longer wa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Damian Chmiel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried, DOJ Propose Jury Questions Ahead of October Trial]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754cfe7930</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/09/12/sam-bankman-fried-doj-propose-jury-questions-ahead-of-october-trial/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T01:44:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Attorneys for FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried and the U.S. Department of Justice filed their proposed jury instructions and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) Transaction Fees Reach 2022 Lows, Entering Inflationary Period?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754cfeaa9e</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-transaction-fees-2022-lows-inflationary/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T01:42:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) transaction fees have hit their lowest levels since 2022, marking a significant milestone for the second-largest cryptocurrency by market capitalization. 
 
According to insights from Ryan Selkis, the founder and CEO of Messari, the average fee for transferring ETH stands at $1.83, while the cost of token purchases via Uniswap is approximately $4.17. 
 
This decline in gas fees can be attributed to reduced on-chain activity related to Non-Fungible tokens (NFT) sales, meme coin trading, and Telegram bots.
 
Decrease In Gas Fees And On-Chain Activity Leads To Increased Ethereum Supply
 
The drop in gas fees has resulted in Ethereum entering an inflationary period. Over the past week, the supply of Ethereum has increased by 4,092 ETH tokens, with a total value of around $6.6 mi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitget unveils $100 million fund to invest in exchanges, data analytics and media]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18895770/Bitget-unveils-100-million-fund-to-invest-in-exchanges-data-analytics-and-media</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18895770/Bitget-unveils-100-million-fund-to-invest-in-exchanges-data-analytics-and-media"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T01:40:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitget's $100 million EmpowerX Fund will invest in regional exchanges, data analytics firms, media organizations and other entities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitget announces further $100M fund for ecosystem development]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18895766/Bitget-announces-further-100M-fund-for-ecosystem-development</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18895766/Bitget-announces-further-100M-fund-for-ecosystem-development"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T01:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Exchange Bitget Establishes $100M Pot to Fund Ecosystem Growth]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18895797/Crypto-Exchange-Bitget-Establishes-100M-Pot-to-Fund-Ecosystem-Growth</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18895797/Crypto-Exchange-Bitget-Establishes-100M-Pot-to-Fund-Ecosystem-Growth"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T01:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC's Gary Gensler to hold firm on crypto enforcement in Senate hearing]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18895753/SECs-Gary-Gensler-to-hold-firm-on-crypto-enforcement-in-Senate-hearing</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18895753/SECs-Gary-Gensler-to-hold-firm-on-crypto-enforcement-in-Senate-hearing"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T01:11:57.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GBTC’s Discount Narrows Amid Bitcoin’s Downturn, But A Bullish Trend Is Coming?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18895732/GBTCs-Discount-Narrows-Amid-Bitcoins-Downturn-But-A-Bullish-Trend-Is-Coming</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18895732/GBTCs-Discount-Narrows-Amid-Bitcoins-Downturn-But-A-Bullish-Trend-Is-Coming"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T01:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) share price has again made headlines. Its premium or discount to Bitcoin’s net asset value (NAV), often viewed as an indicator of institutional sentiment towards the cryptocurrency, has displayed a notable trend recently, even amid the prevailing bearish...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin: This silver lining could be BTC’s savior in coming days]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18895744/Bitcoin-This-silver-lining-could-be-BTCs-savior-in-coming-days</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18895744/Bitcoin-This-silver-lining-could-be-BTCs-savior-in-coming-days"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T01:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While whale selling pressure and little or no buying pressure contributed to BTC's ongoing downfall, the fact that BTC was close to the oversold region meant that the king of cryptocurrencies could see a trend reversal very soon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) Transaction Fees Reach 2022 Lows, Entering Inflationary Period?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18895745/Ethereum-ETH-Transaction-Fees-Reach-2022-Lows-Entering-Inflationary-Period</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18895745/Ethereum-ETH-Transaction-Fees-Reach-2022-Lows-Entering-Inflationary-Period"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T01:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) transaction fees have hit their lowest levels since 2022, marking a significant milestone for the second-largest cryptocurrency by market capitalization. According to insights from Ryan Selkis, the founder and CEO of Messari, the average fee for transferring ETH stands at $1.83,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thailand Authorities Bust $27 Million Crypto Scam, Over 3,200 Victims Affected]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754cfbe2bd</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/thailand-authorities-bust-million-crypto-scam/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T00:41:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent development from Thailand, authorities uncovered a massive crypto scam targeting local investors, with damages amounting to more than $27 million.
 
In collaboration with international bodies, local enforcement agencies went after a fraudulent investment platform, leading to multiple arrests and property seizures.
 
Decoding The Deceptive Web: A Scheme Unveiled
 
A report from the Bangkok Post highlighted the expansive nature of this scheme, which had successfully duped over 3,200 Thai locals. 
 
Orchestrated by five foreign nationals, including four from China and one from Laos, the platform bchgloballtd.com acted as a façade, pulling unsuspecting investors into its trap.
 
 
Efforts by Thailand’s Cyber Crime Investigation Bureau (CCIB), with support from the United States Hom…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[People Won't Use Bitcoin To Buy Things, Says PayPal Co-Founder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155961</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155961/bitcoin-payments-david-marcus-lightning-network"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T00:32:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Marcus says Bitcoin's lightning network will be a universal money protocol for transacting multiple currencies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Launches $20 Million Fund to Support Responsible AI Development]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155970</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155970/responsible-ai-development-google-digital-futures-project-fund-20-million"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T00:20:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Digital Futures Project aims to include diverse perspectives in AI development, tackling bias, fairness, and workforce impact.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase CEO Discusses US Crypto Regulation — Sees More Institutional Investors Coming In]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754ce68636</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/coinbase-ceo-discusses-us-crypto-regulation-sees-more-institutional-investors-coming-in/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T00:10:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong has explained that crypto regulation in the U.S. will happen in one of a few ways. He noted that Coinbase is seeing more institutional investors coming in and signing up as they seek “a flight to quality.” The executive added: “There’s a possibility we’ll just get a different SEC chair in 2024 or beyond.”
 
Brian Armstrong on Crypto Regulation
 
The CEO of cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase (Nasdaq: COIN), Brian Armstrong, discussed various topics, including crypto regulation and stablecoins, in an interview with Yahoo Finance on Friday.
 
Responding to a question about the timing and nature of crypto regulation in the U.S., the Coinbase boss described:
 

It’ll happen in one of a few ways. So, one way is the courts. The courts can be the one to provide the clari…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wells Fargo Manager Predicts XRP Price Will Reach $500, Here’s When]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754ce12b0b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/xrp-price-500/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T23:41:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever since Ripple emerged victorious in its 3-year-long legal battle with the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) over the security status of XRP, the bullish predictions for the altcoin have risen rapidly. The most recent and perhaps the most bullish of these predictions comes from a Wells Fargo Manager, who has put forward a possible three-figure price target for the digital asset.
 
XRP Price Could Rise To $500
 
In a September 11 tweet on the X (formerly Twitter) platform, Shannon Thorp, a Business Development Manager for American megabank Wells Fargo, has painted a rather bullish picture for XRP. The post sees the Wells Fargo manager predict that the XRP price could rise as high as $500.
 
 
Like most analysts, Thorp backs up her prediction with a reason why she exp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Best Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI's Thirst for Power May Be Draining Water Supplies]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155965</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155965/artificial-intelligence-water-use-data-centers"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T23:23:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin mining isn't the only environmental scourge—time to rage against AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Is Losing Favor Among Institutional Investors: CoinShares]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155964</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155964/ethereum-is-losing-favor-among-institutional-investors-coinshares"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T22:59:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With $108 million worth of selling in 2023, it is the “least loved digital asset.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gensler Decries ‘Wide-Ranging Noncompliance’ In Crypto Ahead of Oversight Testimony]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155967</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155967/gensler-cites-wide-ranging-noncompliance-ahead-of-oversight-testimony"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T22:45:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite bipartisan criticism for his agency’s approach to crypto, SEC Chair Gary Gensler is doubling down.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Forces Young Hacker To Forfeit $5.2 Million In Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754ceea66e</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/us-forces-hacker-forfeit-5-2-million-in-bitcoin/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T22:42:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last month, Ahmad Wagaafe Hared, a young hacker based in the United States, was ordered to forfeit approximately $5.2 million worth of Bitcoin (BTC), Stellar (XLM), and a BMW sports car to the government. According to a report, this order was made last week due to Hared’s involvement in a SIM-swapping scheme that targeted crypto executives in North California and the Bay Area.
 
The Bitcoin SIM-Swapping Hack
 
The SIM-swapping scheme, orchestrated by Hared–who went by the alias “winblo” — began in 2016 and was stopped by local authorities in 2019. 
 
Hared and his accomplices obtained their victims’ contact information before entering a plea agreement with law enforcement agencies. They would then contact cellphone service providers, manipulating company representatives into believing they…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dalmas Ngetich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Study: Weekly Digital Asset Investment Outflows Hit $59M; BTC Sees Largest Drop]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754ce9b88d</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/study-weekly-digital-asset-investment-outflows-hit-59m-btc-sees-largest-drop/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T22:10:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the first week of September, an outflow of $59 million worth of digital assets managed by Digital Asset Funds was recorded, the latest Coinshares data has shown. The latest outflow means the value of digital asset investment products under management has dropped by a total of $294 million or 0.9% in the past four weeks. The Coinshares data shows bitcoin (BTC) as the digital asset which had the highest net outflow ($69 million) in the first week of September.
 
Bitcoin Short Inflows the Largest Since March
 
During the first week of September, digital asset investment products saw a net outflow of $59 million in assets under management (AUM), the latest data from the alternative asset manager Coinshare analysis has shown. According to the asset manager’s blog, the latest net outflow figure brings the value of total outflows in the past four weeks to $294 million, or 0.9% of total AUM.
 

 
As explained in the blog, inflows were also seen in short investment products and this may be an indication that the sentiment for digital assets remains poor. Concerns over the regulation of this asset class and the strengthening dollar are cited as some of the reasons why investors are less keen on investing in digital assets.
 
 
In terms of flows by asset, the Coinshares data shows bitcoin (BTC) as the digital asset that had the highest net outflow ($69 million) in the first week of September. On the other hand, short bitcoin net inflows during the same period topped $15 million, the largest since March 2023.
 
Meanwhile, Ethereum’s net outflow of $4.8 million during the same period saw its year-to-date outflows rise to US$108m representing 1.6% of the total AUM of $6.9 billion. Out of all the digital assets tracked by Coinshares, only XRP and other unidentified digital assets are shown to have recorded positive inflows of $0.7 million and $0.4 million respectively.
 
What are your thoughts on this story? Let us know what you think in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Luno Responds to FCA’s Looming Crypto Rules: Halts UK Investments Temporarily]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754cea7908</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/luno-responds-to-fcas-looming-crypto-rules-halts-uk-investments-temporarily/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T22:03:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cryptocurrency exchange platform Luno is set to  
temporarily halt certain clients in the UK from making cryptocurrency  
investments, effective from October 6. This suspension comes just two days  
ahead of the UK Financial Conduct Authority's (FCA) new crypto promotion rules,  
aimed at ensuring consumer protection and transparency in the sector, coming  
into effect.
The United Kingdom's FCA  
is planning to implement a series of rules that will significantly impact the  
way cryptocurrency is marketed and promoted within the country. These rules  
will reportedly categorize crypto as restricted mass market investments and  
impose stringent regulations on advertising and promotions within the crypto  
asset sector.
Luno Streamline  
Operations
Specifically, all  
crypto-related adv…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Vs Shiba Inu: How Do The Memecoins Compare In On-Chain Metrics?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754cd455e2</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-shiba-inu-memecoins-compare-chain-metrics/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T21:44:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s how the various memecoins in the market, like Dogecoin and Shiba, compare against each other in terms of the on-chain indicators.
 
Dogecoin, Shiba Inu, And Other Memecoins Stacked Against Each Other
 
In a new post on X, the market intelligence platform IntoTheBlock shared an infographic that looks into the underlying metrics of the different memecoins in the sector.
 
The firm has compared these assets based on two indicators: the holders in profit and the whale concentration. The former tells us about the total percentage of the investors of assets currently sitting in the green.
 
This metric works by going through the transaction history of each address to see the average price at which they acquired their coins. If this average buying price for any holder was less than the cur…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hououin Kyouma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Insuring Bitcoin Mining: An Interview with Thomas Shewchuck of Bitshure and Evertas]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754cd4931b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/insuring-bitcoin-mining-an-interview-with-thomas-shewchuck-of-bitshure-and-evertas"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T21:41:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris sits down with Thomas Shewchuck from Evertas to talk about having his company Bitshure get acquired to make the bitcoin mining insurance landscape more robust. He talks about bitcoin mining insurance, bitcoin mining, the bear market, and preparing for the halving and the next bull run. 
See the full interview on YouTube. 

Bitcoin mining has become a global phenomenon, with individuals and businesses around the world investing in powerful computers and specialized hardware to participate in the process of verifying transactions on the blockchain. However, this rapidly growing industry is not without its risks. In this exclusive interview, we speak with Thomas Shewchuck, co-founder of Bitshure, which was recently acquired by Evertas, two leading companies in the Bitcoin insurance spac…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trading Firms Deposit Millions in BTC, ETH and ARB to Exchanges as Crypto Sell-Off Intensifies]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754cd628e1</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/09/11/trading-firms-deposit-millions-in-btc-eth-and-arb-to-exchanges-as-crypto-sell-off-intensifies/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T21:27:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto markets dropped sharply on Monday, with bitcoin’s price dipping below $25,000.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitfinex and Tether CTO Paolo Ardoino to Testify in Market Manipulation Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155935</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155935/bitfinex-tether-cto-paolo-ardoino-market-manipulation-lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T21:26:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ardoino will be deposed this week after the court denied his counsel’s request for more time to prepare.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defiant Gensler Returns to Crypto Grievances Ahead of Senate Testimony]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754cd76a90</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/09/11/defiant-gensler-returns-to-crypto-grievances-ahead-of-senate-testimony/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T21:14:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Chair Gary Gensler is doubling down on his crypto objections in his first remarks following the second recent court setback in his agency’s sweeping legal fight with the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Drops to 3-Month Low While Ethereum Takes Harder Hit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155931</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155931/ethereum-bitcoin-altcoin-values-drop-as-ftx-pursues-crypto-liquidation"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T21:06:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price slump comes as bankrupt crypto exchange FTX looks to liquidate its crypto holdings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla Up 10% on Prediction Its AI Chips Will Outperform Nvidia's]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155924</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155924/tesla-up-10-on-prediction-its-ai-chips-will-outperform-nvidias"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T20:46:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla's new supercomputing system could position it as a strong rival to NVIDIA, according to Morgan Stanley.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Will Lead The World Out Of The “Fax Era Of Payments,” Ex-Facebook Executive Says]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754cd2a5c9</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-will-lead-the-world-out-fax-era-of-payments/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T20:44:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Head of Payments David Marcus stated that Bitcoin is set to become the most critical network to take payments to a new era. Marcus believes the global payment infrastructure is absolute and will benefit from integrating with the cryptocurrency.
 
 
 
Bitcoin Lightning, A Solution For Today’s Payment Problems?
 
In an interview with CNBC’s Squawk Box, the former Facebook and PayPal executive spoke about his new project, Lightspak. This company was created to provide payments settled on Bitcoin’s second-layer solution, the Lightning Network.
 
This payment solution improves the Bitcoin network scalability by allowing users to send money “off-chain.” In that sense, Marcus and his company want to turn the cryptocurrency into a “ real global payment network.”
 
The objective is to financ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reynaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Is Racist, Experts Say. Here's Why]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155929</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155929/ai-racist-experts-say-heres-why"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T20:33:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI has the ability to be racist if left unchecked, and it could mean terrible things for our future, according to AI builders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Estate Controls $1.1B in Solana and $560M in Bitcoin Amid Bankruptcy Revelations]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754cdf2c21</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ftx-estate-controls-1-1b-in-solana-and-560m-in-bitcoin-amid-bankruptcy-revelations/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T20:02:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The FTX estate, currently overseeing the bankruptcy and restructuring of the once-active crypto exchange, reveals holdings of $1.16 billion in solana (SOL) and $560 million in bitcoin (BTC).
 
16% of Solana’s Market Cap Is Held by FTX
 
In a recent Monday court filing, a stakeholder update showcases the premier digital assets held by the estate. As of August 31, 2023, these liquid tokens have a combined value of $3.4 billion. Additionally, the update showcases nearly $200 million in Bahamian real estate. Solana (SOL) emerges as the dominant asset in FTX’s portfolio.
 
 
As of September 11, 2023, with SOL’s market cap standing at $7.24 billion, FTX’s slice is a significant 16%, equating to $1.16 billion. FTX’s diverse crypto portfolio also includes $560 million in BTC, $192 million in ETH, $137 million in APT, $120 million in USDT, $119 million in XRP, $49 million in BIT, $46 million in STG, $41 million in WBTC, and $37 million in WETH. Furthermore, FTX possesses over $529 million in securities housed in Debtor brokerage accounts, of which $417 million resides in the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC).
 
 
Apart from that, a modest $0.1 million is placed in Blackrock equity under FTX’s control. Delving into FTX’s venture collection, it boasts 438 investments, amassing $4.5 billion in funded assets. Notably, it includes a significant stake in Anthropic, a rival to Openai and the brains behind the generative AI chatbot, Claude. It’s worth mentioning that FTX also owns over 1,000 illiquid crypto assets, which may not realize their full potential value.
 
What do you think about the FTX stakeholder update? Share your thoughts and opinions about this subject in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hologram Runway Wows Crowds at Amsterdam Fashion Week]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155851</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155851/hologram-runway-wows-crowds-at-amsterdam-fashion-week"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T19:55:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Future Front Row seeks to chart an immersion-first path forward for the digital fashion industry after packing the house in Amsterdam.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pahdo Labs Raises $15M to Let Players Make Anime Games With AI Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155895</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155895/pahdo-labs-raises-15-million-players-make-anime-games-ai-tools"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T19:23:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The studio behind anime game Halcyon Zero will launch generative AI tools for content creation after raising funding led by Andreessen Horowitz.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Is Building AI Data Centers to Power ChatGPT Competitor: WSJ]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155899</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155899/meta-is-building-ai-data-centers-to-power-chatgpt-competitor-wsj"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T19:06:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A person familiar with Meta said the company has hired a new team and is stocking a data center with Nvidia H100s to compete with OpenAI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt AI, Edited by Stacy Elliot</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Reveals Xbox Mastercard That Helps You Earn Free Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155855</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155855/microsoft-reveals-xbox-mastercard-helps-you-earn-free-games"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T18:10:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Barclays will begin issuing Xbox Mastercards to select U.S. applicants later this month, allowing holders to earn points for gaming perks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sushi Expands to Aptos in 'Milestone' Move]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155839</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155839/sushi-expands-to-aptos-in-milestone-move"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T17:24:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The move to Aptos is the first time DEX has been accessible on a blockchain that is not compatible with the Ethereum Virtual Machine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Looks to Offload Billions in Crypto: Here’s What it Means]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155844</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155844/ftx-looks-to-offload-billions-in-crypto-heres-what-it-means"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T17:09:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The defunct crypto exchange is seeking regulatory approval to liquidate $3.4 billion worth of crypto assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Hussey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ApeCoin Plunges to New Low, Down 42% Over Last Month]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155837</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155837/apecoin-plunges-new-low-down-42-over-last-month"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T16:51:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prices for Bored Ape Yacht Club NFTs stopped slipping lately, but the project's associated Ethereum NFT token ApeCoin is still falling.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX's $3.4 Billion Crypto Portfolio Includes Solana, Bitcoin and Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155829</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155829/ftx-details-its-3-4-billion-crypto-portfolio-of-solana-bitcoin-and-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T16:06:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FTX's liquid crypto portfolio is worth $3.4 billion in total.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Animoca Brands Raises $20M to Pursue ‘Single Native Web3 Project’ Mocaverse]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155770</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155770/animoca-brands-raises-20m-to-pursue-single-native-web3-project-mocaverse"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T12:17:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A set of 8,888 NFTs will provide holders access to the company’s ecosystem and a chance to accumulate loyalty points.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Turns Inflationary as Gas Fees Plummet to 2023 Lows]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155762</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155762/ethereum-turns-inflationary-as-gas-fees-plummet-to-2023-lows"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T11:49:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain traders are waiting for the next narrative as interest in meme coin and Telegram bot trading cool off.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Algorand Boss Steve Kokinos Tapped as CEO for Firm Buying Celsius]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155760</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155760/ex-algorand-boss-steve-kokinos-tapped-as-ceo-for-firm-buying-celsius"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T10:52:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celsius creditors played a prominent role in selecting the board for Fahrenheit Holdings—appointing six of the nine members.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Connor Sephton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feds Want $5.2 Million in Bitcoin Returned by Teen Hacker—And A Sports Car, Too]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155747</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155747/doj-demands-5-million-in-bitcoin-and-bmw-sports-car-from-teen-hacker"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T01:02:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Department of Justice accused the teenager and his accomplices of stealing money from crypto executives in the Silicon Valley area.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacker Steals Over $690,000 After Hijacking Vitalik Buterin's Twitter Account]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155738</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155738/hacker-steals-690000-after-hijacking-vitalik-buterin-x-account"/>
        <updated>2023-09-10T22:42:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A fake link promising an exclusive NFT was posted to the Ethereum inventor's feed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shaq Got Nearly $750,000 From FTX Amid Millions In Celebrity Deals]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155732</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155732/shaq-got-nearly-750000-from-ftx-amid-millions-in-celebrity-deals"/>
        <updated>2023-09-10T22:18:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A bankruptcy filing names names: Shaquille O’Neal, Naomi Osaka, David Ortiz, and Trevor Lawrence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SBF Lawyers Again Ask for Pre-Trial Release Because Prison Internet Sucks]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155728</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155728/sam-bankman-fried-prison-internet-trial-preparation-request"/>
        <updated>2023-09-10T20:03:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Disgraced CEO Sam Bankman-Fried doesn’t have enough time to review the documents in his case, his attorneys claim.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prime Trust Bankruptcy Exposes ‘Widespread’ Self-Custody Risks, Says Anchorage Digital Co-Founder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155714</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155714/prime-trust-bankruptcy-self-custody-risks-anchorage-digital-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-09-10T18:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Diogo Monica says applying existing bank rules, not creating new regulations, can ensure business continuity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week on Crypto Twitter: Bankman-Fried Roughs it in Brooklyn Jail]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155705</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155705/this-week-on-crypto-twitter-bankman-fried-roughs-it-in-brooklyn-jail"/>
        <updated>2023-09-10T17:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to a prison informant, the former billionaire linked up with a gang from Manhattan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ted Cruz Says He Is a ‘Big Believer’ In Bitcoin Mining]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155694</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155694/ted-cruz-texas-senator-bitcoin-mining-dennis-porter-satoshi-act-fund"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T20:15:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Appearing on Fox News Radio, the Texas senator said Bitcoin mining is good for his state’s stressed power grid.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Responds to Ripple Filing, Doubles Down on Appeal Bid]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155689</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155689/sec-ripple-appeal-xrp-securities"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T18:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The regulator claims judge's summary judgment order raises "knotty legal problems" worthy of appellate review]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt AI, Edited by Ryan Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Green Candles—But Barely—for Bitcoin and Ethereum as Global Adoption Grows]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155665</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155665/this-week-in-coins-green-candles-but-barely-for-bitcoin-and-ethereum-as-global-adoption-grows"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T18:01:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Also, a member of the European Central Bank’s executive board criticized PayPal USD and shilled the digital euro.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple to Acquire Crypto Custodian Fortress Trust]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155658</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155658/ripple-fortress-trust-brad-garlinghouse-scott-purcell"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T17:01:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fortress was founded two years ago by former Prime Trust CEO Scott Purcell.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Super Mario Bros. Wonder: Everything You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155605</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155605/super-mario-bros-wonder-nintendo-switch-everything-need-know"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mario and friends enter the fantastical Flower Kingdom. But what else is new in Super Mario Bros. Wonder on Nintendo Switch?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT Plus vs Claude Pro: Choose The Best Paid AI Chatbot For You]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155600</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155600/chatgpt-plus-vs-claude-pro-choose-the-best-paid-ai-chatbot-ally-for-you"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T23:20:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI’s ChatGPT Plus and Anthropic’s Claude Pro come at similar price points, but they have very different strengths and weaknesses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fed's Michael Barr: No Word on CBDC and 'Deeply Concerned' About Stablecoins]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155576</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155576/feds-michael-barr-no-cbdc-decision-deeply-concerned-about-stablecoins"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T23:16:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[He also said that the central bank was "a long way" from any decision on issuing a CBDC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Harry Potter' Actors Protest London Dream Home Plans of Ripple Exec]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155620</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155620/harry-potter-actors-protest-london-dream-home-plans-ripple-exec"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T22:23:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Emma Thompson, Imelda Staunton, and Jim Broadbent appear to be seriously aggrieved about their crypto executive neighbor's remodeling plans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Donation Company Says Gifted Crypto Should Require Less Paperwork]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155601</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155601/bitcoin-donation-company-says-gifted-crypto-should-require-less-paperwork"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T20:59:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's ridiculous to require an appraisal of donations made in dollar-pegged stablecoins, like USDC or USDT, the company argues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LBRY Will Appeal 'Unjust and Incorrect' SEC Lawsuit Ruling, Says CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155569</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155569/lbry-will-appeal-unjust-and-incorrect-sec-lawsuit-ruling-says-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T19:18:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company had previously said it plans to wind down operations and the SEC dropped its financial penalty from $44 million to around $111,000.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[France Now Has Crypto Influencer Training to Encourage Paid Ad Disclosures]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155575</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155575/france-now-has-crypto-influencer-training-to-encourage-paid-ad-disclosures"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T19:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[France requires investment communications to be non-misleading and balanced. “It appears that some influencers are unaware of this," said an official.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roblox Is Finally Coming to PlayStation This Year]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155564</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155564/roblox-finally-coming-playstation-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T18:44:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roblox, which hosts a wide variety of different metaverse game experiences, is finally releasing on PlayStation 4 and PlayStation 5 consoles in October.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[El Salvador's Bitcoin Curriculum Will Teach Students the 'Dark Side of Fiat']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155559</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155559/el-salvadors-bitcoin-curriculum-will-teach-the-dark-side-of-fiat"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T18:04:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Students learn about currency debasement, a nod to Saifedean Ammous's "The Bitcoin Standard" book. But he didn't help write the curriculum.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RIP TCG: How Deadfellaz Is Rethinking Card-Battler Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155545</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155545/rip-tcg-how-deadfellaz-rethinking-card-battler-games"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T17:28:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deadfellaz founders Psych and Betty share how the digital trading card game will help grow the lore of the zombie-themed Ethereum NFT brand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Mino Games is Using Artificial Intelligence]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/SrT1Afj7/how-mino-games-is-using-artificial-intelligence</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/SrT1Afj7/how-mino-games-is-using-artificial-intelligence"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T22:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mino Games CEO Sasha McKinnon tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about how the studio's upcoming game Dimensionals will use real-time AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INTERVIEW: How Will Aurory Use NFTs and Crypto?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qv3VwNmM/interview-how-will-aurory-use-nfts-and-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qv3VwNmM/interview-how-will-aurory-use-nfts-and-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T15:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Natoli, Aurory's Head of Marketing and Business Development, tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how the Aurory games will use NFTs and crypto and shares the studio's broader stance on the tech.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Cloud's James Tromans on the Intersection of AI and Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OeD4uoLj/google-clouds-james-tromans-on-the-intersection-of-ai-and-web3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OeD4uoLj/google-clouds-james-tromans-on-the-intersection-of-ai-and-web3"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google's Global Head of Google Cloud for Web3 James Tromans sat down with Decrypt's Jason Nelson to discuss how AI can help Web3 companies come to market faster and the real value of Web3 tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastering NFT Trading - Degen U]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/HQGt1Vrq/mastering-nft-trading-degen-u</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/HQGt1Vrq/mastering-nft-trading-degen-u"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T07:08:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Take Degen U's new course, Mastering NFT Trading, and earn an on-chain certificate. A top instructor will help you identify trends, seize the right moment to trade, weed out scams—and have fun while doing it!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Space Nation CEO on Working With 'Independence Day' Director Roland Emmerich]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LpznLhtx/space-nation-ceo-on-working-with-independence-day-director-roland-emmerich</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LpznLhtx/space-nation-ceo-on-working-with-independence-day-director-roland-emmerich"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T17:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jerome Wu, CEO of Space Nation, tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the upcoming Space Nation Online game in development and shares details on Space Nation Cofounder Roland Emmerich's role in the project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GAME REVIEW: Champions Arena from Gala Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qUE1RlDx/game-review-champions-arena-from-gala-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qUE1RlDx/game-review-champions-arena-from-gala-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Champions Arena is a turn-based fantasy RPG from Gala Games, where characters can become NFTs and crypto can be used to purchase gems, one of the game's synthetic currencies. Decrypt's Kate Irwin takes us inside the game for her thoughts on the fun, mobile-first title.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apex Legends Voice Actor Ben Prendergast on the Future of Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/X3RKdsaG/apex-legends-voice-actor-ben-prendergast-on-the-future-of-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/X3RKdsaG/apex-legends-voice-actor-ben-prendergast-on-the-future-of-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T18:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Voice actor Ben Prendergast, who's voiced characters in games like Apex Legends and God of War Ragnarok, shares his opinions on the tech space's history of "bubbles" and whether blockchain gaming has a future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The future of AI Stardom and Robotics with SingularityNET COO Janet Adams and Desdemona]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yVQaZI71/the-future-of-ai-stardom-and-robotics-with-singularitynet-coo-janet-adams-and-desdemona</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yVQaZI71/the-future-of-ai-stardom-and-robotics-with-singularitynet-coo-janet-adams-and-desdemona"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T16:45:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this interview, SingularityNET COO Janet Adams explains the intricate details that went into creating the Desdemona robot AI from Hanson Robotics and future plans for the AI Diva.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto a 'No-Brainer' for Video Games, Says Mino Games CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rdynom8C/crypto-a-no-brainer-for-video-games-says-mino-games-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rdynom8C/crypto-a-no-brainer-for-video-games-says-mino-games-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T18:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mino Games CEO Sasha MacKinnon, developer of the upcoming Dimensionals game, tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the studio's approach to digital collectibles.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Wagner's 'Controversial Take' on Crypto in Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tc2nKeqA/michael-wagners-controversial-take-on-crypto-in-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tc2nKeqA/michael-wagners-controversial-take-on-crypto-in-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T16:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Solana's PlayGG, Star Atlas CEO Michael Wagner shares his "controversial take" on crypto in games, shares the challenges of developing the upcoming scifi game, and how crypto's volatility has changed his perspective with Decrypt's Jason Nelson.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interview: Angelic CEO on Building the Sci-Fi RPG on Solana and Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/uCzW3K7P/interview-angelic-ceo-on-building-the-sci-fi-rpg-on-solana-and-ethereum</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/uCzW3K7P/interview-angelic-ceo-on-building-the-sci-fi-rpg-on-solana-and-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T15:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Angelic is a sci-fi roleplay game in development that will be free-to-play and offer optional, opt-in crypto features on Solana and Ethereum and a governance token. Metaverse Game Studios CEO and Founder Erkan Bayol tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how he sees AAA traditional games as Angelic's main competitors and shares his vision for the game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apex Legends Voice Actor on AI's Impact on Video Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IOIrmb0N/apex-legends-voice-actor-on-ais-impact-on-video-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IOIrmb0N/apex-legends-voice-actor-on-ais-impact-on-video-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T17:28:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ben Prendergast is an actor who has voiced characters like Apex Legends' Fuse, God of War Ragnarok's Tyr, and Patroclus in Hades. But as debates swirl around the use of artificial intelligence in entertainment in light of the SAG-AFTRA and WGA strikes, Prendergast gives Decrypt's Kate Irwin his honest take on the potential use of AI actors in games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Star Atlas CEO on Developing an MMO Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/WQCaahmH/star-atlas-ceo-on-developing-an-mmo-game</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/WQCaahmH/star-atlas-ceo-on-developing-an-mmo-game"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T13:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Jason Nelson speaks with Star Atlas Founder and CEO Michael Wagner about the MMO game's approach to development, marketing, and blockchain integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aurory's Origin Story: How JRPGs Inspired the Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/O0S201TB/aurorys-origin-story-how-jrpgs-inspired-the-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/O0S201TB/aurorys-origin-story-how-jrpgs-inspired-the-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T16:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Jason Nelson talks to Aurory's Head of Marketing and Business Development Michael Natoli about the origins of the Aurory crypto games at the Solana PlayGG event.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>